Yanei
Go fast
Walk
Is it annoying?
It's okay, keep drinking
How many of you go over there?
Others follow me.
Yes Yes
There are no traces of assassins under the cliff
pursuing
It's me who killed
You're okay again
Eat and drink when you should
Be happy
Father is right
One or two assassins don't need to worry
sons and ministers
A toast to my father
You really drink it
Father's Order
Don't dare to disobey
You can't say that
What if the wine is poisonous?
You're not the one who poisoned me.
How do you know if it's poisonous?
Sons and ministers are stupid
heart
Only respect and love for the father
Didn't think so much
Life is still important
Children and ministers receive education
Where is the Prime Minister?
Go and find him for me
Prime Minister
Yuan Hao this time
It will destroy Brother Ning Ling
The position of prince?
They were all poisoned and assassinated.
Not abolished yet
In fact, you and I have no grudges
these things i do
It’s all just for Brother Ning Ling
Afraid I'll kill you
Prime Minister Qing Tianzi is looking for you
Qing Tianzi
Prime Minister
You tell me before the banquet
Queen meets assassin
I didn't believe it at first
But who would have thought
There really is an assassin
Qingtianzi is protected by gods
Naturally fine
The queen knew the assassin
There is no such thing
That means you are talking nonsense.
Except for the minister
There are also guards who testified.
In my wine just now
Poisoned
Assassins deserve death
The rest of the wine
Do you dare to drink?
My brother is not good at drinking
This wine minister and his concubine drink for him
Qingtianzi gives wine
Can't refuse
Someone attempted assassination at the banquet
Yuan Hao is sending people to search
why are you here
I still think about it
It's important to protect you first
Has anyone been caught in the assassination?
Maybe not
They all jumped off the cliff and escaped
Let's go first
Dragon God Dragon God
If you want to leave the palace
It's closer here
stay home
No
They all jumped off the cliff and escaped
The Prime Minister is not dead
This incidates that
Only the wine in the glass is poisonous
Is there any in the jug?
before this
Only the queen has ever poured me wine
Understood
The Prime Minister delivers the order for me
From today
Abolished the position of Queen Norishi
Your Majesty, please think twice.
The harem cannot be left without a master for a day
Queen's throne
Just leave it to your sister
Thank you Qingtianzi for the reward
Since I am no longer the queen
Naturally, without a face
Exit
Prince
I heard the Prime Minister say
Conspirators with assassins
And you
Absolutely no such thing
The Prime Minister must have made a mistake
look
I just said you got it wrong
Okay, it's okay
Why are you still kneeling? Prime Minister
Find a place to sit
The party is still going on
I read that right
Prime Minister
How can a father and his son kill each other?
Unreasonable
Think about it again
What the king said is absolutely true
I may have seen it wrong.
Please forgive me
What crime have you committed?
You are also dedicated to serving the country.
The prince pays a toast to the prime minister
yes
The Prime Minister is coming
You really have a good idea
The younger generation must learn from you
The prince is serious.
The Prince's Deep Cunning
That's amazing
Invite the Prime Minister
Come
This is used for storage in the summer
No one in winter
There is a cliff behind
It is quite convenient to hide and escape
He and the others did not escape from the palace
Do the opposite
This is the hiding place
But Yuanhao's guard is extremely tight
How did they escape here?
Could it be that you used your magic power?
If I could use my magic power at will
Do you still need to hide?
clear
This is Helan Mountain
They have many gods
To control
Just stay down there for now
clear
Why did you do it?
Wasn't it Queen Yeli who poisoned her?
Failed
It doesn't matter
I'm also poisoned here
I have to thank Hua Shao
No arrangements for you
We're not that suitable either
Hiding Place
Why don't you say anything?
Where are Sister Zhao and Brother Wang?
Yanei
you were rescued
Brother Wang is injured
All because of saving me
I should save you
Is the person still alive?
alive
Can the bleeding be stopped?
Try to prevent the wound from getting too big
I'll stop the bleeding
Yanei
exist
Help me find some charcoal
good
Gotta keep the office busy
Can't let self-blame destroy him
Small Scene
I will definitely save Brother Wang
Prince
I remember to get you engaged
right
Returning to my father, this is indeed the case
The girl who didn’t move home
Yes or no
Exactly
The wedding should be on these days, right?
That's right
In a few days
My son is about to return to Xingqing Mansion
Getting ready for marriage
Don't go back to Xingqing Mansion
Let's go to the palace while the excitement is lively.
OK
Everything is up to the Father
good
I'll make the change
It's better to change the date
Father
In fact, my son is not in a hurry to get married.
The days won't change.
Change people
Previous stage time
I've seen that girl who hasn't moved home yet
feel happy
this bride
I'll marry her for you.
Being favored by the father
It’s the family’s luck that hasn’t changed
good
You can't leave
You have to give a toast at the wedding
That's natural
I'll toast to the prince again
The prince's magnanimity is unparalleled
please
I want to find charcoal for Wang Kuan
Don't leave this building
Wang Kuan wants charcoal
let me go
I'll just come and find you
You wait
Wang Kuan is here to save me
That’s why it hurt like this
I saw with my own eyes my colleague Yashiya
die in front of eyes
but can't do anything
We can't even die together
Wang Kuan is still there
Don't mess around
I see
I'm going to find charcoal
Tie shoulders with rope
Tie tight
Can the bleeding be stopped?
Or not
An injury like this can't stop the bleeding
he will die
Get out of here
Even if this is the case, he is still the prince.
Keep your voice down, the walls have ears
fine
I've seen it for you
No one but me
Someone coming
Drink it
yes
Carry away
come over
Where is Wei Zhuoran?
After the banquet, I have been kneeling in the snow
Refuse to get up
This is quite unbearable
first
First of all, I wish your sister to become the new queen.
You didn't escape
Prime Minister
Yuan Hao deposed the queen
But he retained Brother Ning Ling’s
The Crown Prince
Are you quite disappointed?
catch you
Ning Lingge's crime of collaborating with the enemy
You can sit down
Why should Yuan Hao keep it?
Ning Lingge’s position as prince
Is it because of the deep love between father and son?
Qingtianzi announced in public
Seize Ning Lingge’s newlywed wife
If the father and son love is deep
He would not humiliate Brother Ning Ling like this
He knows that Brother Ning Ling hates him
So I want to humiliate him in public
But why did he
Keep his position as crown prince
Prime Minister
all because of you
In fact, in your own heart
Already know the answer
My sister is now
become the new queen
Ning Lingge’s position as prince
If it is deposed again
You don’t have a hidden clan
No one will be able to control it
He just wants me to be with Brother Ning Ling
Mutual hatred
The more you fight, the more fierce you become
Yuan Hao felt even more pleased
So the Prime Minister
Even if you hand me over
He won’t cripple Brother Ning Ling either.
not necessarily
If the Prime Minister wants to arrest me
I've called someone a long time ago.
What's your last name?
Surname Yuan
Yuan Xiaoge
Don't you hate us?
why do i hate you
I hate my brother for betraying you
I'm not familiar with him.
Is it normal to betray?
The Song Dynasty was indeed a place of outstanding people
Look at the young people
More knowledgeable
Really clever and cute
There are quite a few people who compliment me on my cleverness.
I'm the first one to compliment me on how cute I am
Hate
you come here
Just to talk to me about Brother Ning Ling
Prime Minister
If you want to take charge
What do you think of Brother Ning Ling?
Is it your number one enemy?
if not
With Yuan Hao
There's no chance for you or Brother Ning Ling.
I am loyal to Qingtianzi
I heard that Yuan Hao recently
Getting married again
This queen was ruined once
It will be useless the second time
Just alarmist
What do you think
How does Brother Ning Ling compare to Yuan Hao?
That's far from it
What if Yuan Hao died?
do you think you can
Ning Lingge took it from his hands
Is Xixia powerful?
Qingtianzi is not kind to me
do you want me to
Conspiracy?
Back then, the Yeli clan
How is the reputation
Far better than my brothers and sisters
What about now?
Almost genocide
Prime Minister
You might as well think about their fate
Think again about your fate
To put it bluntly, it’s just one sentence
Yuan Hao's character
How much do you believe?
What are your plans today?
Are you sure Yuan Hao didn't see through it?
Even if I don't see through it now
Can you ensure that he
Don't you have any doubts?
Qingtianzi is the most powerful person in the world
If I plot against
I'm afraid of being criticized by thousands of people.
Xixia is full of talents
This pot
How can you let the Prime Minister memorize it alone?
What Yuan Xiaoge means is
Let’s cooperate with Ning Lingge first
Eradicate Yuan Hao
Revenge for Qingtianzi again
Eradicate Brother Ning Ling
Prime Minister
Such a vicious strategy
Can't you see it yourself?
You have to force your sister to tell you.
Just today's matter
I'm afraid it's Brother Ning Ling
Hate me so much
Then apologize
Very offended
Brother, you can be more sincere
That's okay too
Why not try
Father seizes son's wife
I'm grateful he can do it
You don't like it
Didn't move that girl
Two different things
He is stepping on my face and humiliating me
This is not called humiliation
He just announced to the ministers of the Manchu Dynasty
Talk about you, the prince
The future is worrying
It's better to go directly
Get rid of this prince
Why not abolish it
Don't you know clearly?
He made me fight with Wu Zangpang
The more you two fight, the more fiercely you two become.
The happier your father will be
He can sit back and relax
The two of us keep spending this much
The turmoil of divine punishment in Xingqing Mansion
It will disappear
smooth over the waves
Take advantage of your fights
Attract attention from all parties
Then they said this is the Sheep God
punishment for you
Give you two what you deserve.
retribution
Me and I are fighting each other
The divine punishment also dissipated
This is a combination of elimination and defeat
He is safe and sound
you finally know
Your father
not only
Are you leading troops to fight?
He is waiting
Wait until the divine punishment subsides
This is the day when I, the prince, will be deposed.
we have no time
Your Highness
Seeking an audience with the Prime Minister
No hidden lies
why come again
explain
The Prime Minister looks arrogant
Look
Looks like he's here to scold you
quarrel
Come to the door and quarrel
This medicine can save Wang Kuan's life
Just drugged
He is already unconscious
I need to let Brother Wang sleep more deeply.
Where is the flower tree?
He was called by Queen Yeli
Met the queen
Met the prince
Why does the Prime Minister have time to visit?
I miss the prince.
Besides, I, the Prime Minister of the country,
It’s a life of hard work
I have to bear all the chores
Under the Prince
There are still several battalions of soldiers and horses
their dispatch supplies
It's better to leave it to me to worry about
This is what the father means
I figured it out myself
You are not afraid
I kill you
Prince
How about you kill me?
Get out of here!
Prime Minister
Come in and sit
Queen and Prince
Prime Minister
What are you doing here?
You and I fight
Qingtianzi is happy to hear and see
It was for outsiders to watch.
Isn’t it?
The Prime Minister came here this time
true intention
What is it again?
what is this for
Today's banquet
I was the one who informed Qing Tianzi
I wanted to frame the queen and the prince
Such behavior
Hateful and shameful
Ask the prince for forgiveness
Prime Minister
Seek a future for your family
as a matter of course
Reasonable
If you make a mistake, you should be punished
What kind of punishment are you doing?
Do you have a stick?
A whip is also OK
It's the trick of asking for forgiveness.
What stands out is a word
sincere
Burning the wound can stop bleeding
Stop the bleeding first, then save lives
Let me do it
I'm here to save
The wooden stick is fine without this
this
bring it on
Beat the prince to calm him down
Okay, okay.
let it go
Get up
I really won't fight anymore
hurry up
okay
Do you still dare to believe him?
I don't trust his character.
I believe in human nature
I wanted to overthrow the prince.
After all, my sister
Also gave birth to a prince
Prince, can you understand?
I understand.
but now i understand
This is wrong
Is there something wrong with this?
The Blue Emperor's Great Talent and Strategy
He is here
Those of us who are fighting for power
No way to survive
So you come to me
That change is a bit too fast, right?
no way
If you don’t change quickly, you will die quickly.
I reconsidered
Blood is thicker than water
To be honest, the prince is the wise master
Why is blood thicker than water?
We are relatives
My sister
She was the wife of Yeli Yuqi.
And the Queen
She is the biological sister of Yeli Yuqi
Calculating it this way
The Queen and I are also siblings.
That His Highness
Wouldn’t he become my nephew?
Is blood thicker than water?
Since the Prime Minister said so
That's okay
Then I have to call
The Prime Minister is called uncle
My uncle joins forces with my nephew
Isn’t it natural?
Forget about the law of nature
uncle
what do you want
After the prince succeeds to the throne,
Keep the position of Prime Minister of our country
Also for my sister
stay alive
If I succeed
Daxia Military and Political Affairs
Of course with uncle
Divide and conquer
Don't dare
Just keep your wealth
Brother Ning, I value family ties most.
never let down
Prince Benevolence
Great blessing of summer
Okay, okay.
Let's get down to business.
What's serious
Yuan Hao is not dead
How did he succeed to the throne?
Your Highness, you don't have much time.
There will be divine punishment at this time
People's hearts are in turmoil
Kill Qingtianzi
Only the prince has the chance to win over people's hearts
Control Daxia
If Qingtianzi is allowed to spend this period,
After that
It’s hard to find good opportunities
That uncle
Is there a clever plan?
In a few days, he will be Qingtianzi
To marry a new queen
That's not a girl from the Yi family
It was originally the prince's marriage contract
If you have something to say, say it
Prince
Is there any chance to meet this girl?
But I only have an engagement with her
Not affectionate
How could she help me with the assassination?
If the wedding day
Where is the bride changing?
Who would dare to assassinate my father?
I am a citizen of Daxia
Of course there will be no one
Dare to disobey Qing Tianzi
But we have friends from the Song Dynasty
I remember that Miss Zhao
Wisdom and courage
you mean
Let Zhao Jian replace the bride
Assassinate Yuan Hao on the wedding day
This is the only way
Do you know Zhao Jian
Does it have anything to do with me?
Love each other
Everyone can see this.
But the young hero wants to do great things
Then you have to make a choice
You take the benefits
Let's give up the price, right?
If I could just pretend to be the bride
That's so good
It's not impossible
I mean Zhao Jian
This matter can be discussed
Then hurry up
Just these few days
If you need medicine, a doctor
Just speak up
Wang Kuan’s injury
you don't know yet
Wang Kuan is injured
how's it going
Still too hot
The danger is still there
I'll make some more medicine
who
Can it be saved?
Definitely
How is Wang Kuan?
Let me have a few words with Zhao Jianjian alone.
Very clear
I looked around to see the situation
His arm
Didn't get it back
I'll go tell Brother Ning Ling
Ask him to help get his arm back
it's useless
As long as we stay here
Wang Kuan will definitely survive
Qing Tianzi
Mr. Wei
I really need to say something to you
Why do you have to torture yourself like this?
Guilty
I tell you good news
Your son was rescued by his friend
He is young and ignorant
Mr. Wei
Let me ask you something
You feel
The so-called divine punishment before Xingqing Mansion
Was it planned by Yuan Zhongxin?
There is no god in the world
Let’s not talk about whether there are gods or not.
I am surprised that
These things
Yuan Zhongxin can't do it alone
That's in Xingqing Mansion
Who is helping him secretly?
Han people in Daxia
I'm not the only one
Yuan Zhongxin's biological father
Also joined the Qing Emperor
The bond between father and son
Why didn't Prince Qingtian call him to ask?
Yuantian Pass has long disappeared
Xue Ying saw Yuantian Pass on the cliff
He said
Yuantianguan is always around
Watching us secretly
But he never showed up
He didn't take any action at the banquet
Right
If he took action
Wang Kuan’s arm should not be broken
What does his broken arm have to do with me?
Yuantianguan is hidden
What about the Yuan clan?
They are all
He doesn't want his people anymore.
Where is this person Yuan Tianguan?
Maybe you don't care about anything
Father and son
After all, they are father and son
He cares about his son
Actually I don't care about you either
I only care about my bloodline
remain in this world
You could have saved Wang Kuan
Can
To be honest, I still thought about it
Finally let it go
You don’t always talk about yourself
No personality at all?
This shows that our father and son
In the same vein
Makes sense
So it seems
These actions of Xingqing Mansion
It was done with the help of Yuan Tianguan
pretty close
Ashamed
Ashamed Ashamed
before me
Have you ever doubted Mr. Wei?
It is also inevitable
That seems to be the biggest trouble now
It’s Yuantian Pass
Yuantian Pass disappeared
It's hard to find
I'm talking about the Yuan clan.
All arrested
Do you want him to throw himself into a trap?
a bit difficult
But I have to try anyway
Mr. Wei
Tomorrow
I need to work harder for you
What does Qingtianzi want me to do?
Mr. Wei is a great talent
You just said something
Very well said
Father and son
After all, they are father and son.
Brother Wang, you are awake.
I was rescued by you