You feel
Did I kill Bo Fin?
You have to ask yourself
Lu Nanshan did have someone look for me
Please let me kill your father
I also sneaked into Ning Lingge’s camp
Your father died of illness
You didn't take action
My son is dead
what does it matter
I look down on Yuan Zhongxin
so many years
I didn’t regard him as my son either.
Because I don't need him
but now
Yuan Zhongxin is my only son
At this moment
I should always think about him
Based on your relationship
Why should I kill your father?
Empty words
Do you believe it?
I don't care
this matter
I will definitely get to the bottom of it
If it was your hand that moved it
I will definitely kill you for revenge
What you just said
why not
Yuan Zhongxin’s interview
Who should I tell him?
Did you just want to destroy him?
father
Disciplining your son is the right thing to do
You are afraid that he will go to Xixia
Died in Yuan Hao's hands
So you would rather destroy him
There's still a bit of a father-son relationship
you are wrong
I despise him
Don't let him go
I just don't want my Yuan family
bloodline cut off
If Bob Fin were still there
Even if he dies, I won’t
Take a closer look
As for hating him so much?
Because he is not good enough
What should I do if Yuan Zhongxin is really disabled?
Just don't die.
Unreasonable
What you can do now
Just give me Polaris
Then what
You give Beihe Star to Yuan Hao again
gain trust
Only then can we take the opportunity to kill him
Revenge for my son
I won't give you Polaris
child
Trade his life for Yuan Hao's life
This won't count
Qizhai kills Yuan Hao
Not for personal revenge
Why else?
Prevent war in the world
Keep the Song Dynasty peaceful in the future
Bao Da Song
Why are you guaranteed?
patriotism
patriotic
Your surname is Zhao
Of course I love it
But our Yuan family
It’s Xianbei bloodline
Tens of thousands of people in the Song Dynasty
Different bloodlines
But using the same language
Talking about the same love and hate
Joys and sorrows gather together, honor and disgrace
Hundreds and Thousands of Years
We are connected to this land
cannot be divided
Country is our common name
so-called patriotism
Just love ourselves
You want to impress me when you raise your profile
Who doesn’t know what to say?
I didn't want to impress you
I'm just a little sad
There is no need for you to feel sad
not for you
Actually I never thought about it
you will understand
It’s just that Yuan Zhongxin and Brother Yuan
They all think so
They did the same
You never understood them
Young People
Only know blood
How can you understand worldly affairs?
Is there anything wrong?
I'm tired
correct
Before your father died
let me bring you something
May all things in the world
No longer stop you
yuantianguan
let's make a deal
I promise to let Yuan Zhongxin
Not to enter Xixia within three years
Walk
Why does he feel so much older?
Three years
so
Is to agree
The transaction of Beihexing
Three years
Another chance to kill Yuan Hao
Not a loss
What do you think?
Three Years of Business
I'm OK
I just don't know about Beihexing
What do you think
What if I lose money?
Three years of practicing swordsmanship
The one you want
OK
In this case
Let's meet Pollux again
Seal the deal
You go ahead
That He County Cheng
collude secretly to deceive
Steal people's property
I will take him back to Kaifeng
Discuss on national law
I've been thinking just now
The word choice
I am waiting for the Confucian scholar
How could you not know how to sacrifice your life for justice?
sacrifice one's life
I won't go with you
I want to go back to Kaifeng
Finish my journey
Wang Kuan left
Wang Kuan won’t leave
Wang Kuan is gone
Qizhai is missing one
All good things come to an end
People
When we get together, there will be separation
But even at the ends of the earth
Qizhai is still there
Brother Wang
have you ever had nightmares
The scariest dream I've ever had
Just go back to the past
But I didn't meet you
I once swore to myself
No matter what happens
setbacks and difficulties
I will always stand with you
Small Scene
You can go to Kaifeng with me
Of course I do
But I can't go
The word choice
Easier said than done
Brother Wang
You have to find your own way
I'm actually very proud
because you chose
It is a line that needs oneself
The road to completion
can meet you
I'm very lucky
But I won't give up on you
I will
Will make yourself better
Then one day
i will find you again
Brother Wang
I let go now
I'm not giving up on you
us
will always be together
I know
Sister Zhao
I'm fine
Brother Wang found his own
My own way
I'm very happy
real
What's going on here
Where is the Northern Star?
Went to the fields
fields
Weeding and fertilization
There is a lot of work in the fields
Shall I take you to see him?
can you
I have to go
Then let’s go
He does this every day
Is there farm work in this world?
Endless work
No wonder the government office couldn’t find it
He is Beihexing
If I hadn't grown up in this field
Who would have thought of exorcising demons for the world?
Tell me your decision
Don't discuss it with him.
Also available
But after talking
He will forget it tomorrow.
So serious
Otherwise, why are you looking for it?
Where is the inheritor?
three years later
The name of the Xixia spy
Give us
certainly
make a deal
Then start now
So fast
It has been prepared for you a long time ago
Wei Yuan
Follow the road to the west
There's a caravan there
He is waiting for you there
money earned in three years
Keep enough for your own use later
Send back the rest
Meet the caravan
Do you need any certificate?
unnecessary
What to do if you lose money
Beihexing believes in you
The old man is quite discerning.
these three years
We're afraid we won't see each other again
Still here three years later
Don't forget to come back
The End of the Earth
Seven fasts in one
gone
You stay to practice martial arts
His behavior is ridiculous
I'll accompany him for a while
Remember to come back
I'm here waiting for you
This is also considered a caravan
Not even a horse
It’s a caravan and it must have goods, right?
It's all straw.
under the straw
It's all cow dung
Yeah
Who wants these things?
Xiao Xue
That's the situation
Do you think three years
What can be the result?
Don't think about that
It would be nice not to starve to death
This is already the case
lets go
Where are you going?
have no idea
Think about it as you walk
boarding
Walk
Where is this caravan?
Isn’t this an escape?
The injury is serious
Maybe within ten years
Can't even stand up
we don't have that much time
Try your best
okay
Let's not talk about this now
These are the few of us left
What do I have to do
Each has its own arrangements
Pei Jing
You have two choices
First
Go out into the countryside and work alone
Secondly, follow them
How to do things alone
you don't want to follow them
I want to but I can't
Qizhai everyone
Everyone should be on their own
Even if it's me
We should move forward bravely
Good to work alone
Just rush to the place of disaster
Rescue victims
Disasters can also be divided into droughts, floods
Earthquake and storm disease
you choose one
The disease is also
yes
Then you can study medicine
certainly
I'll choose this
But I want to remind you
The epidemic has left corpses everywhere
It’s hard for disaster relief workers to come out
I can
Why don't you two persuade her?
Qizhai everyone
Can be independent
good
Pei Jing
You go east along this road
Entering the third room in the village
There is a country doctor there
Just follow him
I originally thought
We will always be together
will not be separated
It turns out that's not the case
Silly girl
Only three years
Then it's settled
See you in three years
Brother Yuan
I will definitely cure you
It's all up to you
See you or leave
Brother Wang mentioned
Master Fan said
Either a good appearance or a good doctor
He is going to take the path of good people and helping the world
Then I will go and heal the people in this world
Come on, Xiaojing
Xiao Jing, you can do it.
Qizhai everyone
Everyone should be on their own
Even if it's me
We should move forward bravely
he is injured
I can't separate from him
A letter from Pollux to you
You haven’t read it yet
No need to look
Just tell me
Whatever I do
You really don’t need to separate
Pollux said you two
able
Tacit Understanding
If we join forces
More useful than working alone
Uncle understands quite well
What's this
this is so many years
Inspired by Pollux
students in academy
List of writings
What to do for us
from now on
what are they going to do
It's up to you
We have the final say
No need to consult Beihexing
Need not
He is not afraid of us
sold them
He believes in you
Then I'll tell the truth
Beihexing wants to be in the academy
Find like-minded people
Indeed
But the road went astray
Reading makes sense
How can this be godless?
How can this be biased?
That's right
But their number
Far from enough
Who else are you looking for?
Anyone can do it
Juggler and restaurant owner
Farmer, trader
All these people can
Involved in his great cause of slaying demons
Many blind believers
Rely on a few students
How many people were saved?
There are many of them
There cannot be fewer of us
Otherwise it’s just a drop in the bucket
futile effort
But these people all believe in ghosts and gods
Then give them benefits
what's the use
As long as the benefits are enough
Don't say you believe in ghosts and gods
Even ancestral graves can be sold to you
People believe in ghosts and gods
There is comfort in my heart
What you do is useless
We can make a false god
Yuan Zhongxin
We are now exorcists of ghosts and gods
You want to create a ghost
One thing
Create a false god first
And then destroy it myself
always wakes people up
This is better than persuading and reasoning
Much more useful
Use extraordinary measures in extraordinary times
Dead Ghost Uncle
You might as well think about it
Beihe star for so many years
I just managed to win over a few students.
How did God create this?
We have experience in creating gods.
Do you know Bazhai's Wenwuqi?
do not know
Forget it if you don’t know him
This person
Quite annoying too
He is in Xixia now
Specialized in creating gods
I have to go to Xixia
Find this person here
They are all from the Secret Pavilion
If he can do it, so can I
Okay, okay, then let me ask you
Our first step
what should be done
First we have to make one
famous name
I get up
I have a way with naming.
Father Adult
Make a vow when you leave
I thought you wouldn't come back again
do you still remember yourself
Did you say that?
Remember
If you reach a dead end
I can only grit my teeth and move forward
There is no time to regret
Didn't expect it to be so soon
You will regret it
Actually, I don’t regret it either.
There's just a new way forward
what road
Those in high positions
Maybe it can save the people from fire and water
this road
I gave it to you a long time ago
Do you want to be loyal to the Song Dynasty?
Have you ever thought about that?
Only when you are in a high position can you do your best
There is always someone in a high position
There is no shortage of Wang Kuan
The words still ring in my ears
This changes the course
after i leave
The hope of the next generation of the Wang family
In whose hands?
Those cousins ​​of yours
On knowledge and character
I may not lose to you
i want to see them
Want to fight
It's not impossible
Wang Kuan
It is common for people to take the wrong path
But you have to learn to admit your mistakes
If you are in front of me
Can't even bow their heads
How can I take it back?
one's own position
How can I gain a foothold in the court?
As a Confucian scholar
The truth that is hard but easy to break
You should understand
Hard and easy to break
Soft and permanent
This comes from Taoism
Not Confucian
you
Please father, give me a chance
Let me meet my cousin
so many years
I've never seen you like this
I thought
you will never bow your head
I used to be unwilling to bow my head
It’s the pride and self-respect in my heart
I always feel that scholars should be proud
what about now
Your pride is gone.
Someone asked me to choose
For the Song Dynasty
What am I willing to give up?
what is your answer
Everything can be given up
Be flexible
This is the first step to establish a foothold in the court
It's standing still.
correct
What about Pei Jing?
She didn't return to Kaifeng
Wouldn't you marry her only?
To return to the Wang family
Can't have her
good
I'll give you a chance
To take back what should have been
everything that belongs to you
Get up
I heard you brought someone back with you
Magistrate of Ning County, Jinghu South Road Township
This person secretly formed a party with the government
Ally with fraudsters
In the name of ghosts, gods and disasters
collect money
This person is a criminal
Another witness
Should be dealt with according to national law
Recent rumors on Jinghu South Road
There is a new god in the countryside
Do you know the details of this?
What new god
Look at this name
Nine Heavens and Ten Earths
Invincible golden light protects the country and the country
Minamiyama God
have you heard
What did you hear?
This Nanshan God
Let's talk
Why that place?
Opening Gate
Let me tell you this slowly.
Have you heard?
Give me back the money?
Smashing the statue of the god costs 500 coins
Three Hundred Essays on Killing Disasters
Smash idols and get money
you do not say
Secondary School
You don't understand this
Add a bowl of wontons
okay
Taoist temple
Don't touch this kind of place
Every town
Their self-reliant gods
You can smash it.
Many people have received money
What a good deal, right?
This smashing of the idol will kill the disaster
Will there be retribution?
Look, let me tell you
It's fine
Didn’t I mention everyone’s names?
The golden light of nine heavens and ten earths is invincible
The God of Nanshan who protects the country and Anbang
Why is he called Baoguo Anbang?
That's right why
This secret
Please don’t spread rumors
I tell you
This Nanshan God
Follow the current saint
It's a worship of the son
No wonder
I'll just say it
Pay homage to the current saint
yes
Some people believe this
In the eyes of the people
Holy lord, that is the emperor
How big is the emperor?
Pay homage to ghosts and gods
Not too much
This is the crime of deceiving the emperor.
Zhao Jian chose the name well.
Now the Privy Council
It's already a mess
Everyone is exhausted
This matter has nothing to do with the Privy Council
what is the relationship
Nanshan God has a good name
What's wrong
That god already has a portrait
Do you know whose face it is?
whose face
Lu Nanshan
it's him
At least there is one
The Vice-Chairman of the Privy Council is here to
now
He actually put his own face
Painted as idols
This is not bad
The Privy Council has requested an order to seize him.
Dark enough
Minamiyama God
Nanshan God is just a transition
That is, use this name first
Sweep a batch of old gods
Turn back to ourselves
Destroy the Nanshan God again
This happens again and again
How much does someone understand?
The reason why ghosts and gods cannot be trusted
certainly
And the most important thing
Which point
If the government investigates it later,
The unlucky one is Lu Nanshan.
You are really black
Director Xiao Lu said it himself
If there is a chance to save the Song Dynasty from danger,
He is willing to dedicate everything to the Song Dynasty
i am willing to give everything
we just try our best
meet his needs
Shameless
You are too shameless
I heard that you recently
I visited many temples
Excellent results
Everybody is a soldier
Didn't you meet some tough people?
you didn't notice
Haven't you seen Zhao Jian during this time?
Boss
Boss and the others are all here
On the way
To take the statue back
It's really strange.
I have letters and everything.
You said that if you believe in fox demons and tiger spirits
That's all
Damn it
Some people believe in millstones
God of Mopan
Have been in this village for several years
That’s why the village next door
Never dealt with them
Why
The next village worships the bean god
Bean rice, Jiwheat, bean sprouts
right
Isn't that the Soybean God?
No wonder
Can't deal with the God of Millstone
The boss is about to grab the millstone.
Don't hurt anyone
Call me back
Hit it back, hit it back
Zhao Jian's family is like this
Called
Sweeping holes in the courtyard
Rise to kill
Is it so smooth?
Participants
Everyone has copper coins to take
While Zhao Jian was taking action
I will also treat these liars
means of making money
exposed
since then
I'm afraid there are many people
I can't believe this scam anymore.
come here
Come one or two
three
I still don't know something
You say
This is Wei Yuan’s business
No improvement yet
You guys
Money to make statues of gods and open temples
Where did it come from?
Found a sponsor
Who?
It is you
Where did you get the money?
My home is in Kaifeng City
Jieshen Lane
So what
you should know
Jieshen Lane Gold and Silver Trading
Lots of buying and selling
Give me
The numbers are correct, right?
That's right
People who do big business
Not short of this little money
what business to do
First, the middle line
Then I also do some business myself
So you are rich
Saved some property
Then why do you still want to take refuge?
That Lu Nanshan
one two three
If you have money, you must first have the life to spend it.
rich
If you have money, invest it
Come into this bottomless pit
Guaranteed by Wei Yuan’s personality
I will return it to him when I make money in the future.
Money or not is a trivial matter
I just want to ask Mr.
How is my sister doing now?
Why sleep in a coffin
In a plague-stricken area, nine out of ten houses are empty.
furniture in the house
All stolen and sold
What about the coffin?
What do you mean, sister?
It's time to prepare the funeral arrangements first.
If something unexpected happens
It is also more convenient
Why do you need this convenience?
Can you please bring my sister back?
This is what your sister means
Lime is now spreading on the streets
Burn the body
She's good at it all
The local doctor said
no holiday
Then she can consult independently
Why work so hard?
My sister is compared with before
The changes are really big.
yes
After entering Qizhai
Everyone has changes
including you
It's all them
Taught me bad
correct
Nanshan God builds momentum
The effect is almost the same
You can take Lu Nanshan
Back to Kaifeng
I
Zhao Jian and I
Too busy
Could you please make a trip?
Don't kill him
He killed Liu Sheng
What was violated was the national law
There should be punishment by national law
But after all, he has a Privy Council status
Do not worry
Now the first one wants to take his
It's the Privy Council
Will you be surrendered?
Where is the evidence?
This face and this name
All that is available is his.
Then I'll leave now
Then I won't send it.
Aren't you afraid that he will
Let Lu Nanshan go
Xiaojing, the younger brother
Perseverance
If one day
If the Secret Pavilion is reorganized
Maybe he should be one of them
correct
Let me tell you something
Xue Ying
Never came back to me
maybe everyone
Everyone has their own path to take, right?
I'm going back to Kaifeng.
Xiao Luzhangyuan has good vision
Yuan Zhongxin
Hand me over
Brother Yuan said
You should be governed by the laws of the country
I can't die
Why
because of what i did
It's all right
I am the hope of the Song Dynasty
I admire you.
Even if you kill countless people
Rebellion and separation
You never doubted yourself
Sometimes I really can't help but think
Maybe you didn't deserve to die.
maybe one day
You can really make a comeback
It should be so
But I don't want that day to come
Because that day
You will never let it go
Our Pei family
I I swear
I swear
I don't believe this
hurry up
Wait for me
I'm back
came back
are you tired
Sit together and eat
look at you
Been out for so many days
I don’t know how to write a letter back.
What are you still doing?
Mr. Wei said it all
Let you sit down
Come quickly
Wait a moment
You eat first
Let's go out
good
Walk
Why are you at my house?
Borrowing
Why borrow?
Save money
You don't take care of the caravan anymore
Why run a caravan?
You have to make money
That's too slow
so what
Gold and silver trading in Jieshen Lane
I also started
Do you want to do this too?
No, no, no
Not just a hand
I think gold and silver trading
not enough
What do you mean by not enough?
I think everything can be traded
silk jade
Even rice and vegetables
Jieshen Lane
Transaction exchange
impossible
Who would want such a thing
You do not understand
Everything in this world
All are sources of wealth
That's not right either
You can't always use specialties from different places
Bring them all to Kaifeng
No need to transport it
How to trade if you are not lucky?
Trading is an imaginary number
It is a symbol of goods
What imaginary number symbolizes
I dont understand
For example, ten kilograms of venison
This venison is not in Jieshen Lane
But we can start first
trading swap
For example
You exchanged rice wine for my venison
Then bring me the venison
Then you can't get it again
Ten pounds of venison
Go get this year’s new tea
But I actually got nothing
In exchange for the right to belong
What about venison?
It doesn't matter anymore
How could it not be important?
The person who finally belongs
If you don’t want to change anything
I'll have the venison
Send to his house
this kind of transaction
once started
It's hard to stop
I do not understand
This back and forth exchange
How to make money
you do not understand
This is a cornucopia