father
Walk
Chase them all and kill Yuan Hao.
All go
can not go
I want revenge
Chasing Yuan Hao is impossible
I'm not afraid
Then your father died in vain.
Answer me a question first
Why are these cavalry
Coming so slowly
And there are so few people here
The deputy general in the camp said
There is no military order from my father
You can't leave the camp casually
I only adjusted the personal guards
The mobilization of troops and horses is too slow
I'm really too late
the person who said this
Definitely bought
you listen to me
Yuanhao is nearby
There must be soldiers and horses
if we catch up
It's just to die
what we have to do now
Just race against time
Back to the military camp
if you have no choice
To take over
The location of the Yuzhou Military Supervision Department
Your father's revenge
Maybe there will be no chance to apply again.
We all want to avenge your father
father
Among the people of Xixia
When building momentum for the goat god
Always dressed like this
who wears these
Who is the messenger of the sheep god?
when the time is right
You can also use this image of the sheep god to show people
Recreate the miracle
I raise cranes
I usually use this crane whistle
call them
There are these cranes
It's easier to bluff people
What are you doing with this?
When in Xingqing Mansion
Chu Niao met Wei Zhuoran
I know
Wei Zhuoran in Xixia
Wei Zhuoran had met Chu Niao before
Meet in Xingqing Mansion
Chu Niao’s identity was not revealed
There are two possibilities
one
Wei Zhuoran misses old love
one more
Wei Zhuoran joins Xixia
Have other plans
You didn't test it
At that time in Xingqing Mansion
Yuan Hao keeps a close eye on
I dare not act rashly
Now Yuan Hao has come to Helan Mountain
Xingqing Mansion is empty
You rush there immediately
Want to kill Yuan Hao
You should explore Wei Zhuoran’s tone of voice
is it necessary
Seeing Liang Gewei
So he led his troops to kill him.
Yuan Hao will not die so easily
Do you want to count on Wei Zhuoran?
But what if he really
Took refuge in Xixia
Now the life and death of Yanei are unknown
Just say it
Yanei was harmed by Yuan Hao
No matter whether it is true or false
Son is dead
There is always revenge
You want to use your office to force the palace?
adapt to changing circumstances
how about you
This consecration ceremony
Originally, I was just making a start.
these three years
How to fake gods
Various technical details
Actually it's all you
Ask Xue Ying to deliver it to me
It should be said that this is a plan to enshrine the gods.
If it weren't for your Qizhai's help,
There will be no results today
should
We are creating gods in Tanzhou
Also inspired by you
Moreover
Same as Secret Pavilion
We should have been helping each other
What's more, we are
same goal
So the matter of deification
You continue to take over
you are not with us
not going
what are you going to do
unimportant
No
Very important
tell me the answer
I'll go back to the camp at the foot of the mountain
Confirm the whereabouts of Chu Niao and Ya Nei
hear me out
Chu Niao and Yanei
Nine out of ten
Falling into Yuan Hao's hands
if they are still alive
Even if you all go
I don’t have the strength to save people either.
Why are you going back?
I am calmer and more ruthless
If both of them were still alive
You must be unable to help but save people
It is very likely then
It's a total annihilation
You don't save people
I am a smart person
Smart people are always ruthless
Only look at the pros and cons
How many of you
I am an old acquaintance with Brother Ning Ling
The Youzhou Army only recognizes you.
so you
More important than me
No room for error
The situation is urgent
No time for this
A noisy game
Changes have occurred
When moving forward
Don’t be indecisive
Try the crane whistle
coming
If there is Chu Niao
News from inside the office
Please send message as soon as possible
certainly
Take care
Going Down the Mountain
It's obviously a bird
Why do you still recognize people?
If Liang Gewei didn't
Control Yuan Hao
The situation becomes difficult to handle
but we all know
This business won't go well
It doesn't matter
As long as we are still here
This battle is not lost
certainly
I know you are all worried
Are Yanei and Chu Niao okay?
I also want to rush there
Meet Yuan Zhongxin and Xue Ying
Look at the Yuzhou Army
Have you rushed to the rescue?
But we don't have time
We must race against time
Rush to Xingqing Mansion
Wen Wuqi is right
Yuan Hao is here
Xingqing Mansion is empty
your decision is right
But this means
I left Yanei here
You just need to remember
This decision was made by me
if done wrong
It has nothing to do with you
I think
Wen Wuqi is not what he said
He is a ruthless person
Set off
Go to Xingqing Mansion
I killed Liang Gewei
Father is brave
Youzhou Army
There are generals who are loyal to me
Liang Gewei's death
within today
Youzhou Military Supervision Department
can be used by me
congratulations
My father’s magical power is unparalleled
Worthy of being called the Son of Heaven
Why doesn't the queen speak?
I'm waiting
A woman
Such a big thing
Don't quite understand
There is an injury on the back
Please Queen, please bandage me
yes
It looks like the camp is not big
Don't dare to move the army
My dad
My dad said
If all the troops are transferred from their bases,
A war is inevitable
The one who led the troops this time
There are only two lieutenants
When we mobilized our troops just now
Who is unwilling to cooperate?
Neither of them want to
The worst thing that could happen now is
I'm afraid these two
They have all surrendered to Yuan Hao
Now what
With just the strength we have now
I'm afraid it's impossible to charge directly into the formation.
How about we leave here first?
Rush back to the Youzhou Army Headquarters
no
One step slow, one step slow
Are you brave?
Shaodu unified the army
speak directly
I guess they should now
Waiting for you to return to camp
Find an opportunity to take action
It should be so
Then we'll deliver it to your door
Xiao Xue’s knife is very fast now.
newspaper
The Shaodu troops have returned to camp.
Hurry up and ask the young commander to lead the army.
yes
this
Wait
Try to make the crime of patricide and seizing power
Put it on Liang Maixiang
Then what
Captured alive or
Liang family control
Youzhou has been in charge of military affairs for many years
if she lives
There will be endless troubles
this
Du Tongjun
How could the Dutong Army be like this?
Dad was murdered
Also invite two generals
Make the decision for the Liang family
How did he die?
Shaodu unified the army
Please tell me more details
Brother Ning Ling
Son and minister are here
I'm waiting for your explanation
What does the father want to ask?
Two commanders of the left wing army
How did he die?
Liang Gewei
why here
besides
Sheep Guardian
Let's explain together
Return to Father
Liang Gewei's rebellion
Liang Gewei
He is an accomplice with the Sheep God Envoy
This person is very ambitious
He actually killed his guardian mother
two commanders
and
Also force my son
Turn against his father
Sons and ministers disobey
Liang Gewei actually had murderous intentions
The sheep guardian also plots rebellion
You can know a person's face but not his heart
these three years
The Goat God really helped me a lot
But recently I discovered
Something's wrong with the situation
Within Daxia
Worship God more than me
This is wrong
indeed
so you say
When killing the sheep guardian angel
I didn't stop you
I think you can make it happen
Father
Where do these words come from?
I never thought about it
To kill the sheep guardian angel
Treason
Queen Mother
The Sheep Keeper is involved in many things
How can you let your father
Do it yourself
Say you killed
Just admit it and it's over
Could it be
You don’t listen to my father’s words either
I understand
I won't let him come yet
bear this charge
The Blue Emperor is Merciful
Fine
Let’s not talk about this first
Kill the sheep guardian angel
you say
The commander was killed by Liang Gewei
It's for rebellion
He still wants to kill you
Sons and ministers are loyal and courageous
Then why are you not dead?
My father is like a god descending from the sky
Liang Gewei fled in panic
The fate of sons, ministers and mother
It was my father who saved me.
That's it
It's all Liang Gewei's fault
The sons and ministers never discovered the treacherous plot
Also punished
Anyway, Liang Gewei is dead
Whatever you say is fine
Father
What your son said is absolutely true
Every sentence is true
Lift up
Spreading the will of the Goat God
It turned out to be a Song Dynasty
What's going on?
perhaps
It’s Liang Gewei, the thief
United with the Song Dynasty
Is it Liang Gewei's fault?
There are such vicious people in the world
I trust you
all conspiracies
All from Liang Gewei
Father Wang Shengming
After I came back, I asked the camp
After the two commanders died
It is true that you have never left the camp.
sons and ministers
Trapped by thieves
but there is one person
Have been preparing the army
Buy military morale
Explain it
I deserve to die
Shaodu unified the army
what happened
Everyone
These two unite with foreign enemies
Framing Du Tongjun
Now the traitor has been beheaded
the rest of you
not guilty
At this time
Don’t make the mistake of yourself
Foreign enemies covet
My father was murdered
I am the Yuzhou Army
There should be a concerted effort
Overcoming difficulties together
Everyone
The Liang family will never betray anyone
The Youzhou Army belongs to the Liang family
Also yours
Willing to lead the army for the young capital
Serve
Willing to serve the Shaodu Army
Let the whole army set off
Return to camp
yes
I'm still thinking about it at this time
Two more words
Is it because Xiaoxue’s knife is not fast enough?
Thanks
Do you really want to go back to camp?
How about rushing to kill Yuan Hao now?
What happened to the palace?
I checked the tent many times
There's no way we can hide that many people
Imperial villa
He is from the palace
They sent people and horses here
That seems to have been planned.
Yuan Hao in Helan Mountain
A separate courtyard built at the east foot of the mountain
A place for daily pleasure
It shouldn't be far from here then
That's right
If you want to say that
The so-called dozens of people
I'm afraid it's just bait
Yuan Hao should have an army
Still leaving the palace
Kill it now
Ten deaths without life
If there is an ambush outside the palace
Then why didn't he directly
Take action on us
Your father has commanded the Youzhou Army for many years
If troops and horses are used
Youzhou army must rebel
best countermeasures
Just kill your father
Then use two deputy generals to seize power
what should i do now
You are now running as fast as you can
Rush back to the Youzhou Army Camp
As long as the Youzhou Army is still in your hands
You have a chance to take revenge
good
Wait until I take control of the military
Then he raised an army to kill Yuan Hao
no
Why not?
Those who raise an army must die
You can't beat Yuan Hao
As long as you don't raise troops
We can still maintain a stalemate
Yuan Hao at this time
Nor do we hope that in Xixia
There will be war again
I can't hold out much longer.
Wait for the opportunity
Believe me
I want to kill Yuan Hao more than you do
I wait
Wish you a safe journey
You have to leave
Xiao Xue stayed
I
You go back with Shao Du to lead the army.
I'm afraid Yuan Hao is in the Youzhou Army
Still have a backup plan
In case there is a critical moment
Remember to use the knife
Waiting for your news
Aren't you worried about him?
Worry
In Xixia territory
each time
Maybe it’s goodbye forever
Then why don't you leave with him?
act in desperate situation
We can only move forward courageously
what i want to do now
Just to protect you
Help you take over the Yuzhou Army
Our Liang family hates Yuan Hao
It's because I'm desperate
what about you
Why do you have to kill him?
Because people who have been hurt by war
out on a limb
Don't kneel down in a hurry yet
explain explain
minister
momentarily confused
Became bribed by Liang Gewei
make big mistake
hereby
Apologize to Qingtianzi
Betrayal of Father
Relying on Liang Gewei
It's you
That's right
Killed two commanders
also me
Recognized pretty quickly
at this point
Nothing to hide
Brother Ning Ling
you two
We have a good relationship, right?
Father
did not expect
He has deceived his son for so many years
Seizing power in the military
Imprisonment of the Prince
What is this crime?
capital offense
When to cut
what you think
Indeed a capital crime
They should be escorted back to Xingqing Mansion
Convicted by the Trial Division
No need to bother
Someone coming
Rice poultry north
Tied to the ordering platform
Tomorrow morning
Beheading in the camp
yes
Father
Don't be so anxious
Why is this so anxious?
And I want to let you
Kill him with your own hands
Our father-son love is deep
He lied to you
I can't see it
How about it
I will give you a hand
chance for revenge
My son is so touched
Come
Hang this one up too
Step aside
Young people of the same race
Don't know the importance
Make Qingtianzi laugh
Quite loyal
What is your name
Noriyoshi
What are you carrying?
open me and see
The king has an order not to be violated
You take it with you
What are these things for?
I am young
Feel more
I know you are loyal and brave
But Qing Tianzi
To our wild family
I've never been very reassured
sometimes
You have to know how to bow your head
clear
Such a loyal person
Now there are fewer
I don't know Brother Yuan.
With Xue Ying
how's it going
They can definitely catch up
But no one told him
Let’s go to Xingqing Mansion
Looking for a turning point
Xingqingfu is the only place to go
He can think of
That's good
What are you looking for?
my herbs
What's wrong with you?
This is both medicine and poison
Used separately, they can cure diseases and save lives.
If mixed in proportion
Drug effects are mutually exclusive
That's extremely poisonous
Because taking the wrong medicine is
Taboos in practicing medicine
On the contrary, I remember it very clearly
I think
No matter how brave Yuan Hao is, he is invincible
After all, we are humans too
Makes sense
if we could get close
People around Yuan Hao
There is a chance of poisoning
Ning Lingge and Queen Yeli
The mother and son and Yuan Hao
Be wary of each other
Be more careful than your enemies
too difficult
Isn’t there someone beside Yuan Hao?
My new favorite concubine?
If I could find her way
Enough
Harder
None of us know her
not to mention
People may not be willing to help us
Is it Brother Yuan?
Xixia people
Where did the soldiers and horses come from?
Brother Yuan Haoning
Or the Youzhou Army?
Should I use my identity as a divine envoy to pass the test?
Can't leave
Zhao Jian
The troops are divided into two groups
Chase up the mountain
yes
Brother Ning Ling
You feel
Those people pretending to be angels
Where are you now?
Run away
if they were just for
Scam some money
Then you should run away now
Can't find it
possible
But if they were
Liang Gewei's subordinates
Then follow the Youzhou Army
That makes sense.
There is another possibility
These people are here for me
Then now they will
There's only one place to go
Xingqingfu
I'm not in Xingqing Mansion
The identity of the messenger
Can deceive many people
I'm on the way to Xingqing Mansion
Dispatched the cavalry
Do you think I will gain anything?
Return to Father
sons and ministers
have no idea
Don't run
Ran up the mountain
Chase
Keep up
fine
step by step
Go and kill Mi Qin Mu Bei for me.
Is there a problem
Why rebel?
Born to be a rebel
Is there anything else you would like to say finally?
I failed
But there will definitely be people who come after you
i want to tell them
Yuan Hao is not scary
He is also a human being
How crazy!
kill someone
No need to talk so much
After all, he has military exploits
Leave a whole body
Take action
Father's Mercy
Touching heaven and earth
okay
Give me back the knife
good
Hang up his body too
I want everyone to know
people who are my enemies
What's the end?
quick
Over there
Chase
quick
Walk
kill him
Where are the people?
four people
yes
Three of them were wearing
Sheep Guardian Dress Up
died on the carriage
How did you die?
Killed by a sharp blade
who killed
perhaps
It's internal strife
Then there is another one
Escape on horseback
Cavalry intercepts
In the end, the man was desperate
Jump off the glacier
There's just no body
Didn't catch it
Congratulations, Your Majesty
Kill all the angels
too late
Now those who believe in the goat god
I don't know how many
Or neglected
Just thinking
The benefits of God’s blessing
Ignore the harm he brings
Most of our people believe in ghosts and gods
There is no way
It’s because I believe too much in ghosts and gods
That gives people a headache
If they don’t believe in ghosts and gods
How can I respect you as the Son of Heaven?
Don't say it
Recalling God
People who do this
Really smart
It's a pity that not a single person was left alive.
spread out
Just say Liang Gewei
To kill the angel
That's why I killed him
Yes, sir.
Of course
Kill the Angel
How can you be the Qing Emperor?
Tomorrow's camp
You mother and son
Come with me to the Rikyu Palace.
Stay for two days to enjoy the mountain view
That's great
this child
Always hope
I am being filial under your knees
This time I got my wish
It's good to be filial
Just don't try your best
Become a send-off