I will arrange it for you
Sneak back to Xingqing Mansion
Brother Ning Ling will never do it
Let your son and son be in danger
How can we live up to our comrades in life and death?
This is me, brother Ning Ling
The bottom line of being a human being
Thank you, Your Highness
Thank you, Your Highness, for planning for them
no way
No preparation before
they can't escape
Now that it's been seen, it's useless
Kill it
Wang Kuan and the others are already in the market.
you are already safe
Yuan Zhongxin
Xiao Xue
Chief
You escaped
Who let you go?
Didn't you listen to what Yanei said?
We escaped
It is absolutely impossible for Yuan Hao
Let you escape from the military camp
What else?
Are we ghosts?
Don't talk nonsense
The shadows are all there
Whatever
I'm still thinking about conscription and crusade
To avenge you?
Then do I still have to
I was deeply moved.
Yuan Zhongxin
You should know about your father, right?
What he does has nothing to do with me
But your last name is Yuan too.
Shaodu unified the army
Trouble
Your father said
Listen to me everything
what do you want to do
The Yuan family rebelled
The opening of the examination for the capture of Yuan Zhongxin
Yuan Zhongxin said it all
Nothing to do with him
And Yuan Zhongxin refused
He is from Song Dynasty
Is he from Song Dynasty?
It doesn't matter what you say
Princess Zhao
I have with me a secret order from the Privy Council
Do you want to see it?
I'm fine
He said he would go back to Kaifeng and be tried.
On the way back, I am not a criminal.
For the sake of Princess Zhao,
You are allowed to travel together
please
Let you go
But Wei Zhuoran
No wonder
After arriving in Lingnan, there was no trace
You Qizhai
It's really extraordinary
six people
Half have problems
Who else
Zhao Jian, Wang Kuan and you
I can still trust it
What happened to Xiao Jing?
The rescuer
All dead
yes
Three people in total
Save the Song people and kill their colleagues
after
He was killed again in the corner of the camp
It should be the Song people who killed people and silenced them
This person has been saved
What else are you trying to say?
Song people were cruel
They can do anything
really
this has arrived
It's outrageous
Father
Since someone rescued
It shows that there is another mastermind behind the assassination.
This matter must be investigated strictly
Yes
I'll leave this to you
I
Who else can I trust but you?
yes
Go ahead
Qing Tianzi
It was done by the prince.
I actually don’t really hope to be the prince
I intercepted
However, the three young men were still
Let it go
I heard about it
Mr. Wei's son
and those young men
A close friend
Right
Please forgive me, Lord Qingtian
Those young men
Life or death is not important
Important
I know Brother Ning Ling
It would be fine if he was the mastermind behind it
Mr. Wei
It depends on you
This Yuan Zhongxin and Zhao Jian
Look
Sincere and sincere
Born in Song Dynasty
If you grew up in the Song Dynasty, you are a Song Dynasty person.
I also feel that way
Sometimes
ignorance
Not necessarily a bad thing
what do you mean
Not interesting
Feel free to express your feelings
The affairs of the Song Dynasty have nothing to do with me
So what should the prince do?
take it easy
First give him his military power little by little
take it back
After all, he is his son
It can't be the end of the world, right?
Sister Zhao, are you okay?
No more delay
Set off overnight to return to the Song Dynasty
It's time for us to go
Shaodu unified the army
thank you
Why should my father help you?
Maybe one day we will meet again
Set off
I heard about it
Yuan Zhongxin
You are a member of Qizhai
this matter
will never change
Let's go
Shaodu unified the army
your father is here
father
Why do you want Yuzhou Army?
Listen to that Lu Nanshan
Aren’t we going to kill Yuan Hao?
Yuan Hao
Of course, kill
Then why stop it?
Wang Kuan and others
Yuan Hao is going to die
But you can't die on the altar
I ask you
Who will succeed Yuan Hao if he dies?
Brother Ning Ling
How is Ning Lingge like a person?
Naturally cunning and vicious
If Yuan Hao died
Will Brother Ning Ling take revenge for him?
That's natural
He wants to be justified
This revenge must be avenged
are you worried
A young man from the Song Dynasty was killed by him
Who cares whether they live or die?
I ask you
If Wang Kuan and the others
Assassination on the altar
What identity will you use?
They pretend to be our Youzhou Army
If Yuan Hao died
Just those few
Song Dynasty Youth
Not enough
Brother Ning Ling wants to
After working with us
Destroy our Yuzhou army together
Yuan Hao is going to die
But you can’t catch up with our Youzhou Army
Then why believe it
Where is Lu Nanshan?
buy and sell
Lu Nanshan borrowed trade routes
Gave us military rations
Lu Nanshan was from the Song Dynasty
He gave us military rations
Could the Song Dynasty still do such a thing?
Do you think their court
Can you agree to such a thing?
so
Lu Nanshan was not following orders
He adjusts the food in private
Help other countries’ armies
Such a big deal
Why is he doing this?
One
If the Song Dynasty goes to war with us
He wants our Youzhou Army
join forces with him
one more
Why do I always feel
He's staring at those
Where is the assassin?
shouldn't
They have no grudges
who cares
Years of fierce fighting in Daxia
Almost at the end of the rope
With this military ration
can alleviate
The urgent need of our Youzhou Army
Girl
As long as we can keep our Youzhou Army
others
None of it matters
What about Yuan Hao?
Take it easy
Kill Yuan Hao in no hurry
Important opportunity
Waiting for the sky
As long as we Yuzhou Army
Strong military power
us
I can wait
yes
Land Adult
Yuan Zhongxin
Get off the car
Stay
That's it
Where are we sending people to?
The Privy Council took over
Imprisoned
How to interrogate
Princess Zhao
Your father's funeral
Still waiting for you to go back to take charge
Go home quickly
Go ahead
I'm fine
Princess Zhao
Please help yourself
I still have questions to ask about the rest.
Do not worry
where are we going
Secret Pavilion
How did it become like this?
Now the Secret Pavilion
There is no longer any six or seven fasts
I won't stay here again
Where did it move to?
Military camp outside the city
Born to fight
Why bother making it look like an academy?
My father's way of doing things
It should have been thrown away long ago
The current secret pavilion
There are no more teachers to teach
what's the function
Learning martial arts and combat skills is enough
If you don’t read, you don’t understand
How can I understand
The meaning of the Secret Pavilion
If you only know how to kill
But I don’t know how to be determined
Sooner or later your eyes will be covered with blood
soldier
Just obey military orders
So you don't understand at all
Why does Lu Zhangyuan
Choose a young man to enter the Secret Pavilion
battle of ideas
No need to waste words
The surrounding area has been fortified
No one is allowed to leave here
Why
First
you have to
What Yuan Zhongxin said and did
Write it all down
I need to use it in my case
second
Xinmi Pavilion was established
You want to join
Still need to investigate
Can't you go home?
Please stay in this courtyard for a few more days.
The time has come
Nature will let you go
Is there anything else you want to say?
Do you have pen and paper?
Writing or painting
write memorial
What memorial
Impeach
Who to impeach
you
Impeach me for what?
Lu Zhangyuan died in battle
According to the ancestral system, you should live in mourning, Ding You
Three years of mourning at the grave
Impeach you for disregarding ethics and morality
Disobeying human ethics
He is indeed a scholar
I'll ask someone to bring the pen and paper later.
I'm going to get water
clean up here
Let's do it together
Yuan Family Affairs
not that simple
What
Lu Nanshan handle
Former Nakashin Oshiri Prison
Lock us here again
We should be waiting for someone to come find us.
who will come to us
have no idea
But this person
It should be related to the Yuan family
go in
This is waiting for me
I heard you have the means
Not pinned
I'm afraid you'll run away
What's your surname?
The compound surname is Yuchi
One source per name
Source of Origin
Members of the secret court
Secret Pavilion
Which day
Lu Nanshan’s New Secret Pavilion
This time I went to Yingtian Mansion to search for the Yuan family.
This is the team I lead
The Yuan family escaped but left a trap
Xiao Li's Knife
He was stabbed to death with a flying spear
Lao Gu
die from sting
We are a team of four
The strongest one is Xiao Zhao
he uses sword
This was cut off by a sharp blade
A swordsman wearing a hat
The knife is carried diagonally on the back
A knife is unsheathed
Cut off Xiao Zhao's sword
It also took away Xiao Zhao’s life
Aren’t the Yuan family all gone?
Why is there still someone left?
I don't think so
Someone behind the Yuan family is helping them
All are good hands
But the origin is unknown
This swordsman is one of them
Xixia people
Search the Yuan family this time
It's a top secret operation
We just arrived at Yingtianfu
The Yuan family is empty.
they moved away
Leave us to Yingtianfu
Only one day passed
Someone leaked the news
Someone in the court is helping the Yuan family
answer my question now
Who is helping the Yuan family?
I do not know
Who is that swordsman?
I very much support your revenge for your subordinates.
But I really don't know
Your father is the clan leader
Yuan Family Affairs
you do not know
I never called him daddy
give me answer
I really can't give it
For the Yuan family
How many people died?
I didn’t even listen to what dad said.
if you said
Everything is correct
Why do you need to teach me how to read?
Reading is for understanding
What understanding reason seeks is to be able to distinguish between right and wrong
Ah Jian Na
Dad asked you to get married
Dad won't harm you
If I listened to you today
Just get married like this
Is to put oneself
Hidden in the boudoir
That kind of me
How is it different from the dead?
father
I am leaving
I'm leaving today
It’s to seek the path in my heart
Everything in the world stops me
Undying
Unyielding
Just father-daughter love
never dare to forget
Take care of yourself
father
I'm home
How did you open the lock?
just kill me
People are dead
Just nothing
Why did you send everyone away?
Lu Nanshan didn't let you do anything to me
The Yuan family killed my colleagues
I shall take revenge
understand
goodbye
The subordinate just wanted to teach him a lesson
Well taught
No one has taught me a lesson
Dean
This subordinate will lead a search throughout the city.
Kaifeng city is so big
Can you find it?
But in fact
Where Yuan Zhongxin can go
Not many
Lu Nanshan said
Talk about Xiao Jing’s family
I have been in contact with Han Duanzhang for a long time.
I do not know
impossible
Our family is disconnected from Han
It does not matter
Not in a hurry
Check slowly
Xiao Xue
Why are you saying it now?
Lu Nanshan issued a military order
Let me not tell you
Then why did you say it again?
Because I think you
More important than military orders
What's happening now
You can't check it from Lu Nanshan.
To check
We have to do it ourselves
But there are people watching around
can not go out
There's nothing we can do
Coach Liang
what's the matter
Do you need my help
Coach Liang
how do you know
we are here
It's Zhao Jian
She found me
The chief looked for you before going home.
Zhao Jian said
You guys are in trouble
As expected of the chief
Thoughtful
Someone is guarding outside
how did you get in
I told them
Come and see your students
Just let me in
Say it
What trouble
Long story short
Yuan Zhongxin was arrested
You Qizhai
He is the sickest one.
Actively caught
Should have been caught long ago
Good catch
Afraid of life and death
Is it that serious
What do you need me to do
We can't stay here
Equal results
our own business
We need to check it ourselves
When I came in just now
There are many guards outside
Fight out
Too much noise
No need to use your hands
Then what do you want me to do?
Today's date is just right
Just bring me a letter
Good date
A letter
You guys go down first
Princess, you
I want to be alone
Talk to my dad for a while
let's go
I suffered a lot when I was a child
I think I know something
The truth of this world
what truth
Just one person
As long as it's bad enough and ruthless enough
Don't care about anything
You'll live a pretty good life
It's not unreasonable
But such a person is like
Sinking underwater
Sinking to the deepest bottom of the water
So lonely
alone in the mud
Trek forward
Seems like he can't stand the injury
But it's hard to breathe
Hard to move even an inch
People shouldn't live alone
uncle
The first half of the road
It was you who accompanied Zhao Jian
second half of the road
I will accompany her until the end
Actually I didn't plan to
Ran out
But I am restless
I was just thinking
Maybe kneel here
Take these few words from your heart
Tell your uncle
He can also be at peace
Just to make my dad feel at ease
also for you
Everyone in charge is here
Let's go get someone
Liang Zhu went to see Wang Kuan
He also took a letter away with him
Who is Liang Zhu?
I used to teach boxing in Mi Pavilion
This is Wang Kuan’s secret move.
The troops are divided into two groups
I'm going to find Yuan Zhongxin
You follow Liang Zhu
I want them to understand
All their calculations
All in vain
what are you doing
Dean
I thought about it
Yuan Zhongxin escaped
It's my misfortune
I went to Buddhist temples and Taoist temples to worship.
This willow leaf sweeps the body
Can remove bad luck
Nonsense
You lost someone
What bad luck should I sweep away?
How can we forget the good thing about Zhang Yuan?
open the door open the door
Open the door quickly
open the door
There is a funeral in the courtyard
A funeral is no greater matter than a state affair
Then smash
Chasing the rebels
yes
Xiaolu Zhangyuan is such a coincidence
I just wanted to find you
Yuan Zhongxin escapes from the dungeon
May I ask where the county master is?
I know
I was about to hand someone over to you
meet again
Xiaolu Zhangyuan
He came to find you
He came to pay homage to my father
Then express your heart in front of the soul
It is to soothe the dead
It's also comforting me
Then what
I am very touched
Then tied him up
why
The origin of funeral etiquette is filial piety
How dare you let a fugitive
Disturbing the mourning hall
But he did it for you
The dead are the greatest
How dare I let my late father
There is no peace under the Nine Springs
Take it away
The justice of the princess
I should also pay my respects
No need
what do you want to say
I miss him a little
I mean Yu Chiyuan
Pull over, pull over
Xiaolu Zhangyuan
Xiao Xue
Pour the tea quickly
where is tea
look
It's miserable for us here
What to write
Hold on
Memorial to your impeachment
Please hand it over
You really wrote it
I always do what I say
Yuan Zhongxin escaped
Fleeed to Zhao Mansion
Zhao Jian handed him back again
impossible
Anyway, the person has been escorted back to the dungeon
There is no chance of escape
I know you Qizhai
There is always some cleverness
Actually
Just a group
A young man who doesn't know his place
Dare I ask Mr. Lu?
How high the sky is, how thick the earth is
Do you have a real number?
It turned out that I didn’t know either
The sky is high and the earth is thick
I know Liang Zhu has been here
so what
Wang Kuan
do you know
All your means
I can guess it
Really
Go find out whose mansion this is
yes
You asked Liang Zhu to leave with the letter
Just want to take the opportunity to escape from here
Help Yuan Zhongxin investigate the case
Guessed right
But the Yuan family is in a lot of trouble
I checked that he has a Privy Council Order
You feel
What kind of person
To break today's situation
Not many people like this
Asked clearly
It's a mansion bought by a tea merchant.
There are many official residences around here.
Tea merchants will buy it here
I heard that I bought a petty official
It seems to be the son of the city
Or the coach
Sesame Mung Bean Big Posts
In fact, he is just a petty official.
Sure
I asked many people
can't be wrong
Deputy Purpose of the Privy Council
Acting under Lu Nanshan
able to disobey
There are not many people with military orders in the Privy Council.
But by your side Wang Kuan
But there is one
Can change today's situation
Let your distinguished officials pay homage to the government affairs
It can be called the name of Xianggong
You turn to him for help
This is your plan, right?
I am Lu Nan
I am Lu Nanshan
I'm Lu Nan Shantou
me
I
I'm Lu Nanshan's subordinate
I am Lu Nan
I
me
Well played
beat
Lu Zhangyuan had expected it
Variables here
I dare to ask, but it will be in front of Wang Xianggong
Lu Nanshan, deputy commissioner of the Privy Council
Let us pay our respects to Mr.
See Wang Xianggong
His Majesty is in a high position
He said something
Of course I'll let him go.
But Wang Kuan
have you ever thought about
You are the royal son.
I lock you here
Wouldn’t your father know?
The story behind Qizhai
Am I really the only one like me?
A small new courtyard?
to be honest
lock you here
This is exactly what your father meant.
You also wrote to him
such a pity
All your efforts were wasted
no way no money
How to be so calm
have to say
Your qi-nurturing efforts
I really admire
I've thought about it
What
I'm locked up here
My father should know
Of course I've thought about such a thing
so
put all one's eggs in one basket
take a gamble
Now that I've thought about it
That would ruin the situation.
I can't rely on my father
Not relying on your father
Then the big shot in the court
Who else can you ask?
I didn't invite
Just asking for directions
so
Liang Zhu is the stone you threw
How can he find a way out?
No
Your men
It's the stone that's thrown