servants employed by the academy
Enthusiastic
The academy is dealing with some debris
If you have any needs
You can also ask them for help
Very thoughtful
He looks kind and kind-hearted.
The academy thinks a lot about its students.
You are also a student
yes
The post of director is all filled by students
He is the same generation as Nizi.
Those are all classmates
That
what do we call
Webster
And me
aunt
you are too polite
In fact, just call me Shibo
My surname is not Wei
But brother Wei
It's a masterpiece at first glance
so much
Are you biological?
Less than asking you something
Sir, please speak
Within our academy
In addition to normal regulations
Are there any special taboos?
That's it.
some rumors
but
Scholars should not talk about these things
I'm not a scholar
You can tell me
Actually it's nothing
There are rumors in the academy
Said it was late at night
Don't leave the house
If someone knocks on the door after dark
Don't open the door casually
If I
What will happen if you leave the house?
If you go out at night
Afraid of losing money
Even encounter unexpected events
How could there be such a rumor?
So scary
I’m not sure about this either.
But after all, the academy is built on a mountain
Weak students
It will inevitably attract the covetousness of animals
It's better to stay indoors when it gets dark
That's natural
This is the studio arranged by the academy
All cleaned
Safety
This is
book boy
All like this
Are they all like this?
That
I'll take Brother Wei to the lecture hall tomorrow
If there's nothing else, I'll take my leave now.
What are you going to do in the lecture hall tomorrow?
Class
Still have to go to class
Didn’t you come to the academy to study?
he will go
sorry to bother you
I
It's okay. See you tomorrow.
Really want to go
nonsense
Aren't you pretending to be a student?
How can you pretend not to listen to the class?
I dont go
I can't stand it
How about I become a book boy?
That's too late
Okay, okay.
I think you shouldn't be too angry
I'm not angry
Then you have to do a good job of pretending
Pretend to be sick
yes
I can be sick
Just get used to him
He's really not good at reading.
I'm really not
Say less.
make her angry
what
They really look like a family of three.
nobody
Come
Brother Wang, let me tell you
I'm in the backyard today
saw a chicken
And the dead uncle
That one looks particularly similar
But then it disappeared
I saw Si Qixing
Where is it?
Right here
Really in the academy
Where are the people?
If you don't see me, I'll wait here
See if he will show up again
Didn't he?
Never appeared again
So what did he say?
He advised us
Leave the academy
Why
have no idea
This thing is weird
or
Let’s meet up with Sister Zhao and the others first.
Let's discuss together
Good
Fear
This yard is weird
As soon as the sun sets
There are no students in the dormitory
My aunt also told me not to go out at night
I am here
Let's go
Scared
It's too dark
I'm too timid
Sorrow and sorrow are common to all people
It's fine
Brother Wang, are you also afraid?
Yes
So what are you afraid of? Can you say it?
Say it further
Afraid of the suffering in the world
People's livelihood is difficult
Let’s talk about it closer
Afraid of life and death
especially you
You don't have to be afraid of this
I won't leave
cool enough
Yanei
what are you doing
Leave me alone I'm going to get sick
Why
Otherwise tomorrow
I want to go to the lecture hall to study
It's better to let me die
You guys go in first
I will try again
Yanei
you don't like reading
Maybe it's not the book's fault
The so-called gentleman is not vigilant
The tall building will collapse
You should be comfortable from within
Wet from within
Come, come, come
Lift it slowly, lift it slowly
Does it hurt?
came back
Is it better?
What's wrong with Sister Zhao?
Angry at the office
Is it because of illness?
Let him take a lesson
It's like it's killing him.
really
There's no need to really pour cold water on it
Just pretend to be sick and you'll be fine
Don't talk nonsense
He said
Afraid of being seen through by others
Sometimes there are times in the office
Really stubborn
Yeah, don’t listen to anything you say
Xue Ying
Aren’t you able to talk to Yanei?
How about you go and persuade him?
I don't advise
Why
I was going to persuade him
Result Question
The book boy also has to follow the class
I support Yanei on this matter
Listen
Take a look
You should say something
say something
I'm in Yushu Pavilion
I saw Si Weixing
from internal dampness from internal dampness
Isn’t it better to wear less clothes?
Who?
Didn’t you say you shouldn’t go out at night?
Dead Ghost Uncle
Just so mindlessly
Said a few words
Then the person disappeared
Didn't show up again after that
I guess I saw Pollux.
I think so
River Star
If you really want to see us
Just show up and it'll be fine
The Mystery of Pollux
Bought by a prodigal
What are these?
these numbers
he knows what it is
have no idea
completion
Wang Kuan doesn’t even know
Can't figure it out
But I always feel
these numbers
deja vu
Can not remember
Such complex numbers
If you have seen it
It should be a deep memory, right?
Explain that when I see these numbers
It feels normal
Only then will it be swept away
never remembered
The key is
who would think
These numbers are normal
yes
why
Chief
what
Someone is looking for you outside
Who to look for
Find parents
Came to your door so quickly
Come here so late
clean
I'm waiting to do some chores in the academy
heard about you
A family of three only came to the academy
Came here specially to see you
Don’t leave your house after late at night
If someone knocks on the door after dark
Don't open the door casually
Since I came here specially
Something has to happen
Dare I ask if the three of them are locals?
It’s not that we came here because of its reputation
That'll be easy
Have those three people ever heard of it?
Jinghu South Road
There is always disaster
That's a demonic disaster running rampant
So scary
this
All those who come to the academy are talented people
That is also the future of the Song Dynasty
Those of us who are servants
Just thinking about it every day
We should protect these students
Only worthy of being born in the Song Dynasty
amazing
This gentleman
Although there are disasters in this world
But there are ways to deal with it
Our side
Can you have an adventure?
Unknown
Master and Madam
I would like to go and have a look together
At this moment
If you go out at night, you will lose money.
Even encounter unexpected events
Master and Madam
We can go whenever we want
It doesn't have to be today.
That's it for now
I just heard you say so much
I'm really curious
Is it convenient now?
convenient
Of course convenient
only
The young master still has homework tomorrow
I don’t want to disturb you two from resting.
he's fine
Let him stay here and read
Can we go together?
That's the best
That's it for both of them
Go with these people
Something's wrong with these people
Really no need
Are you following Sister Zhao and the others?
Still worried about them
To say something is wrong
They won't lose to anyone
Too
I have this puzzle
See if there is a way to crack it
Why do you two have to dress up like this?
Bought everything
that is
I always have to find a chance to wear it.
Do you two believe in gods and demons?
Do you believe in gods and demons?
Not a big problem
Then we believe
That's right
Where is this academy?
Everything is fine
These are the students
for such things
No sense of awe
Students don’t believe it
Who says it's not?
so
Find us
Be a father and a mother
Really accurate
We especially believe
special letter
That's great.
You two, please come with me
Walk
now please allow me
A grand introduction to the two of you
The real god in this academy
Please take a look, you two
One worship
Two bows
Three Prostrations
Dare those heads in the Inn
Everyone is waiting here
We have searched all over the world for this
Just found these
Spiritual stone figurine god
Don't hide it from both of you.
Eliminate disaster and avoid disaster
Bless all living beings
As the saying goes
Whatever you ask for
awesome
There is no proof for what you say. Please take a look.
What about this person?
Come to the academy too
A handyman
But since he was a child
these legs
I can't walk
It should be treated
But how to cure a stubborn disease born from birth?
Moreover
He grew up in a poor family
He can't afford it.
Poor
It's too awful
Fortunately, fortunately
He has found faith now.
Ready to sacrifice
Please watch
What miracle happened after the sacrifice?
Wait a minute
Since that
he can't walk
What did the academy hire him to do?
The academy is so compassionate
Yeah
The Academy Master is kind-hearted
Does he live near here?
no no
Live quite far away
He lives so far
How did the academy find him?
And hired him
this this
The academy is world-famous
He admires this in his heart
Came by myself
Just to do some work
I also want to take this opportunity to learn how to read and write.
right
Came by myself
awesome
you do not say
how come
this
Take a carriage?
How can it be
Everyone said that my family is poor
How is it possible to ride in a carriage?
This is not important
I see
What
He crawled here by himself
Have perseverance
Really
Yes, yes, that's it
Look at the one in our family again
Look at other people's attitudes
What a sin
Anxious
What about those two people?
sacrifice
Sacrifice can usher in a turning point
Awaken the Miracle
The so-called sacrifice
Close relatives should be used
fortunately
There are
Holy objects can be substituted
This is the holy thing
In exchange for three thousand strings
Not expensive
That's right, that's right
Such grace is priceless
Please take a look, you two
So green
This is the fire of the gods
The sacrifice came true
awesome
There is a reaction
How about it
Seems like there's a reaction
have a feeling
This is good
I stood up
stood up
My legs are healed
God is obviously enlightened
The sacrifice came true
Well, this is the power of sacrifice
fulfilled
Eiko
Good good good
spinner
Shuangfeiyan
good
well
My legs are healed
Thank God
Can we make a sacrifice?
all right
Just exchange money for holy objects
After the sacrifice
Can be exchanged for children’s gold list title
academically successful
It doesn't sound interesting
Can I change it to another one?
Immune to all diseases
Immortality
OK
This and such a wish
Requires three holy objects
Let me do the math on this.
Nine thousand strings is enough
If there is no cash
You can offer gold, silver, and jade
Why use money?
This is the rule
Didn't you just say
holy object
Better to sacrifice
A close relative
It can be
But it's not necessary
How about I sacrifice my son?
Good idea
Why are you two doing this?
It's okay, you don't have to be reluctant
He is not my biological child
Not biological
Why can't I bear it?
this
After all, it’s a human life
Holy objects can be used in place of living people
There is really no need to burn the son.
This this
Can holy objects be used?
OK
The sacred objects are burned with my son.
Will the effect be doubled?
confused
Look at that stove
too small
Our Wayne can't fit it in
You can chop him into pieces first
It's totally unnecessary
as far as I know
Second place
In the academy
To the son
Ordered one
The most expensive house
visible
Rich family fortune
Look at it like this in exchange for a holy object
The best strategy
so be it
So be it
Let me ask one more question
Please say
Was the academy responsible for the sacrifice?
No, no.
Such a big thing
It was created by a great sage
This person's name is unknown
But there is a nickname
Name
Beihe Xingjun
Then can we see with our own eyes
Go meet this North River Star Lord
Then it depends on fate
As long as two of you buy and exchange holy items
Sacrifice sincerely
There's always a chance
All your wishes come true
Thinking about Polaris
The news is coming
Do you think it’s Polaris?
A scam?
It has something to do with the disaster gods and demons.
But before I saw Polaris
It's hard to draw a conclusion
no trace to be found
Extremely skilled
What's wrong
Your father's letter
Co-authored now one by one
Did you jump out by yourself?
This is the academy
To the kitchen helper
temporary accommodation
Okay, Brother Wang.
You should go back quickly too
You should go back soon
Let's see you tomorrow
go to bed early
Brother Wang
This residence
Only you
Auntie doesn’t live in the academy
Since I'm afraid
Why don't you tell me
I am also a member of Qizhai
You have to bear it yourself
Lie down
I'll wait until you fall asleep before leaving
Can I fall asleep?
Why don't you sit down for a while?
I can chase away nightmares here
Sleep peacefully
The man recovered from his leg injury
Pretend to be a fool and cheat people out of money
But it's all green fire
means of playing tricks
From the bones of old graves
you can find out
If you give it a little heat, there will be green fire
Used to scare people
It won't hurt anyone at all.
Find it from the bones
Hard to find
but
There are other ways
any solution
never mind
Even if I tell you, you don’t want to know.
Tell me about it
Steaming human urine
You can also find this thing
this method
Who discovered it first?
Probably a doctor
Why
After all, it’s a medicine.
Urine can be used as medicine
It is recorded in medical books
It can cure many diseases.
Pain due to colic, fatigue, thirst, irritability
Both are useful
You know this
When I was a kid, I had to learn everything.
You have to know everything
Otherwise, I really wouldn’t be alive now
Then when will you
Take me to play too
Green fire
Then you have to start now
Just start collecting
All kinds of human urine
Let's get down to business.
What happened to your father's letter?
Let me see
I’ll meet you at Yuelu Mountain tomorrow
Not necessarily true
You'll know it when you see it
Okay, I'll go with you.
Need not
I'll go with Zhao Jian
Just you two
No need to use your hands
After all, it is still
Want to borrow his identity
Find an opportunity to get close to Yuan Hao
So there is no need to show up
Things tonight
Be sure to tell Wang Kuan and Xiao Jing
Also
Continue well tomorrow
Pretending to be a student
What time is it and we are still chatting?
There will be no class tomorrow
Can't chat anymore. Can't chat anymore.
Long nights and many dreams
Xiao Xue
Let's tell now
Wang Kuan and Xiao Jing
Let's go
They won't be here tomorrow
Just pretending to be sick
Have you figured out how to dress it up?
What kind of illness are you pretending to be?
I'm most afraid of this thing
Protect me, Xiao Xue
Why is it so dark?
Go fast
Go do your own thing
Want to learn to cook
I have someone I like
I want to make it for him to eat
yes
Wait a moment while I cut the meat
You help
Thank you, aunt
It was the same when I was young
Have someone you like
Just learned to cook
I want to make it for him to eat
So are you married?
It's done
have a daughter
bigger than you
That's great.
you live near here
Right, that village in the mountains
No wonder I go home every day
It's quite hard, right?
Gotta take care of the house
There is no work at home
Quite relaxing
It's my uncle who is taking care of the house.
Not really
Everyone in the family is dead
There is only one mother-in-law left
There's nothing to do
how come
Be in trouble
drought disease
When I came to the academy
passing a village
I saw someone worshiping the Dragon God
This is our village
I saw the faucet fell off
Was cut off
It turned out that when I worshiped God
Praying for rain to ward off disasters has been quite successful.
But this dragon's head was chopped off
The disaster cannot be controlled
Everyone in the village is gone
Who would do such a thing?
College students
What do college students do when they chop off the dragon's head?
heard about it
Is that the devil from Polaris?
Him
Bewitch students
Dedicated to destroying gods
caused this disaster
Why does Pollux do this?
He is a devil
born bad
You have to keep an eye out
In our academy
Too many students
They were all bewitched by him
You can't tell on the surface
You should pay more attention to yourself at ordinary times
It's time for Mr. Wei to go to class
where to
book boy
it's me
The young master is sick
Kill the chicken and make soup
Brother Wei, what's going on?
Si Jiu
Why is this so sick?
Are you going to attend a lecture?
Don't show off
Health is important
Stayed up late last night reading
Scared by bats
I still have a headache now
I'm so distraught that I don't want to live anymore.
What about your father and mother?
Go out for a walk
Wander around
You are so sick now
After all, they are not biological parents.
What a blessing
What did you say
I mean
Brother Wayne's ill-fated
Biological parents are no longer alive
If I get bitten by a bat again
Fortunately, I was just scared
Nothing serious
I feel bad
splitting headache
Si Jiu
I'm afraid I won't be able to read today
There is a doctor in the academy
How about I invite you?
Get a pulse for the young master
Need not
Have taken medicine
Don't take this medicine randomly.
My scholar boy is very knowledgeable in medical skills
Where can I find such a book boy?
Taught by my family since childhood
Brother Wayne really has a family background.
such a pity
I can't get up
Why do you want to get up?
I want to go to the lecture hall
I want to attend class
There is actually something in this world
Such a studious person
If you don’t study, you’d rather die.
What a pity
Really can't get up
Come
Let's take one side
Carry Brother Wei to the lecture hall
I'm afraid it's inappropriate.
After all, I'm still sick
Didn't you listen to your young master?
If you don’t study, you’d rather die.
So eager to learn
How can I live up to it?
Come on, let's carry it
this
how
I want to go
only
I'm a little heavy
Not afraid
I really want to go
But I'm really heavy
The two of us carry it
I'm weak
Can't help
I want to study
I'm afraid it's not possible now.
Okay, I'll carry you.
Come
help me
The scenery is pretty good
Nervous
A little bit
I know
After all, they are father and son
He never took me
Been a son
That's what he owes you
This is the head of the Yuan family
Yuantianguan of Chiyou Banner in those days
Shouldn't have met on the mountain
I’m too old to climb mountains.
I heard that you defected to Xixia
how
met father
Shouldn't I say hello first?
Just because you surrendered to Xixia
Almost hurt me
The head was chopped off
Not only are you not dead
Also came to Tanzhou
Came for you
Desperate
You have to find a way out by yourself
Want to rely on me
Save your life
Take her with you
No way
Engaged
Have to follow
good taste
Okay
There's no need to be modest
Anyway
It's always a good thing when father and son reunite
I won’t embarrass you either
you killed her
I believe you
how
Don't play the trick of pretending to be dead
Fool me
Change the conditions
Xixia people