This steamed cake cannot be baked
Too much smoke
There's something on Xiao Xue's mind
Isn't he practicing swordsmanship?
This guy every time
Practice swordsmanship when you are upset
Look at his face
Why don't you ask him what's going on?
Need not
Go and deliver food to Wang Kuan
I'll come over here
Xiao Xue
Stop practicing
Eat cake
Not hungry
What are you doing
I’ll be on my way after tomorrow
Prepare some mats
Spread it on the saddle for everyone
Otherwise it will hurt your legs
You can also do needlework
More or less
But you are a scholar
You can’t just read books either.
Isn’t it said that a gentleman is far away from the kitchen?
I didn’t say anything about the far needle and thread.
You should eat first
I'll sew for you for a while
good
you have eaten
What's wrong
this assassination
Be careful
I know
What Lu Nanshan said
You heard it all
You are not the only one who chose
But the entire Qizhai
Why Qizhai
Now there is no one available in the Secret Pavilion
Is there anything wrong with this?
He said he chose the entire Qizhai
But don't forget
Originally, the secret order only allowed Zhao Jian to
Come and see Brother Ning Ling
We came here by ourselves
yes
we show up
It's already considered a violation of the order
But Lu Nanshan didn’t mention a word
Just let us
Participating in the plan
So before he
We want Zhao Jian to hide it from us
for what
Inconsistency
It doesn't make sense
this way
Except our Qizhai
Don't believe anyone
What do you think
This little Luzhangyuan
What do you want to do?
I always feel
There is murderous intent in his eyes
To Qizhai
Maybe to someone
I just don't know who he is targeting.
Who is it?
Good knife skills
It’s hard to practice double swords
good
among these people
You are the best fighter
That's right
Xiao Xue is the best fighter
Mr. Xue
Just call me Xue Ying
Xue Ying
Do you want to practice your skills?
I did not mean
I have no other meaning
Just itchy hands
Draw your sword
thank you
We need to fight now
Good knife skills
gave in
Sorry
When I see a master, I want to learn from each other
Winning or losing comes second
It's fun to have a fight
clear
Let’s discuss it later when we have time.
good
Okay, female version of Xiao Xue
What
nothing
I'll just ask
What then?
Your father is the commander-in-chief of the Youzhou capital
yes
I heard that the ten commanders of the Xixia army commanded the army
Each leads an army
Guard one side
Each position has high weight
almost
Then you want to kill Yuan Hao
I just asked casually
It's okay if you don't answer
do you know
At the beginning of Daxia
In fact, they were twelve military commanders
Two more
Back then, two brothers from the Yeli clan
In charge of the Left Wing Supervision and Military Department
and the right wing supervising military department
Especially Yeli Yuqi
Command the right side of Chaoshun Supervisory Military Division
Conquests in the north and south
Make great achievements
Among the Xia people
He is known as the King of Heaven
Yuan Hao killed Yeli Yuqi brothers
From then on, the twelve captains led the army
Only these ten are left
The left wing army and the right wing army
Now he has become Yuan Hao's personal guard
So you want to kill Yuan Hao
It’s to protect the Yuzhou Military Supervisory Department
Not just for self-protection
A beggar
I was kind to my father
revenge
Helan Mountain is a holy mountain
Dead
Where to find peace
Rice Poultry
You feel
can i sit on it
one day
Your Highness will definitely become the Lord of Great Xia
His Highness Qingtianzi invites you to board the chariot
Father
How long has it been since we, father and son, have seen each other?
Return to Father
Fighting all year round
Unable to fulfill my filial piety in front of my father
Death penalty for son-in-law
Is it a capital crime?
Daxia Laws Do Not Count
Sons and ministers are calculating in their minds
Don't always keep everything in your heart
If you hide it, you will soon die.
Father
Sons and ministers are frightened
My father and son made a few jokes
What's there to be afraid of?
Get up, stop kneeling
Thank you father
Father
You have lost weight
You should be careful about your health
Thank you father for the wine
You didn’t die in the hands of the Song people
sons and ministers
Saved a life
You enter the Song Dynasty
No news for a while
It’s hard for Mi Qin Mu Bei
Just for this little military power
He was having a big fight with his dad
I heard everyone has arrived
It's a life-and-death situation.
In the world
How can there be a father and son who have seen life and death?
This time the Helan Mountain Festival
Who is leading the escort?
Liang Gewei, Supervisor of Youzhou Army
Him
Father
Do you want to change to a commander-in-chief?
No
Very good, let's choose him
Okay, it's okay. Come on.
yes
Father
On your carriage
We should also keep some personal guards
So many people want to kill me
You have to give them some chance
How many people are buried here?
Too many to count
Are there any rules for this worship?
Adult men cannot participate
There is no such rule
It’s not that I can’t participate
Most of them are dead
All the people who fought in the wars over the years were in the army.
Countless deaths
This battle
We no longer want to fight anymore
Yuan Hao should pay the price
The place of sacrifice is in front
Already making final preparations
There is a mountain patrol road here
Mid-levels
You can see the whole picture of the altar
Let's go up
I know what you're worried about
Gonho Festival
The guard must clear the mountain
So where to hide?
Only then can he go on stage to assassinate
Actually there is a way
Be a dead person
how do you know
This terrain, this scene
Is it difficult to guess?
You've guessed it
Brother Ning Ling’s plan
Otherwise you think
What is he doing standing there?
Although there are not many tombs around the altar,
But it's enough
what is that
That's the women's shed.
What shed?
put the body on top
Invaded by birds and animals
Three years later, the remaining bones will be
Take it off and burn it
then why
Other tombs don’t do this
A women's shed funeral in the mountains
Just for the battlefield
For the sacrificed soldiers
their lover
Will be dressed in costumes
Welcome back the corpses of the soldiers
After dying for love
He was buried on the women's shed.
What if
What to do if there are no bones?
Even broken armor will do
Relics are fine too
Those girls
That's it for the rest of my life
For Daxia
This is also an honor
This girl's shed is taller
Able to observe the situation
And being able to be condescending
It’s convenient to jump on the altar and assassinate Yuan Hao
It's a way
However, Brother Ning Ling’s method
There is another problem that cannot be solved
Escape
Do you know
Even if Yuan Hao was sacrificed alone
But his bodyguards
They will definitely be ambushed and guarded all around.
Even if we kill Yuan Hao
Can't escape from birth
It seems that Brother Ning Ling has no plans
Let you get out alive
maybe
He also wanted to kill us with his own hands
Revenge for Yuan Hao
I also thought of this
avenged
Only then can we justifiably
Taking over Xixia
In fact, you have a way to survive
The inside should be combined with the outside
The escort will be the breakthrough point
no
What are you doing?
You can guess it
Otherwise, I won’t say anything.
No, no, no, you should say something
I was just talking nonsense
You talk about your
You've all guessed it
That's right
I can arrange for two escorts
When the time comes, he will be assassinated on the stage.
The person pretending to be a guard came on stage first.
capture the assassin
Youzhou Military Supervision Department
Will ask the assassin to be interrogated
Then you can leave with me
Have a chance to escape
why help us
Brother Ning Ling
Maybe he is the next Yuan Hao
Must be prevented
interesting
Do you want to think about it?
Choose two people to pretend to be guards
Can
Don't hesitate
Xue Ying thinks you are trustworthy
real
who
I've checked all these weeks.
It will not affect the assassination at all
Xiao Luzhangyuan is obviously interested in
The circumstances of the assassination are extremely important
He even
Didn't go down the mountain with us
This guy comes to Helan Mountain
There are definitely other arrangements
Companions are not trustworthy
The future is unknown
But it is
Good opportunity to kill Yuan Hao
Do you think assassination is feasible?
Can
OK
Then continue
Yuan Hao is coming soon
The staff is divided into three groups and each group acts independently.
you say
Does this count for us?
Born in the same bed, died in the same grave
Yuan Zhongxin and I
Buried among the bones
Make the first wave of raids
No one is allowed to die
Yanei and Xue Ying went to the women's shed
Observe the big picture
If I and Yuan Zhongxin
Loss or stalemate
Xue Ying made a second wave of forced killings
excuse me
We'll leave in a while
Doesn't affect you two
live here
Wang Kuan and Xiao Jing pretend to be guards
After the assassination was successful
Your first time
Come up and catch everyone
Then in the name of interrogation
Get off the mountain trail
Everyone
Peace of war in the future
That's what happened
Yuan Hao is here
He is Yuan Hao
Xiao Xue
you say
Will we make it out alive today?
Don't say depressing words
If there is an accident
You must fight your way out
Don't even think about turning around to save me
good
no
You don't have to
You agree so quickly?
Really
It’s hard to be cool
No one praises me
Yanei is so handsome
Xiao Xue
Did you hear that
No, this is in broad daylight
Xiao Xue
are you afraid of ghosts
in broad daylight
Not so much
It’s not that big of a deal after we’ve already spoken.
Yuan Hao hasn’t gone to the altar yet
There's still time
You're really not afraid
cut
I'm afraid so I cut it
I have finally waited for this day
Don't cut it, it's me
He spoke again, cut it quickly
It's broken, it's broken
Xue Ying
Long time no see in Yameni
Aren't you that Chu Niao from Bazhai?
it's me
Why did you die here?
I'm not pretending
There's still someone here from Yashira
Yes, I have
That's a real corpse
I remember when you were in Bashai
Disappeared suddenly
Got the mission
what task
Yuan Hao
Kill him
Then we can join forces
Not today
Why
Can't be killed
There is no one who cannot be killed
Animism
Return to Helan
Holy Light Blessing
Destiny
May the sleeping ones and the living ones live forever
All are protected by all gods
The great blessing of the Xia Dynasty is eternal
Just him
good chance
Don't do anything
Former Kota Strong
If you continue like this, you will die.
That's too late
Zhao Jian and Yuan Zhongxin are going to have sex
Why these people
No one went to rescue.
confident enough
too strong
I am coming too
Just wait till I go
I have to go up
You answer
It seems I can't hold it anymore
If you jump down, you will fall to your death
Even if you die, you will die together
Something's wrong
Yuan Hao did not kill him
Yuan Zhongxin
Your brother is much better than you
The Battle of Qichuan Village
The Song people suffered all casualties
The only thing left is your brother’s life
Do you think it's a coincidence?
what are they talking about
Yuan Zhongxin and the others have wrong expressions
What's wrong
Where are Wang Kuan and the others?
The ambush went well
Is Yuan Hao dead?
Why are it just the two of you?
Where are Yuan Zhongxin and the others?
These are your Yuzhou army
yes
Answer your questions
So you don't know anything
what do you know
The winner at the altar remains undecided
These people will take us
Sent here
How can it be
what happened
This is protecting them
Xiaolu Zhangyuan
this is your order
Among the seven fasts
Only you can't get into trouble.
Wang Kuan
etc.
How could I, the Youzhou Army, be dispatched by you?
That's thanks to your father
My dad
My father is cooperating with you this time
Isn’t it to kill Yuan Hao?
What's the matter
to eliminate enemies
We must first quell internal troubles
This is a trap to harm Qizhai
No
It's a test
What is the test?
you guess
Will Yuan Hao kill them?
What did you mean by what you just said?
Your Highness
Do you think Yuan Hao won’t kill them?
Why
You should understand what I mean
Do you think that among the seven fasts
Some people surrender to Xixia
But at least for you
I trust
There won't be such a person in Qizhai
Don't trust others casually
Yes
So I don't believe you
It does not matter
Better guess
Why did I let them protect you?
because of my father
clever
talk to you
Peace of mind
Father
Do you know these three assassins?
do not know
I can rest assured that
Take the three of them down.
Where to take
Please help me ask
Who is the instigator behind them?
yes
Why is it Brother Ning Ling?
Take them away
Why didn't Wang Kuan show up?
What to do now
Not urgent
Look at the three of them
It's okay for now
So you can't go down
Who will save them if you go down?
Makes sense
That
Can you help me save someone?
Wait in the office
There's someone else who didn't show up
Who?
Don't panic
Is that a crane?
What a monster?
It looks like something carved on the rock wall.
Gods
Sheep Guardian
The great blessing of the Xia Dynasty is eternal
God comes to earth
Is he really his destiny?
What
Sheep guarding
god
Walking like a herd of cranes
Sheep head human body
It is a symbol of the sheep god
The Shepherd God
Freeze said
This is the true god
Genkou Sougen Summer Characters
Fupinghou Yeli Renrong
Made into twelve volumes of the national book
Named Wenhai
The sheep-keeper god is clearly recorded
Although Daxia respected Buddhism
You can also believe in other gods
Where can there be gods in this world?
You all saw it just now
seen it myself
Not necessarily true
Your Highness
You mean this goat-keeper?
Could it be fake?
Who dares to pretend to be a god
My dad
The gods appear during sacrifices
His title of Qingtianzi
Isn’t that justifiable?
you mean
Qing Tianzi arranged everything
You walk slower
Yanei, are you afraid of the dark?
I am afraid of ghosts
It's okay, I'll protect you
Why are you so kind?
She is only kind to you
Who?