The Song Dynasty has been unfavorable in foreign wars in recent years
After all
This is the result of civilians taking charge of the army.
You say
Should this situation be changed?
Did you kill Liu Sheng?
If there is a chance to save the Song Dynasty from danger,
what are you willing to pay
you admitted it
i am willing to give everything
What do you plan to do with him?
You mean Lu Nanshan?
in his plan
Your life or death is not important
so
You want us to kill him
I'm afraid of him
Afraid of Lu Nanshan
Afraid of him killing someone
not just this
This person
Always looks calm
But in his heart
There is a flame that cannot be hidden
Once he has a goal
Even if everything is destroyed
I won't hesitate
Even if it's himself
do you understand
Of course I'm afraid of him
Everyone is afraid of crazy people
Then you still follow him?
His Orders
I dare not violate
Even every time with him
while talking
Have to think twice
God knows when
he will feel you
blocked his steps
As long as you are not careful
Maybe he will die
That's better than Lu Zhangyuan back then.
Even more extreme
Can't compare
Lu Guannian knew that he
standing in darkness
fight for light
And he thinks he is the light
You kill your compatriots
He also said that he was the rescuer
The Song Dynasty was in danger
Only when war breaks out can we save the Song Dynasty
The Song Dynasty was unfavorable in foreign wars
More battles are lost than won
The more you fight, the more you lose
Only officials will gradually understand
It is wrong to let civilians control the army
If you lose too much, it will hurt.
Only then can we have the opportunity to change the old system
How many people will die
It's worth it to kill someone
Then why don't you die?
if necessary
I can die too
But not now
Others can do it now
You all don't understand
Now is the best time
After the Liao-Xia War
Liao has been in decline
Although Yuan Hao from Xixia is brave,
But after all, the country is weak
How many more games will you lose at this time?
Will not shake the overall situation
Lose a few games
Change the old system
Haven't we lost enough?
Dead people
Anyway, the Song Dynasty has a vast territory
There are always enough people
Let them die a worthy death
Is it not good
Liao is in decline
Xixia's national power was weak
In this situation
Are they willing to fight?
You are wishful thinking
Planning here
All we get in return is a loss of life.
warmongers
There is always
Yuan Hao is warlike
So you don’t want to kill Yuan Hao at all
As early as in Helan Mountain
You concealed Yuan Hao’s combat power
Prevent the Yuzhou Army from rescuing
Birds are not exhausted, bows are not hidden
Let me ask you another question
why do you think that
Kill Yuantian Pass
Inconvenient to say
Let Yuan Zhongxin ask me
Why Yuan Zhongxin
I know
You have a lot to ask
but i can't hear
It doesn't matter
I'll try to answer first
You came to Tanzhou
Have you seen these disasters?
So are these things real?
of course not
In this world there is no
Diseases of the world
What is the disease in the world?
Godless Demon
Since there are no gods and demons
Why slay demons?
Yuan Zhongxin
You know I'm Da Song
How to deal with world disasters?
sue for disaster
It doesn't matter if you don't know
I tell you
In the Song Dynasty, we implemented the system of suing for disasters
Each state
If there are disaster victims reporting the disaster
Affected people reported the disaster to the government
The county official verified the disaster situation and reported it to the state official
Report to the court after re-examination
To determine relief strategies
I won’t go into details about these.
You probably don’t like to hear it either
Do I like to hear it?
You said it very carefully too.
these past few years
Jinghu South Road suffers from drought and floods
But the victims who reported the disaster
but
Far less than the number of people affected by the disaster
Why
Because they believe this
Real Buddhist temple
Whenever disaster strikes
Money and food will always be distributed
Compensate the people
And the people behind these disasters
But let the people think
The disaster is caused by strange things
It's God's punishment
It's a punishment from gods and demons
Disaster victims apologize to clay statues
But unwilling to report the disaster
think
This is God's will
Can't disobey
so
I'm going to set up a puzzle
looking for me
Like-minded students
what we have to do
Just to let the world understand
Disasters are natural disasters, not man-made disasters
Let the world no longer be afraid of clay statues
Only follow the law and human feelings
This is slaying demons
Many people are loyal to their country
Some are on the battlefield
Some in the court
They do big things
and I
I can only do this little thing
Let there be no superstition in the world
Let people in the world encounter disasters
can be rescued
Can trust the court
This is no small matter
There are so many disaster legends
Fight these superstitions
It's really difficult
We study disasters
Again in a disaster place
Destroy the so-called idols
Tell the people
These are all fake
And after that
I became the target of public criticism
Various families under the rule of Xiangning County
Using superstitious sacrifices as a way to make money
Let the villagers believe in gods and demons
Make money by taking advantage of disaster
The man from the academy, He County Cheng
share their interests
No wonder the government wants to arrest you
Natural disasters hurt people
People suffer
But was defrauded of money by scammers
deceive superiors and deceive inferiors
extortionate taxes
And the government and those liars
But he gets fat by sucking blood
This doesn't change
How should people live?
So you exorcise the demon
moved their interests
Yuan Zhongxin
You came to Tanzhou
I am very happy
Because I also want to see you
Why
because i'm sick
I'm old
I have to follow these
Read what is written
because every year
My memory is fading
Don’t write down a lot of things
I can't remember
I want to see you
Because I know I'm dying
But I am not afraid of death or aging
Not afraid of being caught by them
But I'm afraid of
Things that persist until now
die from then on
Nothing more
Yuan Zhongxin
i see you
it's actually really easy
I hope you inherit my mantle
become this world
New Demon Slayer
Yuan Zhongxin
where have you been
No matter how we look for you, we can't find you
Who rescued you?
Brother Yuan
Does it matter if you are injured?
I'm back
besides
Pollux wants to see you
Exorcism has been in business for many years now
Working hard but achieving little results
Destroyed idols
They will rebuild
It often takes several years to pull
Falling short of success
Count every ten villages
The one who can finally get rid of inner demons
Maybe just one or two
But these two villages
If there is another natural disaster
There is a possibility of survival
With hope of continuation for future generations
Therefore
Even if decades are wasted
Old heart and disabled body
In the end, only one person was saved
Still worth it
But from the hearts of the world
Get rid of fear and ignorance
This is better than killing to save others
It's a hundred times harder
Exorcist
So bold
struggle in this
Maybe it’s harder than fighting on the battlefield
Fighting with gods and demons, fighting with people
It's quite magnificent
Use it for a lifetime
To complete a
almost impossible
I'm a little excited when I think about it.
But if there is no one
If the gods and demons are credible
Facing the vastness of the world
Will you be afraid?
Maybe
But it's okay
Why
I believe you
Xinyanei
Everyone who believes in Qizhai
I believe in Brother Wang more
You are here
I won't worry and be afraid
Instead of believing in mud and stone statues
It is better to trust people of the same faith
Someone you can trust
You can let go of God
Xiao Lu Zhangyuan meets again
I heard you have some problems
Just want to talk to me
let her out
Is this necessary?
No problem, I'll go out
You guys chat
If you need anything, come to me anytime
I was out
OK
In fact, it doesn’t matter if you follow me
say something
I'll tell her when I turn around
So you let her out
In fact, it’s unnecessary
That day in jail
Watching you two become united forever
I'm really touched
Then you can just give me a gift
That's why I let her out
Just to protect you
What's the meaning
Zhao Jian asked me just now
Why kill Yuan Tianguan?
The answer is simple
My father organized spies back then
Yuan Tianguan and I
Have cooperated many times
At that time
We can talk to your dad quite well.
Birds of a feather
So much so that we recently
There is also cooperation
So what he knew
Too much
Once something is leaked out
You and I
All will be doomed
What does it have to do with me
I don't want Yuan Hao to die
because he will become
The Whetstone of the Song Dynasty
so what
So when I see
You cooperate with Brother Ning Ling
I don't think so
Secretly protecting Yuan Hao
People don't know yet
Very touching
I would rather Lingge cooperate with you
It means the official
I can't stop it
so what
I can only invite your dad
Do some tricks for me
Do some tricks
Figured it out
You don’t want Brother Ning Ling
Cooperate with us
You let Yuan Tianguan obstruct it
Go on
explain
How did Prince Zhao die?
if
Zhao Jian knows
His father's death was caused by your father
You little couple
how to face each other
You let Yuan Tian pass
Attack Prince Zhao
I can help you hide it from her
you can continue
happy life
The premise is to let me go
Just let me go
Let me go
Release
You also have to worship this thing
Yuan Zhongxin is like this
disappeared
gentlemen
This is the power of the gods
He was rescued.
How can there be gods and demons in this world?
impossible
If there were no gods
How could so many people believe it?
gentlemen
There is a letter
Dead Ghost Uncle
You are Beihexing
Then you sell your own puzzles
He also charged ten cents
Is this transaction okay?
People can't hear
I'll also figure out a mystery inside the office later.
Make a vote for yourself
Finally met
Everyone, Qizhai
Hello Zhao Jian
Those who can be these people
what's up
Even the eyes don't work
Wei Yuan, your father is still alive
Isn't this nonsense?
Your father is now
Already joined Yuan Hao's army
Car and gun strategy
in the end
Just taking the opportunity to take away your father's authority
Confiscation of property
Your Majesty returns to Xixia
But you insist on killing Yuan Hao
How ridiculous it seems
You know that
Did he submit to Xixia?
I'll find out the answer myself
do you want to see him
what does it mean
I can give you this chance
You have good intentions
Don't care about money
It’s about the right value for money
I'll lend you a caravan
It can reserve funds for the business of eliminating demons
I see you don’t say much usually
Do things at critical times
Quite decisive
Want to get rid of Lu Nanshan
This is the only chance
We won't kill him
Even if he harmed Liu Sheng
secretly start a war
We can't use lynching either
Everything should be punished by national law
OK, I understand
we will protect you
Prevent Lu Nanshan from taking revenge
thank you
Finished chatting
What's wrong
What did you say?
I'll go into the house and watch you chat.
Dean
drink water
How could your Pei family survive to this day?
It's all my help
This is how you repay me
Xiaolu Zhangyuan
Let me just ask
Qizhai
Did you use it
The chess piece that killed Yuantianguan
Shouldn’t Yuantianguan be killed?
Actually, I don’t care who you kill.
After all, my sister is too
A member of Qizhai
Again
Our Pei family owes her enough.
What I want to kill is Yuantian Pass
Not Qizhai
After the death of Yuan Tianguan
Will Qizhai still be there?
They know a lot
That
It's really to protect your sister.
connected by blood
Pei Xuan
Ask yourself well
Is it a sister-brother relationship?
Or make excuses to protect yourself?
No conflict
All a little bit
The wound is not healed yet
Just stop moving
Look at the wound on your back
All cracked
Don't be too entangled
What Lu Nanshan told you
If you don't want to say it, don't say it
You can solve it yourself too
I trust you
He asked Yuan Tianguan to attack your father
My dad
Didn't he die of a sudden illness?
Dean
If you are thirsty and hungry
Just tell me
The president is a man who does great things.
You still have to love your body
This clothes is dirty
Let me dust you off
How did my father die?
Yuan Zhongxin
I thought you were a smart person
Wang Kuan will not lie
You don't have this problem
You can make up any reason
Wouldn't it be over if you lied to her?
If I were
Lying about this kind of thing
I'm ruined as a person
What are you asking for?
How did my father die?
Me and your dad
no grudge
But Yuan Hao cannot die
If there is no war
Our Song Dynasty has no chance to change the old system
He's been lying to us all this time
I just thought about it
My dad's business
Maybe it's just his family's opinion.
Not necessarily credible
Yuantian Pass is located in Yuelu Mountain
We can ask him face to face
Zhao Jian
If you ask him face to face now
He will definitely kill you
we can cooperate
We are at Yuelu Mountain
Kill Yuan Tianguan
Your surname is also Zhao
Also of royal blood
Kill the national traitors for our great Song Dynasty
Why do you want to kill him so much?
My cooperation with Yuan Tianguan
If it is spread
My future in the Privy Council
That's it
But I can't finish
I have to keep living
I have to keep walking
Because that's the only way
Only then can I have more opportunities
Save the Song Dynasty from danger
You've ended up in this situation
Still want me to help you
Zhao Jian is not helping me
It’s to help Da Song
Decisions should be made in order to achieve great things
Really disgusting
Zhao Jian
This is righteousness
What a big fool you are
I don’t need you to give me a chance
I will go to Xixia by myself
So you refused
Not really.
I can agree to take charge of the caravan.
Because of what Polaris did
A bit admirable
Then say you agree
That's not the case.
What do you want?
Do you agree or not in the end?
It depends on other people's decisions
Our Qizhai
Always inseparable from life to death
Xue Ying
You are the most powerful among Qizhai
But it's not enough
I will find you a good teacher
Take you to the next level
This teacher is me
I will teach you these three years
Why should he read the letter?
Can't you just say no?
he
Can't remember
I'll ask him now
Find the Northern Star
Deal with Yuantianguan
If you really take action
You and I are not enough
I can't fight.
Didn't let you fight
Watch him for us
This is no problem
Do they just believe you?
these days
Who can trust whom?
Pei Xuan
As long as you let me go now
I, Lu Nanshan, swear to God
You will definitely know how to do it in officialdom
rise to prominence
Your Pei family
He will surely make great progress
This thing of oath
I don't believe you
Then what do you believe?
Of course I believe you
Dean
You and I have been together long enough
your temperament
I know all
I betrayed you
You will definitely kill me
I
I can change
Hard to change nature
What is this for?
Let him eat something when he is tired
I'll finish reading it for him.
Next is to write to
Wang Kuan and Pei Jing's
The meaning is very simple
I won’t recite it accordingly.
Pollux is sorry
Wang Kuan Pei Jing
Because you never grow up
What does it mean not to grow up?
Those who enter the secret pavilion must protect the Song Dynasty
we have always been
That's what you did
Then you know
What does sacrifice mean?
Sacrificial animals
The word "sacrifice" has been around since Zhou Dynasty
What about this moment?
Want to kill the cow
have you ever thought about
offer yourself as a sacrifice
In exchange for the peace of the Song Dynasty
human sacrifice
yes
This offering is a trade-off
Are you willing to serve the Song Dynasty?
What to give up?
He deafened his ears
Give up fine clothes and food
Just to get rid of demons
This is what it means
We go deep into Xixia
Assassination of Yuan Hao
A narrow escape
Wang Kuan has a bright future
He let go
This is not called giving up
What is abandonment
what is this called
This is called willfulness
he was thinking
Can follow Qizhai
With Pei Jing
Give up everything and never look back
This is to satisfy oneself
brotherhood
Children's affair
Wang Kuan
You gave up your future
With Pei Jing
Have you ever felt wronged?
Never
What is this called giving up?
baffling
if not
Must be separated
Why do you feel so wronged?
The famous Wang family
He could have skyrocketed
But he gave up
Why should he give up?
The Song Dynasty was in turmoil
People's suffering
He could have used the power of the Wang family
Become a marquis and a prime minister
If there is such a day
He can do it for the world
How much to do
Wang Kuan
So you have to give up Pei Jing
Return to Kaifeng
Admit your mistake to your father
according to his wishes
Marry a well-matched person
A woman I have never met
as wife
Depressed ever since
Unable to love
You have to give up your love
To find the way to become an official
You have to live for the world
This is the trade-off
As for
Pei Jing
Have you ever thought about leaving Wang Kuan?
Can you do anything for Da Song?
what is your value
Me and everyone
Too far apart
Then do you feel at ease?
enough
Don't get me wrong
This is the meaning of Polaris
I just convey
He wants us to work for him
This is inheritance
Also a transaction
What to trade
Aren’t you going to kill Yuan Hao?
That's how he helped us
this
is the condition
There were spies back then
Sneak into Xixia in batches at different times
This roster does exist
In the hands of Pollux
Three years later, the task is completed
He gave us the booklet
Lurking in enemy country
Keep a roster
Doesn't it leave a clue?
The so-called spy's life or death is uncertain
Those unilateral
people to contact them
Maybe it's also possible to die violently
Afraid of the Song Dynasty
forget these people
yes
if if not
If this roster
It is estimated that there are many hidden identities
no more chance
See the light of day again
Not a handle but a concern
As long as this booklet remains
Whether you live or die, you can go home
Pollux incognito
Hidden among the people
maybe just for
protect this roster
Roster to us
That is to say
Three years of hard work
There is a chance to make a comeback in Xixia
Do you need to make a decision now?
You can think about it slowly
I've thought about coming to him at any time.
Is it over?
gentlemen
You say
Could it be that this stone pillar has a spiritual effect?
What else do you believe besides these?
Thank you, Mr. Xinyuan.
What's wrong
somebody is coming
Everyone fled
And delivered it to your door yourself
Prince Zhao
It was you who killed
What Lu Nanshan said
There is such a thing
Want to know if I killed him?
Can
Promise me a condition
Find the Northern Star
henceforth
Don’t appear in Xixia territory again
Why
Killing Yuan Hao is my business alone
Don't need anyone to mess with it
OK
I promise you
Now
give me answer
Did you kill Prince Zhao?
You have no intention of keeping your promise
impossible
I'm not that kind of person at all
Change the conditions
fight with me
No matter win or lose
I gave her all the answers
OK
He is injured
I come
You are not qualified to negotiate terms
Others take action
You'll never get the answer
fine
let me
Yuan family
Those who are qualified to fight with me
Only your elder brother
You can't compare to him
You will never be as good as your big brother
know why i
Have you never regarded you as my son?
I go
If you can choose
I would rather you die
Leave your brother
But in the end, you were the one who forced brother to death
It was Brother Ning Ling who killed him
It's you
It's Brother Ning Ling
Why does brother want to die?
That's because he knows
own biological father
Joining the Western Xia
Loyalty and filial piety are difficult to achieve
He has no way to go
He died because of you
How could any father do this?
enough
The match is over
No more fighting. No more fighting.
do not fight
we gave in
I lost
The match is over
give her answer
you alone
come in with me
go
Chief
I'll go alone