alright
The new armor suits you well
My dad said
If the new armor has no blood
Finally less angry
Do you, the Youzhou Army, abide by the Goat God?
How much confidence
Na Yuanhao's response to the divine envoy
unfavorable rumors
It has been passed down long ago
The soldiers were talking a lot
To Yuan Hao
Quite a bit respectful
The soldiers are stable
Only the uncles are left.
Let's go
It’s a condolence
Why don't we see the Shaodu Commandery Army?
Matters of Life and Death
How can we neglect
Uncles, you have been waiting for a long time.
Nonsense
you are a close relative
How can you come here wearing armor?
This armor
My father prepared it for me
The Liang family has no male offspring
He had already thought about it
Let me take over the Yuzhou Army
Do the funeral first
Military affairs
Let’s talk later
I'm afraid to talk slowly
The Youzhou Army no longer has the surname Liang.
after i come back
All uncles present
They are all mobilizing their troops and horses.
Never took it again
Commander-in-Chief of the Supervisory Army
how
Everyone wants to sit in this seat
Shaodu unified the army
you are junior
Not familiar with military affairs
Everyone here
But they are all your elders
You should also buy more
Who is behind you?
Shaodu unified the army
Before this question
You have to think about the consequences
I really don't understand
Invite all uncles today
Come to the mourning hall
You guys really dare to come
This mourning hall is so big
Your soldiers and horses
Can you squeeze in?
How can anyone show their filial piety without wearing armor?
Shaodu unified the army
I was wrong
I asked just now
Who is behind you?
It seems that no one present answered.
Someone in Xingqing Mansion spread the news
If there is a change in the Youzhou Army,
We can gather military power in a moment
Shaodu unified the army
I know I was wrong
Yuanhao taught
Yuan Hao is not
Not Yuanhao
It’s Prince Ning Lingge
Have been communicating secretly
Brother Ning Ling
Good plan
If no accident
The Liang Family will help Brother Ning Ling get rid of Yuan Hao
Once an accident occurs
The Youzhou Army will also fall into
In Brother Ning Ling’s hands
This father and son are really shady.
More calculations
The Youzhou Army still has the surname Liang
See Dutongjun
What do you want to do next?
I just said it
I want to be angry for God
fake miracles
Don't hide it from uncle
I can say this is
Easy to use
Already have three years of experience
You can do it alone
You can't do it alone
So I want to ask my uncle
Do you have any
trustworthy person
No
Go find someone else
But I’m not familiar with this place.
Who am I looking for?
uncle
meet again
Need someone to find me
nice to see you again
News about the Helan Mountain Incident
After spreading
Your father sent me
Keep an eye on Wei Zhuoran's side
He said you just need to come to Xingqing Mansion
I will definitely find Wei Zhuoran
what is this called
Magical plan
Yuantianguan is also there
Your Majesty doesn't want to see you
He said you are a fool
I've warned you so
How dare you come to Xixia to die?
no way
You are now Mr.’s only bloodline
Before his efforts come to nothing
I still want to protect your life
No matter how hard you try, what will be the result?
The husband bought several concubines
Mr.’s original words
As long as I have another son
Love and immortality
Does this sound right to you?
I think sir did the right thing
Think about it
gentlemen
A man of great martial arts and a scholar of heaven
Extremely intelligent
How many lives will this last?
Otherwise what a pity
It's a pity it's not done yet
I think
You are quite suitable to be his son
Separate Separate
How can I match it?
It’s better if you can’t give birth
what are they doing
Watching the moon
It’s all Mr. Yuan’s past three years.
Under Xixia Shou's command
Look at those bald ones
They're all ruthless.
The bald the stronger
Mr. Yuan's meaning
Just don't show up
Something is really going to happen
It's not easy for them to catch you here either.
You have to live safely
Yuan Tianguan said
Protect his bloodline, right?
That's what it means
What do you need
You tell me
Just one word for murder and arson
No, no, no
No need to kill and set fire
Can you commit petty theft?
No problem
Can you carve stones?
But there is no difficult task
Will there be any Kongming lanterns?
i can teach them
But here in Xixia
Kongming lanterns are not common
But you can do
How big can it be
How big do you want
Take a look
Wood carving Wood carving
The goat-keeper flew away
more than
I heard that Xingqing Mansion
Big and small
Dozens of goat-keeping statues
disappeared overnight
Where is the thing I asked you to steal?
All smashed
Buried in Shibuyuan
Then this is
The gods walked away
There are still people in the river
Several stone tablets were uncovered
It is written on the stone tablet
Yuan Hao's blasphemy
Said it was the wrath of the gods
One set after another
The stone tablet is carved
It will be unearthed today
Now Xingqing Mansion is punishing God
Fear is growing
You shouldn't stay in the palace
You should go back quickly
Now is the time when people's hearts are wandering
This is also a perfect opportunity for you
What was the reaction from the father's side?
daily drinking
No action
What on earth is he waiting for?
The stone tablets on the river
What text was written?
It is the Daxia Wen founded by Qing Tianzi
What about the content?
It's all street talk
I dare not repeat it
Since the founding of Daxia Wen
Less than ten years
How old is that stone tablet?
Said to be an ancient stone tablet
yes
Where did the Daxia literature come from in ancient times?
Your Majesty, this is a flaw
This can be used
Refute the theory of gods
Can't refute
This is obviously unreasonable
Why can't I refute it?
I feel it too
Should not use Tangut
It doesn't make sense.
There is no need to speak common sense in front of gods
Why did Xixia script exist in ancient times?
Because of the gaze of the Goat God
Beyond the Past and Present
It is enough to illustrate the divine power
no trace to follow
Even gods can’t curse.
How about you stipulate
What should the gods say?
I dare not
Rebuke mortals with the tone of God
Do mortals have any reason to say?
That opponent
You have to be invincible
Miracles are all man-made
The key is people
But
Can't find who fabricated it
And these miracles
appear more frequently
People’s hearts are getting more and more frightened.
so many miracles
One or two people can't create it
right
Inside Xingqing Mansion
Someone must be secretly supporting
Yuan Zhongxin
tell me the truth
Over there at Sibu Garden
Is there someone like you too?
It’s my first time to come to Xingqingfu
How come there are acquaintances?
That's wrong
Shibuyuan has also been secretly and openly
Rumors driving the wrath of the gods
It's normal
no no
Look
It was previously preached that the goat-keeper god
Shibuyuan has been obstructing it
Why is it reversed now?
Helping spread the miracles
Once upon a time there was a sheep guardian angel
This benefit is not available
On top of Shibu Garden
benefit
There is a god now
No miracles
You can all take it on your own head
The status of Nashibo Garden
Naturally, a rising tide lifts all boats
There are many benefits
It’s the gods who say this.
In the end, it all became a benefit
Where is the god?
It's all human heart
There is no match for this
How to deal with it?
I keep him till now
Just for this moment
he
How long has it been since I left the palace?
No more banquets
Banquet outside the palace
Yuan Hao's order
Important ministers transferred from Xingqing Mansion
Shared Feast
this feast
It's the best time to poison
Is the medicine ready?
Poisonous and fatal upon entry
good
Very poisonous
Yuan Hao has extremely high martial arts skills
Extremely poisonous so there won’t be any accidents
Where is your brother named Wang?
What is there to see in the Imperial Palace?
You are not afraid of being discovered
Never been fresh
rest assured
I won’t run away if I’m here.
Then prepare first
The banquet has only been held for a few days.
I'm looking for a chance
Take you first
Walk around the hall
To avoid accidents
Why do I feel
The prime minister’s intention to kill Yuan Hao
More eager than us
It’s urgent to be kind to others
move
Then let's do this first
You guys are waiting for my news
Prime Minister
Yuan Hao came from Xingqing Mansion
Who are you calling?
Sixteenth Division Chief
Most of them have high authority
correct
There is also a Song Dynasty person
you know
Yuan Hao summons you to leave the palace
Rumors of divine punishment circulate endlessly
Yuan Hao always has to find a way to deal with it
Uncle, when you surrendered to Xixia
What position did Yuanhao give you?
He served as the director of the Mokansi
Mokansi
The Song Dynasty also had a Mokansi
Same here
In charge of the transfer of examinations for officials in various places
Account verification duties
Very important
Just a job
I am from Song Dynasty
Where can I find out?
Performance examination course for Daxia officials
Just getting paid and doing nothing
Yuan Hao often looks for me
Asked about the Forbidden Army of the Song Dynasty
Various matters
Another thing is
Famous generals of the Song Dynasty
What are their personalities and hobbies?
Sure enough, he was trying to find out the truth about the Song Dynasty.
That's what I mean
But this is wrong
uncle your position
It has nothing to do with the rumors of divine punishment
Why did Yuan Hao
Are you summoned to leave the palace?
Who knows?
I'll go with you
can not go
Too dangerous
You are Mr. Yuan’s only bloodline
Can't take risks
Yanei and Zhao Jian
They all lost their traces in Helan Mountain
Maybe in the palace
There is an answer
Their last name is not Yuan
It has nothing to do with me whether I die or not.
You don't have to go
Yuan Zhongxin
Zhao Jian and the others are absolutely safe
how do you know
Pei Jing is not
Are you with them?
what do you want to say in the end
I told you, don’t believe it
Pei Jing
It's possessed by the dragon god
You still don’t believe it
The Dragon God also said he would grant me eternal life.
You saw me with your own eyes
Performed so many miracles
Saw what happened?
fine
I mean
If Xiao Jing is really
If the dragon god is possessed
You should go more
Why?
You seem pious
Maybe I'll grant you eternal life?
That makes sense.
How long has he been like this?
Yuan Hao held a banquet in the palace
We also invited various supervisory and military departments to
Will anyone go?
no one will go
theory of divine punishment
It has spread to all the military supervisory departments
These soldiers killed a lot of people
More and more afraid of ghosts and gods
not to mention
Everyone is talking about my father's death
It was also Yuan Hao who seized military power.
One step conspiracy
Now the commander in chief
I am somewhat suspicious of Yuan Hao
Chilling
See the truth about Yuan Hao
Youzhou Army has no second thoughts
Next
Just looking for opportunities
In various military supervision departments
Just look for allies
You want to leave
Banquet outside the palace
I have to see
Danger
My companion
Missing
Then I
You can't go with
Youzhou Army cannot do without you
still coming back
if alive
I'll come to you again to compete with swords
I can't beat you
I give you a hand
left hand right hand
The right hand cannot be given
Then I still can’t win
Youzhou pigeon
Mountains and water
two inseparable
If there is news
You can leave it to it to bring the letter back
good
Then you and your companions should remember
In Daxia
You will never be at the end of your rope
Because of the Youzhou Army
It will always be your retreat
I've thought about it
I give you your right hand
Yuan Zhongxin
You said the Dragon God is in Xixia
Will you get used to it?
Will it be acclimatized?
Will the gods adapt to the climate?
I think this problem
You'd better go and ask yourself
I'm still a little nervous
It's okay, don't be nervous
gentlemen
I have to tell Mr. Yuan about this.
My hands and feet are all healed
If you want to stop me next time
It is better to go directly
It's easier to cut it off
Do you think I dare not?
If you dare, come, come, come
gentlemen
Everyone is in Xixia
It's not necessary. I can't do it.
do not talk
Can't stop people from dying
I heard you were in Xingqing Mansion
Found a concubine
Then I really wish you
It is a blessing to have children early and have many children.
I asked people to inquire
The whereabouts of Zhao Jian and others were not found.
You have been in Xingqing Mansion for so many days
Never mentioned this either
Not worried about their safety
I believe they are safe and sound
why to believe
If I don't believe it
I can't hold on at all
idiot
Only yourself is the most important in this world
understand this
to live longer
Not affected by foreign objects
You don't know
what do i want to do
Just make sure you live
Do you know what the meaning is?
I really thought
You will cripple me again this time
You won't go if you're disabled
You have to climb
So say it
Can't stop people from dying
Since you know I'm going to die
Then why are you following me?
Follow along and take a look
If I could save you
if not
Collect the body for you
Mr. Dragon God is also here
what
The Dragon God may be in the palace
When the time comes, I will help you make a wish together
Guarantee you more births
A few fat boys
Don't worry
What is this all about?
Yu Chiyuan is a dragon and a phoenix among men.
Can you take him under your wing?
It’s true that the ancestors of the Yuan family have accumulated virtues.
Too much praise
gentlemen
Officials from various departments are on their way
The place for banquet is right here
Look
That’s where Yuan Hao’s main seat is
Isn't it poisoning?
Let’s take a look at the banquet seats
Any functions
Although there are many people and chaos
You can't do it in the kitchen, either.
I still have to be wary of this.
Don't poison the kitchen
Then how to play
Arrive before the banquet
Poisoning in front of Yuan Hao
Of course not.
The kitchen is not good
Even banquets are not allowed
Then only
On the way to the palace
Make an article
Your little brother named Wang
Why not?
Today we're talking about something important.
coming
what's coming
Where can I pick him up?
This side corridor is locked
how did you get in
Don't make fun of me
There is a cliff outside
how did you get in
What should I do if someone finds out?
Not joking
Didn’t the Prime Minister say that just now?
The journey of bringing dishes to the palace
There is a chance to poison
yes
By the time
Miss Pei can pretend to be a maid
Poisoning outside the palace gate
No
Yuanhao's Meals
Escorted here alone from the apse
Poisoned by the queen
No, no, no
Heavily guarded all the way
There are armored guards again
That means there's nothing we can do
No, no, no
Sneak into the apse
Except for the maid dress
I need to find another noble person
The Prime Minister is that noble man
No, no, no
It's not convenient for me to interfere in the affairs of the apse.
Who is that
Not urgent
Let's find another trouble first
Ruo Yuanhao
See through poison
What should I do?
Does the Prime Minister think so?
Hidden on the beam
Blade Assassination
Although Yuan Hao is brave
After all, we are human
Assassination from the sky
He can't react
good
Just do it
Wang Kuanliang and I ambush
Xiao Jing poisoned
If this is true
The person who assassinates him will definitely die.
I'm so kind
How can I just watch
Look at you teenagers
Are you looking for death?
so
I'll give it to you again
Found a way out
Falling from the sky
Assassination of Yuan Hao
There is a way out
If Yuan Hao dies
Who is the Lord of Daxia
Prince Ning Lingge
Brother Ning Ling is a noble man
It is also a way to survive
Wu Zang asked to see the prince
This Prime Minister and I
It's just a nod of acquaintance
His sister
Won the favor of Qingtianzi
He's not here to show off
You're still here to humiliate me.
It's hard to say
let him in
Let's all go down
Prime Minister
Why are you free to come here today?
There is no secret that Pang has met the queen
Met the prince
The status of the Prime Minister is so noble
Why do you do this great gift?
Hurry up and help the Prime Minister up.
Please get up quickly, Prime Minister
Beg the prince to spare his life
beg queen for mercy
Prime Minister
Where did you start talking about this?
I have a word to say, and I will die if I say it
But I have to say
Prince
The Qingtianzi resorted to military violence
Several years of war
Within Daxia
People have long been living in poverty
All industries are in decline
My Big Summer
It's been a long time since I've been suffering from Qing Tianzi
I sincerely request the prince
For the sake of millions of people in Daxia
as soon as possible
Instead
absurd
I am so happy today
All thanks to my father’s unparalleled achievements
Now the war is decided
Peace on earth
How can we talk about resorting to militarism?
Prince
Today's Taiping
It's just Qing Tianzi's plan to delay the war
After the peace treaty was signed
All supervisory departments are working hard to prepare their troops
Recuperate and recuperate
Your Highness, you don't know
Within five years
As long as the national power has eased
The Blue Emperor will certainly send out troops again
Causing chaos in the world
Citizens of Daxia
Unable to fight for years
But he is my father.
Citizens of Daxia
personal relationship
Which one is more important?
Of course, livelihood is the most important thing
Since the livelihood of the people is the most important thing
How can it be done for one's own sake?
Personal Affection
Is this the right word to use?
Just bear with it
Prime Minister
You get up first
What does the Prime Minister want to do?
Your Highness
you can get to know them
never seen
Several of them are from the Song Dynasty
they come here
Just to assassinate Qing Tianzi
Bold
Your Highness, the livelihood of the people is the most important thing.
I absolutely won't
He attacked my father
This is my bottom line
No need to use your hands
I'm here to plead
plead
These young people from the Song Dynasty
Have a loyal and brave heart
If something unexpected happened to Emperor Qing
It must be His Highness who is in control of the situation.
When
I also hope that Your Highness
Give them a way to live
besides
what else do you want
One more thing
If you want to poison
Someone must be sent to sneak into the apse
This matter
We still need help from Your Highness and the Queen.
Isn’t your sister the princess?
she takes care of children
And he doesn’t care about the chores in the back hall all year round
If you suddenly arrange someone
too abrupt
Queen Mother
The Prime Minister is still there
Not feeling well lately
Fell asleep instantly
what are you talking about
Empress Hui
Your Majesty and the Prince
Talk about national affairs
As the saying goes
National affairs
I won't listen anymore
I don't understand either
correct
Your sister recently
A prince was born to Qing Tianzi
Born very strong
Here I am
Prepared some goldware for children
I'll send someone to deliver it to you later.
It's also a celebration
Queen Xie
Prime Minister
To make the brothers and sisters have today
It all depends on my father
assassination now
Wouldn’t it be self-destructive?
There has to be an explanation for this.
Kind
How about this answer
What do you say?
Let's tell the truth then
Your Highness
In fact, the reason is very simple
We brother and sister
Heavy feelings
Kill brother-in-law
The prince should know
My sister's previous husband
Yeli, the King of Tiandu, meets a beggar
He died at the hands of Yuan Hao
Husband-killing hatred
How can I forget
She's out for revenge