Xixia people
Ask you something
You rely on me
Is it for
Take this opportunity to get close to Yuan Hao
do you think i am
The kind of person who is looking for death?
It wasn't before
Stupid now
Want to kill Yuan Hao
It's not your turn
Brother Wang
I made it with my own hands
New dishes learned from my aunt
It smells delicious
correct
The aunt said
Pollux is a deluded student
To cause disaster
What happened to Yuan Zhongxin last night
They are also taking advantage of disasters to defraud money.
Is Pollux a bad guy?
It's hard to say now
do not know either
Brother Yuan and Sister Zhao over there
how's it going
Just arrived at the academy
Yuan Tianguan discovered Yuan Zhongxin
It shows that you are watching closely
But even so
Still no whereabouts of Polaris
This mystery may not be true
True or False
You have to figure it out and then look at it
bunch of idiots
Arrived here
Haven't changed clothes yet
How could you fall in love with him?
Because he is good
Compared with his brother
He is a waste
fine
I'm used to him saying that
I'm not used to it
Mr. Yuan
I think you are not qualified
Say this about him
I'm not qualified
child
I am his father
You are his father
How many times have you seen him?
unimportant
Whether his brother is in literature or martial arts
All outstanding
He even lives
He can't even reach his elder brother's back
Yuan Zhongxin is also outstanding
Ability and knowledge are all in a mess
What else can be compared?
Personality and character
Courageous and clever
Are you serious
Personality can be removed
In fact, you can hold on a little longer
I really have no confidence
All right
Courageous and intelligent character
You know he grew up
Is he just a gangster?
Cheating, deceiving, treacherous and slippery
the word you said
Which one is he good enough for?
I've seen him in life and death
I've seen him survive from desperate situations
have you seen
He has been a gangster since childhood
why
Because of this father
Never let him go home
He can only be in despair
struggling to grow
He has no choice
The so-called treachery
It's just a protective color for him
But even in
Growing up in such an environment
He still chooses to use
Face it all with a smile
Such Yuan Zhongxin
Just as amazing
Such insignificant things
nothing to argue about
it's very important to me
you are lucky
Just my taste
Then I'm going to follow Auntie
Learn to cook more
I’ll cook it for you from now on
OK
What's wrong
nothing
Just thinking about stopping the war
Yuan Hao must be eliminated
We still have to go to Xixia
After Yuan Hao
There should be no more tasks
After all, the secret pavilion is gone
But it will be very dangerous
I recently
I always think of the destruction of Sanzhai
Be classmates with them
It seems like just yesterday
I'm not afraid of death, Brother Wang
I'm just worried
if we
What are we
nothing
If we don't have a future
what to do
Yeah
before
i don't know my future
what will it be like
until I met you
I will no longer be afraid
The end of time
I've thought about it a lot
What we have to go through together
surprise or surprise
Then started to be afraid
If there is no such future
What a pity
I know
Our Qizhai
This is to fight for the Song Dynasty
I always think about myself
Especially bad
But what you said yesterday
I can't help but feel uncomfortable
never mind
I can just tell myself
Eat quickly
It will get cold later
Small Scene
somebody is coming
You eat slowly
I'll collect it after you finish eating.
palm book
please
That's it.
The topic went astray
If you praise me, say it later.
what do you want to do
Kill Yuan Hao
Don't you understand?
why
for me
Your elder brother
He is my son Yuan Tianguan
so what
But he died
my son is dead
Revenge of murder
I have to report it
It was Brother Ning Ling who killed him
So the one you want to kill is Brother Ning Ling
not enough
Brother Ning Ling is Yuan Hao’s son
Their father and son are dead
That's revenge
their father and son
It was tit for tat
If Yuan Hao really wants to take action,
Brother Ning Ling has died a long time ago
No matter how prepared you are
After all, they are father and son.
Just like this guy
I don't look down on him anymore
Let him be named Yuan
Can I change my last name to Fang?
Mr. Yuan
Do you want to cooperate with us?
cooperate
you don't deserve it
I can destroy him
he is your son
less hands
Still my son
what are you up to
Finding the Northern Star
Put people in my hands
You release Yuan Zhongxin to me first.
Give me Polaris
I'll take this crap
Back to you
You don't mind if you break your hand?
Yuan Zhongxin
Don't move
I heard that you are going to take leave and go home
Yes, my father’s birthday
That should be
Not really.
My father's birthday
New Moon
Calendar calculation
Birthday this year
When there is a solar eclipse
My father is worried about a bad year
So I have to go home to feel at ease
It also makes sense
What's wrong
did you hear that just now
They talk about birthdays and stuff
Calendar calculation
There will be a solar eclipse on your birthday this year
After all, all solar eclipses fall on the first day of the new moon
Calendar calculation
I know the numbers
What is it
What book are you looking for?
here
This row is
Books published by Si Tianjian over the years
look
Qianyuan calendar
Seven years of peace and rejuvenation
Si Tianjian came out of the Qianyuan calendar
exchange for old calendar
every calendar change
The number of years in the Yuan Dynasty
All need to be replaced
Xiaojing, look at the Qianyuan calendar
What is the number of weeks in years?
Yes
Two hundred and fourteen thousand
Seven hundred and sixty-four
The old number is
Two hundred and fourteen thousand
Seven hundred and sixty-four
the same
What is the second old number?
The fourth year of Xianping
ceremonial calendar
For Qian and Yuanli
The number of years in the celestial calendar
Three hundred and sixty-eight thousand
Eight hundred and ninety seven
It's the same
That is to say
This so-called new number
That's us now
Chongtian calendar used
That's right
First year of Tensho
Si Tianjian worshiped the Tianli calendar
Replacement celestial calendar
Still in use
The number of years in the Chongtian calendar
3.86 million
Seven thousand nine hundred and forty
It's a new number in this puzzle
That's right, that's it
But this row behind
Why do you write "none"?
Look at the remaining years
Fifty-five thousand five hundred and forty
It’s the same as on paper
Let’s look at Yitian Calendar again
Fifty-two thousand nine hundred and seventy
It's this old number
But the row in front
Why is the old number written as None?
Because of the Qianyuan calendar
There is no way to survive
The old and new numbers are both sixty.
Sixty-one years
All disciplines and laws remain unchanged
So the answer to this puzzle
It's the calendar
to be precise
new number
It refers to this Chongtian Calendar
found the book
Didn't see it either
Where is Pollux?
And this last line
Pollux returns to its place
What does it mean?
Logically speaking
It wants us to be in the Chongtian Calendar
Find the description of Pollux
should be
In the Chongtian Calendar
The name of the star official will not be written
That's wrong again
Not wrong
Think about it differently
Calendar Star Official
Wait a moment
Beihe star belongs to Jingsu
That's right
The first of the seven stars of the Vermillion Bird is the Jing
every calendar change
The orientation of each constellation changes
This is the twenty-eight stars
zodiac degree
Use calendar to record zodiac degrees
Well House is among them
With the zodiac constellation
Why is it sticky?
Sure enough it's here
Well-house
Chongtian calendar is thirty
clues point to
This is it
Wang Kuan
This puzzle is
Designed for you alone
River Star
Made for me alone
That is, Brother Wang
read so many books
Only then can we calculate from numbers to calendar
wrong
Someone mentioned it just now
Only then can I think of the calendar
That's good luck
Made for me alone
The reminder just now
It's too timely
they did it on purpose
These two people
I'm afraid he's not an academy student.
He is Beihexing's subordinate
I heard you are looking for me
Should I declare my home status?
I am Beihexing
sage writes book
Is it so complicated?
I can find every word
Seven or eight meanings
I'm about to vomit
I have vomited
Who can bear this?
It's all your fault
You said you were pretending to be sick
What class are you attending?
I'll just be polite to him
who knows him
Really carry me to the lecture hall?
It's too real
I have to go to class tomorrow
What should I do
Then I'll stab you.
Why
If you're injured, you don't have to go to class.
Let me think about it
I can stab you then.
You are the young master and I am the book boy
I'm injured and you still have to go to class
You are hurt
Neither of us need to go
Xiao Xue has become smarter
okay
Come on, let me stab you wherever
You really stabbed me
pick a place
Are you not tired enough from class?
There is still time to worry about
The chief is back
We study today
What a great read
Where is Yuan Zhongxin?
Let us take Yuantianguan
Northern River Star Exchanges Yuan Zhongxin
Isn't that his son?
yes
never seen the world
There is such a father and son
good luck
The hand is saved
Then I thank you
Finding the Northern Star
I will let you go
What if I can't find it?
you ruined me
Or kill me
I won't kill you
Even a tiger won't eat its own cubs
Ashamed
Can't help it
Ask you something
Yuan family
where are you now
In Xixia
Then do you know
You want to kill Yuan Hao
what will be the result
The Yuan family fell
You are the patriarch
They are not my sons
Too raw
Have you seen Pollux?
That's not right.
Exchange Northern River Star for Yuan Zhongxin
What a change
Beihexing defrauds people of money
He doesn't look like a good person
Making sacrifices to get money
Not necessarily him
I heard you are looking for me
Should I declare my home status?
I am Beihexing
Wang Kuan
Among the seven fasts and six sons
Whether it is knowledge or character
The one I trust most is you
you know us
i know who you are
I also know why you are here
I would like to join forces with you
Fight together against Yuantian Pass
Why
I was
After all, I did things for Lu Guannian
Although they parted ways later
But the secret pavilion he established
I've heard of some
You teenagers
They are our descendants
If you say
If there is a trustworthy person in this world
Maybe it's just you
Wang Kuan
This puzzle is
Designed for you alone
Finally, it’s your signature
I said that
Among the seven fasts and six sons
I trust you
Since I choose to show up proactively
Why bother setting up puzzles?
what's the point
This was supposed to be a test
After finding Chongtian Calendar
There's another puzzle
Test your ability step by step
You can prove that you can help me
I will appear
but
I have no time
Do not have time
so many years
I have been hiding in the academy
But recently
The academy has changed
What's the meaning
Someone is like me
Hidden in the academy
Although I don’t know who this person is
but
He used my identity.
Impersonate you
right
There are people in the academy recently
Stealing money under the pretense of disaster
The person behind the scenes
Used my name
False River Star
why do this
I want to know the reason too.
I'll help you deal with Yuantian Pass
The only requirement
I just hope you can
Help me get the fake Pollux
find out
If there are any clues
How to find you
Just put a candlestick by the door
I will appear
So you say offering sacrifices is cheating money
That's fake
Could it be related to Yuantianguan?
Could it be that Yuantian Pass
Find someone to impersonate Beihexing
I want to take the real Beihexing
Force it out
Why don’t Xiaojing follow you?
Come back together
She went back to the kitchen first
Come over when you're done
Yuantian Pass and Beihe Star
All appeared
Our fake identity
What's the use?
Isn’t there a fake Polaris?
I have an idea
We caught the fake Pollux
Give it to Yuan Tianguan in exchange for Yuan Zhongxin
But you didn't say
Fake River Star
It’s Yuantian Pass
Did you find someone to impersonate you?
My head is so big
Nice environment
He came quite quickly
You and Yuan Zhongxin
Why did you run to Yuelu Mountain?
And you're the only one who's back
We found someone lurking in the mountains
who
have no idea
Only traces but no person
What about others?
Looking for clues in the mountains
If he really ran away
This charge of rebellion
Will stay with him forever
He has no choice anymore
In the Song Dynasty
Lived uprightly
You said this before
If you find Yuantian Pass
Remember to tell me as soon as possible
I've said this before
never mind
I can't explain it to you either
Let Yuan Zhongxin come to see me
He is in the mountains
I'll give you one day
get him back
one day
no problem
This Yuan Tianguan betrayed the Song Dynasty
Joining the Western Xia
This person is unforgivable
Remind you
Don't forget your identity
I think Lu Nanshan
I really want to capture Yuantian Pass
So today's
I kept it secret for the time being.
clear
Just let the chief decide
But one day
How to save Yuan Zhongxin
Pollux doesn't mean
Will you help us fight against Yuantian Pass?
Why don't you discuss it with him?
Why hasn’t Xiaojing come back yet?
Missing a knife
Go up and have a look
That kitchen knife
Newly cut
Just this knife
after use
Put it back on the table
The key is in the house
There are no signs of fighting
Prince Wang
why are you here
I'm here to find my sister
she is not here
Come first
Princess Zhao is also here
Is there something I need from Xiao Jing?
You don't have time
What's the meaning
Lu Nanshan mobilized troops to surround the academy
Mobilization of the Guiyuan Army
Need to be recorded
It’s not good to leave the camp at will
The chief only needs results
tomorrow
But there is training in the mountains and fields
The headmaster said that Yuelu Mountain is also a mountain.
It’s just that the academy is famous all over the world
Send troops without orders
I'm afraid it's hard to explain
Jinghu South Road
Are there bandits?
Back to the abbot
should not
I think
maybe there is
What did he mobilize his troops for?
search
Take people
Capture
Even set fire to the mountains
He didn't believe your explanation
He felt that since Yuan Zhongxin had
Found Yuantian Pass
Father and son will definitely join forces
Then what's the use of surrounding the academy?
It's you he wants to catch
He believes Yuan Zhongxin
The only thing that matters
Just you guys
Now that the Yuan family father and son have joined forces,
He's going to use you as bait
Yuan Tianguan arrested Yuan Zhongxin
We can't be the bait
How could Yuan Tianguan capture Yuan Zhongxin?
They are father and son
Why did the Guiyuan Army help him?
cooperate
What kind of cooperation?
They also want Yuantian Pass
No
What the Returning Army wants is North River Star
Is there a military order?
No
That is the secret pursuit
What happened to Beihexing?
God knows
Except for the returning army
Even people from the government office
Also secretly chasing Beihexing
Who knows what he committed?
Secret pursuit
No official document
No
Or there is no evidence
Either
It's just unspeakable
It doesn’t matter what Pollux does.
We can't control it either
The key is now
You have to leave quickly
Otherwise wait till tomorrow
The Guiyuan Army is coming
You really don't have time
You came here specially to deliver a message
Is it for Xiao Jing?
That's my sister.
I already owe her enough
By the way, where's my sister?
Why haven't I seen her back so late?
Our Qizhai is about
That's what life is like, right?
Yuan Zhongxin was captured
Lu Nanshan mobilizes troops
Xiao Jing's whereabouts are unknown again
But at this time
The Returning Army is coming again
There's not much time left for us
It takes time for the Guiyuan Army to leave camp
You have to pretend to be a bandit
Really come to the academy
I'm afraid it's going to be dusk
Times of Day
So much trouble to solve
Let's meet up with Xue Ying in Yanei first.
Everyone works together
Not at this time
Something happened in Zhaishe too
Not so much
I'm just kidding
This bean cake is quite delicious
Small Scene
Brother Wang
Sister Zhao
Please try the bean cake I made.
have a taste
Where did you find the scene?
no
Xiao Xue and I were getting ready to go out
Xiaojing came in by himself
Guess who I met?
His Excellency Dragon God
it's me
Yu Chi Yuan
yes
His Excellency Dragon God
What you told me has been settled.
Find Yuantian Pass
Find the leader
Mortal things must be done by mere mortals
If you can accomplish this
I will give you eternal life
do not worry
Let’s come to Tanzhou
I'm looking for Mr. Yuan.
yuantianguan
Yes
I know where Mr. Yuan is.
He knows where Yuantian Pass is hidden
Where is this painting from?
Where is Yuchiyuan?
He is still in the academy
I'm thinking
Let me tell everyone about this first
Let him wait alone first
where to wait
He said
I will find a hiding place by myself
He has no objection
He thinks it should be like this
Dragon God
It must have a shelf.
The letter is confused
Yu Chiyuan
Know where Yuantian Pass is hidden
This mess
Even if there is a thread
Then let's go rescue Yuan Zhongxin
Yuantianguan has extraordinary strength
You have to go then.
We shouldn't fight alone
If there are any clues
Just put a candlestick by the door
I will appear
You look for me
you said before
Want to help us fight against Yuantian Pass
certainly
we can find him
When to take action
after dawn
So fast
Lu Nanshan wants to mobilize troops to surround the academy
He doesn't trust us
so
You have to do it yourself
Go catch that Yuantian Pass
Can
I can help you
My companion
Will confirm the location of Yuantian Pass
Then I will leave the academy
Go find him
I led my men to follow you secretly
leave no trace
It’s a deal
Have seen it all around
No ambush
No one is following you either
They took the bait
As expected
Yuantianguan won’t
Leave your son alone
The head of the court asked Mr. Pei to reveal secrets
Spread the news about troop deployment
It's a brilliant move
under pressure
the only way they can
found helper
It's just me.
Things were done properly
It all depends on the master’s miraculous calculations
I didn't understand it at first
Why did the Commander-in-Chief let those
Sacrifice someone who cheats money
Go and provoke Qizhai
did not expect
The chief court has already charged the sacrifice
It was pinned to Beihexing.
Now you have
The identity of Beihexing
If true Pollux appears
People who live in Qizhai will definitely think that
He is
The fake Pollux that sacrificed money to defraud people
Until then
Naturally, people will be
Delivered to your door
Confuse the real with the fake
It all depends on the commander’s instructions.
Cooperation
mutual benefit
You want Beihexing
I want Yuantian Pass
Qizhai
They are our pawns
Unfortunately
The true star Pollux did not appear
You feel
Will he really come to Qizhai?
Go find those boys
He County Magistrate
There are many students in our college
All secretly conspired with North River Star
causing trouble among the people
what does this mean
explain his eyes
Keep staring at the academy
Now there are new students coming to the academy
He will always show up
Don't worry
The lower body is the county magistrate
Hiding in this academy all year round
Thoroughly investigate Polaris
A lot of pressure
Over here at the government office
I can't make things clearer
Fortunately
A master appears
That's when there was a turning point
In fact, I always feel
This North River star is hidden in the academy
Already thought about it
The academy has already checked
you know too
My best men
They are all working as handymen in the academy.
This thorough investigation from top to bottom
Except for the one with ten cents
Beyond anagrams
There are no more clues
But
Found the Chongtian Calendar from the crossword puzzle
This will never happen again
I doubt it
This is a puzzle
It's a lie
Speaking of which
Did this old man selling crossword puzzles check it out?
checked
His wife, children, and children are all here
It can't be the Northern Star
Wife and children
Not necessarily true
it is true
The old man was born in the village
The family has lived together for decades
Never changed places
I also sent people to test many times
His deafness is also real
Not fake
Did you see that old gentleman?
Not young anymore
yes
You can wear it on weekdays
But there was a sudden loud noise
Normal reactions cannot fool anyone
we tried many times
He is indeed deaf
yes
Will it be North River?
I can't hear myself
impossible
Although I have never seen Polaris
But my father once mentioned
Pollux is by no means deaf.
That's weird.
This Pollux star confuses the public with its evil words
Cutting people and wealth
Many jealousies
Thanks to him hiding it well
Until now we have not
Catch him by the leg
Who is it?
A puzzle for the old man to sell
Have you checked?
Didn't check
this old man
Started setting up a stall a few years ago
Those ones
Bag puzzle is overnight
piled in his warehouse
Not sold out yet
Has anyone bought one over the years?
Anyone else got the answer?
There is no way to count it.
Look below
This Yuantian Pass is just a
Just a charlatan
Know how to embroider legs with some tricks
bluffing
this
Sirs, please rest assured.
Even if Yuantianguan finds out something
I also have some means
Let him tell the truth
By the time
After we subdued Yuantian Pass,
Then use Qizhai to find Polaris
Everything will be fine
yes
When you arrive
Just ask him directly
No, that's all.
Yes Yes
Chongtian calendar
What is the relationship with Beihexing
what is the relationship
And this Yuantian Pass
What exactly did you find?
Once you come to Tanzhou, you won’t leave.