Qingli four years
Under the Great Song Dynasty
Hidden internal and external troubles
So the Song Dynasty won over young people from all over the world
Establish a secret court
Facing the secret war
Defend the Song Dynasty
There are ten rooms in the secret pavilion
Among them, the seventh fast
especially outstanding
Among the seven fasts
Lots of talents
Have noble character
The gentle Yuan Zhongxin
Virtuous and virtuous
The frail Zhao Jian
Domineering and heroic
Wang Kuan, a simple-minded person
this
It's your sister-in-law.
You are my uncle
Intelligent and astute
The calm and capable Pei Jing
Why don't you just run forward by yourself?
Yes
Then I have to catch up quickly
If you lose it, you have to pay for it.
Knowledgeable and gifted
Xue Ying, who values ​​harmony
Simple and honest
Wei Yuan, who is clean and self-possessed
Let’s talk about Fengyue
Six people gathered together
A close friend
Event
Methodical
Be polite and courteous
that's all
Try harder
Don't worry, I'm definitely right
Dean
Secret Pavilion Teacher vs. Qizhai
Appreciate it very much
Much appreciated
You have been sick for seven days
After the Secret Pavilion was established
Qizhai cooperation
Complete various special tasks
Experience life and death
Solve the mystery
Car and artillery
It's a conspiracy
stop
Persevering in Qizhai
With efforts
Secret Pavilion
Unfortunately disbanded
The Secret Pavilion is broken up
Seven days of fasting
However, Qizhai Liuzi
Has not changed its original intention
Always defend the Song Dynasty
stop war
Struggle endlessly
Qizhai
All of them once sneaked into the prison camp
While breaking through the chaos
Met someone who called himself
Ding Er's Xixia Secret Agent
This person has great respect for Qizhai
Especially for Yuan Zhongxin
The relationship with Zhao Jian
Sincere blessings
No matter how much the price is, I won’t let you
Times have changed
Xixia and Song Dynasty
Peace talks in Pizhou
Just arrived in Pizhou City
They're all here to kill me
If this happens
The Song Dynasty will usher in
decades of peace
Save lives from suffering
Qizhai also went to the place of peace talks
And discovered Ding Er again
This person suddenly came here
I'm afraid it's not simple
Ding Er suddenly changed
Already the Xixia General Mi Qinmu Bei
This person is bent on sabotaging the peace talks
Intention to start another war
Qizhai Tongxin
Taking advantage of internal conflicts in Xixia
Finally defeated Mi Qinmu Bei
Put him in jail
where is my dad
I caught him
Let him go
However
Rice poultry and livestock
The reason for capturing Zhao Jian’s father
Your father's life is gone.
Force Zhao Jian
Take him out of jail
Go to Xixia
Everyone in Qizhai
Don’t believe Zhao Jian
would make such a choice
So he chased away
Take a trip
no matter what the truth is
They are all ready to meet Zhao Jian
shared responsibility
life and death together
Change to normal
of course i do
Walking alone with you
But now the heavy responsibility lies on my shoulders
Can we set off quickly?
Can you find me a horse?
Don't say you let him go
To save my father-in-law
this kind of thing
You can't do it
Yuan Zhongxin
The title of father-in-law
How can you use it randomly?
Have a task
Miss Zhao
Such a big deal
Remember to keep it confidential
You wait a moment
I will never forget my brother’s hatred
Do you believe it?
Sooner or later you
One day you will die in my hands
I really don't believe it
How about I sit in the bank?
Let's take a gamble
Okay
Life is a bet
You shouldn't have let me take charge
Why are you staring at me like this?
miss you
It's only been a few days since we separated
Just miss me so much
I'm that good
Then you still run
Miqinmubei proposed
Cooperation with the Song Dynasty
Who agreed?
The Privy Council felt
This idea works
How to cooperate
Zhao Jian
Help Ning Lingge
Kill Yuan Hao
It’s okay to kill Yuan Hao
But how can he believe it?
Killing Yuan Hao is my heart's wish
only this
I will never lie to you
Why did the Privy Council let you
Send him back to Xixia
My father is in his hands
It's reasonable for me to send him back
Yuan Hao won’t be suspicious either.
Then why don't you tell me
It was my father who was saved.
There is no reason to go with Qizhai
Moreover
Killing Yuan Hao will lead to ten deaths and no life.
Then if you have to die
We didn't die together
What a pity that would be
I don't want to involve you
Do you think you can drive me away?
Wang Kuan
Small Scene
They come anyway
Do you need me to get them away?
no
They were holding horses and holding hands
More than just holding horses and holding hands
He also held hands while riding on the road.
Isn't that dangerous?
My equestrian skills are okay
that
Everyone listen to me
I don't believe anything you say
Wang Kuan you
Seven fasts in one
Never give up
Wang Kuan just made a guess
no matter what the reason
You are definitely going to Xixia
Without my skills
How can you do it?
Yanei
Xiao Xue
Your horse is too wild
Don't care at all
The handsome image of Benyanei
Yanei
What are you doing
The fall was beyond recognition.
Small Scene
What's your expression like?
Doubtful about my handsomeness
No no
Yanei
You look a bit
Not like you anymore
Men change at their 18th birthday
But still handsome
Right Wang Kuan
I don't lie
You are really willing
Is Xiaojing in danger?
unwilling
If it's really a desperate situation
At least I'll fall in front of her
I tried my best
I really can't get rid of it
Seven fasts in one
Never give up
Everyone
the road ahead
Maybe a dead end
Just come with me
Forget about life
I'm really going to die.
Can you not die?
Don't be so cowardly
Let's be lucky
Fight for a living
as long as i live
you won't die
Then you must not die
Living towards death
Defeating Xixia
border emergency
Liao Lord's Third Army
One hundred thousand elite soldiers invade Xixia
Battle of Hequ
Defeated by Yuan Hao
under great defeat
The Lord of Liao almost became a prisoner
Since Yuan Hao became famous
Almost no defeat
Everyone understands
Yuan Hao negotiated peace with the Song Dynasty this time
Just to recharge your batteries
He will eventually come back
This time we go west
privy council is hope
Use Ning Lingge to divide the general trend of Xixia
The court has its own right path and hopes for peace
But seeing the residual scene in front of me
We understand vaguely in our hearts
Yuan Hao must die
maybe his death
It cannot eliminate the war in the world
But for the people on the border
gain a bit
Possibility of recuperation
is enough
How nobody ah
All escaped
Why escape?
War between Song and Xia
This was a battlefield
Now the Song-Xia peace talks have ceased war
Then they can all go home
May not be able to come back
War in mountain towns
leave scars
It’s the same with people’s hearts
these scars
Maybe it will never be as good as before
What's wrong
I also had this one when I was a kid
My dad asked someone to sew it
Tiger Eats Five Poisonous Animals
Seek help to drive away poison and avoid disasters
No one had time to escape
Under the scourge of war
Human life is like grass
I said
Let's hurry up
There are people waiting in front
We are not from the same place
Surrounded by hatred and deceit
Threats of killing and fear
finally
You will all become like me
That won't
No matter how it changes
I'm even more handsome than you
Guests come like clouds
Just make an appointment here
This Ning Lingge
After all, he is the prince of Xixia.
Why didn't you lead the army yourself?
Maybe he is weak and incompetent
Failed to take military power
Or maybe
Go deep alone
No need for men and horses
Come and embolden yourself
This Ning Ling brother is too arrogant.
I'll meet him when I come to the office.
minister
Miqinmubei
Welcome His Royal Highness the Crown Prince back to Luan
Your Highness
You are finally back
Avoid accidents
introduce
this
This is the real Miqinmubei
A rare good general
Please get up quickly
Thank you, Your Highness
He is Miqin Mubei
how about you
You are Brother Ning Ling
I didn't mean to lie to you
after all
It was within the Song Dynasty
Identity or something
Still have to be cautious
You personally sneaked into the Song Dynasty
to be honest
I am safer in the Song Dynasty
Your Highness
You are worth a thousand dollars
How can you go into danger alone?
I have told you many times
you just don't listen
Am I okay?
It's okay
You let them catch you
At least still alive
Your Highness
The Holy Lord does not take advantage of danger but takes advantage of luck
Losing an official
If you are serious, you will lose your throne.
Do you
Have you forgotten all your great things?
Yes Yes Yes
I understand too
You can no longer take risks alone
Look at your bad temper
Where's my dad?
Where's our dad?
Take less advantage
Prince Zhao
I'm all here
Get the person
Send it to Miss Zhao
take it easy
If you really regret it
Let's mobilize the army
What's wrong
Miss Zhao
Condolences
Why should I express my condolences?
Where's my dad?
Your father passed away
I ask you again
But don't get me wrong
My way
We are all together
this matter
I was also very sudden
cause of death
Death
Where did the disease come from?
What's wrong with your father?
Don’t you know yourself?
This illness is too sudden, right?
Could your father be faking his illness?
Force you to get married
Will not
Changed Sanbo Langzhong
Don't know each other
Diagnosed results
all the same
My dad is really sick.
I advise you
Better put down your weapons
You also know
The Song Dynasty wants to cooperate with His Highness
Please put the overall situation first
What a fucking mess for you
Who can prove that it was due to illness?
I can prove
Who are you
Lu Nanshan
You know him
He is the son of Master Lu
I was nearby before your father died
There's something wrong with the heart
There is no cure
Where did he die?
Our military camp
Then I want to ask Mr. Lu Zhangyuan
Why in the Xixia military camp?
What's this
Privy Council orders
Restart the Secret Chamber
Lu was ordered to take over
It became the Head of the Secret Pavilion
I have been wandering around Xixia for several days
Meet Brother Ning Ling today
naturally for
Assassination of Yuan Hao
Didn't expect
Really Ning Lingge
It turned out that he had already been in Song Dynasty
should be true
Mr. Lu wants to inherit
The legacy of the Master
The secret pavilion created by my late father
I never agreed
So his legacy
I don't want to take it either.
in my hand
will be a
Brand new secret pavilion
Xiaolu Zhangyuan is really
Ambitious
My dad is now
where are you
Into the coffin
Sent back to Beijing
Why don't you wait for me
You are going to Xixia
Help me kill dad
His parents died and he died for three years
Even if you are an official, you should also be Ding You
How to continue
The principle of following orders
My Secret Pavilion
Put national affairs first
mourning
Wait until the task is completed
Unreasonable
The so-called New Secret Pavilion
It is to cut off human feelings and cut off common sense
No reason to rely on
How different from animals
If there is any doubt
Can exit the Secret Pavilion
Unknown situation
Your Highness
you go first
I made an appointment
coming
Your Highness
Very good
Everyone is here
Let me introduce it first
Song Dynasty
Want to kill my father
Xiaren
I also want to kill my father
Everyone say hello to each other
You actually cooperated with Song Ren
sincerely
Lessons from the sun
How to plan
Wait a minute
Let me ask first
Killing my father
Are you still participating?
Why did you choose me to assassinate?
There are two reasons
One
It's me who is in your hands
I have to save myself
two one
you have to ask him
He chose you
You are not the only one who chose
But the entire Qizhai
Why Qizhai
Now there is no one available in the Secret Pavilion
How many other fasts are there?
All scattered
some
Act according to old orders
elusive
some
disappear without a trace
No trace
There are more
Already completely wiped out
Can be mobilized now
It’s just you Qizhai
So
Let’s talk about the plan first
Everyone
look there
What to see
Pillar
There seems to be a flying insect
In this direction
Keep going forward
Keep moving forward
there is a holy mountain
its name
called Helan Mountain
This is crying
see holy mountain
Moved
Can't see
I saw it in my heart
How long has your highness been sick?
You are sick.
My Highness, this is the true nature of your heart
Your Highness
Let’s get down to business
Do you know
Helan Mountain
Why is it called
The first of the three mountains of Daxia
sacred mountain
Because the party members believe
After death, the soul will eventually return to Helan
The legendary soul of Dangxiang’s ancestor
Still on Helan Mountain
That's right
Even if you die in a foreign country
family
I will also go to Helan Mountain to offer sacrifices.
So the whole mountain
It is a place of sacrifice
Helan Mountain
It records my Daxia lineage
All hopes and inheritance
It is the beginning of all
It's also the end of everything
That is why
Yuan Hao will rush to Helan
for calendar years
in the war
Sacrifice to the Lost Xia People
on the holy mountain
Let the dead find peace
This is the best time to kill him
When did Yuan Hao go to Helan Mountain?
enough time
You must arrive first
How many soldiers and horses are around him?
The elite left wing army is responsible for escorting
besides
Guarding the Helan Festival
And me, Daxia
Youzhou Military Supervision Department
Headquarters troops
That's not easy to do
introduce
this
It’s the Commander-in-Chief of the Military Supervisory Department of Youzhou
Liang Gewei's daughter
daughter
I am Liang Maixiang
Youzhou Shaodu commanded the army
Youzhou Military Supervision Department responded
I dispatch from it
You all start to assassinate
You can do it yourself
Why do you need us to help you?
My father is the Lord of Daxia
I'll start here
It won't end well later
Sandpipers and clams fighting
No, no, no
It's what each needs
Specific steps
How to assassinate and escape
this
Have to wait for everyone
We’ll make arrangements when we get to Helan
When to set off
Me and Miqin Mubei
Set off now
Go back to Xingqing Mansion and be a good son
Heading to Helan Mountain with my dad
Just take a day off for the rest of you.
tomorrow
He Shaodu unified the army
Let’s go to the Holy Mountain together
Why delay
We'll set off immediately
I have to arrange
This road covers your journey
Can you give me one night?
That's it
Everyone
See you in Helan Mountain
I'm outside the door
Depart early tomorrow morning
Shaodu unified the army
There is a room at the back
Need not
Wait a minute
You haven't said it yet
Which fast was completely destroyed?
Sanzhai
Isn’t Fu Qingyu from Sanzhai?
That's right
Everyone is gone
yes
How did you die?
What I can tell you
It's them who finished it
mission Impossible
the price paid
That is, all members of Sanzhai died in the battle.
No one survives
You really like
That girl Zhao Jian
What's wrong with her?
you say it
I asked her to change
If Your Highness really likes her,
How could you agree?
She goes to Helan Mountain
As soon as they go
Afraid of life or death
How can life and death be so unpredictable?
Rice Poultry
Not surprising
There is no life but death
do you mean
Their assassination failed
You think so
If they succeed in assassinating
Do I have to show up?
Avenge your father
Next
Gather his old troops
will be easier
So I have to kill those Song people for revenge.
What if the assassination fails?
Then there's no chance of leaving anyone alive.
What if they are caught by their father?
Wouldn't I be in danger?
So whether it succeeds or not
These Song people must die
It still hurts to think about it
to be honest
Really reluctant to part with it
But think about it carefully
For the great cause
I can give away my life at any time
What's more, my sweetheart
I arranged for her to die
I can still remember her in my heart
Also
Two hearts reflect each other
Is this how two hearts reflect each other?
Where is the horse hitch?
Front
Decide first whether to accept this mission or not.
others
Talk to you later
Sister Zhao, just decide
Listen to you
The chief's decision
It's Qizhai's decision
Said everything I wanted to say
I mean that too
we join
Set off tomorrow
have a good rest
Are you talking about Lu Nanshan?
He took over the Secret Pavilion
Must be an upstart from the military
I'll tell you another secret
He appears this time
Not to help Qizhai
Let's go
There's still a long way to go
Not this
You drink it while it's hot first.
Behind the Yanei
Light the fire and bake the pancakes?
You'll be able to eat it in a moment
Cooking in the office
He said he was good at cooking
Do you believe it
fine
Steamed cake
Eat something that won't kill you
or
I'm going to help
Need not
later
You still have to watch the first half of the night
Brother Wang said
He stayed late at night
today
None of us should disturb Sister Zhao.
She must be in a bad mood.
yes
or
You go accompany her
Brother Yuan is gone
Brother Wang said
at this time
Everything should be left to Brother Yuan
Too
Yuan Zhongxin is eloquent
Only him
when did you come
It's been a while
I didn't even notice
fine
very strange
I can't cry no matter what
Everyone is confused
fine
do not worry about me
People
Birth, old age, illness and death are inevitable
I'm fine
look
It's me
Very good at comforting myself
Yuan Zhongxin
It's me
Quite unfilial
why do you say so
It stands to reason that a relative dies
I should rush back immediately to mourn
But all I can think about is
Return to Beijing after completing the mission
If you spread the word, you will be scolded to death by others.
Who dares to scold you?
I just want to do something
Do something big
Make my dad proud of me
I know
Mr. Lu
I've been to your soup cake shop
The materials used are very practical
I remember
Your family is from a military household in Hebei Road.
What does Mr. Lu want to say?
speaking of
Your parents
Can you come to the capital to open a soup cake shop?
It was still the arrangement of my late father.
Now my father has passed away
Your soup cake shop
No one is protecting you
Can it still be driven?
Why can't I drive it?
Don't panic
Your family’s military status
My dad put it on.
I am the son
How can the verdict be reversed?
And as soon as the New Secret Pavilion is restarted,
Your business is my business
This soup cake shop
Drive on with peace of mind
Thank you Mr. Lu
The temple
Thank you, Manager
do you know
Among these seven fasts
You are the one that matters to me most.
I
Children of military households
Know the rules for following orders
Xue Ying
I want to ask you something
Do you think that among these seven fasts?
Who has any dissatisfaction?
alienation
Be more specific
Who will betray the Secret Pavilion?
No one knows
What if I said yes?
That's why you're wrong
This trip west
Give you a job
Keep an eye on them for me
look who's there
During this assassination mission
harbor dissent
Or act sneakily
Never
If there are any clues
You need to draw your knife
This is a military order
how
Don't take military orders
Xue Ying in Charge
so i said
You are the one that matters to me most.
These words
Do not tell others
Keep it in your heart
The wind is getting stronger
Did you hear that
It should be debris that fell from the eaves.
blown down by the wind
Touched the window lattice
Don't open the window
its me
Before entering the Secret Pavilion
live at home
I always quarrel with my father
He wants me to get married
I won't
I always feel that living is so boring
Chest tightness
Can't breathe
Always quarreling with him
Then I put myself
shut in the house
My dad is worried about me
Just outside the window
open the window
Open a small gap and peek at me
See if I have eaten
Not happy
Did you sneak out of the house secretly?
He stood there for a long time.
thought i didn't know
Actually I know everything
Him
clumsy
Arms and legs
Always banging against the window
that voice
Exactly the same as this one just now
Actually I never believe in ghosts and gods
but don't know why
I feel it right now
He is the one who came to see me
My dad is always worried
I'm alone in this world
Can't stand it
The wind stopped
He has been here
My dad is gone.
I'm the only one left in this world
And I
what is that
I just saw
There is a shadow on the cliff
Presumably high up
Someone is offering sacrifices to the dead
wrong
I saw that shadow
With horns
Sheep horns
right
Either I saw it wrong
Either
It's the gods who show up.