Which way to go next?
The post house is this way
what sound
Where does this lead to?
a village
Let's leave quickly
He sounded very nervous
Is this village far away?
Not far
It's not far
It has nothing to do with us
Going Around
Take a look
why
No sense
Taught by the Headmaster
Everything in the world may be related
Can not be ignored
What's the meaning
This road looks
No one has repaired it in a long time
It must be because the people in the village are too lazy
Let's go back
just in front
My son
Just say it
Weeping at the grave
Isn't this sacrifice put on display?
Son, my life is so miserable
How come so many people died?
This village is old
Maybe they're all buried here
These tombs look quite new.
The village should be right ahead
Go and have a look
Curiosity kills
Go go go go
this way
interesting
Look at horse hoof prints
It should be going to the right
This Yu Chiyuan has also learned to be smart.
He's still raising suspicions
It's not easy for him either.
We are surrounded by people
Already arrived at Jinghu South Road
Maybe it’s not far from Yuantian Pass
Look what I'm doing
Now that the mark has been found
let's go
gentlemen
We've all come this far
your chicken
Can you stop barking?
so
Tell it yourself
In fact, just don't let it open its mouth.
This specification
It definitely doesn’t look like a wild house.
This is the highest level post house
I set up a post office in the Song Dynasty
Such a standard inn
It must be built on the official road
Why are you in the mountains?
too quiet
What's going on here
There used to be a lot of people in this village.
There was no such thing before
Is this the person just now?
No sacrifice at the grave
Instead, it is used here
I see
This is the Dragon God
What happened to this village?
Maybe it's the dragon god appearing.
Set Tulong
What
Sculpture dragons out of clay for worship
Usually used to pray for rain
how do you know
heard before
Use the method of earth dragon
There was it in the Han and Tang Dynasties
It has been circulating for a long time
It’s just that in our Song Dynasty
This method is rare
Basically use
How to draw a dragon to pray for rain
I've heard of dragon painting
soil
Three years of drought in Jingde
Useful
This is how to draw a dragon and pray for rain.
Then the earth dragon takes shape
Less and less
Maybe here in Tanzhou
Still using the old heritage
No, no, no, no
I was here two years ago
Absolutely not this
This village is not like that either.
It's really not right
Since ancient times, earth dragons have been worshiped
But never seen
Which one cut off the dragon's head?
Be careful
No one
It's normal that no one lives there
But even
There are no postmen or post officials.
It's very strange
Why are these all books?
Crap
What's wrong
This house is attacking me from all sides
I get a headache when I see the book
Yuan Zhongxin and others
We should have taken the fork on the right.
But why the mark
But they all stayed on the left side
The post house is the end point
That should be right
They go to the fork in the road
K
What happened temporarily?
is the enemy
probably not
No signs of struggle
So it’s not a big problem
This station
Looks like it's been abandoned for a long time
This inn is extraordinary
Such specifications look like
Like the old customs of the Chu people
There is something
What did you see?
There seems to be something in there
The dragon heads were cut off
How much I hate this dragon
Think about it the other way around
Plastic dragon prays for rain and then beheads and destroys eyes
Maybe he wanted to ruin the sacrifice
There's something missing here
Are there any sacrifices?
From a style point of view
It feels like a sacrifice
Sacrifice with the dragon
Is the thing very precious?
snatched away
this ceremony
Want to be sacrificed together with the dragon
unless
Unless something
Unless there's a real dragon inside
real dragon
Such a small box
Can pretend to be a dragon
There really is a dragon
have
There was in ancient times
Not just ancient times
The late emperor had it at that time
Let me think about it
The third year of Dazhong Xiangfu
Still four years ago
The late emperor sent his servant to find the real dragon
Made a prayer for rain
If your guess is correct
in a box
That should be it
Stop talking. Stop talking.
I figured it out.
You will know what
The truth is right before our eyes
Dragon statue damaged
Dragon God is angry
disaster from heaven
Village Finished
Not fluent
Is it reasonable?
I understand everything.
Let's go quickly
It's better to spend less time in this place
want to know the truth
Just ask if you can
Who to ask?
That old lady just now
It seems to be going in that direction
Has she always been this bold?
Aren't you curious?
Ask less about gods and Buddhas
In case you encounter something strange
It's not something we mere mortals can control.
Even if it was caused by gods and Buddhas
That also needs to be taken care of
What did you say
It's a mouse
Rat in clothes
It's for children to play with
no
This mouse costume
Not the dress of this dynasty
So what are you wearing?
Han Dynasty clothing
Not a mouse
It's evil
People found
Just in the village
Opened his mouth
Silent at first
Just leave some money and let's talk.
Where is the family?
Almost dead
living people
They all fled
What happened
I'll make a long story short
This village suffered a disaster
drought
Not only the disease
Not that scary
The epidemic has passed
Praying for rain
It is also a way to eliminate disasters
It seems
Didn't succeed
Drought is rampant
disease outbreak
Most of the people fled
Only the old people are left
Almost starved to death
Then use food as a sacrifice
It is said that some villain broke the dragon statue
So all the disasters
Because of this, they are all out of control
They just want to worship devoutly
Ask the Dragon God for mercy
What's there to worship an earth dragon?
Separate Separate
Don't talk nonsense
Pah pah pah
Who cut off the leader?
Students from Yuelu Academy
Wollu Academy
Aren’t they all scholars?
Why do scholars destroy dragon statues?
Are you bringing disaster to the world?
Why do students want to behead dragons?
It doesn't make sense
The luggage and clothes are all there.
People can't disappear into thin air
broken
What's wrong? What are you doing?
I want to put it out
it is aware
What's wrong?
Are you crazy
Chickens will sense something is wrong
Then you suddenly
Why did you let it out?
It's going to poop
There is a hole in my basket
Shit has been leaking out of me these past two days.
we want to be here
Been here for a while
Let it out and move it around
What if Yu Chiyuan sees it?
Is there any problem with raising chickens in the post house?
No
Yanei
what is that
have no idea
Someone is worshiping this thing
Is there such a strange snail in the world?
Definitely not
Who would worship a conch?
then what is it
Don't understand
Ask Wang Kuan
Wang Kuan may not know everything
i know what this is
look
What did I say?
It's just as evil as this one
It seems like this
There should be more than just these two
besides
There is no one at the inn
But find these two things
Someone set up an altar to offer sacrifices
really
Is there any more?
Gone
We also found it here
its not right
There should be one more
Where will it be?
Don't think too much about it
The village is so close to the inn
Academy people
Why destroy the dragon statue?
Mr. Yuan may know the reason
that is not
Chicken?
Common things that happen when raising chickens and ducks in a post house
What's all the fuss about?
I have little knowledge
Is the cock's mouth tied?
Why tie the chicken's mouth?
Yes
why
Understood
Mr. Yuan thinks it's noisy
So I tied it up
Then why keep it?
Eat to gain weight
This is not simple
so smart
Never mind it
Mr. Yuan
They won't run into your father, right?
Let’s see what surprise I bring you
Mr. Yuan
gentlemen
Where are the people?
There's no way there's no one there
Brother, don't worry
Let's find it together
Mr. Yuan
gentlemen
Sir
what sound
anyone there
no one
The posthouse is empty
send him away
What a ghost
Why is there no one?
Have you found anything there?
Indeed no one
Could it be that this dragon's head has been cut off?
It affects here
It's possible.
Not far away after all
If you want to say so
Aren't we also in danger?
It's so possible
The faucet is broken and you still touch it?
In this yard
There are no heads left either.
Excuse me then
what do we do
How can we eliminate the crisis?
yes
what should we do
I see
Worship sincerely
Please forgive me Dragon God
As long as you sincerely offer sacrifices
Maybe we can save the day
Is there such a good way?
Why didn't I think of that?
yes
We still
Not as good as
Mr. Yuchi
far-reaching wisdom
Can't say that either
Everyone has their own strengths
I'm just good at thinking
Then this will be easy to handle
Let's find someone to go back to
Just light some incense
OK
I go
Then we'll wait for you here
Go quickly and come back soon
etc.
you know
How to burn incense and worship?
of course I know
Isn’t it just to bow and burn incense?
How can that be done?
If you are not sincere
Might even anger the Dragon God
Makes sense
Then let's find someone who is sincere
Go with him
Then I'll go.
You can forget it.
You just go
if not
I just washed my face this morning
You didn't even wash up
dirty
How to worship God
Can't you be sincere?
This is the attitude
never mind
None of you can do this
Look at it this way
I need to take him for a trip
Who else would I be?
He said I was dirty
Let's go wash up
People left
How did you let him go?
Went to worship the dragon
Bailong
Let’s talk about the key points first
Yu Chiyuan said
Yuantian Pass is in this post house
But there is no one in this posthouse
Any vision?
have
What's this
It feels a bit familiar
Just four?
Is there one missing?
Wang Kuan also said there is another one
You know this thing
Of course
Old thieves and the others
I believe these ghosts and gods the most
This is called Five Elements Evil
No wonder it looks familiar
Saw it in books
Disasters in the world are divided into five elements
This is Huang Yi soil
Late Han Dynasty and Three Kingdoms Period
Someone from Wei has seen it
Spoken words determine life and death
This is just one of the earth-type evils
There are also formless and formless
It is said that when Emperor Zhaolie of the Han Dynasty conquered Wu
When I met in Zigui, the ground was filled with yellow air.
Stretching for more than ten miles
That's also Huang Wei's vision
Then came the great defeat of Yiling
So Yiling was defeated
Because of
Emperor Zhaolie meets Xie Yi
It's ominous.
It's just far-fetched
All major events
Always looking for some so-called secrets
In fact, there is no evil
All heaven’s secrets are determined by man
However, some people would rather believe
These evil theories
I don’t want to believe that everything is man-made
What about the others?
This is the turtle tree
right
I found this in a tree hole
Isn't this a snail?
What do you call a turtle?
In ancient times, snails were classified as turtles
It is said that Jin minister Wei Guan saw this object
The following year, Wei Guan's family of nine
Then he was killed by people sent by Empress Jia
So this thing
Represents the disaster of weapons
Bad luck
Wei Guan's death stemmed from Empress Jia's abuse of power
Nothing to do with this
Caterpillar's evil is metal
Nanyang appeared during the reign of Emperor Wu of Jin Dynasty
After that, the royal family was in chaos
The world is in turmoil
Chi Yi belongs to fire
When Gongsun Yuan claimed to be King of Yan
Xiangping appeared
After that, the Wei army captured Xiangping
Liaodong Pingding
Disaster of the Five Elements
Jin Wei becomes a monster
Wood is auspicious
Earth is a disaster
Fire is a disaster
Metal, wood, earth, and fire still lack water.
Water is a disaster
Four have been found now
It feels like the fifth one is coming soon.
I've looked for it twice.
I found this in a tree hole
Xiaojing, which one is yours?
Huang Yi is the earth
Found it in a stone statue
One is offering sacrifices by the stove
There is a weapon in a house
Fire and Gold
That water
Could it be in the pond?
possible
Have to look for
I still need to find all these things.
But these things
They are all images of disaster
Affiliated to Xieyi
Who will come to worship?
yes
How unlucky
Not as good as
Xiao Lu Zhangyuan said something
After all, this journey
It was you who brought us here
Presumably Xiaolu Zhangyuan
More enlightened than us
do something
Pushing the envelope
wasting time
Let's find a pond first.
Did you bring any sacrifices?
What do you think?
That's inappropriate
Can't be empty-handed
I have to go get something
Knives cannot be used as sacrifices
Meat is best
The faucet is gone
who is there
If there is anyone in this village
If you stay
Must be very pious
You shouldn't dare to touch this
you mean
something has been here
who
What happened?
Maybe I'm seeing things.
What did you see?
Just behind that
A dragon flashed across
Dragon shape
Could it be
The true dragon appears
It flashed by and I didn’t see clearly
Don't get me wrong
We didn't break your head
This is bad
What if this confuses my mind?
It would be bad if he got possessed again.
Or we
Who goes down
The hero volunteered
The time has come
I have to feed the chickens
If I had known I would have raised something
As early as in front of the secret pavilion
Didn’t you have two dogs?
What kind of dog is it? Is it cute?
Five elements of disaster
maybe with
The whereabouts of Yuantianguan are connected
Just this pond
It's really dirty
Otherwise, you can look for it again.
Are there any other
Clean pond
Makes sense
If you want to do big things, you still have to be afraid of getting dirty.
The Chief
Change over time
How can we look forward and backward?
I thought about it again
In fact, the last one is as disastrous as
Not necessarily in the pond
Didn’t you say that the last one is water?
It’s true that it belongs to water
But look around this pool
no altar
The remaining four disasters were sacrificed
Then if the last one
In this water
How to offer incense and worship?
Yuan Zhongxin, what you said makes sense.
I knew it
Impossible in a pond
Is there any other place
Didn't notice
words related to water
water tank teapot
Didn't you tell me earlier?
Xiao Lu Zhangyuan works
I'm a little too anxious.
Don't worry, Commander
Look everywhere again
It can't be in a pond anyway
Dean
Come
Headmaster, be careful
There are fish on the roof
Do you want to take a look?
Drying salted fish?
It's all done now
Why on the roof?
There is no water on the roof again
Are you waiting for rain?
This is fish evil
Fish are born in the abyss and thrive in the house
It is extremely yin covering yang
Lord evil and disaster
During the reign of King Wei Qi
Then there is this image in the world
That year there was the defeat of Dongguan
okay
The five evil elements are gathered together
Then what
No or I don’t know
Where is Yuantianguan?
at least we know
What was he worshiping?
And also know
who are the people around him
There's something underneath the fish
Then why don't you take it down?
If you don't take it off, it means you can't take it.
correct
Xixia Sacrifice
Sheep Guardian
What is the Goat God?
It is the god worshipped by the Xixia people.
Yuan Tianguan betrayed
There is a Xixia man next to me
It's normal
Xixia people feared ghosts and gods
Even the changes in the sky are awe-inspiring
So worship this
Not surprising
That makes sense
But he didn't come here
The whereabouts of Pollux?
But why don't you get down to business?
Should we let the Xixia people do this?
Think differently
This disaster
Since you are not from Xixia
Worshiped
Then why do Xixia people use
How to worship the Sheep Guardian God
Come to worship it
Fear of disaster
Use Xixia gods to suppress
fear of suppression
Yuantianguan and Xixia people
Not getting along well
You mean they're fighting among themselves?
They left the inn
This is also the reason
Where is Yuchiyuan?
Something unexpected happened
What an accident
The faucet is gone
It's the broken faucet
right
Yu Chiyuan noticed something was wrong
Chased into the jungle
I didn't catch up and the person disappeared.
What is this situation?
Could it be
yuantianguan
Then we have to check it out.
But we haven’t finished searching here yet.
I'll go check it out.
thank you
No need to say thank you
I'm just curious
That's thanks too
I said you're welcome
Go south to Tanzhou
The friendship between you and me has become clear
What will I do next
It has nothing to do with Xiaolu Zhangyuan
Actually I think
You can't blame the dead uncle.
after all
He who keeps company with the good becomes good.
He who is near mud is mud
Xiao Lu Zhangyuan's body
It really makes people
Not easy to get close to
Everyone
Xiaolu Zhangyuan
Don't take it too seriously
This person Yuan Zhongxin
Just a little out of tune
Set here
Dean
Let's change clothes
There must be something hidden here
other clues
Please continue searching
Don't be impetuous
Follow the teachings of Xiao Lu Zhangyuan
Where is Yuchiyuan?
Knocked out
I won't wake up for a while
Where is the person hiding?
In the woods next to the post house
tied up
look
Poems and essays by students in the state
They are all books printed by Tanzhou itself.
so what
Avoid Lu Nanshan
Call everyone together
The chief has gone
What are you looking at?
Chief
Are there any other clues in this yard?
Lu Nanshan asked us to search
Let's help him find it
I just saw
something passed
I seem to have seen it too
right
It should be in a stone box
The lost dragon
What a real dragon?
There is a stone box in front of the dragon statue in the village
The real dragon inside ran away
Are you serious
It's the right thing to be here
what is right
Come
Come and see the real dragon
Chief, you lied to me
This is a lizard
Also called Xiaolong
real or fake
During the reign of Dazhong Xiangfu
The late emperor sent his servant
Go to Maoshan to find the real dragon
This is what I'm looking for
I found two and ran away with one.
After praying for rain
Sent back again
Run so far
Catching lizards
This method existed in the Tang Dynasty
The emperor believed it.
At that time, it was Yang Yi’s book
This is what is recommended
Lizard's Rain Prayer
Yang Wengong
Yang Wengong opposed it all his life
The late emperor built buildings and sought immortality
I was praying for rain
They want to carry out large-scale construction projects
As a result, he recommended this method
It did save a lot of money
In the end, people
Just a trip
You said that even officials believe in ghosts and gods?
Not to mention the people
Officials all believe
Will it be really useful?
The real dragon was eaten by the chicken
This is the god they believe in
etc.
This lizard
He was brought back from the village
The five disasters of the dragon statue are related to each other
The disappearance of Yuantian Pass
It should be inseparable from these
You just now
That's not what you said
You said that inference just now?
A set of
That makes sense.
all wrong
Tell it to Lu Nanshan
Or our office
Look carefully for clues
no
What you just said
It's all wrong
It sounds pretty reliable to me.
Are you saying that the Xixia people were affected by disasters?
Internal strife with Yuan Tianguan
That's all bullshit.
Yuantianguan surrendered to Xixia
Belongs to a surrendered general
If the Xixia people were because of
Words of disaster and dissatisfaction
Just do it directly
Why bother
What statue of a goat guardian should you draw?
But we all believed it
Actually I don't believe it
Why
Just now
When they are talking about this
Brother Wang pulled my sleeve
And shook his head
I knew it
Can't believe what they say
You pull her sleeve
Already so familiar
As soon as I heard it, I knew it was nonsense.
then why do you
Don't pull my sleeve.
unwilling
Everyone is a vegetarian
What's the difference between me and Xiaojing?
You are so unfaithful
What you said is a bit too much.
I'm just talking
It doesn't matter
Those evil things
Is there another explanation?
Not just an explanation
maybe we can know
Where did Yuantian Pass go?
No way
change direction
Think about Yuantianguan coming to Tanzhou
what is his purpose
adult
Will it
Yuan Tianguan noticed something was wrong in advance
Just ran away
This trip south
Why few people know
Just afraid of leaks
Yuan Tianguan
Will it be unpredictable?
Here in Tanzhou
There should be troops stationed there, right?
More than Xiangjun
Tanzhou is a stronghold in Xiangling
It has been a battleground for military strategists since ancient times.
Under the Imperial Guard
The main camp of the Guiyuan Army is in Tanzhou
Your Excellency is the Head of the Secret Pavilion
It’s another deputy commission of the Privy Council.
Why don't we use the Imperial Army to investigate this place?
You are not unaware of our dynasty's system.
Military commander
All are civil servants
Want to borrow troops in a big way
Impossible
Obviously working
How could it be so difficult
This is why
i will let you
Contact Han Duanzhang
My late father and I have never had the same ideas.
But this is the only thing
I've always been behind you
Just want to take advantage of the war
Reversing the situation of the wealthy and the powerful
It's a pity that the success failed
After the Liao-Xia war, both sides suffered losses
In recent years, I have wanted to use the military again.
unless
Unless something
Yuan Zhongxin said
Sooner or later Yuan Hao will raise another army
What do you think
Yuan Hao should be this kind of person
Qizhai kills Yuan Hao
As a secret agent of the Song Dynasty
It's natural
But as long as Yuan Hao is not dead
There will be war in the future
A military commander wants to gain fame
Still need to rely on war
Many people will die
Everyone is mortal.
But if your mind is as strong as iron
Why be afraid of blood flowing into a river?