I am a witness
who is he
Why did he appear in the Yuan family?
How do you know Yu Chiyuan?
How can I follow you?
Come together
I was also entrusted
The Yuan family who followed Yu Chiyuan
Who asked for it?
Yanei
Have you ever thought about a question
What
I said
Treason is a crime punishable by execution
Even the princess, you don’t care about him
What's the use of having him?
He will be taken to the execution ground soon
beheading
Xiaolu Zhangyuan might as well hurry up
You have to be quick
As you wish
Is there a problem with this?
The death penalty of my Song Dynasty
The process is very complicated
It can't be done in three days
Right, so I went out of the city to kill him.
There is a law
Whether in the city or outside the city
It's impossible to kill people at will
So this is
A lynching in Lu Nanshan
Rikunanzan Present
The new president
Entered the Privy Council again
It can be said that the future is bright
do you think he will
Are you so easily impulsive?
Besides, things like lynching
Once revealed
What's his future?
There's no benefit in killing me
yes
Think about it again
Why would he let
Yuchiyuan looked at me
Mingming Yuchiyuan’s testimony
Already said
He has a grudge against the Yuan family
Isn't he afraid?
Wei Chiyuan in prison
Take revenge on me
Kill me
Then after I die
How else can the Yuan family investigate?
So this is unreasonable
Yanei
I give you those lessons
do you remember
last night
why don't i see you
Yes why
Because this matter of the Yuan family is very involved
I was thinking of finding a way on my own
Don't drag you into the water
Can you understand?
understand
But now Yuan Zhongxin said
let me find you
Let's help rob the prison together
Can you understand?
clear
I also understood
You don't understand
All the classes in the Secret Pavilion were in vain.
Think about it yourself
As a lesson
Such a big crime for Yuan Zhongxin
But he wants to drag everyone into the water together
This is not in line with his behavior
So from that moment on
I knew it
There is something wrong with this execution
The Law of Calamity
It won't hurt anyone
All the unreasonable
In fact, it is the same as
The same person who entrusted this gentleman to
is the same answer
So Headmaster Xiao Lu already knew
Yuchiyuan is a disciple of the Yuan family
So let Yuchiyuan guard you
this lynching
There will also be subsequent tribulation fields
All for one purpose
Let Yuchiyuan kidnap Yuan Zhongxin
use this opportunity
Find out the whereabouts of Yuan Zhongxin’s father
There are results
In Tanzhou
Tanzhou
Be more specific
the day after tomorrow
The day after tomorrow Yu Chiyuan
Take me to find someone in person
Go south to Tanzhou
I'm with you
Thanks a lot this time
The Lu family is kind to me
I want to repay this favor.
How many more favors do you owe me?
the last time
Go south to Tanzhou
Please come with us
Why do you let me go with you?
have you seen him
Finish helping this time
Neither owes each other
Can
The execution ground is indeed a lynching
But put you in jail
This up and down
But everyone knows
nonsense
People are put in prison and guarded by the military
It's strange that the above doesn't know
so
Cha Yuan's family plots rebellion
There has to be a result
Let’s go to Tanzhou together
is the result
The court is fake
But arresting you is real.
Report it to the police now
It was you who escaped from prison
Why
Threat
If I want to clear my name
You have to help him catch someone
You don't believe Yuan Zhongxin
certainly
Who named him Yuan?
Okay, there's no need to be angry.
I understand
If you run halfway
This charge of treason
I can't clean it up in my life
I see
very good
You are the son of Yuan Tianguan
you know him
Former colleague
May I ask what your identity is?
See you the day after tomorrow
Been making trouble for a long time
Everyone is in the pit
Yu Chiyuan is alone
Then you and Yuan Zhongxin
That time in the woods
He is also deceiving Yu Chiyuan.
If Yuan Zhongxin fails to gain trust
Me and Xiao Jing
Will take the opportunity to get close to Yu Chiyuan
Don't you lie?
I didn't lie in the woods
Didn’t he deceive Yuchiyuan?
You let him speak for himself
You do the math
I said a few words in total
you are hurt badly
Please explain
Give you a chance to explain
No need
Why don't you leave here with me first?
The chief does not have to be like this
This sentence is long
Don't you feel guilty for shouting?
I have a clear conscience
What did I say that I lied about?
Small Scene
you have to be careful
What's wrong
Your Wang Kuan is so bad
He is the best in the world
You are done
Wait a minute
You made an appointment with Mr. Lu
meet here
yes
How did Wang Kuan know that?
He was still waiting here in advance
I was reminded in the woods
What did you remind him of?
The human heart is more dangerous than Yu Yuan
Such people
God knows he will do it again
What kind of thing is coming
The sun enters Si of Yuyuan
Dawn at Menggu's Pond
The place where Yu Yuan disappears
Isn't this night?
That's it
Yuan Zhongxin speaks
Never like rhetorical embellishments
Sudden elegance is inevitably abrupt
Why do you sound like you are scolding me?
He has another sentence
If it weren't for the
Someone tipped off the news
Lu Nanshan’s New Secret Pavilion
How could he fail in the Yuan family?
The Secret Pavilion has already changed
Such people
Stop talking about taking care of us
I'm afraid it's Qizhai's old place
I can’t even remember clearly
Suddenly mentioning the past and the old place
Not connected with the previous sentence
Plus Yu Yuan
I guess it just keeps me at night
Waiting in the old place of Qizhai
You can all guess this
How do you two usually talk?
It does not matter
First think about his crime of treason.
Yes, I’m going south this time
Must be washed out
His charge of treason
Actually
this is bad news
also good news
take the blame
How can this be considered good news?
The court is fake
That means your net worth
At least it's still innocent
To be honest, this time I went south
In fact, it's my own trouble
If you want to say
You go south alone
It's better not to say anything
That's not what I meant
I mean
Your net worth is still clean
What if I go south this time?
What trouble did you encounter?
Then it's up to you to support me.
Will I be safe this time?
It's all up to you guys.
I want to ask
Today's business
Is it finished?
Yes
I have a question that I have been holding back for a long time.
Sister Zhao heard that you are engaged
deal
But
Brother Yuan has been in prison all this time
Where did you make the appointment?
Right in the jail
From the beginning of the world to the present
No one gets engaged in prison, right?
That's not certain
If not
I'll set a precedent
Why don't you speak?
Excuse me
What's there to be embarrassed about?
We are not thieves
Sister Zhao
what happened
Please tell me in detail
What's there to say?
to be honest
I just love hearing this
Why aren't you sleeping yet?
Brother Wang
I'm really happy for them
Brother Yuan and Sister Zhao
both of them
experienced so much
Finally got the result
And Sister Zhao, she’s so awesome
Dare to think and do
I really envy them
do you know
Today I also begged Sister Zhao
I saw her and Brother Yuan
concentric knot
I think
That's nothing more than a rare treasure
All are precious
for you
Don't envy
You can also have
How did you get it?
Finger cut
But I can't
You can also use a knife
Then I'll go find Sister Zhao to borrow a knife.
Then go to sleep
I have to travel far tomorrow
Do not be afraid
they are here to find me
come in
Which of you asks first?
You said Yuan Zhongxin’s father
I was your colleague
That year in Lu Guannian
Work under you
Is it convenient for you to tell me what I want to do?
Why was the Secret Pavilion established?
Fight against Xia Liao's spy
The Song Dynasty was founded for more than 80 years
have you ever thought about
before the secret pavilion
Who will fight against the enemy’s spies?
It's you
Long before the Secret Pavilion
Lu Guannian established
Your own spy
Select people at that time
Or choose among the military
Or choose a strange person among the people
Or
Prisoner
With training, you can meet the enemy
Your father and I are among them
and after
The so-called spy
Trapped in darkness and fighting endlessly
Years of fighting against the enemy
Countless casualties
Dead people
Can't even leave a name
It’s been a long time
People's hearts are floating
Some people think
Lu Guannian deliberately let us die
some people doubt
Lu Guannian is cruel and ruthless
Disregard for human life
so
Some have returned, some have reversed
Some want to kill Lu Guannian to vent their anger
What about you?
Of course I won't be right
Lao Zhangyuan did it
My life was given by him
you
He is also the son of Lu Zhangyuan
Just pretend he doesn't exist
That might be my misunderstanding
Fighting among colleagues
I got chills later
This is the result of fighting to the death
So I chose to quit
The commander has never said this before
Better to raise chickens
Not tired
Not tiring
Lu Guannian established the Secret Pavilion
Choose from teenagers
He is afraid of making the same mistake again
So to say
you are us
A true senior
I'm a useless person
What do you call your senior?
We used the stars as our sign
I belong to the Xusu Department
In the name of Si Wei
Si Weixing
That's right
There is another name
Si Weixing
Also known as Si Gui in the Han Dynasty
devil
My cook used to
That’s how I call my housekeeper.
Don't tell me nonsense. It's not those two words.
Dead ghost is also good
right
I also feel like it’s called kindness
these two names
You can call me whatever you want
I will call you from now on
Dead Ghost Uncle
casual
I really have a talent for naming names.
Named after the stars
That
what is his name
The spy back then
In addition to the twenty-eight constellations
There are also some named after demon stars
Yuan Zhongxin, your father was
It is known as
Chiyou Flag
Are you familiar with him?
Haven’t seen each other for many years
Yu Chiyuan said
Yuan Tianguan is looking for someone in Tanzhou
Who do you think he is looking for?
River Star
The Northern River Star
It's this one
Also a spy
That's right
This person is rarely seen
At that time Lu Guannian
Sent to Xixia and Daliao
Many hidden lines
After Lu Guannian's death
Who are these people?
What position did he hold?
Nobody knows
But as far as I know
In the hands of North River Star
There is a roster
Do you think he's looking for this roster?
So I agreed to go south
Yuantianguan took refuge in Xixia
this roster
We must not fall into his hands
All the spies back then were dead
Now our secret palace
Take up the mantle of our predecessors
If the roster really exists
We have the same answer
Never let this roster
fell into the hands of the Xixia people
Yuantianguan took refuge in Xixia
this roster
We must not fall into his hands
The so-called spy
Trapped in darkness and fighting endlessly
Years of fighting against the enemy
Countless casualties
Dead people
Can't even leave a name
We're going on a long journey tomorrow
Family in Beijing
Go say goodbye today
Here we go
I don't know
When can I come back again?
Do you remember this place?
The old thief's residence
But look
It seems like a long time
No one has come back
No one knows where they are going
carefree
How nice
elder brother
I still cry when I grow up
Not afraid of being laughed at
Wait till I die
you won't die
leave me here
You are Yuan Zhongxin
Who are you
My name is Yuan Bo Fin
I am your big brother
Come home with me
People from the Yuan family have nothing to do with me
Now there is
I'll protect you from now on
With me you have a home
elder brother
Yuan Family Rebellion
The relics can only be hidden here
My brother was wronged
this world
will forget his name
you will remember him
I am also a guilty person
in this world
Except you and my brother
I have no one to say goodbye to
I now
There is no one left to say goodbye to.
Then we can't
Are you a miserable mandarin duck?
Not bitter
I never thought about it before
I'll be caught
Regret
Can I tell you if I regret it?
It's too late to regret
It's too late, it's too late
Yuan Zhongxin
I actually thought
Will you escape secretly?
Where to escape
leave us behind
Go south alone with Yuchiyuan
Me in the past
No matter how big the incident is
I always want to carry it alone
If you don't ask for help, you won't owe anyone anything.
Always thinking about this life
No debt or debt
What now
Now I find that I actually
Quite afraid of being alone
In fact, I have always been afraid
Don’t be afraid anymore
No delay or arrears
How to face the human world?
Her father
Come and help me twist it
Father Adult
I came to say goodbye
This time I went
I don’t know when I can come back
Take care of yourself
Wang family’s generation
I originally regarded you as
Family hope
If you leave
From now on, the future has been cut off.
Father, forgive me
Do you want to be loyal to the Song Dynasty?
Have you ever thought about that?
in a high position
Only then can we try our best
There is always someone in a high position
There is no shortage of Wang Kuan
If one day
You've reached a dead end
Discover yourself
All it did was a joke
You can't save anything
Nothing can be done
You will regret your choice today
If you reach a dead end
I can only grit my teeth and move forward
There is no time to regret
this way please
Dean
How did you come
I'm leaving tomorrow.
I have to say goodbye to my family today
Then why did you come to me?
in the capital city
I have no family anymore
What does it have to do with me
I'm just thinking
Should do something serious
What's serious
Xiaolu Zhangyuan
Going south this time
The journey is not close.
I know
We plan to split into two groups
Zhai Chang Yuan Zhongxin and Xue Ying
Along with Yu Chiyuan
I am Wang Kuan Xiaojing
The oriole is behind
Xiaolu Zhangyuan
Do you want to come with us?
Let's run together
All
Xiaolu Zhangyuan
you know too
This Yuan Zhongxin Xiaojing and Xue Ying
Basically a poor guy
My house was raided again.
Wang Kuan also had a falling out with his father
There is only one captain left
We still have to go with Yuchiyuan
What do you want to say
This time I went south to Tanzhou
Will I need to take a boat along the way?
Rent a carriage, eat and stay in a hotel
want money
We are also for
Mr. Xiao Lu, what are you doing?
right
Save some money
Xiaolu Zhangyuan
Jinghu South Road
More than three months
Really not enough
How much do you want?
How much property do you have in total?
Going south this time
But it's all for you
Is this true?
Here you go
This scabbard
sharkskin
There is a history
It is said to be a famous sword in the prosperous Tang Dynasty
Famous Swords of the Tang Dynasty
Your collection
Do you have a name?
name
I really don’t know the name
It's a sword anyway
I've always been reluctant to use it
Always treasured
how
try
It is said that cutting iron is like clay.
This, this, this
I have treasured this for too long
It's okay, it's okay, Dad
Just apply some oil on it
The knife is still a good knife
One more and one more
Come
It seems to be rusty
Look at this
This knife is just like a human being
It's not like the older the better, right?
It's okay, it's okay, Dad
Doesn’t this also have a scabbard?
Shark skin is so valuable
I'll get there
Replaced mine
good
By the time
Dad
Clean the knife for you
son
Look, our shop is not open either.
or
Eat before leaving
good
Your mother is not at home either
Then just eat whatever you want
good
Drink the whole drink
I can do it all
My collection of fine wine
It is a treasure
Is this wine different from this knife?
I'll take it.
I'll take it
What's wrong, dad?
son
This wine
I can't take them all out
I have to leave a jar
Keep it
I don't drink much either
This jar of wine
Can I drink it when you come back?
good
Keep your word
I'll take it. I'll take it.
Dead Ghost Uncle
You still need to reshape it?
I'm bored
Don't know what else to do
keep it
Keep it, keep it
There is emotion
You didn't find it
What you really want to do
Fame, wealth and power are all you want in the world
But that's it
boring
You said goodbye to your family
I glanced at it from a distance
Didn't come in
they were
Exchanging letters with Han Han
If I leak it
News from the South to Tanzhou
It might hurt everyone
Think so carefully
Shouldn't we spend money along the way?
Where did the money come from?
Our Xiaolu Zhangyuan
Still have some family property
Save some money
Remember to come back if you don’t use it up
Don't worry
There are so many people
No more left
Dare to fall in love with so many people
I'm the only one spending money
You are the new president.
Where are Yuan Zhongxin and the others?
They went directly to the gate of Chenzhou
Then we are all here too
It's almost time to leave
Not urgent
There is one more person
Who else?
sister
Drinking
Had two drinks with my dad
Drank too much
No
My father and mother drank too much
That's because I can't bear to leave you
I know
Xue Ying
actually
You don't have to go
Stay in Kaifeng and take care of your parents
It's also very important.
No
I have to protect you
We still need your protection
Can you beat me?
Sometimes people are not necessarily
It has to be solved by force
You have to rely on outsmarting, you know?
Then can you beat me?
Can't beat
But than you
There are so many people with strong military skills.
Not bad for you either
It's really not possible
We'll go back and pay for one.
That won't work.
except me
nobody
no one will
Risking my life to protect you
All right, all right
Stop talking about risking your life
ok
If I stay
I will never feel at ease in my life
Why are you so stubborn?
I definitely won't stay
OK
Go together
But don’t risk anyone’s life
We have to come back together
good
alright
Let's go
Walk
Where is Yuchiyuan?
What are you doing
Traveling far away
Pay homage to all the gods and lords
Bless peace
Quite particular
Sincerity leads to spirituality
Sincere
spirit
Let's go
Wait a moment
What are you doing
Traveling far away
Say hello to Lord Ma
Bless peace
this is a horse
The horse is not the King of Horses
Lord Ma, I'm sorry
Young people are ignorant
Don't blame
Okay, stop trying to persuade me.
This kind of person believes everything
I just won't believe you
Why are you following Xiao Lu, the headmaster?
Xiaolu Zhangyuan was commissioned by the Privy Council
bright future
It's very dangerous, you know?
Seeking wealth through risk
How can you ask for this?
Don't ask him
Not a word of truth
Sit down first
Why haven't they set off yet?
Why is Yuchiyuan still kneeling down?
baffling
Dead Ghost Uncle
You should take this with you too
No?
let me guess
Is this
What is your name?
particularly important friend
died suddenly
Then take this chicken
Entrusted to you
Your friend is dead and entrusted with this
Then it's been a bumpy road
It can't bear it
It's tougher than you.
They moved
Follow us
Let's go
Look at what I'm doing
You can't hear it from so far away
Be careful
It's not louder than me
Give it a moment, give it a moment
This mountain spring water
It's sweet
did you hear
hear something
The cock crows
What's wrong with the cock crow?
That's not the case
But do you feel
Along the way
Hear it every day
What's wrong
My people of Song Dynasty
Can’t you raise chickens?
That's not what I meant.
What do I want to say?
it's getting dark
Before Dark
Can we go to Tanzhou?
No need to go to Tanzhou
There is a posthouse in the woods ahead
Just get there
Wrong?
Our post house in the Song Dynasty
Always built on the official road
How could we be in the depths of this dense forest?
Abandoned post house in the early years
Now occupied by Mr. Yuan
If nothing unexpected happens
You can see Mr. Yuan in the post office
Generally speaking, it’s surprising
Stop talking nonsense
I came here to pay my respects
All gods and Buddhas will bless you
Do you believe in gods and Buddhas?
Is there anyone who doesn’t believe it?
have you seen
All these gods and Buddhas are in heaven
How can a mortal see it?
Then you haven't seen it
How do you know it's true?
How could it be if it wasn't?
So many people believe it
Logic genius
Hurry, go faster
Which way to go next?
The post house is this way
what sound