Your Highness
Everyone is here
very good
It's almost time
Ready to kill
remember
I am waiting for King Qin to escort you.
Revenge for Qingtianzi
You go down
yes
about there
Walk
Yuan Zhongxin and Wu Zangying Pang
Didn't you come to answer the call?
Qing Tianzi is in danger
Kill the thieves
Save my father
My son is filial
It’s really touching.
Not even for a moment
separate from me
stop looking
By seniority
You have to call me mother now
Sons and ministers heard
He didn't hide anything and blackmailed Pang to cause trouble.
Came in a hurry
Keep your father and king safe
real
otherwise
How dare I bring a sword to see you?
I always believe in my son
Come
Come closer
You and I, father and son, are united in our hearts
let's go out together
Kill the rebels
Why don't you come over?
There is no hiding the traitor Pang
He actually killed his father
I swear to God
This beast must be killed
To avenge my father's death
Come in and escort
The prince is drunk
Send the prince back to rest.
yes
do not worry
Brother Ning Ling doesn’t know
It was you who made his every move
told me
I only hope that the Qingtianzi will give it to the Yeli clan
a chance
Of course
I promised you
Give the Yeli clan a future
me
Always keep your word
No hidden lies
arrange escort
Arrange a banquet
No change
Not really
Call him over
yes
I have seen the Qingtianzi
Have you ever seen the imperial concubine?
Drank too much
I am terrified
Did you see the corpse outside?
They are all traitors
Minister dereliction of duty
It has nothing to do with you
The prince's handwriting
divine punishment
Turmoil in the court
Then I ask myself
If I want to kill myself
What's the best time
Of course now
Now in the palace
who can be closest to me
Of course she is the newly married princess
People who want to kill me
I need this wedding
Then I will give them this big wedding
I thought
That girl from Song Dynasty
Will I change the bride?
Princess's Guard
I have always been the one arranging it.
How do they change it?
So the Prime Minister
You have lived up to my trust
I have no second thoughts
It is even more impossible to be with those Song people
Cooperation
Believe it now
Get up
What a pity, Prince.
Didn't pass this level
Over there with the prince
The position of the prince cannot be moved lightly
these days
punish god
Move it to the prince
The prince is immoral
Only then did he attract the wrath of the gods
accumulate some public grievances
Destroy him again
Qingtianzi's methods of governing the country
breathtaking
tell your sister
put her at ease
her son
I will take the place of Brother Ning Ling
Xie Qingtianzi
Okay, go down quickly.
My wedding is not over yet
Yes Yes Yes
yes
Yuan Hao actually
be prepared
Yuan Hao used his weapons to appear and disappear
very smart
Last night's assassination was a great opportunity
all we can think of
He can also think of
so
You didn't change your identity
Think about it now
It's right to be careful
Be careful
But he didn’t tell Brother Ning Ling
Prime Minister, look at the current situation
Brother Ning Ling wants to kill him
It's not just Yuan Hao
you
I
He won't let it go
After this incident
Yuan Hao should
I trust the Prime Minister more
After these days
Assassination
But there is no chance
Wait a little longer
What are you waiting for?
Waiting for transfer
This is the situation now
Will there be any turning point?
As long as people live
It’s not the end yet
What are you panicking about?
It’s come to this point
The building is about to collapse
Life in the World
There are always more setbacks than good times
you have to remember
Only Death
Can really defeat you
Hope you give me a chance
Let me go back to Xingqing Mansion
Then I can still gather the old troops
How are you still alive?
Yuan Hao imprisoned us in the dungeon
There was no way to survive
But I never expected it
Those Song boys sneaked into the dungeon
rescued me
Yuan Zhongxin and others
And the Prime Minister secretly helps
What do they want to do?
Everything was ruined by them
Brother Ning Ling
Don't be anxious
where are they
Qizhai asked me to bring a message to His Highness
explain
say what
Said His Highness is too murderous
Wedding
Not only to kill Yuan Hao
Also kill Qizhai
They are grateful
So they are afraid, right?
They don't dare to take action, right?
they said
Yuan Hao still wants to be killed
I'm like this
How else to kill?
That Yuan Zhongxin said
There is still a transfer
Where did this turn of events come from?
newspaper
Qingtianzi
Emergency report from the army
Hurry up and hurry up
Youzhou Military Supervisory Department mobilizes cavalry
Now close to leaving the palace
Youzhou Army
Liang Gewei's daughter
Headquarters Cavalry
Already close to Helan Mountain
Du Tongjun
If there is a dispute
The consequences are unimaginable
I'm waiting for training
Where did the dispute come from?
If the Qing Emperor ordered
Let the cavalry return to Youzhou
Then go back.
Youzhou Military Supervision Department
Always loyal to Qingtianzi
Then let's train here
What's the point?
Youzhou Army rectified military discipline before
But we caught a lot of traitors
I remember
They are all the confidants of Brother Ningling
Brother Ning Ling is hateful
But now I heard
People have been imprisoned
Those traitors
Still saved a few lives
yes
Du Tongjun is kind
Let them go
Release
Brother Ning Ling is in our Youzhou Army
Have a confidant
But what about the other military supervisory departments?
Do you think he will let it go?
How much is that
They all were bribed, right?
Give these letters to those traitors
Then let him go
Youzhou pigeon
Mountains and water
two inseparable
I don't want them to separate either
If there is news
You can leave it to it to bring the letter back
Remember with your companions
In Daxia
You will never be at the end of your rope
Because of the Youzhou Army
It will always be your retreat
I can help you
There's only so much left
Qing Tianzi
The military situation is urgent
In addition to the Yuzhou Military Supervision Department
Other military supervision departments
All soldiers and horses left the headquarters
The scene is so big
nominally
It’s the same as the Yuzhou Military Supervisory Department
It's said to be a training exercise for soldiers and horses
But actually I heard
I heard that I received everything
The Prince's Clothes Order
Said to be
Prince and Qingtianzi
Confrontation in the Imperial Palace
It's about to be replaced.
Let his subordinates raise troops to serve the king
these individuals
It should be Brother Ning Ling
Last resort
Qing Tianzi
or
Let’s go back to Xingqing Mansion first.
No need
Once they all jump out, it will be easy to clean up.
I'm just afraid things will change.
What are you afraid of?
you and
The garrison who left the palace said
Camp at the foot of the mountain and wait for our military orders
Qing Tianzi
still
Let’s mobilize the garrison of Xingqing Mansion first.
If the palace guards are moved,
Afraid it will affect
Palace guard
The defenders of Xingqing Mansion must not be moved lightly
Just do it
The garrison of the palace is enough
this is a good thing
take this opportunity
The military power of these supervisors and military commanders
Take it all back
Raise for a year and a half
Then we can send troops to Song Dynasty
Less worries
But the people's livelihood in Daxia was in decline
Not one for a year and a half
I'm afraid I won't be able to recover.
I protect the people of Daxia
so many years
It's not an exaggeration to feel wronged to them, right?
That's natural
A man’s meritorious deeds should come from troubled times
If the world is peaceful
Then kill him and bring chaos out of the world
one day
Our Great Xia flag shakes the mountains and rivers
When I leave my name in the history books
These dead people
It's nothing
Qingtianzi Shengming
What did you just say the prince used?
Clothes edict
The edict hidden in the belt
There is also some literary talent
It's just too much of a belt.
Where did I get so many belts?
I'm not a clothing store owner.
I am the prince
This is all from my time in the military
last resort
How could they be so impulsive?
I heard about one
There are clothes and belt edicts
one more
See the Youzhou Military Supervision Department
So loyal
Someone takes the lead
Naturally, some people are unwilling to be second to others.
Where did the Youzhou Army get its loyalty and bravery?
All my people were plucked clean
Do not worry
Queen Mother
head-to-head confrontation
How can they be the rivals of their father?
I've been hiding it for so many years
Now it is destroyed in one day, the Queen Mother
At least it's a variable
The queen is right
You actually have the nerve to come see me
The garrison at the Imperial Palace has gone down the mountain to set up camp.
Currently in the Imperial Palace
Only ordinary guards remain
so what
Guard dispatch
The Prime Minister personally controls
So tomorrow afternoon
There are very few guards around Yuan Hao
Go there again
Join forces to assassinate
We agreed
Assassination on wedding day
Isn’t that what we agreed to do?
Now is a better time
My father’s military power is superb
Even if we join forces to attack
Can't kill him either
In fact, the layout of the wedding
no waste
We actually met the new princess
What
There's something wrong with the wine
Drugged
What medicine
This medicine can save Wang Kuan's life
Just drugged
Drugged
Can't we just poison it directly?
Yuan Hao takes the guard to test the poison
The amount of drugs in alcohol is very small
It's not a big deal if you drink one or two pots
But if you drink it for a long time
Unavoidable confusion
Weak hands and feet
Yuan Hao takes the guard to test the poison
Won't cause any trouble
this arrangement
why didn't you tell me in advance
Don’t you understand this yet?
People can't trust you at all
Then we don't have to
Collaborate again
If you don’t assassinate Yuan Hao
Is there any way to survive?
Battle tomorrow
It's the end
It’s also your last way to survive.
There's poison in the wine
Not highly toxic
Drink for a long time
Only effective
This wine
Still haven’t moved the gift from the imperial concubine’s house?
But drugged
It's Qizhai
Invisible
Now Ning Lingge
Supervising military departments in various places
mobilize means
They did it too
they just want you
Lead troops to fight
this medicine
It makes me exhausted
maybe
Died in front of the two armies
Since we want to cooperate
You can't die
what is this
Don't believe me
I often drink
I drank a lot these days
so what
so
If your body feels wrong
I can detect it
stop looking
All changed
You are alert
You really want to cooperate with me
After the wedding
I'm afraid I won't have the chance to kill you again
I want to go back to Song Dynasty with them
Danyuan Tianguan
Not dead yet
I'll always find him
After returning to the Song Dynasty
I also want to lend you this place
Climbing up
So you
The identity of the ruler of Western Xia
Better hold still
what do you want to say
I heard that on the wedding day
you despise gods
divine punishment
Not you yet
What a good thing
have you ever thought about
What if the gods surrendered to you?
Shibuyuan has been suppressed by you
And those costumes of the Sheep God
It should be in your hands too
In the past, divine messengers had their own lineage
Unrestricted
but you can let
A new angel appears
Even the gods are shocked by you
Willing to surrender
If the gods are also at your disposal
Who else can threaten
Your throne of the blue emperor
Within the palace
reset altar
Fake Messenger of God
God this thing
Who can use it?
Since people's hearts are now in turmoil
Then let the gods speak
Admit this to me
The Power of the Blue Emperor
enemy means
for my use
Wonderful
When to arrange
It’s urgent to win people’s hearts
Tomorrow
Yes, sir.
Poisoning in wine
You told Yuan Hao
He noticed it himself
Sister Zhao said it a long time ago
This long-term method of drugging
Actually it’s not easy to use
Especially those who lead troops all year round
Something strange about the body
There will always be something noticed
There is no medicine in this world
It really can
No early symptoms
Then one day
It broke out suddenly
If you really want to be useful
Still have to take some strong medicine temporarily
Yuan Hao has already decided
Fake Messenger
hold a ceremony
Wonho Present
I should already trust you
Revenge for killing father
How could you not believe it?
If it weren't for Wang Kuan that day,
I can't get through it either
this life
I owe you
If you want to take
You can take it anytime
I don't want your life
I want to kill
It's Yuantianguan
Yanei
I have a question
Yuantianguan kills uncle
Is it really for Yuan Zhongxin?
sudden change
emotionally charged
Actually calm down
Of course you can think of it
what comes to mind
You also heard what Yuan Zhongxin said
Those explanations of Yuantianguan
Actually I'm fine
Taking care of your feelings
Logically speaking
I will kill directly
Just your friends
it's good now
I kill Wei Zhuoran
There is a gap between you and Qizhai.
If it is really to make Yuan Zhongxin
Cut off contact with Qizhai
He admitted directly at that time
Killed Prince Zhao himself
It's over.
Now kill my uncle again
unnecessary
If not for Yuan Zhongxin
Then why did he start?
What we want is
Yuan Tianguan and his uncle
What kind of relationship is it?
What does this have to do with
Yanei
Let me explain first
The relationship between Yuan Tianguan and his uncle
This is just my guess
no evidence
You speak first
you should remember
Yuantian Pass was once
Lu Zhangyuan’s Demon Star
The spy back then
In addition to the twenty-eight constellations
There are also some named after demon stars
Yuan Zhongxin
Your father was
It is known as
Chiyou Flag
I know this
But what does this have to do with my dad?
Si Weixing also said
Where did the spies come from back then?
Long before the Secret Pavilion
Lu Guannian
Create your own spy
Select people at that time
Or choose among the military
Or choose a strange person among the people
Or
Prisoner
With training, you can meet the enemy
Remember
when saying this
I am here
What is the first rule of selection?
Military selection
If there is no military order from the Privy Council
How can you select people from the army?
That's the case
There should be people in the army
Familiar with Lu Zhangyuan
Exchange what is needed
you mean
My dad
Yanei
do you remember
Why did you enter the Secret Pavilion?
Because I met you and Yuan Zhongxin
Why did Master Lu choose you?
because
My father is the palace commander
If so
The head of the hospital should be the general
Children of important civil and military officials in the court
Just search them all and bring them in.
Aren't you the same?
I got him involved.
I stay in the Secret Pavilion
It's my own free will
what about you
The dean summons you
Is it just a coincidence?
That
Why did the Chancellor choose me?
Now it seems
Uncle's cruel plan
There was a plan at that time
Now that I'm ready to lose my reputation
The only thing I can't let go
It's just you
entrust
It was he who handed me over to the governor
Act in this way
Not a close friend
My father and the dean are old friends.
At that time, the commander-in-chief organized secret agents
Military selection
My father is also helping him.
cause and effect
Is it appropriate?
Makes sense
What about Yuantian Pass?
Lu Zhangyuan established a secret agent that year
With the full support of the Privy Council
What do you think of the Privy Council?
To the person chosen by the Chancellor
Can you really ignore it and not ask?
My father and Yuan Tianguan have known each other for a long time
Yanei
Your father was kidnapped
Do you think he was
What are you most afraid of?
What is my dad most afraid of?
Uncle pretends to surrender
Nature has long put life and death at risk
He is not afraid of death
My father is not afraid of death
But Yuanhao wants to force you to show up
My dad is afraid
It's me showing up
If it were you
What should you ask for then?
Wish to die
So he killed my father
It's to save me
Yuantianguan if
I have known your father for a long time
They want to kill Yuan Hao
Not necessarily impossible to cooperate
Say it again
Just a guess
no evidence
Nayuan Tianguan
why not tell the truth
wrong
He wanted Yuan Zhongxin to leave Xixia
This is also true
Connect it like this
And it does make sense
let me see
let me think again
What is the truth?
You still have to ask Yuan Tianguan
This is Jean Yuanhao
Opportunity to relax your guard
I avenge my father
Reasonable
First round of wedding
Exposing Brother Ning Ling
This round of mutiny
Another reminder of drunkenness and drug addiction
After all, who would have thought
You will do it with your own hands
Burned Webster's body
besides
a broken arm
Make the best use of everything
Better than decaying into dust
who would have thought
We are so hard on ourselves
Especially in Yanei
Go and see Yuan Hao in person
It's very likely that he'll come back alive.
So he won't doubt it
Who would take their own life?
Come for adventure
yes
how could they know
Now that we are here
I never thought about going back alive again
look
no difference
Everyone
Tomorrow's Road
Maybe it's the end
I'm very happy
can meet you
Seven fasts in one
life and death together
Why didn't the other two follow?
Broken arm
How else to fight?
My arm is broken and I'm alone
Where is the other one?
You have to stay and take care of me
Not bad for them
Now in this palace
There are not many guards left.
Most of them were transferred by me
If it is a guard
What should I do if I hear the noise and come back?
The passage in front of the palace gate is narrow
If there are reinforcements
I'll stop
good
Loyalty of the Yeli Clan
never let me down
my family
friend
partner
All died on this land
their will
I'll inherit
yes
How many heroes are there in the Yeli clan?
Died at the hands of Yuan Hao
I understand you
I'll go check it out again
Can you protect these people?
Move further
Wish you all
Immediate success
There is no hiding the insidiousness and cunning of Pang
Immortal
I will never let you go
On insidiousness
You won’t lose to Mu Zang either
I only have this one subordinate now
No threat
Kill or hide Pang?
The way to coexist
rest assured
If you don’t hide it, you won’t die.
He will definitely not let us go
So we will definitely kill him
After all, we ourselves
I still want to find a way out.
talk to smart people
It's just peace of mind.
What's this
help you wake up
Isn't the drug in the wine?
Let's go
Go see Yuan Hao for the last time
Wait and push them out first
It’s better to lose both sides
They all say he is Qing Tianzi
It’s not appropriate to never return to heaven.