Prime Minister
Things about Wei Zhuoran
let me think again
yes
I'll take my leave first.
We're getting married in a few days
Serve some snacks
I understand
Go ahead
Just one step away
You've got the body
Why did you change your mind again?
God knows he heard it again
what news
I can't snatch the body by force
Don't panic
At least you saved the Yuan family.
There is an explanation
The Yuan family was saved
But the Wei family
My father is dead
It's really urgent.
Something bad happened
What should I do?
yes
Revenge for killing father
Irreconcilable
You show up on your own initiative
Is there anything you want to tell me?
I'm only talking to you
You all go down
yes
alright
There are only two of us left
Have something to say?
I want my father's body
what would you like
unimportant
your father's body
Not important
Important
I
what to get
I'll cooperate with you
Take your companions
Leave it to me
No
Qizhai Tongxin
I will never betray my companions
Then why are you cooperating with me?
I want to kill Yuan Tianguan
Don't you want to
You have to cooperate with me to kill Yuan Tianguan
Revenge for killing father
How can you not repay it?
Makes sense
You Song people are really
So interesting
Your father's death
I also have a responsibility
Still want to cooperate with me
Kill the first culprit first
As for you
I won't let it go either
Good
Then you know
Where is Yuantianguan?
have no idea
But you can force him out
his weakness
It's his son's life
Yuan Zhongxin
As long as you set a trap
Put a few of us in dire straits
Yuantianguan must take action
Didn't you just say that?
Won't you betray your companions?
you have to promise me
Only kill Yuantianguan
Don't move them
I can promise you
Can you believe it?
That's my thing
good
Tell me about it
How do you want to set a trap?
How to force them out?
Wang Kuan’s broken arm
still there
Body hair and skin
Received from parents
Don't dare to damage
Takayuki
The most taboo thing in life
Just dead without a whole body
use this arm
You can fish people out
Kid
you mean it
Revenge for killing my father
Condolences to Mr. Wei
Where is my father's body?
I'm thinking of a solution
Excellent wound medicine
Prince Wang worked hard
And the Yuan clan
I was also rescued
They are all rebellious
Somehow they are related
Where is Miss Zhao?
At this moment
Stop wandering around
In case of discovery
We're all finished
What are you panicking about?
Aren't I worried about Miss Zhao?
You're not worried about me
Are you afraid that I will leak the news?
what news
What's wrong
Yuan Hao wants to kill Wang Kuan
My arm is burned
Can't
Don't be impulsive
This is forcing you to die
It’s not certain who will die.
This is clearly a trap.
If Mr. Yuan wants to take action
Maybe there's still a chance
It's no use begging him
You still have to rely on yourself
Too
Asking others is better than asking yourself
etc.
There's a wedding assassination coming soon.
at this time
Don't take any chances
Small Scene
I am disabled
classified as disabled
Disability
Duji third grade
People like me who lose one limb
It's a second-class disease
The disabled are not allowed to take the imperial examination
No official career in life
I'm sorry for wronging you.
I didn’t expect you to be an official
real
I know you are talented and knowledgeable
But I don't care if you are an official or not
As long as it's you
No matter what
It doesn't matter if you break an arm
It doesn't matter
That means
I am more important than a broken arm
certainly
Then what's the use of it?
Let’s come to Xixia during Qizhai
Is it for an arm?
we still have each other
Only each other
In this palace
The remaining
All can be discarded
The prince is well-versed in everything
Teach people to admire
The Prime Minister is right
The wedding is coming soon
That was the one who assassinated Yuan Hao
The best chance
It's also our last chance
No one is coming
Won't come
Want me to say
It doesn't have to be so troublesome at all
You lead the way
Rushed over and caught the person
Yuan Zhongxin was arrested
Yuantianguan will naturally take action
Then I will join forces with you
They would have discovered it
So what do you have to hide?
You only look at now
What's the meaning
After killing Yuantianguan
I will go back to Song Dynasty with them
Then what
If the family property had not been taken away
Distributed to Lingnan
My father wouldn't be here today either
The hatred of the Song Dynasty court
I haven't forgotten
Wait until I return to Song Dynasty
I will climb up at all costs
By the time
I will contact you secretly
If a war breaks out
I can also help spread some news
You want to join forces with me to destroy Song Dynasty
With your help
It's easier for me to climb up
one day
I will sit
A higher position than my father
I won't let him down
Are there any torches?
what to do
That arm is useless
you can take it back
How do I explain
I can't do it anymore
Where is my father's body?
Buried
You Song people
Isn’t it important to pay attention to burial?
foreign land
No refuge
I'll send him on his last journey
father
won't let you die
How about someone else lights the fire?
I'll give it to you
Prepare a jar
No
My dad loves the sky and the sea the most
Can't stand the cramped conditions
Collect in the altar
He will feel wronged
Today's wind
It was blowing towards the Song Dynasty
He is going home
Kid
You will definitely be a person in the future
On their wedding day
Make a move on you
Join forces with them
It's Brother Ning Ling
Originally the Crown Princess
Now she has become a princess
Are you happy?
Prime Minister
vassal
before wedding
The placement and protection of the imperial concubine
Take it up here.
yes
The new princess who has not moved to the clan is coming
what do you want me to do
Do you think Brother Ning Ling trusts you?
Your identity as a member of the Yeli clan
Will there be any hidden dangers?
Yuan Hao
Noriyoshi
I heard you this time
Always with the Queen
With the prince
Not the Queen anymore
Your wild family
It's endless.
There's always talent coming up
Why are you still carrying this?
used to sleeping
nostalgia
It’s good to miss the past
Nostalgic person
Only then will he be loyal to his old master
only
Pity
You should ask me now
What a pity
What a pity for your last name
Shame on your clan.
Where to start
The Yeli Clan
Once glorious
Decline now
You bear the surname of Yeli
shouldn't it
Should we shoulder the burden of reviving our clan?
Be a guard
obscurity
Doesn’t this count as letting down the family’s kindness?
look
If you have anything to say, just say it
If you say so, you will be punished by death.
I'll spare you the death penalty
The decline of the Yeli clan
It's because your butcher knife is sharp
Good boy
Have courage
well said
I can destroy a clan
I can too
Let a surname rise
I'll give you a chance now
Take control of military power
why me
Because you are loyal
I like loyal ministers
I also know
You are loyal to your old master
I promise you
Although I deposed the queen
But I will never kill her
This can be considered
The terms of your service to me
how
It is most rare for young people to understand current affairs
Get up
After the wedding
I'll let you take control of the military
But before the wedding
You have to do something for me first.
What is it?
Not urgent
You guys from the Nori family?
Too much
I can't tell who is who
I haven't seen you before
So identity
Still need to confirm
I know
Superfluous
Blame me
think too much
I heard you have a best friend
Selling horses in the capital
I sent for him
Get your friends together
bring people in
yes
Meet the Qingtianzi
you know me
The army returns to the city
I’ve seen your heroic appearance from afar
I heard you have a friend
Yeli Langlie
The Little Man and the Yeli Clan
No relationship
I have absolutely no sympathy for you
What am I asking you?
Villain
I know Nouriro Retsu
But with him
Just talk about horses
Never involved anything else
look up
look at this man
Who is he?
Isn't he
Noriro Retsu?
Did he commit something?
The villain must
Tell everything you know
Won't cover up
young people
Be cautious when making friends
This friend of yours is not good
Does he still want to live?
Finally making friends
Kicked out of the palace
I'll just say it
It's just superfluous, right?
Okay, let's get down to business.
Actually it's very simple
Before the wedding
You keep an eye on Brother Ning Ling for me
His every move
Just tell me everything
rest assured
Even a tiger won't eat its own cubs
I won't kill him
It's just that this kid is very ambitious
Gotta be on guard
I'm also afraid that he will make mistakes
This is also for his own good
minister
Take orders
Do your job well
The Revival of the Nori Clan
It's on you.
how do you
So simple
got used to
people alive
There are always some preferences
like you
Nothing can be seen
Either
Calm as water
ulterior motives
My beloved horse
So I got acquainted with the horse dealer just now
Another Day
Give you some good horses
Thank you Qingtianzi
Where are you hiding?
Cliff outside the window
Yuan Hao is here to win people's hearts
i heard
That horse dealer is also from Song Dynasty
no
Then why did he hide his identity for you?
I choose the name Noriro Retsu
that's because
He doesn't have many acquaintances in Xingqing Mansion
three years ago
I'm approaching this horse trafficker
In fact, he is not the only one
three years
I have a lot of so-called friends
All for this moment
so
Just asking
Yeli Langlie's acquaintance
It's all your fault for the past three years
Created connections
almost
Not afraid of anything unexpected
We know each other in Xingqing Mansion
A wild and fierce person
All gone
Cruel enough
Not all of them will be killed.
Some found reasons to move away.
Don't show your weakness
Wen Wuqi disdains joining the world
But secretly planning for me
My side
no trace to be found
If there is no war
they should be able to
Keep living
Become an old man and an old woman
The way those guys are getting older
I can't imagine it at all
quite funny
I remember that time in the Secret Pavilion
Just take it with you
yes
I heard
You fall asleep as soon as you enter class
It made even the captain angry.
People are lazy
But leave this quilt
I can't sleep no matter what
recognize the bed
In this case
Why don't you put this quilt on the bed?
How long has it been since you closed your eyes?
After Wen Wuqi and Chu Niao left,
You never rested
Yuan Hao is not dead yet
You are the only one left in Bazhai
So I have no way out
Why are you looking for me?
For Brother Ning Ling
The imperial concubine will stay here for the time being.
If needed
Just look for me
I'm not the princess yet
We're getting married in a few days
It doesn't hurt to call in advance.
The Queen is tired
Please step back first.
Be alert everywhere
Remove my order
No one is allowed to touch the princess
You two stay here
Always listen to orders
yes
Zhao Jian changed people
unnoticed
Guarding the imperial concubine
They are all my soldiers
God is helping me
wrong
It should be God helping you and me
Qing Tianzi has an impatient temper
Planning to get married before the New Year
Then there are only a few days left
Poisoned wine and sharp swords
Everything is ready
When
I will arrange
Those young men from the Song Dynasty
Stay outside the door
Responding to Zhao Jian
Walk
after
It was the prince who was ordered to do so in danger
Taking over Daxia
It’s me and the Prime Minister
Sharing power
Don't dare
Prince
The Lord of Daxia
Prime Minister
This arrangement is very appropriate
Thus
Those Song Dynasty boys
will escape safely
It's all cooperation
Each one takes what he needs
Only looking forward to the prince
Take control of Daxia as soon as possible
Prime Minister
You have worked hard
These are the personal guards stationed at the palace.
so are they
People who are secretly loyal to me
The prince also has secret chess in the palace
Hidden until now
just for this moment
You gather them secretly
wedding day
let them together
Follow me outside the temple
When the time comes, raise your troops and attack
In the name of revenge for the Qingtianzi
Kill those young men
Then
No more hidden lies
Just let these thieves
Sacrifice to my father’s spirit in heaven
Let all the ministers see it
I would rather your brother respect filial piety and love
It’s good that everyone will return to their hearts
Prince's good plan
After all, the love between father and son is deep
avenge father
as a matter of course
Qing Tianzi
Since we are getting married in a grand ceremony,
now
It’s time to worship the gods of heaven and earth
What god do you worship?
It's time for the gods to come and worship me
Qing Tianzi
Already killed the angel
And brought about divine punishment
Now the whole world knows
The Sheep Guardian is angry
In this case
What's the point of worshiping him?
The goat god wants to kill me
OK
Let him come
today
I slander God
Just want to see
What can God do to me?
If I don't die
It is God's will
Even the gods will avoid my sharp edge
henceforth
All the gods
Everyone will kneel at my feet
Qingtianzi Shengming
sons and ministers
Congratulations, Father
Brother Ning Ling
I married your bride
I owe you one
Sooner or later, I'll just give you one back.
Everything in Daxia
They all belong to the father
well said
You spend the New Year here
Let’s go back to Xingqing Mansion
Sons and ministers obey orders
Take a look
the two of us
It's clearly a loving father and a filial son.
But how could there be
So many people think
You and I are not in harmony
Father
That’s because everyone in the world has seen it wrong.
Do your job well
Prince
It's still yours
Thank you father
Get up
yes
Today's Good Date
We want to be in this temple
Three Days of Drunk
dance
Can't stop
happy
liquor
Can't stop either
Xie Qingtianzi
They are all loyal ministers and filial sons
Is there anything to be wary of?
Let's go drink
yes
You all go out
Someone coming
exist
Drink it
yes