We are lacking sacrifices.
Just a few of you are here
Brother Ning Ling is here too
The two of us are really
A loving father and a filial son
good
Give you a ride
No hidden lies
Xiao Xue
Such a big divorced palace
Hide some troops
It's not a difficult thing, right?
in this world
I only believe in myself
Retreat first
Leave it to you
your time is running out
If something cannot be done
Don't blame me for turning around and leaving
Sheep Guardian
Stop looking at it
The world's fundamental
There is no god
all fake
Killer of thieves
Bounty knighthood
Tomorrow's Road
Maybe it's the end
Just come with me
Forget about life
Seven fasts in one
life and death together
kill
you can't kill me
I just want everyone in the world
all know
Even God
You have to kneel at my feet too
Bow down to me
Divine Punishment Divine Punishment
good chance
Success
Where is the flower tree?
You deserve to sit here too
Prime Minister
kill him
Kill him and it'll be over
Prime Minister
Wonho is currently seriously injured
Kill him now
best time
Do it
Prince Conspiracy
I should work hard to kill him
Qingtianzi, please rest assured
I said something wrong
It must be that the gods are disgusted
He encountered the assassination of his own son again
It can be said that the sky is angry and the people are resentful.
from now on
There is no more Qingtianzi
No hidden lies
Eliminate evil
Catch up with Brother Ning Ling
revenge for the king
yes
Queen Mother
I killed him
you sure
you already
Kill him
So seriously injured
No way to survive
Then you are at this moment
He should be taking over the throne
why would you
run back to me
There is no hidden secret and Pang wants to kill me
Hurry back to Xingqing Mansion
Gather the old troops to reverse the situation and break the situation
Mother, go!
That's too late
No hidden lies
Do you dare to kill the prince?
The prince's crime of regicide is heinous
Only death
Prime Minister
I am willing to give up my position as prince
When Yuan Hao dies, there will be disputes
I have some prestige in the military
I am willing to help the Prime Minister take charge of power
to find a way to survive
How about just talking?
standing
Queen Mother
Did not you say
Is living the most important thing?
You feel
Does he give you a way to survive now?
He is giving it to you now
Humiliation before death
Brother Ning Ling
If we have a way to survive
to kowtow
That's no problem
But if we
There is only one way to die
So dignified
Stay in the moment
ok
The queen mother is right
She is worthy of being the Queen of Daxia.
It's not anymore.
Farewell, Prince
Queen, rest assured
It is only the prince who is plotting rebellion
I will not be rude to the Queen
It’s just that this world is chaotic
Too dangerous
Thinking about the queen's safety
from now on
Just don't leave this house
Thank you to the Prime Minister for your love
But don't worry
I will definitely live well
Because I still want to watch
What about the ending without a collector?
Queen
You go back and rest first.
Qingtianzi's side
I'll take care of it
Didn't expect that
No medicine, no treatment
That's it, Your Majesty
I can still persist to this day
How long
It's been more than ten days, right?
Are you worried about the state affairs of Daxia?
There is a minister here
Qing Tianzi can rest assured
after you die
My son is the prince
absurd
What prince?
The new Lord of Daxia
Qing Tianzi
You can relax
Brother Ning Ling is dead
From now on
No one will fight with my son anymore
Qing Tianzi
Go with peace of mind
Farewell to the passing of the Qing Emperor
You should at least pay your respects.
Brother Ning Ling will die these days
No twists and turns, right?
Brother Ning Ling
Assassination of Qingtianzi
Saw by a group of guards
I kill him
as a matter of course
from now on
Summer
It’s just that I don’t have a hidden clan
The world
correct
Where are those young men?
Yuan Hao and Brother Ning Ling are dead
did not expect
Such a difficult thing
It was actually done by you guys
The Prime Minister does not have to be humble
without you
Nor are we today
I won't make up my mind either
go on this road
history will remember
Death of the Tyrant Yuan Hao
Died by Ning Lingge
Died because I didn't hide the truth
Maybe
There will also be your names
there won't be us
Because we don't exist at all
Congratulations to the Prime Minister
take charge
Now I know the truth
we are the only ones left
yes
Only
You guys
Go further
It is within the Song Dynasty
I won't send it.
The Prime Minister will not kill us
The day of the assassination
Japanese Red Cross Society
how did you do it
calculated
Just happened to meet him
Which country believes in
How can this be counted?
It seems
It is God's will that Yuan Hao should die.
If it weren't for this celestial phenomenon
Even if you kill Yuan Hao that day
He will also be
The soldiers under his command beheaded
We all know this
so
Except for this celestial phenomenon
Where is the way you arranged to survive?
No
Just kidding
How could someone go to the road of death?
I just want to say something
Just because this celestial phenomenon is abnormal
The Prime Minister will let us leave alive.
I'm not that lunatic Yuan Hao
Daxia is just a small country
Unable to fight
from now on
We still have to rely on Da Song to live
If I kill you
Wouldn’t that mean being an enemy of the Song Dynasty?
Not worth it
kill us
It means being an enemy of the Song Dynasty
You go through life and death
Assassination of Yuan Hao
On
There must be an order from the Privy Council of the Song Dynasty
Not good
It was arranged personally by the Emperor of the Song Dynasty
this kind of thing
Can't hide it from me
Have you ever thought about it?
We want to kill Yuan Hao ourselves
It has nothing to do with the court
Absolutely impossible
If it weren't for the secret order from the court
Threats from family members
How could there be someone
risking death
Doing such a big thing
If it is to eliminate war
To protect the peace of the world
Just for this
I don't want my life anymore
Who would believe it?
yes
Only a fool would believe it.
You young people are promising
Go back this time
He must be a high-ranking official with a generous salary
Congratulations in advance from my side
look forward to
Goodbye
It's really stupid to think about it
Come along this way
No benefit gained
This has to be postponed until now
I won't wade into this muddy water
You and Webster
Have you known each other for a long time?
So you kill him
Is it to help him escape?
My new concubine
Already pregnant
Yuan Zhongxin
from now on
You and I have nothing to do with each other anymore
answer me
He doesn't answer
Wait until I'm healed
I still want to kill him
To avenge my father
I'll help you then
That
After we return to the Song Dynasty
what to do
Of course, I need to recuperate first.
What about after the injury heals?
Can't live forever
There is no goal anymore
There are ten rooms in the secret pavilion
There are several other fasts
Missing
maybe we should
get them back
Makes sense
When I was in the Secret Pavilion before
Other fasts
Several people owe me gambling debts.
You have to get this money back, right?
Why don't you go see Liang Mixiang?
Let's talk privately
No
She is the Commander-in-Chief of the Young Capital of Youzhou
I am a child of a military household in the Song Dynasty
I just hope we won’t see each other on the battlefield in the future
I'm satisfied
Then it's settled
After recovering from the injury
Let's search together
The whereabouts of the rest of the group
Not good
They still have a mission
It's quite interesting when I think about it.
Chief
What do you think
Let’s get married first
What first?
After we recover from our injuries
Yuan Zhongxin and I
Xiao Jing and Wang Kuan
Give me your kiss first
Then think about other things
Chief
Are you so direct?
For me
That's the top priority