I saw Brother Ning Ling
See you
why assassination
He also asked
he asked
I also answered
Revenge?
Human nature
He believed it
except revenge
He couldn't think of
What other reasons do we have
Want to assassinate Yuan Hao
What about those Song people?
Left behind by him
Arrange for someone to sneak into the back hall
How to poison
Naturally, I have to ask more carefully.
should
Think about this banquet
So many people are going to die
I still feel a little uncomfortable
In the mud and bones
can bloom
Then let more people die.
let this flower
Open more vigorously
You were saved by Wu Zangxuanpang
He also planned the assassination of Yuan Hao.
They are brother and sister
really for
Wild profit meets beggar's revenge
and take this risk
According to your situation in Xixia
Yuan Hao is dead
What good do they have as siblings?
No benefit at all
Then there is no reason
It can only be revenge
good
Then believe it for now
you are still alive
I am very happy
I'm happier than you
I'm getting married
what do you want to say
Congratulations
She is of the unimmigrant family
I am also a member of the Daxia clan.
Marriage between big families is reasonable
It’s a pity that men and women in this world
It's all fate
That doesn't mean
My engagement here
It's still perfect
It is said that
Yuan Zhongxin fell into the glacier
No bones left
He's not dead
I didn't dream about him
What
If he died
Will definitely come to my dream
say goodbye to me
Do you believe this?
You do not understand
This is the engagement
The order of life and death
Big things are happening now
Just cooperate wholeheartedly
The queen mother is right
wedding day
I'll take this girl to the back hall
I'd better do it
You arrange the maid
inconsistent with common sense
It will inevitably arouse suspicion
Okay, then I'll trouble my mother.
Everyone
Help my son take over Daxia
My mother and I are allies
There will be a big reward after the deed is accomplished
I heard Wei Zhuoran is coming
Yes, tomorrow morning.
I want to see him
There's no road ahead here.
The road must be walked by people
Yuanhao didn’t invite you
That's what you plan to do
Walked over swaggeringly
Watch the horse for me and don't lose it
It's not easy to tame it
Don't worry, sir.
I'll be there when I'm on horseback
You go your own way
I will dive into the darkness
Let's go
Take care sir
How many days have I left the palace?
We'll live here
This looks like the security is not tight.
Going further inside is the main hall of the Riigong Palace.
This is near the palace gate
It was built long ago.
Accommodation for accompanying officials
This Yuanhao wants to build another Wangjun
Helan Mountain is easy to defend but difficult to attack
perhaps
He really has this plan
I know you are still alive
Do not reveal my name
The gods in the outside world also have eyes and ears
Understand I understand
Why did you suddenly kneel down?
Didn't you hear what she said?
No one is talking in this room
I heard you alone
Talking to oneself
Xiaojing didn't say anything
did not hear it
Understood
This opportunity
Belongs only to me
It's a pity that you don't have this blessing
it's okay no problem
Just think I'm stupid
Qingtianzi summoned Mr. Wei
Please lead the way
Wei Sizheng
exist
We know each other
know
It's the dog
Sheep Guardian
Colluded with Liang Gewei to plot rebellion
Your son is here too
This child has been acting since he was a child
Out of place
I heard that Xingqingfu
Miracles have been reported frequently in recent days
Is this true?
really
There are sheep heads floating in the sky
What do you think
Is it really a miracle or man-made?
I guess it's people
I think so
Under the Helan Mountain
There are always fish that slip through the net.
The key is
These fish that slipped through the net
They are all friends with your son
You said they came to Daxia
Who will you ask for help?
I rebelled against the Song Dynasty
They hate me so much
Didn't come to me
I really don’t know whether I should believe you or not
Wei Sizheng
But it doesn't matter, it's not important
Believe it or not
The important thing is that the new year is approaching
before new year
You have to catch these fish that have slipped through the net
Catch it for me
But I don't have the power to arrest you
I don't care, I just want to see the result
remember
during the New Year
if i can't see
These fish that slipped through the net
I will kill your son
That's it
you
Father and son may not have seen each other for a long time.
Have a good chat
I won't bother you
remember
Your son's life is in your hands
Daddy
father
you once said to me
The final army Changying
Weak crown surrenders to the country
The man defends the country regardless of life or death
Do you still remember these words?
father
I just want to ask
You surrendered to the enemy and treason
True or False
Fake
Vehicles and cannons are easily damaged
I can’t hide it from Yuan Hao
After that I was demoted and assigned
Confiscating the house
It's all taking advantage of the situation
Why send me to Lingnan?
Because it was discovered inside
Yuan Hao’s spy is hidden in Lingnan
Eyeliner hidden in Lingnan
Lingnan
Many of the criminal ministers and officials of the Song Dynasty were assigned to me
Although Yuan Hao was an enemy of the Song Dynasty,
but he is willing
Gather the people of Song Dynasty for his use
So this is the second bitter trick
Officials knew that Yuan Hao was murderous.
If he raises an army while I'm here
It might as well be reported to the court secretly
Be prepared early
father
I knew you wouldn't be treasonous
Shouldn't I be asking these questions?
originally
I should hide it from you
But if I hide it from you
How cruel to you
father
How can I bear it?
Don't worry, Dad.
I will never reveal this
Dad believes in you
You've grown up
Father Xingqing Mansion Divine Punishment
Do you know
Yuan Zhongxin did it
He looked for me
he's fine
Very good
father
You can't sell him
It doesn't matter whether I die or not
You can have another one, too.
father
won't let you die
Dad, please don't
Qing Tianzi
Finished chatting
How was the chat?
scolded me
It's shameful to say it's traitorous
Children are ignorant
I'll try to persuade him later
Good birds still choose trees to roost in?
Things about Xingqing Mansion
I'll give you an explanation
Okay, go down.
Wei Sizheng
Come early for the banquet tomorrow.
After all the fun, get down to business
Wei Yuan
In Yuan Hao's hands
It has been locked in the apse
Yuan Hao threatened me with his life
Find out the truth about the miracles in Xingqing Mansion
how much time do you have
Years ago
That's not a few days away
Yes, it's only a few days away
When to have a banquet
tomorrow
There's enough time
uncle
I don't know exactly
Why did we come to Xixia?
But please believe me
In the current situation, only Yuan Hao dies.
Only then can we ensure the integrity of the yamen
Before the time limit expires
I won't hand you over
There will be many guards at the banquet tomorrow
So I can only tonight
bring you in
understand
Poisoning success
Stand still
If there is an accident
Assassinate immediately
Where is the girl who poisoned me?
The queen has made arrangements
Anyway
I'm only responsible for taking you to the back hall
others
I can't control it.
certainly
remember
Open less and talk less
To avoid any flaws
After father's death
What are your plans
After the matter is completed, he will return to the Song Dynasty
Good
Fallen leaves return to their roots
Noriyoshi
Take her to the maid's house
yes
Wen Shao and Chu Niao
Are they okay?
died
Don't think so yet
at the beginning
They all say Brother Yuan
Death in the Ice
Aren’t you safe and sound now?
I watched them die
Flowers
Condolences
Start tomorrow
How can I help you here?
Sister Zhao said
Just pretend you don't know about this
if we lose
There is hope of completing the assassination
It's just you
That's what he said at the time
The sneaky one in the back
you know
Is it Yu Chiyuan?
I don't need you here
Then where should I go?
Go find those mortals
If you have something to say, say it so he can't hear you.
he can't hear
In Xixia
The dragon god has such magical powers
That's it
His Excellency Dragon God
Aren’t we talking about bestowing divine grace?
After Yuan Hao's death
I will give you eternal life
Thank you Dragon God
Could you please ask me one more question?
Is it okay to pray for a child?
no no
Don't get me wrong
No, I am my benefactor.
He urgently needs this kind of magical power.
Discuss later
yes
Then I'll say goodbye first
What are you asking for a child?
He thought I was the Dragon God
What do you think?
never mind
Secret Pavilion knew it right away
That guy Yuan Zhongxin
Can do any kind of scam
At that time, I loved cheating
He's not the only one
You and Mr. Wen also like to fuck
Think about that time in the Secret Pavilion
It seems like just yesterday
yes
Secret Pavilion had classes every day at that time
I felt tired and annoyed at first
But think about it now
It was great then
yes
There is no hidden truth. This person cannot be trusted.
You should be careful
Wei Sizheng
It turned out to be the Prime Minister
Si Zheng, please come this way
Qingtianzi said
Si Zheng and his son
Today's banquet can be shared
father
I survive on my own
Don't hurt Qizhai
Qizhai assassinated Yuan Hao today
Yuan Hao has outstanding martial arts skills
How to kill?
And there are so many guards here
How to escape after the incident?
Mr. Yuan
why are you here
It's too noisy up there
Get some peace and quiet
what is this for
Life-saving
Whose life should I save?
You will know when you go up there
Won't you go?
Queen Arrives
Sit down, everyone.
The Queen Arrives
No Zangshi has ever seen the queen
Met the prince
They are all family members
Why does my sister need such a big gift?
Meet the Queen
should be respected
sit down
Everyone, please take a seat.
Kings
Everyone is here
Report to the King
Someone stabbed me
Be more detailed
There is a banquet today
There are many complicated things in the palace
I am afraid of chaos
So we arranged some more staff.
Be careful
result
What's the result?
As a result, I met a few
A boy I have never seen before
Secretly contacted the Queen and the Prince
At first, I didn’t dare to think too much.
Just sent some people
Quietly inquire
Then I learned
There are two people
Under the arrangement of the prince
Hiding on the beam of the banquet hall
Only then did I feel that something was wrong
Come and inform
Are you still there now?
It's still on the beam
The minister also sent guards
eavesdrop on conversations
These young men are from Song Dynasty
Except for the two on the beam
The queen also betrothed a girl from the Song Dynasty
Hidden in the passage of the apse
Prepare for the banquet
Kill the king with poison
Now that everyone is here
Let's have a banquet
Danger in the palace
Let's catch the assassin first.
How can we miss the wine and meat?
I'm going to a banquet
Go and kill the girl who poisoned her
Catch it for me
yes
The king arrives
No one is in the Prime Minister's house
Why is there no one?
Walk
Okay, no more time wasting
Serve wine and have a banquet
This is getting cold feet
The entire apse area
Search carefully
yes
Where have people gone?
Who are you?
In fact, if the Prime Minister suffers a loss, he will suffer a loss.
Never seen who I am
are you still thinking
Where did Xiaojing go?
You are also a Song
Don't misunderstand you and I are allies
I saved your companion's life
Actually we have thought about it
Why did you want to kill Yuan Hao?
that's because of me
Putting aside those kindnesses, let’s not talk about them
Yuan Hao is dead
what's in it for you
the answer is
No
Don’t kill Yuan Hao
What should I do to save you?
Yeah, what are you going to do to save us?
So we just
Changed my mind
Prime Minister and your sister
what do you want
And for these
what will do
Just had a baby
Another son
Mother
But there are still hidden dangers
Why
Because of the position of the Xixia Prince
Someone is already sitting
I sincerely wish my father happiness, longevity and health
never disaster
The queen doesn't have to do the work herself
We are all a family
This is what I should do
Why are you so polite?
Only the prince can be deposed
My sister’s son’s talent
Become the new prince
Then if you want to depose the prince
We must let Brother Ning Ling
And Queen Yeli
ruined
This is what you want
Prime Minister
You might as well think about it
Where did Xiaojing go?
a reminder
Or poison
No, no, no
Not so vicious
After all, I still won’t
Attack children
Just always be wary of me
This is so chilling
on this banquet
No one will poison me anymore
The poison still has to be administered
Queen
Just heard
There is an assassin hiding in this hall
How about I settle this matter first?
So as not to drink later
lost interest
Take advantage of the situation
Your people are not on the beam either
How dare you?
Prime Minister
The clear path you pointed to
We really don't dare to leave
This is
fine
It seems the rumors are wrong
Everybody, get up and keep drinking
Don't let this little thing spoil your mood
your accomplice
Not above the palace at all
exist
But not entirely
you
What are you talking about? You really are
Chief
Xue Ying
why are you here
Waiting to see Yuan Hao die
You are the one who hung the chain
Made by Wang Kuan
This side corridor is locked
how did you get in
Don't make fun of me
There is a cliff outside
how did you get in
What to do if someone finds out
What's the meaning
Someone set a trap
We'll wait outside the trap
Advance, attack, retreat and defend
Although I don’t understand
Will you take action later?
possible
That's good
Don't kill me anymore
The Prime Minister is anxious to death
Not that anxious
That’s it
In fact, it means the same thing
Let bygones be bygones
We can still cooperate
What's the cooperation?
What do you think, Prime Minister?
Brother Ning Ling is one
what kind of person
Not as brave as Qing Tianzi
Cruel but cruel
What do you think
If Brother Ning Ling takes power
people like us
Can you leave Xixia alive?
actually
Let me tell you something from my heart
What does it have to do with me whether you die or not?
What if Yuan Hao died?
Brother Ning Ling takes over
Prime Minister and your sister
what will be the result
The matter of folk unearthed stone tablets
Return to the divination garden to take care of it
You read it to me
What is written on the stone tablet?
above this
They are all disobedient words
I dare not
taboo for the venerable
Loyalty can be learned
Shiboyuan recently
Contribution to calming the people
Wine should be given
Come
Xie Qingtianzi
Alcohol is highly toxic
There is a stone tablet on the beam
It seems there is really an assassin
What does the queen think?
Assassin Vicious
Please also ask Qingtianzi to avoid
hide
Then kill them
Otherwise it'll be fine
I'm afraid it's hard to find.
Still need to look for it
I let them come out on their own
I'll kill him now
Don't be Qing Tianzi
It's up to you whether to save me or not.
Calm the wrath of the blue emperor
Qing Tianzi
Please don't kill my son
Pull it down
father
Qing Tianzi
Don't kill my son
father
Save Yanei
Just wait for this sentence
son
Daddy
You can't kill my son
Yanei
Go fast