Yuantianguan’s purpose of coming to Tanzhou
Not just looking for
What about Polaris?
Nayuan Tianguan
Why do this?
What about natural disasters?
how could I know
Will it
This is how to find Pollux
Right
I don't understand
What does this have to do with finding someone?
According to the dead ghost uncle
This Polaris star is not easy to find.
Yeah, and then what?
Looking for someone in Yuantianguan
The details he cares about
Will it
It’s all related to Polaris
Have you searched every room?
There are books in the house
I found them all.
Not in the book either
With a secret message or something?
What kind of books do you have?
There are all kinds of books
poetry
Annotation
Miscellaneous notes
Wu Jin
How many are there?
What is the proportion
I didn't count this
Among ten books
Five of them are witchcraft books
don't you think
Is this a bit much?
The Theory of Disasters in the Five Elements
and sorcery
Originally from the same lineage
You said this Yuantian Pass
He did it for no reason
What are you doing all this for?
What does Xiao Jing want to say?
I'm afraid of saying something wrong
It's okay, it doesn't matter if you're right or wrong
If you have an idea, say it
Would it be less complicated?
Maybe
He just likes these things
Only then can I read these books
get these objects
Yes
What Xiaojing said makes perfect sense
we started
That's what I thought too
but not like this
why
Because in every room
All these books
A person can be said to be a preference
Everyone has
It's more like a collective effort
Looking for clues
and
Yuan Tianguan is surrounded by Xixia people
The Xixia people had their own gods
They can't
Run to the territory of the Song Dynasty
to study these things
Take a look
Small Scene
I can already draw inferences from one instance.
Research disasters
Related to Polaris
That is to say
Beihexing is also studying this
Or
Where the star Pollux appears
There are natural disasters
Yes
If we talk about cutting off the dragon's head
Related to Polaris
So the Xixia people
Worship these five evil elements
You can guess why
Treat disaster with disaster
That's right
Pollux is related to natural disasters
And the Xixia people were also superstitious
So they are afraid
So worship this five-element vision
I want to borrow
The so-called power of disaster
Resist crisis
I see
Sacrifice habits of the Goat God
It's also the same truth
Please be more safe.
There is progress in the office
What about Yuantianguan people?
Why are you missing?
It’s the same problem just now
Yuantianguan comes here
for what
Find the Northern Star
Has he already
Found the whereabouts of Beihexing
So just left here
there is a question
A natural disaster is a natural disaster
There is no evil in the world
I know this
The Northern Star
There is disaster wherever you go
Why?
because because
because
Depends on human effort
Pollux is causing man-made disasters
So scary
The one who cut off the dragon's head was also Beihe.
Just returned to the village
The faucet is missing
Yu Chiyuan was frightened
I just found a chance to knock him out.
The faucet is missing
Isn't that dangerous?
Nothing will happen to the damn uncle, right?
River Star
If Yuantianguan
The whereabouts of Polaris have been found
Doesn't that mean
Is he faster than us?
People in the village said
Who cut that dragon statue?
A student from Yuelu Academy
in ten books
Five of them are witchcraft books
What about the rest?
There are all kinds of miscellaneous books.
yuantianguan
Why do you need to read these miscellaneous books?
He can watch whatever he likes
But there are books in every room
so
Xixia people also read these miscellaneous books
Think about it carefully
What about these books?
All have one thing in common
I just flipped through it casually
Didn't look carefully
Chief, you know
I am destined to commit a crime
I feel dizzy when I read the words
So just tell me
Is the answer good?
all these books
All come from Tanzhou literati
And these people who write books
There is also one thing in common
They all came from Yuelu Academy
It’s Yuelu Academy again
Yuan Tian Guan is at Chabei River Star
every book found
All from Yuelu Academy
This direction couldn't be clearer
Cutting off the dragon's head will bring disaster
They are also students of Yuelu Academy.
all clues
They all point to Yuelu Academy
That's right
Then we also have to enter the academy
Pretend to be a student
No
not just students
if we
I want to take Yuelu Academy
Check it thoroughly
Just by being a student
I'm afraid not
What are their identities?
Wang Kuan, you are here to give lectures
Directly serve as a teacher
Wollu Academy
There is a plaque inscribed by the late emperor himself
Extremely strict in academics
It is not easy to fake the position of lecturer
There must be nothing wrong with your knowledge
question of identity
Leave it to Lu Nanshan
Then I'll try
And me
Small Scene
Wolulu Academy and Secret Pavilion are different
They don't accept female students
Would you like to go to the kitchen?
Okay, I'm good at this
Xue Ying takes a nursing home position
good
Nursing home lectures and kitchen
All aspects are available
Then the three of us
when a student
No way
Yanei
You are the only one who is a student
What about you?
Actually about the academy
have a place
Already used by all of us
Ignored
Didn't take care of it
Which
parents
What's the meaning
We Qizhai do things
Always
Watertight
Zhao Jian
sacrifice something
Both of us
be a parent
This is interesting
You two actually
its not right
Whose parents are you two?
Yanei
You are the only one who is a student
No way
I am your father
this
It's your mother
We are a family of three
Have fun
This makes it very real
your age
How can you be my parents?
This is very unreasonable
Will anyone believe me if I tell you?
It is completely reasonable
How is it reasonable?
Suppose there is a student
You are this student
your biological mother
Leave early
So your biological father
Renewed the string
Reasonable or unreasonable
Zhao Jian is so beautiful
Your father married her
Reasonable or unreasonable
Chief
Don't be so happy first
how about you
Then your father passed away too
The girl you have now
Also played a new chord
So the two of us
Although with you
There is no direct blood relationship
But they are still your parents.
Reasonable or unreasonable
Your biological mother died early
Then your father passed away too
So the two of us
Although with you
There is no direct blood relationship
But still
Your parents
Reasonable or unreasonable
This is wrong
look
Wang Kuan found it unreasonable
To remarry after losing one's wife is to renew the relationship
If I find you again, I will remarry.
right
Wang Jianshu said this
All the loopholes are plugged.
Why do you have to pretend to be a parent?
It's not necessary
child
Think about it carefully
Should North River
The same generation as the dead ghost uncle
his age
Even if you are young
It is impossible
Young like us
That's true
Since you are this age
It has to be related to the academy
is it possible
Is the student’s parent
possible
Does that mean someone has to
Pretending to be a student’s parent
How about investigating from this angle?
It seems to make sense
Yanei
I know you feel awkward
It's really awkward
Zhao Jian and I are also very awkward
this kind of thing
It really makes it difficult for us
Very sad too
but
Forced by the situation
We are also for
Investigate the North River star
It’s also for the sake of righteousness
We all have to hold on
Then the good thing is settled like that
But I always feel
It still doesn’t seem right
next topic
Before we entered the academy
First you have to
Yu Chiyuan’s situation is clarified
What happened to Yu Chiyuan?
First
we need to know
Is Yuchiyuan lying?
if he starts from the beginning
Just lying to us
Then all our calculations
There may be defects
That
Of course it's unlikely
second
That dad of mine
It might be a bit difficult to deal with
So just to be on the safe side
if possible
Still have to make a secret move
Buy Yu Chiyuan
but he looked
Very loyal to your father
But he is afraid of ghosts.
You have to pretend to be a ghost
The word "yanei" is used correctly.
Small Scene
Do you want to be a fairy?
Everyone in the yamen held on.
I can do it too
I
Everyone deserves the name Qizhai
its not right
I suffered a loss
Is it the same thing?
Xue Ying
I didn't break your head
There is no trace of Yuantian Pass now
perhaps
There will be clues if you go to Yuelu Academy
We really have to sneak into the academy
Just need to change my identity
Change identity
How can it be that easy?
yes
We are in Tanzhou
No acquaintances
Difficult
I'll arrange it
Xiaolu Zhangyuan has close friends all over the world
At least I have one
The identity of the Deputy Privy Councilor
I must go there myself
Guiyuan Army Camp
Not difficult
What about us?
You just stay here
If traces of Yuantian Pass are found
Get it now
Rest assured, Xiaolu Zhangyuan
I'm sure I'll kill my relatives out of justice
Better remember what you said
adult
I'm in town on business
you stay here
yes
Si Weixing and Yu Chiyuan
mysteriously missing
I hope not
What's wrong with you again?
Definitely stay here
Qizhai and others
What was said and done
Remember to tell me when you come back
clear
Pei Xuan
Han Duanzhang's incident
without me
your whole family
Everyone will be involved
Your kindness is unforgettable
Tanzhou is done
The so-called kindness is wiped out in one stroke
Do you agree?
What's the name of the Commander-in-Chief?
Even if there is no kindness
The villain is also willing to follow the leader
My Pei family has prospered
All hope is on the head of the academy
Just have this idea
very good
Mr. Pei didn't follow him into the city.
What is this for?
Second place
Mr. Lu this time
Take me to Tanzhou
You should use my identity
after all
My sister is also a member of Qizhai
I am here
Mr. Lu can control my sister
Control my sister
You can threaten Wang Kuan
You see it quite clearly.
The villain follows here
It’s also a helpless move
After all, with my status
I can't afford to offend Mr. Lu
Of course I can't afford to offend you either.
so what
Mr. Lu has entered the city now.
No matter what you do
I'm here
You will be a little worried to some extent
Please take a look, you two
This is a water bag
This is a magic trick
Look again,
This is sweat medicine
Why do you bring this?
Be prepared when you go out
What are you doing?
I'll take a nap first
Don't bother everyone
Xiao Xiaojing, this younger brother
A bit interesting
completion
It's over. It's over.
Dragon God is angry
The Dragon God is definitely angry
Mr. Yuan is gone
Xue Ying is gone too
what should I do
sorry Sorry
sorry
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Huang Wei
Lord Huang Wei bless you
Get rid of rats
I am most afraid of big rats
You're welcome
Just ran away
Wait a minute
There are two more words
Go fast
who
Wang Kuan
Why are you in Tanzhou?
Are you stalking us?
What are you asking for?
No breath
died
Pei Jing
Why did you come to Tanzhou?
How did you find this place?
Xue Ying
Wasn't it Wang Kuan just now?
No way
Just ran away
Really scared
Something bad is happening.
Haunted
What's wrong, don't be afraid
speak slowly
Wang Kuanren
Crack!
died
The so-called life and death
But in one thought, I
Are you Pei Jing?
Why did you come to Tanzhou?
Where is Xue Ying?
How come you can still talk like this?
Why are you back?
Didn’t you go to worship God?
That's right
Has the Dragon God not forgiven you?
That must be because he is ungrateful
It hurts us
become like this
Don't, don't, don't come here
do not come
who the hell are you
Give me my head back
I see
Xue Ying said he saw a dragon shape appear
obviously
Are you possessed by the Dragon God?
I swear to God
I didn't take your head off
I didn't take it either.
at this point
You should know very well
Could it be
You want me to get the faucet back?
Otherwise it will
receive the same treatment as them
punish
but
But you have great powers
Why did you choose me?
Yes, why?
why
I see
What do you unserstand
Mortal things must be done by mere mortals
I have believed in various gods since I was a child
at this point
No one else can compare to me
So you look for me
It's a test for me
Choose me again
is not it
You are quite smart
My greatest characteristic is that I am smart
Reversal of life and death
Manipulate the time
Then you now
know what to do
eyes closed
fainted
Small Scene
You did a good job
In fact, most of it is him
Guessed
People
It’s easiest to lie to yourself
sharp
Xue Ying
dragon
dragon dragon god
What dragon god?
Xue Ying
Why is he here?
where is this
This is Tanzhou
Tanzhou
Why did it appear in Tanzhou?
What do you think
I was still in Kaifeng just now
How did you end up in Tanzhou?
Then do you remember
how did you come
I don't remember at all
God's Power
It's really otherworldly.
woke up
Xiaojing, why are you here?
I do not know
Appeared here in the blink of an eye
suddenly appeared
you are crazy
People are thousands of miles apart in Kaifeng
Why did it suddenly appear?
Just that
What
Shut up
What's wrong
you didn't hear her
hear something
Keep your mouth shut
I know
What do you know
nothing
Small Scene
How did you get here?
I do not know
Stop asking
people suddenly appear
Why can't you ask
let me tell you
She is possessed by the dragon god
Do you believe it?
you ate the wrong thing
Why are you sleeping here?
The Mongolian sweat medicine is pretty strong
Slept pretty well
Mr. Lu is back
Not back yet
But before he comes back
Let's discuss it
If he comes back
what are you going to say
nothing happened
Then why are you helping us?
After all, my sister is also in Qizhai
Then follow Lu Nanshan all the way
What do you want to do?
nothing
Just timid and obedient
Are you afraid of Lu Nanshan?
Taking into account the relationship between siblings
Just in case, always choose one
What should you do?
Find Yuantian Pass
Find the leader
The faucet was broken by Mr. Yuan
Mortal things must be done by mere mortals
If you can accomplish this
I will give you eternal life
do not worry
Let’s come to Tanzhou
I'm looking for Mr. Yuan.
you go alone
Myself
Row row row
It's not good if there are too many people doing this kind of thing
I know
I'll go find it myself
My business
Do not tell others
clear
Especially Yuantianguan
OK
His Excellency Dragon God
Can I replace
Mr. Yuan, please give me a favor
If he really cut off the dragon's head
I have one anyway.
A small feat in retrieving the faucet
or
Please forgive Mr. Yuan for once
After finding Yuantian Pass
See you at Yuelu Academy
Wollu Academy
Row Row
Quite easy to deceive
He is afraid of ghosts.
so these things
I really can't believe it.
Xiaojing, you did a good job
real
But it was all taught to me by Brother Wang.
for example
Action
And your expression should be more serious
I studied very seriously at that time
Wang Kuan is a person who can’t lie
teach you these
your relationship
What happened to the relationship?
Quite clever
Yu Chiyuan took the initiative to find Yuan Tianguan
Even if this secret move has been made,
After Lu Nanshan comes back tomorrow,
We should be able to successfully
Infiltrate Wolulu Academy
but
They can’t all be students
it's simple
Xiao Xue
You go back and pretend to be my book boy
Am I not a nurse?
Nursing home is unreasonable
It is only right for a scholar to lead a scholar
Does it fit
Just don't draw the knife randomly
besides
Be careful
I changed my name
Don't make a mistake
what is it call
Wayne
OK Wayne
You are confused
Call me Master Wayne
OK, Master Wayne
Mainly because they are too senior
Otherwise you will call me master
They are all temporary status
No matter what you call it, it’s the same
no the same
happy to hear
One final explanation
This trip south
You must find Yuantian Pass
otherwise
Yuan Zhongxin’s crime
But it can't be washed off
And don’t forget
The mission to kill Yuan Hao
we are not done yet
If you can convince Yuan Tianguan
Let him help us eradicate Yuan Hao
eliminate war
Not a bad idea
I'm afraid that he will be determined to serve Xixia
Of course it would be best if we can cooperate
But all our things
Still have to go first
Think about the worst
Another point
Polaris has not appeared yet
If you really encounter
Don't take it lightly
Let’s not let Beihexing
Fall into the hands of Yuan Hao
That's what it means
clear
besides
The whereabouts of the dead uncle are unknown now
He is so skilled
also disappeared without a trace
It can be seen that the road ahead is difficult
As the name suggests
Wollu Academy
Built at the foot of Yuelu Mountain
At first there were only about sixty students
Fortunately, Shan Changzhou style
Valued by the late emperor
Therefore
Middle gate plaque
Four characters of Yuelu Academy
It is the late emperor’s personal inscription
The academy became famous as a result
The number of students has already exceeded 100
Tell you so much
Just hope you
able to act with caution
Don't make a big mess
Don’t worry, Xiaolu Zhangyuan
Our Qizhai
He is the least likely to cause trouble
Nothing will go wrong
Handwritten by the late emperor
It's really rare
You should be able to sell it for a lot of money
This can also be sold
Someone will definitely collect it
It's not easy to take
It's not impossible
Go back and find a fake to hang up
Isn’t this just small talk?
Pay attention to your identity
We are now
After all, I am also a parent.
Evil Son
You want to piss me off
This is obviously what you said
You still talk back?
Go Go
Stop it
Go in first
make preparations
If Beihexing is really hiding in it
I'm afraid it's very hidden
Never easy to find
what to write
real or fake
What did you just say?
How can there be such a thing?
This little girl is not very old either
Willing to work in the kitchen
Pay off debts at home
It's not easy either
What about the job of the kitchen?
will you do it
I'm used to it all
That's good
This kitchen is too much work
I was saying there is a shortage of people
what to do
Just tell me directly
There's no water in the tank
Go get some water
Brush that pot
good
What's wrong? I can't carry it.
No
you just said
There are quite a lot of students in this academy.
That's quite a lot.
The daily food
I guess it's quite a lot.
This is delivered every morning
This is all our work
yard
What don’t you raise?
For example, chicken
Naturally, they are raised
No wonder I just saw one at the door
Did you see it
There are many scholars in this academy
Our chicken can't be outside
I have to go check it out
Uncle, do you know Beihexing?
What's the meaning
he can't hear
Who are you?
Dare to ask
Is this Mr. Wayne Wei?
it's me
Brother Wei, my surname is Yu
both students
He is also the Secretary of Zhaishe
Inside the house
One matter
You can tell me anything
Come, let me take Brother Wei to Zhaishe
You just said he couldn't hear you
Your Excellency is
this
It's the dog
Please also take care of Yu Sijian
You are his father
No, I'm not his father.
I am him
Father
The academy is rigorous in scholarship
The position of lecturer is not easy to arrange
We can only let Wang Kuan temporarily take charge of the book.
Worked at Yushu Pavilion
Benefits are
No one restraint
Easy to move
I see
First the stepmother and then the stepfather
Although not biological
But at least
He is also our son
I just want to find a good way out for him
So I sent him to
This academy is here
Rest assured,
The academy has its own responsibility to teach and educate people
Zhou Shan has a long history of learning from ancient to modern times
I will definitely help your son to change his mind.
Who is this
book boy
It’s better to take it first
Mr. Wei went to settle down in his residence.
You just
Said he couldn't hear
yes
If you are interested
Just put money on the table
The academy doesn't care
Elders from surrounding villages
Set up a stall here by yourself
Disaster in the village at the foot of the mountain
Mountain people have no way
Chief Zhou Shan said
As long as you don't enter the lecture hall
Not entering the house
harmless
How much money can you make from this?
What happened to Polaris?
Beihe is a star official
Affiliated to Jingjuku
I know this
I just want to ask
you know here
What are you selling?
This is not clear
I haven't bought it
How long has this stall been here?
This uncle comes often
Just keep it there
Isn't it?
Wayne
replace old with new
old number 210,000
Four thousand seven hundred and sixty four
The old number is 360,000
Eight thousand eight hundred and ninety seven
New number 3.86 million
Seven thousand nine hundred and forty
Old number fifty-three thousand nine hundred and seventy
New number fifty-five thousand five hundred and forty
The old number and the new number are all sixty
Pollux returns to its place
This sounds like some kind of calculation
I feel dizzy just listening to it
I don't understand either.
this
This is rich
I can’t bear such flowers either.
fine
It's not my money anyway
Just treat it as disaster relief
So pitiful
it's the same
It feels like some kind of puzzle
who knows
Maybe it's just written to deceive people.
Let's go
Send our son to Zhaishe first
Over there is the lecture hall.
The daily teaching sessions are all there
Go further inside Yushu Pavilion
Come to the Zhaishe
Most of the houses here are shared
Since Mr. Wei loves Jing,
Pay more
Yes
Arrange a separate room
only
It would be a waste to live alone
not alone
Even if you add the book boy
Only two people
We both live there too
I'm mainly worried.
Don't worry about him
Can I stay with him for a while?
There is precedent for this
I'm mainly worried about him.
Okay, it's just ahead.
Let's go
Gone Wayne
why are you here
How could it suddenly disappear?
What's wrong
Stop looking for it
What
Leave here and don't look for Pollux
have you met him
you at this moment
Shouldn't meet Pollux
Why
It's not you who are looking for him
It's him looking for you
I do not understand