It’s time for chicken soup too
Yeah
The chicken soup has been simmering until now
It's time
Yeah
That little scene, let’s go
Go help your mother with some work
Excuse me
Let's go out for a while
Walk, walk, walk fast
A Xuan
You accompany the prince.
I'm going to check out the chicken soup
Prince Wang
fine
Sit down
daughter
close close
Come
Come sit down baby
daughter
father
long time no see
thank you
father
You have gray hair again
This is not important
You and Prince Wang
What step have you reached?
No need to hide your family
Tell it like it is
Love each other
Have vision
The son who can catch Wang Xianggong
It is indeed our little scene.
Although it is impossible to tell that the matchmaker is marrying
You can always make an outdoor room
yes
A worry-free life
What kind of outer room?
What is the identity of Wang Xianggong?
You can still be our in-laws
Yes, the Wang family has talked to us
People are also reasonable
Not trying to break you up
As long as you don't have a name
We can still be together
It doesn't have to be this way
Mr. Wang is too polite.
My parents are old.
Seeing that you can find a home
I'm also happy in my heart
The Wang family has sent word
He said that as long as you can take this step back,
can make your brother
Entered the Sixth Ministry as an official
There is a real seal
From now on, it will never be the same again
Official status without power
Reunion
That's all you tell me
this
This is business
right
Your brother's future
It's all on you.
yes
right
Your brother
It's all up to you
can hear
Good to go there
Come, come, come
Go over there and say
daughter
No
you agreed
actually
so-called status
I don't care
The legal wife is also good
Even the outer room
As long as I can be with Brother Wang
enough
Isn’t that the truth?
The children have grown up and become sensible
yes
Even if you have no status
I should call you brother-in-law
It really doesn't matter
But I can't promise you
Xiao Jing
Don't be confused
yes
Let's go, let's talk over there
Walk
Brother Wang told me
We want to come together
It won't be easy
I promised him
We have to face it together
The difficulties and obstacles in this world
He doesn't give in
I won't give in
child
You must understand
yes
You can't
Marry into the Wang family in a formal ceremony
Don't be too greedy
Make an outdoor room
Live peacefully
Yes
Is it not good
Xiao Jing
Think about your home
Think about your brother
right
If he can enter the six departments
Then he has unlimited prospects
yes
But I can't let down Brother Wang
How do you call this a letdown?
Can't you be together?
Yes
But this is different
Xiao Jing
We are all for your own good
The Wang family will not recognize you
right
Brother Wang recognizes me
enough
you
Parents
sorry
Even if you hate me and blame me
Only this thing
I will never give in
if not
I can't be with him
Standing side by side
Prince Wang
Mr. Pei
Don't dare to take it
You and Han are broken
There has been correspondence
Had
I see
late night visit
Sorry to bother you
Small Scene
let's go
This little scene
How did she become like this?
She used to be so obedient
Really
Princess
Slower
Prepare some hot rice porridge for me
It's always hot
I'll bring it over right away
Prepare another carriage
It's not day yet
I have to go out now
hear me out
Put blankets on the carriage
When driving later
I will rest in the car
Wake me up when you arrive
It's better to get some rest before going out.
besides
I have to trouble you with some things
good
Princess
Here we are
Princess Zhao, the head of the court, is here
I see
It's really unexpected.
Princess Zhao actually came
I'm not in a good mood
I won't be polite with you.
Look at you like this
You should have a good rest
I Yuan Zhongxin
Leave it to you these days
What happened?
what do i want to ask
You catch him
Definitely trying to get it from him
get something
It doesn’t matter what it is.
But I believe
You don't have an answer yet
why do you think so
I know Yuan Zhongxin
His mind is beyond ordinary people
no matter what you want
If he doesn't want to answer
You won't get anything
Princess Zhao came to visit in person
Just to talk to me
Yuan Zhongxin's Mind
I can persuade him
you
I am the most suitable candidate
betray him
you can let me try
Excuse me then
what do you want
I want to help him
you do not need to worry
In my current state
How is it possible to rob a prison and save someone?
what we want is
Where are the Yuan family members?
Is there anyone in the court?
Cooperate with Yuanjia
The most important thing
Where is Yuan Zhongxin’s father?
good
I see
I'll ask him
Not urgent
Take a break first
Need not
Aren't you afraid that he will hate you?
Does he hate me?
What does it have to do with you
Please lead the way
The princess’s current physical condition
It's really not appropriate to come here
This kind of place
There is no suitable time to come
What is my original intention?
I don't want to execute
But this is the Privy Council
I can't interfere too much.
not to mention
The Yuan family is very involved
Yuan Zhongxin is now
the only clue
I see
maybe you will say
Yuan Zhongxin is innocent
But you know
This treason
But the crime of killing everyone
Even if he is innocent
He also has to admit his guilt and punishment
And this life
Time is running out
I know
so
Advise him well
Let him tell everything he knows
This is actually saving him
at least
How long are you going to keep talking nonsense?
Ready
You guys wait for me outside the cell
rest assured
Even if I'm crazy
I want to save him.
You can also rush in immediately
no way
I can only tighten his hand
Otherwise he will untie it himself
Yuan Zhongxin
You came
If I had known I would have washed my face
I look ugly like this now
I washed him
Who asked you?
fine
God will wash your face for you
They asked me to ask you
Do you know where your father is?
I really do not know
I trust you
them
Let you ask me something
I want
Find a way to make it up a little bit
Make it easy for you to do business
the weather is nice today
yes
sunny
Quite suitable
suitable for what
After returning to Kaifeng
I have been kneeling before the soul
Never rested
Because I want to apologize to my father
What are you apologizing for?
Yuan Zhongxin
I'm too willful.
What about these days?
I asked my family to help me
Did a lot of things
they were all frightened
Because it's during the funeral
things i asked them to do
It's all against etiquette
Maybe you'll get struck by lightning.
What's so serious?
I redid two birthday posts
this is mine
this is yours
That's right
I made one for you too
If there are some in it
Errors and Omissions
You better not be angry with me
Just bear with it
Why do you make a birthday message?
Yuan Zhongxin
Let’s get married
What kind of method is this?
not my business
Just handed the person over
Why do we need to get married?
how could I know
Then I'll go in and stop you.
Listen to what they have to say
you
Say it again
I heard wrong
Yuan Zhongxin
Let’s get married
here
Now
Didn't I tell you?
The sun is very good today
natadogina levy
Welcome this
Nothing can be done
Save it
lifelong events
Just save it
Why not?
I thought it was normal
I am the best
unruly
What about that one?
I didn’t expect the critical moment
You are much crazier than me
Then you promised me
I want to think about it
What do I have in mind?
Of course I do
Look at what you look like now
You can’t even hold a scarf during worship, right?
Then you have the right
Just find a loser
Then I’m not at a loss
I owe you first.
Are there any scented candles?
What do you say?
No wine either
Forget it
forgive them
What kind of broken cell is this?
Being married is so awkward
forgive them
Let me discuss something with you
All the property is yours to take care of
Isn't this nonsense?
you have nothing
It's definitely my responsibility
I owe it first
Let's talk business
My father passed away
I'm still in mourning period
So we are talking about this marriage?
It can only be considered tentative
After the period of mourning is over
Talent counts
Makes sense
So we are now
Not considered a couple yet
Not yet
Yayuki
This is going to suddenly make me change my tune.
I'm still a little used to it
It's true that I'm not used to it
This private contract is settled
According to the laws of the Song Dynasty
Even private deeds are subject to deed tax
How to collect this?
have no idea
Forty articles per pass
That's called the cattle and horse tax
How to calculate marriage deed tax?
Various laws of the Three Divisions
No tax on private marriage contracts
The Song Dynasty really wanted to collect this kind of tax
It should have been over long ago
Long live the Song Dynasty
Borrow a knife
Salary
give her
It's all been like this
Do you still care about a knife?
Birthday messages were also exchanged
The private contract has also been finalized
There has to be a witness, right?
look
concentric knot
Think of it as a wedding ceremony
The ceremony of bunking
It's for couples to worship each other.
In the bridal chamber
You only feel it now
Isn't it inappropriate for etiquette?
Too
Yuan Zhongxin
What about the keepsake?
I accepted it
This private contract cannot be changed.
Thousands of miles apart
The erosion of time cannot change it
In charge of this
Just take it as a witness
OK
The ritual has become
Kissed too
Mrs. Yuan
Should I persuade him to do something?
lied to you
Borrow an excuse
Otherwise, how could we see him?
Then you before
Why hand him back?
This matter is unreasonable
Ridiculous
I have a weird temper
Whatever you think, you will do it.
Please bear with me
OK
never mind
Seeing you two
For the sake of separation and death
I won't pursue
What do you mean
I said
Treason is a crime punishable by execution
Even the princess, you don’t care about him
What's the use of having him?
He will be taken to the execution ground soon
beheading
Is there anything else to say?
Xiaolu Zhangyuan
Aren't you afraid of long nights and many dreams?
What's the meaning
what do you think
I don't care
Xiaolu Zhangyuan might as well hurry up
good
as you wish
three days later
Immediate execution
Sure enough it's fast enough
do me a favor
explain
I really don't want to die
three days later
Call Wang Kuan and the others
Rob a court
The Jie Dharma Hall is crowded and lively
good
Three days
Can you hold it?
I try my best
Xiaolu Zhangyuan
Then see you in three days
Think it over
Privy Council Court
Any action is a capital offense
Nothing can be done
Who made the private contract?
I'll keep the birthday invitation for you.
You Qizhai
Are they all so lawless?
Laughing
Is the princess returning home?
Go to Wang Kuan's house
Wang Kuan
At the residence of Wang Bo, who participated in political affairs
yes
Thousands of miles apart
The erosion of time cannot change it
Yanei
How about it
The government has asked
After Wang Kuan went out last night,
never came back
There's no one in Xiaojing's room either
Xiao Xue
Good thing
They must have eloped.
impossible
We still have to save Yuan Zhongxin
What about that person?
This is the city of Kaifeng
How can people disappear like this?
two persons
Princess Zhao is here
Chief
last night
We're going to find you, you know?
I know
Then why don't you see us?
Is there anything to eat?
anything else
Slowly, slowly, slowly
Haven't eaten for a long time
Not good to eat too eagerly
Haven't eaten recently
I have no appetite for the wake.
The cook of the Wang family
nice
The consistency of this porridge is just right
He really has a hand
Their bamboo shoot meat sandwich
The marrow cake is amazingly made
I was so full last night
Yeah
I'll try it later too
Said it was the cook
Vegetarian meat sandwich is better
Better than minced meat
There must be mushrooms inside.
mushroom
Talk about something serious
right
I was confused when I saw you eating porridge.
Chief
I have something to tell you
Just right
I also have something to tell you
Then you first
Yuan Zhongxin asked and beheaded three days later
Where is Wang Kuan?
call him over
Discuss it together
that's what i want to say
Wang Kuan is missing
Even with Xiao Jing
Why is it missing?
Wang Kuan went to Xiao Jing's house last night
Never came back again
Walk
where to
Didn’t you say you were going to Xiao Jing’s house?
Go and have a look
Let me tell you
this money
Be sure to watch it carefully
I know
That person
Unreliable
This is it
how do you know
Where is Xiaojing’s house?
When I lived in Secret Pavilion before,
I live in the same room with Xiao Jing
She mentioned it during chatting
You will remember this
is it hard
Why is there always someone in her house?
in and out
Not far from here is Jieshen Alley
A lot of gold, silver and silk
trading place
The Pei family has lived here for a long time
I know many shopkeepers
follow their path
Can deposit and withdraw gold and silver
This kind of method is needed to deposit and withdraw gold and silver.
There are thousands of transactions like this
Need to find a reliable dentist
Pei's family left
This is the way to introduce it
I know this
Gold and silver prices fluctuate
If one fails, everything will go bankrupt.
If there is no reliable matchmaker,
Who trusts strangers trading?
you know too
Played before
Still making money
Then what
Then
I discovered that a young lady is worth more than gold and silver.
interesting
I won't play anymore.
What's wrong
Lu Nanshan said
Yuan Zhongxin ran out once
I asked you to hand it back
Everyone said it was impossible
This must happen
Are you still thinking about saving people?
That's true
it is true
This is also what Yuan Zhongxin meant
You discussed it
That's right
scared me
Don't you say it's fake?
If you lose, you'll have to twist your head off.
There's a secret behind this
Besides, why do you want my head?
Don't you say collection?
Can't you collect some good things?
you said it
There should be no one inside now
Then let’s go in and ask now.
Wang Kuan’s whereabouts
In case this goes missing
Is it related to them?
Ask honestly
There may not be any results
What should I do?
To ask
Just ask a little more boldly
Did I tell you?
Look left and right
Don't let anyone in
Why are you still pretending?
Robbing a house
It's so easy to tell the truth
That's not the only way, right?
Xiao Jing was taken by the Pei family
Sold to the owner
do you know
Do not worry
I'm just scared
Be sensible
Chief
Let me tell the truth
Since you met Yuan Zhongxin
There isn't much of a thing like proportion left.
Don't blame the chief
Blame Yuan Zhongxin
Hero Rong Zhen
Our family is really poor
Really no money
yes
Who are you lying to?
Don’t hide it from this big brother
Really short of money
but
Brother, you can’t come here in vain
There is a bowl of chicken soup on the table
For you, drink chicken soup first
or
I'll heat it up for you again
less nonsense
Do you think I am a hero?
I came to rob your house.
What else?
Did the hero go to the wrong door?
This hero sneaked into Kaifeng
Naturally, I want to make a big pen
Guess who I'm eyeing?
The son of Wang Bo, who was involved in political affairs
The one named Wang Kuan
You know?
Someone saw it last night
He came to your house
Never went out again
Say it
where are people
Hero
People did come
Left soon
Really gone
Didn’t drink much tea
yes
Why did my men say they didn't leave?
Hero
What if your men missed it?
yes
Hero, please
Don't touch my son
If you want to kill me, then kill me.
Where is Wang Kuan?
He, he's gone
He really left
I dare not lie
The hero knows clearly
He really left
Our yard is so big
Do not believe
Hero, you can search it
Where have you gone?
Where has he been?
No
Definitely
Back home
Yes, yes, he is home
So Wang Kuan and Xiao Jing have been here
But left again
From here to Wang's house
People are just gone
Chief, it's just like you said
They treat their own sons
attach great importance to
Doesn't look like he's lying
I was thinking
There may be something wrong with the Pei family
if not
That would be difficult
Xue Ying
The Wang family is concerned about this matter
How do you plan to deal with it?
They didn't panic
Talk about Wang Kuan’s recent years
Never return home
Already used to it
I was still thinking about it
Borrowing the Wang family’s connections
Ask about Yuan Zhongxin
the exact place of execution
So what should we do now?
Now we can only wait for Yuan Zhongxin
Post your own message
Why did Yuan Zhongxin release the news?
Isn't he in jail?
last night
why don't i see you
Yes why
Because this matter of the Yuan family is very involved
I was thinking of finding a way on my own
Don't drag you into the water
Can you understand?
understand
But now Yuan Zhongxin said
let me find you
Let's help rob the prison together
Can you understand?
clear
I also understood
You don't understand
All the classes in the Secret Pavilion were in vain.
Think about it yourself
As a lesson
The secret pavilion is gone
Why do you still have homework?
Let's go to my house first
What do you unserstand
No need to understand
Listen to the chief
That's okay too
sit
This house is
I live
Chief
You have so many hobbies?
When I was young, I was brave
Want to learn everything
Forget about hobbies for now
What should the chief do now?
Wang Kuan and Xiao Jing are gone
Where was Yuan Zhongxin executed?
No whereabouts either
How to save people
Asking others is better than asking yourself
What's the meaning
Right now we do
Encountered some setbacks
But it doesn't matter
Yuan Zhongxin can save himself
You guys sit down first
I'll get you a pot of hot tea
Self-help
How to save yourself
Don't be nervous
take it easy
Yuan Zhongxin's side was heavily guarded.
locked in dungeon
How can he save himself?
I do not know
Aren't you panicked?
Yuan Zhongxin's accident
Who is the most nervous?
The chief is calm
It shows that things can turn around.
I don't know what the turnaround is.
But I believe in the chief
I also believe Yuan Zhongxin
this is trust
Aren’t you just breaking the pot?
What are you talking about?
What do you mean?
Didn't you understand?
what am i talking about
If there's nothing wrong with my ears
You asked me to find Zhao Jian
Give me the time and place of your execution
Tell her everything
yes
Are you crazy
What is my relationship with you?
What is your relationship with me?
Blood feud
My colleague died tragically and his blood has not been avenged.
It’s all thanks to your Yuan family
That's what my dad did
I don't know
good
Even if it has nothing to do with you
The most I can do is not kill you with my own hands
How could I help save you?
You are so brave
It's absolutely impossible for me
Need not
No need for you to do anything
Just spread the news
Why
you want revenge
right
nonsense
What if I die?
The clue is broken
The Yuan family can't be found
How to avenge
Can I take revenge if you don’t die?
Of course
Why
Xiaoyuan
Think about it
who is my father
Former Landlord
So what do you think if I get caught?
Will he come to save me?
Since they are father and son, they must be saved.
Then why am I
Being locked up here for so long
He didn't even come to save me
nonsense
This deep prison is heavily guarded
How to save
Looking for death
What if
The time and place of my execution
leaked out
He knows
Is it possible to come and save me?
Nonsense
It's possible
Then do you think it is one?
Good opportunity to catch him
but
No, but listen to me
Tell Zhao Jian the news
This thing is equal to
leaked
right
Then my father
It's possible to save me
right
You and Mr. Lu
Set up an ambush in advance
It's possible to catch him
right
Is it right
so
You wait a moment, wait a moment
I'll take a look
do you want revenge
think
Then there is no need to stroke it
Go directly to Lu Nanshan
I teach you
The first thing you say when you see him is
Dean
I thought of a clever idea
What do I say, do you still need to teach me?
Dean
I thought of a clever idea
clever plan
Former Zhongxin Chingqiqi
before killing him
Why not use it as bait
What's the way to make bait?
Where we can carry out executions
leaked out
If the Yuan family wants to save him
Must come
We can lay down a dragnet
Then we will set up a dragnet
Maybe we can catch the head of the Yuan family
you mean
The news of Yuan Zhongxin's execution
Let it go
no
Such an arrangement must be a bad thing
What happened?
Because it's too fake
Not a big shot
Kill someone like me
The news spread throughout the city
Others will know it's a scam when they see it
Because it's too fake
He's not a big shot
Kill him for this news
Make it known throughout the city
Others look at
You will definitely think there is fraud in it
So kill me for this news
It must be spread out cleverly
kill you
Kill him
Yuan Zhongxin
How to do it cleverly?
Dean
Can be leaked to Zhao Jian
Zhao Jian is so bold
I've been thinking about robbing jail all day long
We pass the news to her
She will be looking for help everywhere
The Yuan family will definitely be involved.
When the time comes, the Yuan family will
Together with Qizhai and the others
lawless
captured together
Wouldn't it be better to have the best of both worlds?
Dean
That's quite logical.
Carefully thought about
The key now
Just let someone tell this news
Leaked to Zhao Jian
It's me, of course.