Mr. Yuan
Yuchi is here too
How did he
Will find it near here
He is your subordinate.
or
Ask yourself
Are you there?
Afraid that I'll run away
I'm all tied up here
It's hurt like this and you're afraid that I'll run away
I swear on my character
I will never run, okay?
Don't give me any trust
Mr. Yuan
Only you
Who else
How did you find this place?
gentlemen
I was supposed to be in Kaifeng
but guess what
Lu Nanshan wants to kill Yuan Zhongxin
Thanks to me for responding in time
rescued people
Take it all the way to Tanzhou
This road is full of mountains and rivers
Cross mountains and ridges
Didn't ask you this
What do you want to ask, sir?
How did you find this place?
No trace of Mr. is found in the post house
I was at a loss
But think about Mr.
Aren’t there Xixia people?
Xixia people don’t understand food
Eat meat all day
This side of Jinghu South Road
Not in the mood for roasting
But I look at this mountain
There is smoke rising
touch near
in ashes
You can also smell some meat
Follow this path and touch it down
I found out that my husband was living in seclusion here.
Not too stupid.
gentlemen
Don't make fun of my intelligence
If it weren't for me
Yuan Zhongxin died in Kaifeng
This way
Dining in the open air, trekking through mountains and rivers
Tired of traveling over mountains and ridges
Why send Yuan Zhongxin to Tanzhou?
Of course it’s for Mr.
Father and son reunited
Wormwood
gentlemen
I use my wits
Rescue people
I just don't know
Where have people gone now?
gentlemen
What about the Xixia people around you?
died
Killed by the Dragon God
what
At once
Village near the post house
A statue of a dragon with a severed head
i know that
gentlemen
It was you who cut off the dragon head
not me
It wasn't Mr. who cut it off
What are you doing
That'll be fine
What does it mean to be okay?
Then Dragon God won’t
Blame it on Mr.
gentlemen
Then you know
Where is the dragon head now?
Isn't it in the village?
It's not that the head is missing
If it’s gone, it’ll be gone.
gentlemen
How about we get the faucet back?
What are you looking for?
gentlemen
Do you want to live forever?
Immortality
Have you ever been hit in the head?
No
Mr.
Do you know who cut off the dragon head?
You're done with Longtou
Sir, do you know?
If you know, just tell me
gentlemen
Made by the students of North River Star
River Star
Beihexing in recent years
On Jinghu South Road
Always with these
Disasters and disasters are implicated
result
Those Xixia people are afraid of ghosts and gods
I also found some disasters to worship
It made the place full of smoke and smoke
Later I traced
Beihe star may be in Yuelu Academy
I just chased you here.
gentlemen
Will the faucet be there?
In the hands of North River Star
have no idea
Mr.
Are you here to check?
The Fall of the Northern Star
Not easy to check
Tanzhou
From official office to garrison
Take out wealthy villagers
They're all catching him.
No results either
why
I also want to know
What on earth did he do?
Causing anger and resentment
Sir, this place is a paradise.
It's not a place for humans to live.
Yuan Zhongxin
How come it hurts like this?
coming
who hurt you
Don't panic
I'll take revenge for you
I chopped him alive
Go ahead
I move my hand
why
gentlemen
I've met people from Qizhai
They said they found the star Pollux
He also said he wanted to use it
Beihexing will replace you with someone
Who should I change?
Qizhai asked you to send a message
gentlemen
I think there's something fishy about this
You said that Polaris has excellent hidden potential
How are they
So easy to find
When to replace
Today
gentlemen
Maybe it's fake
unimportant
This deal is negotiable
Lu Zhangyuan
Something big is about to happen. Let's keep up.
etc.
Where are the rest of Qizhai?
There is no difference in where they live
Where is Zhao Jian?
It's the same
Wang Kuan's side
Please, Mr. He County Cheng, please follow me.
I'll go to Zhao Jian's place to have a look
this
The whereabouts of Yuantian Pass
Right before your eyes
This is Lu Zhangyuan
Why sacrifice the near for the far?
yes
baffling
Follow secretly later
Missing the other party’s whereabouts
Don't show your body
adult
Let me add two more words
After seeing Yuantian Pass
Don't be too harsh
Disabled at most
Unfatal
yes
Set off
Dean
Why don’t we go capture Yuantian Pass?
yuantianguan
Must be with Yuan Zhongxin
That should be
Related to Yuan Zhongxin
Why didn't Zhao Jian show up?
Won't you follow?
Just to deceive others
Your sister and these two guys
insignificant
Does Wang Kuan have any county magistrate following him?
The only thing Qizhai wants to keep an eye on
Zhao Jian is the only one
This Zhao Jian
He is as smart as Yuan Zhongxin
Where does this road lead?
This is
The mountain gate leading to the back stream
Keep up
Fan Chi asked
Confucius said
Serve the people
Respect ghosts and gods and stay away from them
It can be said that I know it
Ask Ren
say
A benevolent person first encounters difficulties and then gains
It can be said to be benevolent
Let's just say she's smart.
Fortunately, the hospital responded quickly
Want to get out of my control
Easier said than done
It's the master's clever plan
If we really go to see Yuantianguan
I'm afraid it won't work just with you and me.
We have to go to Guiyuan Camp to mobilize troops.
Then the Commander-in-Chief will mobilize troops.
I'm going to keep an eye on Zhao Jian
I'm afraid you can't keep an eye on it.
You go and mobilize troops
I'll keep an eye on it
yes
Then I'll go back soon.
How to find a director
follow it
Remember
No registration allowed after leaving camp
Don't use ordnance
Pay attention to hidden traces
To prevent Yuan Tianguan from noticing
Don't worry, sir.
i know what to do
The vegetables are washed
I'm here
You washed it all.
Some chores today
Can I take half a day off?
go Go
Thank you, aunt
why you
Where is Zhao Jian?
Sister Zhao’s whereabouts are restricted
A little person like me
won't be noticed
Do you want to use Polaris?
Exchange of Yuan
people brought
Mr. Yuan, please come with me
You stay
Protect Yuan Zhongxin
yes
Where are the soldiers and horses?
The adults ordered
I let them hide their tracks
Surround this place
Just wait for the adult's order
Pretty clever
It all depends on adult guidance
This matter
Your Pei family
No more worries
Han Duanzhang’s incident
That's it.
Grace
Isn't this the previous inn?
Why is there no one?
That's wonderful
What's wonderful
when we identify
Yuantianguan has abandoned this post house
Instead, he hid again
What a turnaround
If not for following Zhao Jian
I really didn't expect it to be here
It seems that it is really Yuantian Pass
Thank you sir
Mobilize the returning troops early
Surround this place
Let’s see where he can escape from Yuantian Pass
adult
What should we do next?
After all, Qizhai
He is a disciple trained by his late father.
Since the front yard is under the care of the Guiyuan Army,
Let's take a detour
Go to the backyard and watch
Mr. Lu is thoughtful and considerate.
adult
Zhao Jian went in
It seems that he has no intention of coming out
Wait a little longer
Yuan Family Father and Son
Maybe already on the way here
The Great Calculation of Adults
When the time comes, all troops and horses will be dispatched
There is no doubt that Yuantianguan will die
wrong
Go to the front yard again.
yes
coming
There's someone over there
I can see
Not a lot
Pollux is coming
Helping catch Mr. Yuan
Just sell him
compared with him
Brother Yuan is more important
but
Beihexing has many men under his command.
They are all Tanzhou elites
Yuan Tianguan is so stupid
Alone
who cares
Mr. Yuan is alone
I'm afraid he's not his match.
Get him for me
Remember to stay alive
superior
Come on, come on
Come on, come on, come on
quick
help me
what are you going to do
I want to go home
Give me up
Get out of my way
you
Let go of you
You also serve the Dragon God
yes
I didn’t believe in the Dragon God at first
But guess what
Just a blink of an eye
People went from Kaifeng to Tanzhou
You say God is not God?
Really powerful
but
I just don't get it
This Dragon God wants Yuan Zhongxin
what to do
It must be related to the faucet
You can figure this out
Ordinary people don't have the wisdom I have
How can we speculate on the psychology of the Dragon God?
Walk
Give you Yuan Zhongxin
So awesome
The name Chiyou Banner
Ordinary people don’t dare to accept it
Yuan Zhongxin is inside
Before Mr. Yuan goes out
And knocked people unconscious
Never seen it before
Doing this to your own son
impossible
How could there be in this world
Such a strong person
another
Don't come here
Don't, don't, don't come over
Don't, don't, don't come here
Don't come here
Don't come here Don't come here
do not come
He is Beihexing
To him it's Polaris
you
You are complicit with him
There is a misunderstanding here
I am not Beihexing
I am the county magistrate of Fuya County
You in front of me
That's not what you said
I lied to you
I want to take advantage of you
Find the whereabouts of the Northern Star
You are Lu Nanshan’s subordinate
Lend me a hand
Fight against Lu Nanshan
It turns out I can’t hide it from Mr. Yuan
Even if it's not Beihexing
Can cut off Lu Nanshan’s men
It's also a good thing
Separate Separate
Mr. Yuan
you listen to me you listen to me
Lu Nanshan and I
Just a partnership
Not one of his men
actually
I have no ill intentions toward Mr. Yuan.
etc.
Separate Separate
He is also looking for Beihexing
Maybe it can help us
Zhao Jian never came out
Never came out
Something's not right
Go to the back door first
If there is a chance
Get Zhao Jian first
coming
You are here too
Xiaolu Zhangyuan
Where is Yuantian Pass?
I do not know
There are just three of us here
Lied to me
wrong
I must have lied to you.
unless
Unless you have seen through it
That Polaris isn't real
Just set up this game
Hitting the mark
when will you
Found out he was fake
You said the wrong thing the first time you met me.
What did I say wrong?
Wang Kuan
Among the seven fasts and six sons
Whether it is knowledge or character
I
The one I trust most is you
What's wrong with this?
I know Qizhai
I heard your name again
This is not surprising
Actually
North River knows Wang Kuan
Not surprising at all
But Wang Kuan solved the mystery
Find Chongtian Calendar in Yushu Pavilion
What did he find in it?
clues point to
This is it
Wang Kuan
This puzzle is
Designed for you alone
River Star
He said this riddle
Only for Wang Kuan
You should believe Wang Kuan
Any questions
But the answer to the puzzle
I found it in Yushu Pavilion
You guided me to discover the Chongtian Calendar
leave a note
So this Chongtian calendar
It was hidden in Yushu Pavilion in advance.
Hiding in advance
Mr. Yuan also discovered
Actually the problem is very simple
Wang Kuan is in Yushu Pavilion
The post of Ren Zhangshu
you say
Who would know about this arrangement in advance?
Of course it’s you, Xiao Lu, Zhang Yuan
our identity
You arranged it all.
except you
No one can possibly know
Wang Kuan in Yushu Pavilion
So there are only two possibilities
Either he is fake
Either
Polaris has been hidden for many years
Actually it is
Xiaolu Zhangyuan, your subordinates
to this point
Whether true or false
We can't trust you anymore
Of course
From the facts, you are lying
What did you say just now?
Magistrate of Fuya County, right?
yes
My surname is He
He is the magistrate of Xiangning County
But all this
It was all under the command of Lu Nanshan
I didn't think about it
I am your enemy
You want to catch
Just the Northern Star
you do not say
Why arrest him?
This ruins people's wealth
Like killing parents
Just a small flaw
then identify that
The North Star is fake
Too arbitrary
Dean
The troops will not come
It's you
So let's talk
We can’t be arbitrary either.
Is there no witness to this?
Lu Nanshan wants to mobilize troops
how do you know
According to the orders of Xiao Lu Zhangyuan
I should be eavesdropping outside the window
I only learned about it by chance
But this is not the case
These words
It was Xiao Lu who taught me what he said.
I'm looking for your Polaris to be fake.
He wants to use you to follow the clues
Capture Yuantian Pass
I thought
You are loyal to Lu Nanshan
The letter to Han Duanzhang that year
It was also arranged by Xiao Lu Zhangyuan
The letter is in his hand
Our family's life
It's in his hands
Life is in other people's hands
Feeling uneasy after all
What happened back then
Lu Nanshan also participated
Lu Nanshan has always been ruthless
play hard
Pei Xuan, ah Pei Xuan
You really impress me
Don't dare
good
OK
You are all here, right?
There are many of you
I know current affairs
I surrender
Good knife skills
Carry out a sneak attack
Who doesn't know how to sneak attack?
How's it going over there?
The fake Beihe star is the county magistrate of Xiangning County
Yuantianguan gave people to us
So easy to talk to
All he wants is the Northern River Star
Where is the county magistrate now?
Locked up in academy
The kitchen lady is helping to watch.
Hard to fly with wings
Is it going well for you?
I met Yu Chiyuan
seen
Brother Yuan was rescued
How is he injured?
Yuan Zhongxin is missing
Where is Yuan Zhongxin?
I do not know
Was here just now
Could it be Yuantian Pass?
Hiding people
impossible
Mr. Yuan has always been with me
How can I have time to hide people?
What about that person?
Could it be the appearance of the Dragon God?
Saved people
I have no power
We also know this
Ke Yuan Zhongxin
Just disappeared
I doubt it
Is it ghosts?
Tanzhou Trip
The name Polaris
Always around
But this person never showed up
It will be Polaris
Why does he want Yuan Zhongxin?
let's go back to
First question
Who is Polaris
Inexplicably disappeared and suddenly appeared again
And he rescued me
Dead Ghost Uncle
It's so mysterious
You were captured by Yuantianguan
We all see it
However, the force of Yuantian Pass is too high
I'm no match for him
you
who are you
River Star
want to see you
That's why you've been missing for so long
I saw Polaris
I told you at the beginning
I think what's going on in the world
boring boring
But what Beihexing does is different
what is the difference
Let him tell you himself
These days I ask
The puzzle of ten cents
Has been around for years
So the puzzle is real
But Wang Kuan has already solved it
The answer is Chongtian Calendar
I must have interpreted it wrong
Pei Xuan said
The county magistrate only learned about Chongtian Calendar
There is no further content
so
Chongtian calendar is not the answer
wrong
Both old and new numbers can match
The puzzle must point to the Chongtian Calendar
But have you ever thought about it
The calendar is a commonly used book
Bookstores are often used as accompanies
The academy is full of students
Scholars have a calendar
Not surprising
Then everyone has a calendar
In which book is the answer?
No, not a certain one
is the answer to all Chongtian calendars
All Chongtian calendars
All are answers to riddles
So the answer
It must be nothing
paper clipped
But on every calendar
Here again
But saying
Our every move
you all know
Someone help him pay attention to you
Someone
College students
right
there are others
have
Auntie in the kitchen
She is Beihexing
she is not
Then why is she helping you?
Disaster destroyed her village
ruined her family
It also ruined her life
But she didn't say
It’s because Pollux destroyed the idol
Did this happen?
If she didn't say that
The government office suspected her.
Then why are those victims
There are also students
Everyone is on the side of Polaris
Let him tell you
Why did you last time
Find that folder
Beihe star belongs to Jingsu
In the Chongtian calendar
Naturally recorded this calendar
The zodiac degree of Jingsu
right here
Well-house
Chongtian calendar is thirty
thirty
Since every Chongtian calendar
All are answers
That clue is
Well 30
thirty
This is the age of a person
impossible
if that is the case
The puzzles change every year
Moreover
He can't be that young, right?
Will it be on your body?
There are engraved with the number thirty
It's impossible to be so straightforward
I always feel like I need to change the question
River Star
Why is this puzzle given?
He is afraid of others
Can't find him?
zodiac degree
what does it mean
Wait a moment
River Star
Has been wooing college students
So the academy is also the key
But thirty
What does it have to do with the academy?
No
Thirty is not just a number
What else is that?
That’s the meaning from the beginning
Star sign
exactly
What did they both understand?
We are all human
Why is the difference so big?
What does Xingxiusiudu refer to?
Heaven
No
It’s also the human world
Just now
I saw inside the inn
The remaining pages of the book fell from the sky
i remember this book
Studying the art of witchcraft
There are also divination disasters
It is inevitable to also record celestial phenomena
Just reminded by Wang Kuan
I just remembered
Xingxiuxiudu is not just the starry sky
It’s also the human world
Don't understand
It is common for the stars to mark their directions
And the earthly place
Corresponding to the location of the constellations
It is also often mentioned
Heaven and man echo
So we put the stars
Move it to the ground and see
what would it be like
Above ground
Nothing
Academy
Academy corresponding constellation chart
Let go of the ground
Viewed from a height
The academy is a whole
What are the degrees of the zodiac like?
Just a circle
Substitute the academy into it
Well 30
Convert it
Where should it be in the academy?
It should be here
Xiao Xue
Can we still be friends?
When I practice swordsmanship
Some steps
Just follow the stars
So remember
I feel abandoned
That's where it turned out to be
Where is that?
You take a panoramic view of the academy
Put it into this circle
You can see where it is
Have no idea
It turns out to be you
Answers to puzzles
It's the starting point of the puzzle
The effect is the cause
person who asked the question
The answer is
to be honest
We also guessed it at first
but
You pretended to be deaf and there was no flaw
amazing
It is worthy of being the Northern River Star
he can't hear
he is deaf
Pollux is deaf
He cut his own ears with his own hands
Deaf
why
For the sake of being in Yuelu Academy
The secret of selling Polaris
To select students
In order not to let others doubt him
Do you know why the government office
Don't you doubt him?
Because he can't hear
no
Because he is in the next village
Have sons and daughters
There is land to grow and chickens to raise
Of course
Of course what
His cock is not as good as mine
But the trajectory of his life
All in the village
And he is a
Really deaf
If I hadn't seen him before
Who knew he was Polaris
So his children
all fake
real
How can it be
How long has he been preparing?
lifetime
He has been a farmer his whole life
so this place
It's his hometown
Yes
No wonder people
No flaws found
But why did he
To pierce your ears
His identity
There is no flaw anymore
His old man said
The most difficult thing to control
It's just my subconscious reaction
if in ear
Suddenly heard a special secret
He was afraid he couldn't control himself
discovered by others
if deaf
It's really foolproof
As for that?
you know too
The whole Tanzhou is looking for him
Why
Just ask him
I'm going to patrol around
In case of accidents
Hello Yuan Zhongxin
I am Beihexing
In fact, I already knew
It’s about the secret pavilion
People are caught
But what to do next?
After all, he is an official
He not only has official status
On him
Maybe there's another secret hidden
The letter to Han Duanzhang that year
He also has a plan
I thought about it
maybe at that time
Unsolved riddles
There will be an answer now
Xiaolu Zhangyuan
You should be awake
What answer do you want?
You have a privy council
The Deputy Secretary's Mission
so what
then
we are involved
Han Duanzhang case
Liu Sheng, the head of the Five Fasting Houses
died in prison
when he died
Obviously under the control of the Privy Council
under protection
His death
It was someone in the Privy Council who did it
Isn’t this case settled early?
Lu Nanshan
Did you kill Liu Sheng?