You came back from Jinghu South Road
So have you recently
I've seen the chief and the others
seen
How are they now?
quick
Sit down and tell me
Let me tell you about my sister first.
Thanks
Come and see
Thank you Miss Pei
Because life is too short
The previous years
I only learned some sewing and cooking
Because I feel that in this life
It probably passed in a daze.
Until I entered the seventh fast
I just found out
Turns out like me
Useless little person
I can also fight side by side with everyone.
I am a member of Qizhai
I can never be ashamed of this identity
Do you know yourselves?
what are you talking about
Mr. Yuan
By now
Can't you see the situation?
All the gods within a hundred miles radius
They were all smashed by that person named Zhao.
This is a good thing
Mr. Yuan’s merits surpass those of his master.
why she
Don't come in when you're outside
why let us all out
Why do I need to see you alone?
Isn't this obvious?
Want to seize power
Boss
did you see
The temple door is closed
No one comes out
Didn't they say
one month
After settling the accounts?
Can you believe this?
The pig is exhausted and the knife is hidden.
Sorry for what you said
All the pigs are dead
The butcher's knife is no longer useful
Is it because the birds are gone and the bows are hidden?
This is wrong
My family used to be hunters
If the birds are gone, there will still be rabbits.
Deer, wolf, etc.
How could Gongzang be there?
Which hunter only hunts birds?
You have a life
You decide
so
this scene
It's obvious that I'm going to attack you.
What do you think
Strike first to gain the upper hand
She is unkind
I can't blame you for being unjust, right?
Don't worry
I am protected by Nanshan God
Mr. Yuan
When has it been?
And Nanshan God?
I said something unpleasant
If the Nanshan God could appear,
Are you still in a wheelchair?
It's useless to believe anything now
Only trust people
You all think so
Everybody thinks so
How can there be any divine protection?
Boss
At first we believed it
but follow you
Smashed so much
After the mess of idols
I understood it all at once
If there really is such a thing
Just us
Can have a good
right
It's all lies
yes
It’s not unreasonable to say that.
Boss, have you thought about it?
How to deal with it later
This one's surname is Yuan
No need to think about it
I saw the man named Yuan
Put the knife on the neck
That's it.
Be careful about hiding people in his temple
There's no way to hide it
Just these few people
They all know outside
Plus
The guy named Zhao is so good at fighting
A few of us plus
It’s also for free
So what do you mean?
We surrender directly
Mr. Yuan
What about you, strategizing?
Tell us the truth
Are you ready?
We feel at ease this way
You poisoned the water
Poisoning is good
Poisoning is good Poisoning is good
Come out, come out
The boss is here
Miss Zhao
It's been a stalemate for so long
It's all dark.
We follow your requirements
All come out
Where is Mr. Yuan?
I want to talk to you alone
please
Boss
Boss, wait a minute.
I'll go and scan around first.
In case they have an ambush beforehand
Miss Zhao
Mr. Yuan to you
Always trusted
You know
Miss Zhao
this way please
I have something on my mind
I can't help but speak out
Did you ask the truth?
Then Miss Zhao really wants to
Attack you
If you had no backup plan
Run away quickly
I'll try to help you sneak out from behind
Miss Zhao
The water is poisoned
Don't hesitate to go in soon
Do it directly
Thanks
It took three months and three months
I now
Became a follower of the Yuan family
it's good now
I can finally change my family.
Thanks a lot
This guy surnamed Yuan is also good to you.
You have no regrets at all
I want to be a good person
Why help me?
Still believe in Nanshan God
Who still believes in God these days?
My house suffered a disaster before Mr. Yuan
It's the money you gave me
Help my family tide over the difficulties
Although I know
You are trying to win people over
But this life-saving grace
We can't forget
right
You should run away quickly
Don't do any more god-like things in the future.
In this world
Only people can be trusted
Let Miss Zhao come in
What
Mr. Yuan, she is particularly good at fighting
rest assured
i can handle it
There's nothing wrong with the boss
How long have we not seen each other?
Can not remember
Thank you for your hard work these days
Running all the way
How are your legs?
Almost there.
Not completely healed yet
Did you hit it?
we succeeded
All nearby gods were eradicated
Including those around us
I no longer believe in any Nanshan gods.
and
They also turned against each other
Some are out of love
Some are for profit
have you ever thought about
When we go out later,
How does it end?
Didn't think about it
I don't want this
My mind is occupied with thinking of you
How can I have time to think about anything else?
Why is there no movement at all?
Seemingly silent murder hidden behind
God knows what kind of confrontation there is
In fact, we are in the same group
What do you mean
Let's go and settle it
Walk
I'll have to smash this thing soon.
Why do you keep a cloth covering your head?
Lu Nanshan's face
Who can stand it after watching it for so long?
If this were your face
I never get tired of watching it
Very good at talking
The truth
There really are them
You didn't even think about going over to see them
No
Three years later
Will meet again
Is three years a long time?
Not short or short
have you ever thought about
What will happen if you all change?
people alive
changing every day
Aren't you afraid?
Got stuck in this
What should I do?
I still have a date
uncle
Ask you personally
Yuan Zhongxin
you are healed
Almost there.
It all depends on you
us
Xiaojing has been practicing medicine in the countryside these years
Various methods for internal and external injuries
Use them on me
There are also many medicinal materials
from all directions
Delivered continuously
Zhao Jian almost killed me
The smell of medicine is coming
It is said that there are some
Something more valuable than gold
You found it all
Worth it
I said you would be able to move around in ten years
Scared us to death
We have plenty of money now
Why are you still plowing here?
Isn't this the land of Polaris?
What about others?
He forgot everything
Completely forgotten
from some angles
There is no more in this world
The Northern River
I am sick
I'm old
I'm almost done
But I am not afraid of death or aging
Not afraid of being caught by them
What I'm afraid of is
Things that persist until now
die from then on
Nothing more
Can't remember at all
What I just said
Forgot in the blink of an eye
What is the disease?
Can turn people into this
have no idea
I guess there will be people in the future
Do you know the answer?
correct
Where is the chief?
She has something
not coming
will come
What about Xiao Jing?
Isn’t it said that medical skills are successful?
Where is she?
Looks like a miracle doctor
The miracle doctor is here
Don't kneel, don't kneel, don't kneel
Everybody, get up, get up
Meet the miracle doctor
That's a
coffin
Get up, get up
Meet the miracle doctor Meet the miracle doctor
Stop kneeling
Meet the miracle doctor
Don't kneel, don't kneel
How is my pulse?
wait
a bit strange
Strange
And it’s weird that you’re sitting in a coffin.
I've been carrying it with me for the past three years.
why
This disease-infected place
Death becomes commonplace
I prepared this for myself
Fortunately, I never used it.
Then those villagers just now
Why are you kneeling?
I don't want to either.
Saved some people
They're always like this
That Xiaojing’s medical skills are now
Very powerful ah
Pretty clever, right?
Then what kind of pulse do I have?
How weird!
You put it here and I'll take it again
A bit like
Joy pulse
impossible
It's fine
It's okay
Don't be nervous
My pulse is just fine
Only studied for a few days
Then you still talk about yourself
Excellent medical skills
I'm very good at boiling medicine and dissecting corpses.
autopsy
The epidemic is rampant and the cause of death needs to be investigated
These are inevitable
Aren't you afraid?
A little bit scared at first
Gradually I got used to it
these three years
Sometimes I am scared to tears
But I always think of you all
If it weren't for you
I'm afraid I won't be able to survive now
Brother Yuan
Where is Sister Zhao?
Arrive late
How are you feeling lately?
It’s normal to have relaxed hands and feet
There's a stab wound on your arm.
Three Years of Exorcism
It is inevitable that you will encounter some disturbances
Is it effective?
This year Jinghu South Road
Any village or town affected by natural disasters
More than 80%
Report to the government
Three years ago, it was only 20 to 30 percent.
They don't believe in ghosts and gods anymore
Maybe you still believe it
But I don't believe those anymore.
In the name of ghosts and gods
People who make money
After all, in the past three years
Countless lessons
Been cheated countless times
Learned well
Countless lessons
Zhao Jian and I gave it to
listen you both
He doesn't look like a good person.
Why aren't you a good person?
Slow down
Slow down and don't fall
this child
Has Wang Kuan been here in the past three years?
He has his own way to go.
Have you written a letter?
Don't worry he will definitely come
But within three years
Brother Wang is not here
Dead Ghost Uncle
Where is Zhao Jian?
Arrive late
Where is Xue Ying?
Didn’t he learn martial arts from you?
Didn't he go with you?
After the first journey of the caravan
He just left
He never came back
Have you not seen him in the past three years?
No
Unexpected
Xiao Xue is better at skipping classes than me.
All right
so
He also has his story
I guess he won't come today either
Come
This is what I promised you
Sent to Xixia
Agent roster
so thick
hard won
We have so many helpers
They are all in Xixia
Some of them were buried in Xixia
But most of
No bones left
died
All dead
yes
three years ago
Northern Rivers has committed
The business of slaying demons
right
He has not had the chance to go to Xixia in the past three years
yes
So these people
Three years ago
Even earlier
already dead
He wants to save you
what does it mean
three years ago
You all want to go to Xixia
Assassination of Yuan Hao
You also knew it at that time
There is basically no chance of survival
This desire to die
Mostly out of youthful ambition
Beihexing doesn't want to
put your name
Also stay in this booklet
So just use this
He lied to us for three years
People
Can't be a boy forever
After three years of hard work
You all have it
My own achievements
Jinghu South Road can illustrate
Zhong Xin and Zhao Jian
Has mastered the art of slaying demons
Xiao Jing
The name of the goddess doctor
Rumor has it
Yanei
these three years
I didn't know you were out there
what kind of business
But the money you sent back
We are all used to suppress disasters and eliminate demons
Forget it
Forgot the trip to Xixia
Growth is not a bad thing
Through you these past three years
Your own efforts
You all have your own direction
Why waste your life in Xixia?
It took three years
In exchange for us not being young anymore
This is what Pollux means
right
yes
He doesn't want you to
Die in vain
You already knew
yes
I hesitated at first
I advise you not to come to Polaris
But then I felt
What he did was right
Just think Xixia is a
A boy's dream
Now I wake up from the dream
Your future is there
Something else is possible
these three years
We get along well, right?
Chungking
If you want to raise an army to accuse
I can apologize to you
are you right to me
I still have some understanding
certainly
Then am I the person?
Not too honest
You want to evaluate it like this
I think it's inevitable
a bit conservative
What do you think three years ago?
I would be so easy
Do you believe in Polaris?
What's the meaning
Chief
Yanei
Sister Zhao
Small Scene
The senior spy in this booklet
All are no longer alive
We were all deceived by Polaris
Strictly speaking, it doesn’t count.
Was he cheated?
After all, what I said at the time was
Give us the roster after three years
There is no agreement whether to live or die.
Makes sense
Not being cheated
This is Xixia’s military elite
With this
You can enter the country smoothly
This is the map of Xixia
various passes
The garrison formations are among them
With it
The so-called enemy country has become a gateway
impossible
In the past three years, you have been
With Won Jong-shin
How do you have time to prepare this?
Not prepared by me
Who is that
have you ever thought about
Why Xue Ying
Didn't come back to find you
yuantianguan
let's make a deal
I promise you
within three years
Don't let Yuan Zhongxin go to Xixia
what do i want to give
very simple
You have good skills
Help me bring Xue Ying with me
Xue Ying
The one with double swords
I have to go to Xixia
He will go too
these three years
Xue Ying has been in Xixia
So these three years
You have been preparing
these things
I promised Yuantianguan
within three years
Yuan Zhongxin was not allowed to enter Xixia
But these three years
He promised Polaris
Help Beihexing to eliminate demons.
He didn't have to go to Xixia in the first place
Is such that
But Yuan Tianguan doesn’t know
Hello Zhao Jian
Kill two birds with one stone
You are lying on both sides
This can't be considered a lie, can it?
After all, Yuan Zhongxin
I really didn’t go to Xixia
yes
We are all honest people
After three years of hard work
You still want to go to Xixia
Even if you clearly know
Going there is like sending yourself to death
Dead Ghost Uncle
three years
changed many people
We have also experienced a lot of things
Maybe they have become more mature
But who said Qianfan was too late?
One cannot remain a teenager
Still a teenager
Chief
What's wrong
Won't you sit in?
Is there a seat for me inside?
Too
Do you think you are okay?
Take so many things with you when you go out
Be prepared
To tell you the truth
I'm relatively rich now
If time were not tight
I can do this on a larger scale
Do you believe it?
How rich
This is hard to describe
Opened a shop
What is a shop?
Then you go to Xixia with us
What to do with your industries?
Who cares?
Small Scene
What’s wrong with you
I'm fine
Why are you all the way?
Don't even speak
Feeling a little uncomfortable
Why
My coffin this time
I can’t bring Xixia with me.
I definitely can’t bring it with me.
Too unlucky
Mainly because I can't let go
You've been with the coffin for the past three years
Lying down with emotion
Who would fall in love with a coffin?
Then why are you sad?
Because when I left
Villagers worship the coffin
Worship the coffin
Explain that you, the female doctor
Respected
Even the coffin was stained with light
We spent so much effort
Isn't it just to beheaded?
Are there any ghosts in their minds?
In the end it's still like this
Just think
Quite helpless
no way
something
It cannot be changed in two or three years.
Not even one generation or two generations
It can be done
But in the past three years you
It's somewhat effective.
At least
This liar is not easy to deal with.
Then you can leave like this
Won’t all your efforts be in vain?
So these three years
Let the damn uncle follow you
what we did
How to do
He knows it all
Just leave it to him
In fact, this guy, the dead ghost uncle
not bad
Chungking
I can go to Xixia with you
You'd better stay
Have you forgotten what you said before?
I'm bored
Don't know what else to do
Fame, wealth and power
What the world wants
But that's it
boring
What did you say you were looking at?
All feel bored
But these three years
But you are with us
Fight alongside
I think Polaris
Doing good things
You young people are interesting
so
Congratulations, uncle.
you finally found it
What you want to do
How can you go to Xixia?
If you go
What to do here
but
Kill Yuan Hao
too difficult
It's really too difficult
Does it have to be just a few of you?
How do you say something?
What should you do when you are born?
In fact, it is fate
Do you believe it
Of course I don't believe it
If I believe in fate
I can't make it today
So there is nothing
What you are destined to do
It has to be someone else's words
road
It's all chosen by people themselves
just like you
Didn’t he also choose the path of North River Star?
right
The path you choose
As difficult as it is
gone
try your best
come back alive
Hurry up Hurry up
good
Three years
The market has changed a lot
The war can no longer be fought
Where did this waistband come from?
Are you sure you can pass?
Didn’t I say that?
Xue Ying has come to Xixia a long time ago
He has acquaintances in Xixia
It's cavalry
An acquaintance is here
meet again
You are the
Youzhou Shaodu commanded the army
Liang
Liang Maixiang
I remember you and Xue Ying
We have a good relationship
I often practice swordsmanship
He is much stronger than me now
Can't practice anymore
You gave me the waistband
Didn't we make an appointment at Xingqing Mansion?
Why is it so early?
Want to meet you early
Why
I said you may not believe it
Let your own people speak for themselves.
Is it Xiao Xue?
Wang Kuan
Brother Wang
I won’t go to Xingqing Mansion for the time being.
two reasons
Do you still remember
The eight-year-old text is indefinite
A plan to become a god?
Remember
arts
Wen Wuqi faked the birth of the goat-keeper god
She also knows this
Wen Wuqi is not that good
But the work is okay
Although Xixia mainly believes in Buddhism
He worked hard for three years
The Goat God finally spreads widely
Including Xingqing Mansion, the capital of Xixia
There are also believers
Not only that
People from all walks of life in Xixia
People who believe in the sheep god
is more and more
certainly
This is also indispensable
The secret assistance of the Yuzhou Military Supervision Department
should
All to get rid of Yuan Hao
Wang Kuan
The changes you mentioned are related to Bazhai
Queen Yeli
I want to go to Helan Mountain to worship the gods.
Yuan Hao's wife
Wen Wuqi has rushed to Helan Mountain
Get ready to meet the Xixia Queen
Why do you want to see her?
Winning her over to kill Yuan Hao
Isn't this crazy?
They are a couple for life.
Prime Minister Bai knows that he still presses his sword
The key is how can we help?
Leading the team to protect Queen Yeli
It's Brother Ning Ling
Another acquaintance
But Bazhai and Ning Lingge are not familiar with each other
understood
So I thought about him
It's up to us
That's what it means
Then I will definitely go
Wen Wuqi begged me
He has today too
so happy
OK
So what are you waiting for?
Go to Helan Mountain as soon as possible
Not available for now
My dad wants to see you
when
Already on the way
What about Xiao Xue?
My dad takes him with him
They have such a good relationship
My dad means
If you hide from him
Just chop off Xue Ying's head
this
What kind of temper is this?
Have personality
I like
Then let's meet
This Yuzhou capital controls the army
Small Scene
are you
Do you have any questions?
It's warmer here
I'm back
Brother Wang
Don’t you want to go your own way?
The road is over
So fast?
You have already entered Zhongshu University
I kowtowed to my father
after i leave
The hope of the next generation of the Wang family
In whose hands?
Those cousins ​​of yours
On knowledge and character
I may not lose to you
i want to see them
Want to fight
It's not impossible
Wang Kuan
It is common for people to take the wrong path
But you have to learn to admit your mistakes
My dad thought I saw him
Those cousins
It's from their hands
Seize the so-called family inheritance
But he guessed wrong
Become a marquis and a prime minister
It doesn't have to be me
Who else could it be if he wasn't him?
The Wang family is flourishing
Most of them are teenagers
But it was Wang Kuan who wanted to save the Song Dynasty.
Many people want to save the Song Dynasty
How could there be only
Where is Wang Kuan?
Brother Wang wants to be a teacher
Put the method in your heart to save the country
teach to others
In fact, it is not a national salvation law.
Just some thoughts
I'm just an ordinary person
Not necessarily can be made a marquis or a prime minister
Not to mention cleaning up the long-standing shortcomings of the Song Dynasty
What I want to do
Just find one
A more suitable person than me
entrust your hope to him
Then you found it
found it
It's those cousins ​​of yours
Not those few
Then who did you find?
Not native
But his last name is Wang
There is some blood connection with the family.
Just related to each other
After all, our last name is Wang.
What's the use of that?
There are many people with the surname Wang.
Without the support of the Wang family
How to climb up?
No need
With his ability
Will definitely stand out
You think so highly of him
His talent
far above me
impossible
Absolutely impossible
How could there be someone
Better than Wang Kuan
have no idea
Anyway, we haven't seen it before
Wang Kuan himself swore that
This person is in the future
within decades
Will definitely be promoted to prime minister
Another talented boy
Listen to Wang Kuan
That person is older
Already a Jinshi
Already appointed official position
I rushed to Huainan specially
meet him
And after that
Talk all night long
What I have seen and learned over the years
Inform all
There is such an unparalleled talent
The ambition to save the country has been entrusted
So this road
I'm done
I'm back
What about him?
Go to Liangzhe Road and rule Mingzhou
Appointed county magistrate
Be a county magistrate
Shouldn't it be the Beijing trial to enter the pavilion?
He has his own way to go.
me too
from beginning to end
I never wanted to leave you
Three years of grinding medicine to dissect the body
My hands are calloused
I know
you are awesome
I'm sorry for wronging you.
My dad is here
Xiao Xue