Brother Wang, you are awake.
I was rescued by you
do not Cry
I
I don't actually feel pain
How could it not hurt?
you know too
my life
never lie
I'm a very stubborn person
How could I break myself?
Bottom line and persistence
So you believe me, Xiao Jing
I am okay
I don't feel any pain
Wang Kuan
you're awake
what do you mean
I'm thinking of advising you again
Do you still want to persuade me to leave?
alive
Anything is possible
People don’t live just to live
you are wrong
People start from birth
Just struggle to survive
Just survive
To prove that you are still there
after death
The so-called persistence of faith
All in vain
But it is precisely because there is
Thousands of beliefs and perseverance
Changed the world
If not
From ancient times to the present
The world is still a pool of stagnant water
you are all crazy
maybe
They're crazy and you're with them
Do you care?
you
different from them
What
You are different from the others in Qizhai
Not a fellow traveler
You're doing this to me again, right?
Xianbei bloodline, right?
The one inside woke up
rest assured
I'm watching for you outside
If your father wants to take action
Already moved
The little girl is sensible
I heard your father is outside
We quarreled again
It's time
You still have time to take care of this matter?
Don't use this expression
Didn't I agree before coming here?
Regardless of life or death
Besides, I'm not dead either
How is he injured?
Just save your life temporarily
He just comforted me and said
He doesn't feel any pain
Not a comfort
It's true
You treated it well.
I'm all right
I'm going to ask Hua Cishu
Let him arrange for you to evacuate here
where to
Return to Song Dynasty
I think it's OK
Let Wang Kuan go back to recuperate first
No
Don't be brave anymore
you are hurt too badly
My injury
I'm afraid I can't stand running thousands of miles
Better to stay first
Always helpful with suggestions
Forget it, forget it.
You stay.
This guy is very strong
what did you tell him
He won't listen
My temper is okay
It's not like I don't know you
I'm going to make another medicine
Don't be too tired
I know
Don't you lie?
No pain
she cried
Been holding on to it all my life
I will avenge you
I will definitely give it to you
Kill Yuan Hao
Can't
Let’s kill Yuan Hao
It is to eliminate the war
It can't be for personal vendetta
You are like this
I said it all
I'm a very stubborn person
Don't cry and look sad, either
Affect my mood
I am in a bad mood
How to heal
Do you want me to do this at this time?
Do you still smile at you?
Tell me about it
What is the current situation?
No hidden lies
Join forces with Brother Ning Ling again
Brother Ning Ling still dares to believe him?
Yuan Hao will be getting married in a few days
The bride is from the Meiyi clan
I was engaged to Brother Ning Ling before.
There is no hidden false suggestion
On his wedding day
replace the bride
Assassination on the spot
How to change the bride?
Arranged by Ning Lingge
Who should I replace it with?
Who will do it
I
Too dangerous
yes
Isn't this a dead end?
There's someone hanging over Yuan Hao's side.
what
This is the Yuan clan
hung on a shelf
I saw someone hanging on the shelf
I'll report it as soon as possible.
You're looking for me
gentlemen
You just sit here like this
Do I still have to rush over?
Yuan clan members
With a patriarch like you
It can be said that the whole family is unlucky.
People
You have to live for yourself
Not all the people hanging here are members of the Yuan clan.
Who else
Sorry, Mr. Wei
Qing Tianzi
What do you mean by this?
This is not about your son
Please come out?
You are father and son after all
Failed assassination attempt at banquet
I'm afraid they have escaped long ago
It's possible
But what if
Gotta try it
Show your sincerity
This knife cut a little deep
If this doesn't stop bleeding
Mr. Wei, I'm afraid
Can't make it through the night
But don't worry
I think
Your son will definitely come
His character is pretty good
them
He really ran away.
Then you'd have died in vain.
Qing Tianzi
You act this way
How to win people's hearts
If you really die
I will definitely follow the etiquette of the Song Dynasty
Bury you with honor
The first seven days
I can definitely cry my eyes out
No need
I can't bear it
I have to save him
Isn't this nonsense? Let's go
I'll go alone
Go alone, you're crazy
Xiao Xue
listen to me
My dad told me
His taking refuge in Xixia was a bitter trick
He is not treasonous
after i leave
You leave here immediately
Find a hiding place again
I'm afraid I can't stand it
I'm afraid I won't be able to withstand the torture
As long as I don't know
where are you
The secret will not be leaked
What did you say
Chu Niao died in front of my eyes
Wen Wuqi followed the crane into the fire
Both of them were dead
I ask you
Wen Wuqi went to rob Chu Niaoshi
Why didn't I call you?
why did he go alone
Because he assassinated
Yuan Hao's mission
entrusted to us
I'm going to do what I have to do now
The hope of killing Yuan Hao
Entrusted to you
help me take revenge
Let him go alone
I am the chief
It's not his turn to give orders
We can't leave the office alone
face all this
That's natural
Xiaojing, guard Wang Kuan
gentlemen
what should we do
what would you do
not my business
Yanei
Didn’t we all agree?
What do you want to do?
who is the chief
you
Then stop talking nonsense
Don't take action
With Yuan Hao
No one can escape
I want to save people.
Say it
What conditions are required?
You are willing to take action
if i was hung there
I wouldn't want him to show up
if you were hung there
Definitely not going to show up in Yanei
And you
will you come
I didn't think about it
All stay here
Don't come over and cause trouble
Mr. Yuan
I owe you a life
What did you say just now?
I take action
What conditions are required?
No conditions
what's the situation
Do you want to repair the relationship with you?
Mr. Wei
did you see it
Yuantian Pass is coming
To cast oneself into a trap for the sake of one’s own people
I didn't expect this
Still a little bit human
I was wrong.
superior
father
Yanei
Calm inside the office
kill him
What's going on?
Yuchi is here too
Mr. Yuchi will help you
All lives are gone
What are you laughing at?
Pity
Bury it
Remember to give a generous burial
I promised him
Yanei
calm
let me go
Why did he kill my father?
Yanei Yanei
Yanei
Dad believes in you
Good
grown up
My dad said
He believes in me
I grew up
So I won't rush out
I want him to see
He didn't believe his son wrongly
come up
gone
I want to live
Live to avenge my father
I have no idea
I do not know why
why did he kill him
Shibo’s life and death still need to be confirmed
Nothing to confirm
Dead
why did you kill him
You risked your life to come to Xixia
Don’t you just consider yourself a member of Qizhai?
I am
Say it again
you
different from them
Look at Wei Zhuoran
Eighty percent of it is a secret line from the Song Dynasty
Serve the country wholeheartedly
Not to mention the Zhao family
royal blood
Xue Ying’s father was a military householder
Destiny to guard the territory
Wang Kuan is a member of a famous family
Although Pei Jing is a foreigner
But he has a grudge against Liao State
Pei family surrenders to Song Dynasty
It's also natural
what do you want to say in the end
They kill thieves for the country
Emphasis on love and justice
That's how we were born
Family history and bloodline inheritance
A real story
And you
Yuan Zhongxin
You are rotten from the root
With a dad like me
You have nothing to pass on
You know it yourself
so
You follow them and risk your life
Isn't this stupid?
They have heritage and foundation
and I
A selfish little person
Why are you joining in the fun with them?
Wake up, Yuan Zhongxin
You are not the same type of person as them
I'm a bad person
My son should be born like this
How sad!
That's how things are.
Lao Tzu enters the prison camp
My son was called a thief
You should have seen this kind of thing too often
He grew up with fine clothes and good food
You're crawling in the mud
Born in the mire
All are corrupt things
Actually I'm fine
Taking care of your feelings
Logically speaking
I'll kill you directly
Just these friends
it's good now
I kill Wei Zhuoran
There is a gap between you and Qizhai.
Just find a step and escape completely
Yuan Zhongxin
A choice you can't make
I'll do it for you
This situation now
You guys can't do it either.
Let’s part ways and go back to the Song Dynasty as soon as possible.
You can go together
No need
Are you going to persuade him?
it's useless
He has a father like me
It's destiny
I don't advise him
real
Yuan Zhongxin’s decision
No one needs to persuade him
you're right
I have neither
Family inheritance
nor
Loyalty of fathers
I'm different from them
I really want to understand
Figured it out
Just figure it out
Everything must have a beginning
Since I have no inheritance
Then let’s start the inheritance from me
Since there is no door tradition
That Yuan family tradition started from myself
i want you to know
In the abyss and mire
It can also produce flowers
Let me see how you face Wei Yuan
What happened in Yanei?
My uncle was murdered
It's Yuan Hao
Yuan Tianguan's moving hand
How could it be Yuantian Pass?
I also want to know
I gonna go see
How did you get hurt like this?
Is Pei Jing here?
i want to see her
His Excellency Dragon Dragon God
do not move
Let me help you treat your wounds first
Xue Ying helped me pack the
medicine
His Excellency Dragon God
You use your magic
my injury
Will it be fine in a moment?
Can't I use my magic power?
cannot
I know
Western Xia territory
They are all local gods
Mana cannot be tampered with
How did you get hurt like this?
I saved Mr. Yuan
Small Scene
You feel
Is what my father said true?
What did uncle say?
It was he who came to Xixia
It's actually a trick
I think it's true
That
when he died
Is he a hero?
Of course it counts
That's good
I said it a long time ago
My dad is number one in the world
But I can't even collect his body
Wang Kuan
Why is this world
It is always the hero who suffers the most
cry it out
no
I can't embarrass him
I can't cry
Yuan Zhongxin
Have you seen Mr. Yuan?
tell me quickly
Did he escape?
You blocked the pursuers for him
he's fine
That's great
Very good
He left you, you don't hate him
I am Yuchiyuan
Mr. Changyuan's life
Not a loss
Moreover
Am I not dead yet?
It surprised me that
I actually killed him
Also saved a life
Am I strong or not?
What did he do for you?
Make you willing to die for him
For Mr. Yuan
Haven't done anything
for me
A great favor
I was born in the army
Military household
Poor life
When I first joined the army
The military leader doesn't like me
Withheld military pay
Want to take the blame on me
I thought I was dead
It was Mr. Yuan who saved me.
and took me under his command
He's trying to take advantage of you
Can be used by Mr. Yuan
Is it not good
dragon dragon god
Dragon God
How is Yanei?
Wang Kuan is with me
Where is the chief?
Miss Zhao
Miss Zhao, this is the palace.
We're still planning an assassination
Just stop running around
In case someone discovers
We all have to die
Do you need some medicine?
I said it all
I'll send it over in person later
I heard they want me to pretend to be the bride
Assassination of Yuan Hao
You can't do it forcefully
Can
Miss Zhao understands justice well
I want Wei Zhuoran's body
What
Miss Zhao
Calm down first
The reason why Yuan Hao buried Wei Zhuoran generously
Send someone to guard the tomb
I just guessed Wei Yuan
Go to worship before the meeting
There's really no way around it
good
Then don't assassinate
Miss Zhao
Yuan Hao prepared his troops vigorously
We will send troops again within a few years
This person can't stay.
This is justice
Never do it because of personal selfishness
Shake the righteousness
Do you want some face?
I also want Wang Kuan’s arm
I really can't do it
We think of something
There's no reason to talk about righteousness
Just let others suffer
Miss Zhao's assassination
It's going to blow your head off
Let's help with something
as a matter of course
OK
saw the body
I'm the bride
Prime Minister as soon as possible
do you mean
Your father killed my father
Essentially
It’s to get you to leave Qizhai
He doesn't want his bloodline to be cut off
Then why should my father die?
Your father doesn't deserve to die
He is dead
Zhao Jian went to find Zang Pang.
She will help you find it
your father's body
do what
I swear to God
What Yuan Tianguan did
I didn't know beforehand
But after all, there is such a relationship
Yanei
if you are angry
Take my revenge
What are you doing for revenge?
It's not you who did it.
what are you doing
this life
I owe you
If you want to take
can be taken away at any time
stand up
You get up first
Get up
I don't want your life
I want to kill
It's Yuantianguan
Yanei
where to
Feeling depressed
Go out and sit
I'll go with you.
No
I want to be alone for a while
Xue Ying
Help press
Too much blood loss
Can it still be saved?
you promised me
grant me eternal life
I'll keep your soul
Back to Song Dynasty
I will give you eternal life
Thank you Dragon God
And there's more
I my that
Gong
Praying for a child
I’d rather trouble the Dragon God to worry about it.
he is
His name is Yuan Tianguan
yuantianguan
It’s come to this point
Are you still thinking about this?
Mr. Yuan
Mr. Yuan must not have expected
I'll be seriously injured
Fortunately, the Dragon God is here
Otherwise I'll really die
Mr. Yuan
I will also feel sad and blame myself
what you do
I want to kowtow to the Dragon God
have you ever thought about
will i
Not the Dragon God
Of course I thought about it
just in case
Both
What should I do if he lied to me?
Figured it out
I can't figure it out
forget about it
Why
this world
Not good for me
In addition to Mr. Yuan
no one needs me
Believe in the protection of the dragon god
I'm not so scared anymore
Mr. Yuan is in danger
I also
Dare to stand up
you have to be real
Otherwise I can't bear it
Can't stand it
Except Dragon God
I have nothing to rely on
this world
Not good for me
Dragon God's Protection
How lucky I am
You know me
What do you hate most about gods?
Blind believer
hope for everything
Entrust external things
But always forget
The one who crosses the world
Only people
Maybe they are just afraid
no support
Facing the world on their own
Too weak
so
Courage is the rarest thing
By order of the Blue Emperor
I asked Wei Zhuoran
People familiar with Yuan Tianguan
All returns are gathered here
I'm too lazy to look
Just tell me the result
Wei Zhuoran and Yuan Tianguan
After each surrendered
have no contact with each other
Everyone has asked
indeed
These two people
Almost never spoke
Then this is ridiculous
Leave it at Yuantian Pass
I don’t care about my family members
Take the risk to kill Wei Zhuoran
Then where did this killing come from?
Perhaps these two people were together during the Song Dynasty
There is hatred
Even if he doesn't take action
Wei Zhuoran will die as well
Why risk revenge?
Too
Wei Zhuoran was laughing when he died
This smile
I really don't understand
I thought about it.
Yuan Tianguan ignores
The life and death of the Yuan clan
Logically speaking
The Yuan clan should hate him
That's the truth
That's better
Save the Yuan clan
They should be better than us
I want to kill Yuan Tianguan even more
Also for Qingtianzi
Leave a name for cherishing talents
Good
Let go of that
Let the Prime Minister arrange it
yes
I have another plan
I don't know if it's feasible
explain
Even if Wei Zhuoran is dead
Can also be used as bait
People in the Song Dynasty paid great attention to matters after death
Not as good as
Take Wei Zhuoran's body
Leave it to Wei Chen
Carefully arranged
Force his son to show up
Prime Minister
Things about Wei Zhuoran
let me think again
yes
I'll take my leave first.
We're getting married in a few days
Serve some snacks
I understand
Go ahead