This is the place where Yuan Zhongxin was executed
South City Wild Forest
Why did the beheading leave the city?
Officials are kind and considerate of the people
My Great Song Law
Although there are hundreds of death penalty entries
Since the founding of the country
real execution
But less than ever
Especially in Kaifeng
Anyone sentenced to death in the capital
Three memorials are required for official approval.
In addition, there is always forgiveness
Over the years, even if he was sentenced to beheading
real execution
Only one out of ten
So just go out of the city and kill
A traitor like Yuan Zhongxin
No need to alert the officials
Behead someone outside the city to avoid accidents
Then why do you need the news?
tell us
I think Yuan Zhongxin has a pure nature
Not like a traitor
Let’s talk about the Yuan family
He was indeed not involved
Just die like that
It's quite unfair
Look at him pitifully
I am kind again
So just
The place of execution is given to you
afterwards
You can also collect a corpse
Three
Any more questions?
have
Pure nature
Are you sure you are talking about Yuan Zhongxin?
stop
Dean
That's it
Aoyama Midori
How about it
satisfied
If you are satisfied, go first
Yuan Zhongxin
Death is imminent
You have to be quick with your words
I know you're not convinced
It doesn't matter
I'm waiting for you to come to me
Must come
pull out
Execution
Dean
So fast
The time has not come yet
No need to wait
Kill or save?
Be careful
Zhao Jian
How dare you come?
Can you stop talking so much nonsense?
Who arranged it?
I do not know
I've arranged everything
Yanei
Watch your steps
Be careful
Protect the courtyard
Incense
This is an ordinary incense
This cigarette is not poisonous
Yuan Zhongxin
quick
stop him
Don't panic
There aren't many of them
superior
Is it true?
Fished out the Yuan family
Great idea worked
Stop him and don't let him run away
Fast Chase
I go
Chase
Who are you?
It's you
Let's go first
Xue Ying
Robbery of the Privy Council
You never thought about it
Will it hurt your parents?
If you don't want to be caught, go together.
Come on you
I'm going to chase someone
who are you
Don't be in a hurry, young hero
The truth lies ahead
You are from the Yuan clan
Wang Kuan
You came here with the swordsman
It seems that that person is Yu Chiyuan
The so-called Yuan family swordsman
So the real one who joined the Yuan family
Not Yuan Zhongxin
It's you
The human heart is more dangerous than Yu Yuan
Such people
God knows what he'll do
What kind of thing is coming
you are hurt badly
When did you
Walking together with the Yuan family
Don't worry
You know Wang Kuan’s character best
Let him explain first
OK
Then I'm not in a hurry
I listen to your explanation
I'll give you a chance to explain clearly
No need
What do you think of this person’s attitude?
He doesn't say anything
And the swordsman
He is obviously a disciple of the Yuan family
Do you want this kind of person?
How to believe him
It doesn't make sense
The Wang family is a famous family
His father also held an important official position
He has no reason to betray Song Dynasty
If it weren't for someone in the court
Tips
Lu Nanshan’s New Secret Pavilion
How could he fail in the Yuan family?
The Secret Pavilion has already changed
Such people
Don't say you're looking out for us
I'm afraid it's Qizhai's old place
I can’t even remember clearly
Why don't you leave here with me first?
You don't explain clearly
I won't go with you
The chief does not have to be like this
This sentence is long
Don't you feel guilty for shouting?
I have a clear conscience
Stop
Don't force me to draw my sword
Yuchi is here too
Go fast
Go to the hut in the woods
What is the situation now?
There is an ambush in the forest today
If I hadn't blocked it
None of you can leave
How can you help us
Explain later
Go over there quickly
go over there
The opposite
I don't like it the most
listen to other people's arrangements
I'm saving you
Do you think I believe it?
you
do not move
I have something to ask you
How did you get along with that swordsman?
Walking together
Are you also disciples of the Yuan family?
Speak clearly and don't leave yet
What's going on with Wang Kuan?
Yuan Zhongxin
Didn't you agree to ambush in advance?
How did you arrive?
This is the time according to military orders.
Fake
This is Yuchiyuan's own hand
handed to you
That's not the case
It was sent by Yuchi's soldiers.
Lead the team to search for forests
Get Yuchiyuan back to me
yes
All
Walk
Who are you?
Didn’t you say there is truth?
Where is it?
say
Those are
You
why would you
Join forces with the swordsman
Those are your people
what do you want
This is obvious
I'm saving Yuan Zhongxin's life
Why
Answer my question first
why would you
Join forces with the swordsman
What swordsman
The one who appeared with Wang Kuan
Wang Kuan
How did you meet Wang Kuan?
I'm not blind
impossible
Wang Kuan is missing
Why don't you leave here with me first?
Don't force me to draw my sword
You don't explain clearly
I won't go with you
Why is it so messy?
Wang Kuan is not with you
Are you here to save people?
Don’t you understand the official language?
Wang Kuan is missing
Quite a simple thing
Why can’t I understand it?
You haven't answered me yet
Why should we save Yuan Zhongxin?
Who are those people?
You wait for a while, you wait for a while
Yu Chiyuan
Time is running out
I want to go back and play with Lu Nanshan
You will meet up with Yuan Zhongxin, right?
What's the meaning
Tell him when you meet
Wanshengmen ghost market tonight
I'll give you the truth
Subordinates are incompetent
Yuan Zhongxin
Let the Yuan family swordsman rescue him
That's right
Although wearing a hat
But I definitely know the sword skills
I have a blood feud with him
Never admit mistakes
It seems Qizhai
We also cooperated with Yuanjia
have a look
This is
This is the wrong time to ambush.
Dean
I had someone give it to me
It's definitely not this
Who was the one who gave the order?
Yard Infantry
I also often follow him to do things.
Where are the people?
today
I should be on duty in the hospital today
Then why are you still kneeling here?
Find someone to go
This isn't your boudoir, is it?
if not
sit
This is the home of my youth
Does it hurt?
how could be
It doesn't hurt at all
Lie to face
Aren't you worried?
Mouth is quite sweet
always sweet
Don't you make me mad to death
I'm just thankful
Speak with conscience
Have I ever been angry with you?
In terms of conscience, do you have a conscience?
Or do you understand me
transfer
Where is Xue Yingyanei?
I told them
Meet at my house
Is it seriously injured?
ringworm disease
You wait for me here
I'll be back soon
Don't move around
Chief
Are you two okay?
I slipped away a long time ago
On the way back, I met Xiao Xue
Chief
Yu Chiyuan and those men in black
We're in a group
They said they also saw Wang Kuan
We also saw it
Yu Chiyuan also said
Wanshengmen ghost market tonight
give us the truth
Good to know
Yuchiyuan’s identity change
Is it a little too fast?
I'm hungry. Let's go cook some food in the kitchen.
I'm not hungry
Leave them alone for a while
I'm hungry
OK
That
Find yourselves something to eat
it's okay no problem
You're busy
leave us alone
good
Sleepy
How many days have you not had
Have a good sleep
Not long after
Sit on the bed
Clothes are too dirty
less nonsense
Take off your shoes
Go up
This isn't appropriate, is it?
All engaged
Is there anything inappropriate?
What is this for?
The blood is all dried up
I want to wipe your face
I can just wipe it myself
Didn't I tell you to stop moving?
how
You can only be sweet to me
I also want to be sweet to you
No?
Okay, you have the final say
The water is a bit hot
I'll wipe it for you later
Your boudoir is quite nice
But you are the princess
Compare this to
Also unbelievably luxurious
Compared
Who to compare with?
Who else’s boudoir have you seen?
Never seen it
okay
Lie down
not sleepy
My father is a prince
I have no power and no money
But home
Just be comfortable
childhood
I live here with my dad
Still quite happy
are you still hungry
Not completely full anyway
Let me tell you
They both now
Can't control us anymore
This is what I said
The seniority is wrong
They are both unavailable now
no way
Only by yourself
Cook for yourself
You forget it
Your father and mother’s craftsmanship
You haven't learned anything at all
I just practiced swordsmanship
It has to be me
Those two aren't here.
It all depends on me
You burned the cake last time
No baking this time
Make soup cakes
Wait
soup cake
Not handled well
If it weren't for the headmaster teaching us
Say don't waste food
I will never eat your soup cake.
Try it first
What's wrong
It tastes pretty good
It’s not hopeless after all
Take a look
You still have to rely on me
Should you call me
A big brother
Think about it carefully
what to think
Zhaizhang and Yuan Zhongxin compete with you
Which of you is senior?
Then they must be both of them
Then I call you Big Brother
how to call them
yes
Is it possible to call me daddy?
Just wait a moment
Wait until I finish eating and then go get two bowls
besides
Too much noodles
There are many
Can I not count this?
Do not worry
We can definitely finish it
You just keep looking at me
Dreamed about your brother
how do you know
You keep frowning
Dreamed about it for a while
In my dreams I am
I can't see him clearly
never mind
Let’s not talk about this anymore
It's fine
There is no one in this world
It is indestructible
Everyone is qualified to be vulnerable
I'm not in front of you
Have you cried many times?
you know i often think
My brother knew him at first
When I was of Xianbei bloodline
Know Yuanjia
When serving Xixia
What does it feel like inside?
During the reign of Emperors Yan and Huang
There is only Central Plains in the world
The integration of each surname
Achievement
The current power of China
family past
Just a mark in the history books
Born in the Song Dynasty and raised in the Song Dynasty
write the same words
say the same thing
Song people
You are comforting me
I really think so
Maybe one day Liaoxixia
All will belong to the Song Dynasty
But it's possible that one day
It's not called the Song Dynasty anymore.
But China will always be there
But we can't see it anymore
So we have to tightly
seize now
I took Xue Ying and Yanei
Forget about it
I'll take a look at them
What are you two eating?
soup cake
All soup cakes
I love eating soup cakes so much
I don’t want to eat soup cakes anymore in my life
What nonsense are you talking about?
I made this at home
Your father should be sad when you look back
Who is to blame?
Why are you sitting here until now?
You didn't even say a word to me.
fine
It's good to sit and eat something
is not it
Yes Yes
Wanshengmen ghost market
Okay
Let's go later
Meet this Yu Chiyuan
But I don't understand
Yu Chiyuan
Aren't they Lu Nanshan's subordinates?
Why do you need someone to save you?
Because he may be an accomplice of the Yuan family
But he is not
Do you want to seek revenge from your father?
How could he be an accomplice of the Yuan family?
Who said this?
He said it himself
When you are ambushed
Are they all together?
That's not the case
Searched separately
But not far away
first
Xiao Li was ambushed near the ancestral hall
Xiao Zhao also rushed there quickly
Lao Gu also joined the siege
Just the ambusher
Very strong martial arts
Hidden weapons also make people skilled
The whole plan was almost flawless
They even set traps in advance
Even if there are a hundred secrets and a few sparse places
It's hard for them to fly even if they have no wings.
so smart
amazing
When they were searching Yuan's house
Did you find anything?
Only some furniture and clothing left
All the letters and the like are gone.
The clues were also burned away
no trace
Understood
The Yuan family is about to ambush
But the trap
Only located near the ancestral hall
Not available anywhere else
There are so many people in the Yuan family
But only the swordsman was left
Yu Chiyuan said that their team
are searched separately
But what if
one of them
heard fighting
Don't go directly to the ancestral hall
Instead, ask for help
how to deal with
Will it
What is hidden in the ancestral hall?
That's not right either
He later found nothing in his search
That's right
all burned
No clues
In that case
There is still an ambush person left.
do what
Isn't that unnecessary?
There was no news
Nothing can be found
Just leave a clue
What if this ambush person
Got caught, the ambush failed.
what to do
possible
It's his confidence
What's the point?
Excuse me
Should we kill Yu Chiyuan's group?
Is there any difference?
It's unnecessary
May also be cruel
Warning to the court
My so-called dad
Never act impulsively
Do those useless things
Everyone has gone
Why leave another clue?
Since that
No need to kill people
Why leave someone to ambush you?
Yu Chiyuan's words
listen
Seems a bit logical
But when I think about it actually
Isn’t it a bit
suspicious
Think about it from another perspective
Maybe you can figure it out
That's right
The most critical
Actually that's the sentence
How many of your group were injured or killed?
Except me
All died
Xinmi Pavilion wants to investigate the Yuan family
Someone leaked the news
So who could it be?
The Yuan family is complicit in the court
If
No internal accomplices
who could that be
But Yuan family
He did escape beforehand
In addition to the court
Who else knows
A person who takes orders
If we talk about the person who tipped off the information
That's Yu Chiyuan
what will happen
he
You may not be able to escape
The eyes and ears of teammates around you
So Yuchiyuan’s team
Must be wiped out
This is silence
In this way
The Killer Chigen Squad
Just what must be done
rather than dispensable
Yuan family accomplice
It's Yu Chiyuan himself
He unites the Yuan family
Kill his colleagues
and then accuse
Blame it on the so-called swordsman
But who is that swordsman?
Yu Chiyuan said that the swordsman
Appeared with Wang Kuan today
Not in a hurry
one by one
Foresight Complete Retelling
When did you start
Beginning to doubt Yu Chiyuan
After listening to his story
It started
So you have no proof
You are not afraid of your own guesses
is it wrong
If it is a guess
That could be wrong
But this kind of thing
How could it be just conjecture?
Is it possible that there is evidence?
He is the only one left alive in the whole team.
Where can I find evidence?
Let’s go to Wanshengmen first
Waiting to meet Yu Chiyuan
Let me show you the evidence
coming
It should be him
Are you surprised?
No need to pretend to be calm
Didn't you expect that?
it's me
Save your life
I know you are at this time
Already full of doubts
Unable to understand
yes
We both thought hard
Never thought of it
Why did you save Yuan Zhongxin?
Thinking about it makes us almost crazy
right
I
I'm so anxious that I'm getting angry
Don't get angry
There are always people who are better than you.
I have a good plan in mind
I just pretend to be straightforward and honest on weekdays.
This scheming
Of course others can't guess it
you thought you were in a dungeon
Tricked me into leaking my address to Zhao Jian
Am I really fooled?
all of these
It's all in my plan
shocked
Brother, hurry up and say it.
There are puzzles that cannot be solved
It's really worrying
He really wants to know the answer.
Going crazy
Whatever
I will tell the truth
Let me know
Why should I save you?
naturally for
Yuan family bloodline inheritance
That's right
I'm the
Yuan family accomplice
Didn't expect it
Are you
Didn't hear what I was saying
I see
who can imagine
Unexpected
Really talented
Dragon among people
Yuan Zhongxin
Your Majesty has explained
Want to protect your life
You should understand now
He is your biological father after all
Don't be upset, either.
Think carefully
Your own name
What happened to my name
Your brother's name is Yuan Bo Fin
Your name is Yuan Zhongxin
Brothers, brothers, uncles, and cousins
This is the order of direct brothers
in your name
Since it has the character Zhong
Explain your father
I have always regarded you as my own flesh and blood
You misunderstood him
My name was given to me by my elder brother
That's pretty much it.
Your Majesty to you
Also concerned
Then do you know
He used to torture me
They suspect that I am pretending to be the son of the Yuan family
If my elder brother hadn't dissuaded me
I can be beaten to death
After all, they are father and son
Not so much
Then come and save me
It was he who asked you to come
That's not the case
Your father is not in Kaifeng again
Save your business
I planned it
Then you pretended to be at the Yuan family before?
ambushed
He taught you
Not really
I figured it out myself
Figure it out yourself
flawless
Death without evidence
who can guess
I
He is the Yuan family's accomplice
That swordsman in a bamboo hat is also you
Figured it out myself
that is not
When at the Yuan family
I've actually seen this guy
I was wise and thoughtful at that time
There will always be mistakes
For a little mistake
I had to bear the pain
Secretly assassinating colleagues
He may have seen it
I'm in the story
treat him as a murderer
I also want to borrow the power of the government
Find this swordsman
Take the opportunity to eradicate
to eliminate future troubles
But he
How could he and Wang Kuan get together?
Who knows?
execution
He and Wang Kuan are also here to save you
He is also a disciple of Mr. Yuan
Could it be that I really guessed it?
That
You save me from this
Aren’t you afraid of Lu Nanshan?
Find out the clues
Lu Nanshan is deep in thought
I really can’t stay in the capital anymore.
Just right
you can come with me
Go see Mr. Yuan
you know where he is
of course I know
Your father is here
In Tanzhou
Jinghu South Road
what to do there
Looking for someone
Who to look for
You go to Tanzhou
Mr. Yuan told you himself
I'm the best at keeping secrets
How can you say
Then when will we set off?
so
Afternoon
find a place
Join partners
Yuchi Yuan did not follow secretly
Everyone watching around them has also withdrawn.
How was the talk?
He is indeed a disciple of the Yuan family
So we have to save Yuan Zhongxin
Not only to save
I also want to reunite his father and son.
where to
Jinghu South Road, Tanzhou
When to set off
the day after tomorrow
But Wang Kuan and the others
Still missing?
Don't worry, go.
This is not the way back to Saicho's house.
Why are you back here again?
Go in first
There's someone waiting inside
Who?
Wang Kuan
Small Scene
Sister Zhao
coming
Why are you here?
When did you make an appointment?
Isn't it agreed?
Do you want to tell you the truth?
So you have no proof
You are not afraid
Is my guess wrong?
Let’s go to Wanshengmen first
Waiting to meet Yu Chiyuan
I'll show you the evidence
What evidence
Of course it's a witness
I'm at Yuan's
Saw Yuchiyuan murder someone
I am a witness