so
Liang Zhu is the stone you threw
How can he find a way out?
No
Your men
It's the stone that's thrown
I guess
Your men
Should follow now
Coach Liang, right?
Your Majesty’s Approval for Privy Council Affairs
Who else in the world can break the situation?
Saw my husband
We are following the Xuanwu Army in the capital.
Liang Zhu comes
Liang Zhu went to Qizhai
You may have a plan to come here now
Sir, please pay attention
Xianggong
We are really Lu Nanshan’s subordinates
Lu Nanshan, deputy commissioner of the Privy Council
Then drive people out
Word spread
Now that there's been a fuss
Just make things clear
Get up
Xie Xianggong
Someone just entered the backyard
yes
Warrant from Xianggong's Mansion for visitors
He only said that he was ordered to inspect the carriage.
This happens every day
Just let him come in and do some work
That person is Liang Zhu
Find people
yes
Lu Zhangyuan sent greetings to the Prime Minister
Mr. Ling has returned to Kaifeng
Please rest assured, Mr.
Wang is only involved in political affairs
Second rank official position
I dare not say the word "husband"
Sir, you are too modest
No one in the world knows
It is the prime minister's right to participate in political affairs
Now the Song Dynasty is peaceful and peaceful
It was all done by Mr. Wang alone.
It can be said that the Song Dynasty was lucky
How can it be considered as one person's strength?
Can be considered
it's him
Liangzhu, the capital of Xuanwu Army
I’ve met Mr. Xianggong
why did you come here
Your Majesty asked me to bring you a letter
Bring the letter
The son said
this letter
Want me to read it aloud to you in person?
No need to bring it over
Xianggong
You'd better listen to it
Read it
Trouble Coach Liang
this letter
Please read it out loud then
It's that simple
The one who bows down to me, my father,
Although my son is stupid
But I also know how to be a human being
Self-respecting and unconventional
Don’t be righteous within yourself
During the turbulent times of the Song Dynasty
The son threw himself into the Secret Pavilion
Just want to be a torch
In the gloomy place
Shine a ray of skylight
Qizhai was established
Although he has no achievements in the world
But with a clear conscience
I wait
Once in prison
Once surrounded by enemies
The line between life and death has not stopped
What Qizhai did
The heart of desire
Nothing but worthy of others
Not afraid of God
most critical time
My Heart
No worries
This life has been devoted to the Song Dynasty
You should sweat your heart out
Enter China again in the next life
Narrow escape
without regrets
Everyone in Qizhai
All like this
Prince Wang Kuan
Crying blood and stopping one's head
Such a boy
If you are still suspected by your own family,
What else is there to say?
Write to him
official
Kaifeng city
There is a person who is higher than my father
Who are you talking about
Mingdao 2nd year
After the officialdom is abolished, you know, right?
Why did you mention this matter?
The first year of Jingyou
The official family thought about establishing another queen
I know
The current Queen Cao?
At that time, His Majesty was interested in
Shouzhou Chen family
But the other party has a low status
The ministers advised and admonished
Finally let it go
Chen's father is a tea merchant
Bought the official position of city envoy
Officials are generous and affectionate
Although Chen did not enter the palace,
But it has never been forgotten by the officials
How do you know this?
Secret meetings between officials and their families outside the palace
It's all arranged by my father
I know it, of course.
Xiaolu Zhangyuan
do you know
Today is such a coincidence
Just in time
You are so brave
Dean
Liang Zhu entered the courtyard of a tea merchant
I also followed in
Then Mr. Wang came
The officials are also there
Dean
The officials have spoken
What did you say
Calculation
explain
Oral admonition
Official
Oral advice to you
Official oral instructions
You have to
Since the establishment of Qizhai
Although the behavior is absurd
But after all, young and energetic
Loyalty can be learned
No need for house arrest anymore
Let them do things
Who would have thought that the official family would be there?
What a Wang Kuan
no
I think it’s wrong
This official had a private meeting with the Chen family
Wang Kuan, you got him out
What if the official family
suddenly become angry
Then our brains are gone?
The official is kind-hearted
What if you are suddenly unkind?
Don't worry
My father is involved in political affairs
Officials won't kill me
What about us?
Based on the relationship between Xiaojing and me
Of course she's fine
Wang Kuanna
It's still too late
Xiao Xue and I are looking for your father
Become a foster father
That's okay too
An urgent and helpless act
What about the future
Just change your name to Wang Ying
I'll call it
Wang Yuan
You can go
There is a purpose
You are so brave
This is it
Even if the government is kind-hearted
What if we don't care about this little thing?
Lu Nanshan captures Yuan Zhongxin
was supported by the Privy Council
And my father is involved in political affairs
My father and the Privy Council are working together
The officials don’t know
what would he think
What if the officials know?
The Yuan family disappeared
Before the case is settled
Who will inform the officials?
Unsolved troubles
It’s always a matter of incompetence
Will report back after resolution
That is to make a great contribution
The order before and after is correct
them
I'm punishing you again
I thought you would be the first
Do it to me
Beat him until he can't resist
Not interested in
Didn’t you make a move when we first met?
I was angry
My colleagues are all taken advantage of by your Yuan family
Killed
understand
So I took you
when dizzy
And put you on the grass
Let you lie down comfortably
calm down
I was careless.
honestly
It's no use catching me
The Yuan family won't come
Don’t speak too absolutely
blood is thicker than water
Where are Wang Kuan and the others?
Forget it
That kid is too brave
Alarmed the officials
Now
Fish returns to the sea
Break free from the cage
Your home is quite stylish
It looks better than mine
good
I'm almost lost
It doesn’t matter if I’m homeless
Why did you come to Wang Kuan's house?
Afraid of causing trouble to the family
Hello, sir
Our Dad
what does it mean
Should we go?
Say hello
Take three of them
Take me to the yard where I studied when I was young
Arrange accommodation for each
how about you
I'll come as soon as I go
don’t worry
You say
This father and son meet again after a long separation
Will you hold your head and cry?
Three of you, please come with me.
Why don't you tie it so tightly?
I drink it myself
Afraid you'll run away
I already said that
I
No running
You don't run
Plan to stay here forever
Not long
how
Thinking that Wang Kuan and others will come to rescue you
Where is Zhao Jian?
There's a wake
Just give up.
She tied you up and handed you over
I've made it clear that I don't want to talk to you.
You Qizhai
How did it come together?
to be honest
It was Zhao Jian who forcibly captured me.
Then what
Then these idiots
Just drag me into the ditch
You know the most fatal thing
What is it?
What
follow them
We've been together for a long time
I've become as stupid as them
How to call stupid
Just believe
Good in the Heart
believe
This world still has meaning
I believe it’s better to be together than alone
Is there anything wrong
if a person
I have been involved in intrigues and deceptions since I was a child.
Come out after being beaten and beaten
he will know
These things
How childish is that?
How stupid
But you still believed it
I've become stupid too
So joined them
Do you regret it?
have you ever thought about
You may live a lifetime
I can't live without this prison.
I can no longer see the outside world
Your companions are helpless
No one can get you out
If it weren't for you and them
Getting too close
Maybe it won't be today
Maybe
even so
No regrets
never regret
you should regret
What do you regret?
know these people
You said Qizhai
you are a scholar
There should be a bright future
where are they
Who are they?
for these people
You plan to
The fate of the Wang family
Are you all on board?
Why did you come around in a circle to get here?
The master said
I want you to listen
The so-called Qizhai
They are all people who act ridiculously
Then Zhao Jian is still a royal relative
A bit like a lady
nothing
Zhao Jian looks like Zhao Jian
Why be the same as others
a princess
With someone like Yuan Zhongxin
Come together
They match each other very well
You also know about the Yuan family
Yuan Zhongxin is finished
Can you let me see him?
What's the use of meeting each other?
Or
You want to find the location of the prison
Find a chance to rescue him
Who else
Xue Ying
A son of a military family
Afraid of even reading the sages’ books
Haven't read it yet
The words engraved on the back of his hand
You may not be able to wash it off in this life
Except for brute force
What else can he do?
Don’t you have anything to say?
You finish first
Who is left
Scenery in Yanei
Wei Yuan
Unlearned, unskilled and stubborn
The character is also low
People like him
How can I be with you?
Uncle is right
The last Pei Jing
Let's go and stop listening.
Look at the signature first
Han Duanzhang
Let’s see who we write to
Pei Xuan
My brother
Still remember Han Duanzhang
Is this the name?
Remember
The Liao people killed his father
Dayanlin
Killed all his relatives
Han Duanzhang, Superintendent of Tiyin in the Great Liao Dynasty
Bohai Survivor Liao Kingdom Secret Agent
Want to provoke war between Song and Liao
Long before Han Duanzhang went to Beijing
The Pei family had correspondence with him
See for yourself
The letter made it very clear
The Pei family already knew about Han Duanzhang
Have revenge
What do you think this means?
The Pei family and Han may be accomplices
I do not know
Of course we believe you
Have you met Han Duanzhang?
seen
Pei Jing was also there at that time
That's right
Han Duanzhang once blocked others
Attack Xiaojing
Is this true?
Died
Don't hurt innocent people
have
why not kill her
Just because they are both Bohai people
That's what I just said
They were accomplices
Where did the letter come from?
Found out
Where are the Pei family?
Didn't catch them
It's also for your accomplices
Save some face
Why did you think of searching the Pei family?
Because of the relationship between Xiaojing and me
This letter is not a fake after all
a letter
How can we convict
Pei Jing is of Bohai bloodline
Another old case with Han Broken Chapter
unclear
What is your identity?
You are my royal son.
Both character and knowledge are of the highest quality
Now
Even the officials know your name
Your life has unlimited potential
A woman like Pei Jing
How can I be worthy of you
Three
I've heard everything I need to hear.
please
where to
Of course I will settle you down
thank you
please
Can you give me this letter?
You keep it
You said so much
what do you want me to do
with your wisdom
Will you not understand?
I still want to ask
You were with them
Not from the same world
Released
Let go of friends
Teenager's friend
How many people can stay the same with each other?
Mostly parting ways
There is always someone who goes with you all the way
Wang Kuan
What is called growth as a person walks in the world
sometimes
Just learn to give up
What to give up
past self
Don’t let go of your past self
How can I cope with this world?
Frost Sword
Wakubun Wakuwa
The world is changing
Dynasties also changed
What's more, people
Kuan'er
Everyone has their youth
Juvenile
Sometimes it's a sweet dream
Now I have woken up from my dream
It's time for you to grow up too
the father i know
All human beings
will eventually change
I hope you understand
maybe one day
I will betray who I am now
Live in a way that you hate
but not now
Of course people change
But have some thoughts
have some persistence
should not waver
if you grow up
Just kill yesterday's self
Abandon the light in your heart
Then I would rather spend my life
always young
You make me very disappointed
me too
What's the point of your insistence?
Persistence is meaning in itself
See how filial you are
I don’t even want to leave
You can't leave either
Now there are three floors inside and three floors outside.
There are people trampling outside
They were all scared by you
learn from mistakes
I'll know later
Zhao Jian ties you up
You don't hate her
In this life
You will always meet someone special
What's special
No matter what she does to you
You won't blame her or hate her
are you willing to do it for her
Climb all the mountains
Even willing to do it for her
Give your life
That's not stupid.
And you
in life
Is there such a special person?
indeed there is one
How far has it developed?
What step
Have you ever held hands?
Have you made an appointment?
Which hand do you hold and what is your marriage?
The one I'm talking about
He is an upright man
It's not what you think
The one I'm talking about is my benefactor
no matter what he does to me
I won't blame him or hate him
Even willing to cross mountains and ridges for him
Killing and stealing goods
even
Give your life
Roughly the same
Who?
You will know later
I will know later
Looks like I know him
What nonsense are you talking about?
What did I say
what did you say
My benefactor did it to me
cruel training
Not from my mouth
Reveal secrets
underwent brutal training
Could it be
Lu Nanshan Bar
How can that be?
Isn’t it the current head of the Secret Pavilion?
Lu Nanshan?
It looks like it is indeed Lu Nanshan
Stop guessing
How about it
How about what
The rooms are cleaned
Scanned
All good
Your yard is not bad either
these books
You read them all when you were a child
That's not bad
No wonder he is knowledgeable
My dad gave it to me
Talk about your home
I had exchanged letters with Han Duanzhang
Just show it to Xiao Jing directly.
Why not?
normal person
Why don't you just keep it a secret for now?
No need
If you have something to say, you should be honest
hide concealment
It will only breed suspicion
The so-called misunderstanding between people
Often this arises from
maybe it's true
Small Scene
Think about it carefully before speaking
There's a date on this letter
Think back to that time
My family does often meet with people
There is correspondence
And help deliver letters
They are all caravans heading north to Liao.
I asked my dad at that time
He said he was in contact with his fellow tribesmen
But never said his name
Looking at it now
It should be Han Duanzhang
this
How did they know each other?
Han Duanzhang ah
I don’t know that either.
But this matter
You don’t have to do this either
Admit it honestly
Brother Wang treats me with sincerity
I don’t have to lie
What did I say
Did I just meet you?
Let's just say they are a perfect match.
No
You take care of others as soon as you meet them
Call me little lady
Why are you talking about this?
I also want to be honest
Why don't you shut up?
My dad said something to me
Generally
Just say that you are all cunning friends.
You want me to cut off contact with you
to be honest
actually
we all heard it
Yeah
My father arranged for you to listen
if not
Xue Ying
In addition to force, you also have courage
can be your friend
it's my honour
me too
Small Scene
My father will not marry you
What
I am the one who will marry you
So what does he think of you?
Doesn't matter
what about me
no no
Don't think about the previous sentence
I mean
Your father also said that I am uneducated and have no skills.
What are you going to tell me?
My dad is right
Wang Kuan
You don't have to be so straightforward
I don't lie
Then you don’t have to say it
you asked
Then I was wrong
It doesn't matter
what
You start to forgive me
You are indeed ignorant
naughty
But to say you have low moral character
absolutely wrong
Yanei
You have a pure heart
Almost Tao
Although I didn’t understand
But you should be complimenting me, right?
I just read too few books
No need to add the last sentence
I won't leave you
Isn't that nonsense?
Our seven fasts are one body
Let's all settle in first
Small Scene
Come with me later
where to
Go to your house
Are you so direct?
good
You agreed now
Why do you talk so much about other people's affairs?
Fortunately, Xiao Jing fell in love with Wang Kuan
What if Xiao Jing was
It's me
I can't stand it
Such a straightforward person
okay
No one likes you
Walk
What do you know
Do you know Bashai Chuniao?
Do you know what she thinks?
never mind
With a rigid person like you
It doesn't make sense
Everything is mine
Go a little further
We're almost there after passing Jieshen Lane
Not urgent
Walk Slowly
Your home is not far from Jieshen Lane
yes
I can be considered around that area
grown up
Remember Jieshen Lane
There seem to be more gold and silver shops
My parents also did that business
But later I got into debt
All paid off
Returned
It was the manager who helped pay it off.
Lu Zhangyuan
Mr. Lu is familiar with your parents
Not really
At that time, Lu Zhangyuan
I need my Bohai identity
Go north to Liao
My parents took me
Sent to the Secret Pavilion
The governor settled the debt
Isn't this just selling you?
There's nothing we can do
Where's your brother?
My parents asked the dean
Gave him a patch
The vacancy of the right guard
Later, it seemed that I was in the Planning Department of Beijing North
Sending
It's what you got in exchange for it.
How long has it been since you last seen them?
After entering the secret pavilion
Not seen much anymore
they never came to see you
They are also busy
It's okay, Brother Wang
Do not be angry
What can I do for my family?
it's always good
Moreover
How nice it is to be in the secret pavilion
I also met you
Let's go
Keep leading the way
Xiao Xue
Xiao Xue Xiao Xue
What's wrong
Go out for a walk
Something
Aren’t we going to help Yuan Zhongxin?
yes
Then you have to tell the chief.
Right
Tell us about the current situation
Also discuss what to do next
Let me tell you
To save Yuan Zhongxin
The chief is definitely interested
But Lu Nanshan didn’t say
Before the chief, Yuan Zhongxin
Handed it over
Can you believe this?
I bet you
If this is true
I'll take my head off and play with it for you
What's so funny about your head?
Just treat it as a collection
Really
Let me tell you
Just Zhaizhang and Yuan Zhongxin
impossible
Go Go Go
Why don't you close your eyes and sleep?
What if someone saves you?
Maybe for colleagues
chance for revenge
Quite persistent
When you went to Yuan's house
How did you get ambushed?
Ordered to search your home
After arriving, the house was empty.
The whole clan is gone
And after that
After that, I searched at Yuan’s house.
Let's see if there are any clues
Then they were ambushed
That's how it goes
The Yuan family is gone.
Obviously someone tipped off the news
Left early
How many of your group were injured or killed?
Except me
All died
Talk about it in detail
Didn’t you say everything?
Search your home
When you are ambushed
Are they all together?
That's not the case
Searched separately
But not far away
first
Xiao Li was ambushed near the ancestral hall
Xiao Zhao also rushed there quickly
Lao Gu also joined the siege
It’s just the martial arts of the ambusher
Very strong
Hidden weapons also make people skilled
The whole plan was almost flawless
They even set traps in advance
Even if there are a hundred secrets and a few sparse places
It's hard for them to fly even if they have no wings.
so smart
amazing
What's wrong
Any questions
When they were searching Yuan's house
Did you find anything?
Only some furniture and clothing left
All the letters and the like are gone.
The clues were also burned away
no trace
why are you laughing
I understand it basically.
What did I say
What do you understand?
What does the ambusher look like?
Didn't I say it?
Wearing a bamboo hat
The knife is carried diagonally on the back
The knife is very fast
Swordsman with bamboo hat
strangeness
Why is it so late at night?
Still wearing a hat?
Have you seen it before?
Go to your house
Princess
Someone wants to see you
who
Said to be the companion of the princess
One named Wei
A person named Xue
Sorry, both of you.
The princess is still keeping vigil
Can't see guests
Did you say what our name is?
Naturally said
Princess
I also know who you two are.
Then did you say that we
It’s about Yuan Zhongxin
All said
Then why don't you see us?
Why
Wake up
A wake is not a closed door to thank guests
It stands to reason that we should also
Go in and worship
Don't ask me
How do I know
The chief doesn't care about Yuan Zhongxin anymore
Will Yuan Zhongxin be handed over?
It's also true
Won't
The chief is in mourning
This situation is special
Then what about
We save people ourselves
How to save?
you say
Our Qizhai
It won't break up, right?
Didn’t you just say you still don’t know how to do it?
I'll just say that
it's okay no problem
Go back to Wang Kuan to discuss it.
Not a big problem
blood stains
not much
It's been some time
Small Scene
Which room does your parents have?
It's bolted inside
what to do
There seems to be a slight movement
There's someone inside
Breaking through the window
You answer
good
Hero, spare your life
How many are
A Xuan
Parents
what are you doing
sister
Could this be the prince?
I'm Wang Kuan
Finally waited for the prince
Prince Wang
You get up first
Never kneel
can we sit down and talk
sorry
I'll go back and find someone to fill this window.
Don't think about smashing it early.
Breathable
It's so open
Yes Yes
father
Why is there blood in the yard?
The chicken I killed for lunch today
Stewed until now
Just waiting for the prince.
how do you know
Brother Wang is coming
My dad told me
What kind of person is Mr. Wang?
Find a servant
Just a little reminder is enough
Why explain it in person?
What happened to the money?
Xiao Jing
Our family is quite broad.
Can help people do some business
They just come to the door
Don't tell me yet
Where is this person who comes to the door?
He is a generous person
Is it legal?
How can you collect that money?
First time is first time
If you don’t believe me, ask your parents
Yeah
Just the first time
But there’s more than one box, right?
The one who was wearing a hat just now
I'm also here to do business with you.
is not that right
What a weirdo
Arrived at the house
Don't take off the hat.