You two already knew
What’s the matter with Wang Kuan?
It's not too early
Then you should be in advance
Tell Xiao Jing
Is it still a surprise if you tell me in advance?
you
Did we grow up together?
Not really
We've known each other for a few years
Only a few years
can be entrusted with life and death
Didn’t Wang Kuan just say that?
Prime Minister Bai knows that he still presses his sword
It doesn’t matter how long we’ve known each other
What is the white head?
Prime Minister Bai knows that he still presses his sword
Wang Mojie's famous sayings
Wang Mojie is also your friend
He is not
He was a poet of the Tang Dynasty
You Song people
Can everyone read and recite poetry?
Definitely not everyone
What about Xue Ying?
Him
He knows how to wield a knife and a gun
Memorizing poetry is a mess
But I think
Sword dancing is good.
My dad is here
Xiao Xue
calm
Go back and sit down
This is the commander-in-chief of the Youzhou capital
Liang Gewei
Xiao Xue
sit down
Aren’t your martial arts skills even higher?
Why was he arrested as soon as he showed his face?
No matter how high your martial arts skills are
There are too many people.
What did the commander-in-chief of Liang Du say?
I'll give you a moment to burn incense
tell me
why should i
Risking life and death with you
Enemy with Qingtianzi
Is the truth made clear?
I will cooperate with you
give him back to you
What if it doesn't make sense?
I'll give you his head back
sit
I can't get up
Then I sit and talk
If you don't cooperate, then don't cooperate.
Why kill people?
It makes no sense
Do you think I look like a reasonable person?
It doesn't really look like it
You should be more attentive in persuading me.
let's start
remember
The time of a stick of incense
Fragrant
What
You just said the time for one stick of incense
Don't light this fragrance
How do you calculate time?
You didn't bring any incense
OK
Yanei
What is he doing?
Going to look for incense
Don't be in a hurry. Don't be in a hurry.
Take it easy
The time of a stick of incense
The fragrance is ready
Why do you bring incense when you go out?
To tell you the truth
If not for this
The space in the car is not big enough
We even brought the coffin
Yes, that's what I use for sleeping.
Wouldn't that be very disturbing?
I have a mattress inside
That's okay
you listen
hurry up
You don't have much time
I'll do that
Go ahead
Let me confirm with you again
what you just meant
It takes a stick of incense to convince you
Cooperate with us
right
Then if it takes just one stick of incense
Exceed
Just chop off Xue Ying's head
Right
That's what it means
It's up to you whether you can save him or not.
OK
Went out
You kill Xue Ying
what are you doing
Kill you and kill Xue Ying
these words
Which word do you not understand?
Do you think I dare not?
what are you doing
Willing to admit defeat
Liang Du ordered the army to invite
father
You just can't keep calm
Look at other people
You really think I don’t dare to kill him
Of course you dare to kill him
Of course he dares to kill us
Then what
Are you waiting for Yuan Hao to kill you?
Why did Yuan Hao want to kill me?
The left wing commanded the army
and the right wing both commanded the army
has now become
Yuan Hao's personal guard
This situation now
Can't you see?
Did you really explain it to him?
I talked too much
Excuse me
What does Yuan Hao want to do?
Du Tongjun, you know best
so
We are not here to advise you
cooperate with us
Rather, you have now
No way back
Lu Nanshan
Anyway, walking in the Privy Council of the Song Dynasty
what about you
A bunch of common people brats
Lu Nanshan didn’t dare to kill Yuan Hao
we dare
I heard I have money now
I heard you are very good at fighting now.
amazing
Cooperation can
a condition
Convince Queen Yeli
The Queen Does Not Enter the Game
Youzhou Army stayed out of the matter
I know
I will take a trip to Helan Mountain myself
Waiting for your news
How about I send them to Helan Mountain?
you are with them
How can I stay out of it?
Walk
Let’s discuss later
We Qizhai are together again
very nice
Three years
Everyone has changed
yes
But you haven't changed
Even you have changed
Looks better
real or fake
real
Feeling particularly good
Maybe the rouge used is better
What rouge
I've prepared it for you too
No, no, no
This has nothing to do with rouge
The most important thing is to have a good foundation
How do you say that
Naturally beautiful
Yuan Zhongxin
You have changed too
How has he changed?
Become more fond of telling the truth
Makes sense
Okay everyone
Our current goal is simple
Go to Helan Mountain first
Meet up with Yasai
Then meet Queen Yeli
Convince Queen Yeli
Winning over the Youzhou Army
reuse at last
Bazhai's plan to become a god
Three-pronged approach to capture Yuan Hao
Now it seems
Sounds like the hardest level
This is the level of Queen Yeli
Ning Lingge’s mother
Yuan Hao's wife
Didn't know it would be
what kind of person
What are you doing up so early?
I really have a dream
Your Highness
Please go faster
Didn't wake up
What time is this?
I was so tired last night.
what did you do last night
hunt
beat
Helan Mountain is a holy mountain
How dare you hunt?
Keep your voice down
Not good to be heard
Then don't go
good
move
The Queen has been waiting for a long time.
Come on, your highness.
Please wake up
Queen Mother
why are you crying
This tastes terrible
How do you eat it?
The grass seeds from the East Wing are here
This is what the tribesmen eat because they have no choice but to eat it.
Fighting every year these years
In my territory of Daxia
Can you still eat this?
Already rare
You are the Queen of Daxia after all.
Not to the point
You silly boy
This is for others to see
Let's eat it every two days.
Those common people
I'll be moved to tears just by looking at it.
Let’s talk about eating grass seeds
able to win over people's hearts
Not a loss
But there's no one else here
Eat for you to see
The Queen just
Met several generals accompanying the army
No wonder
How about it
People's hearts are tightened
They are all the elites of the Left Wing Army.
Your father's confidant.
How can it be so easy?
take it easy
But everyone is gone
Just stop eating it
I am short of food in Daxia
This is not a waste
Okay, okay, okay, I'll come
It really tastes terrible
I am the most loyal minister of Daxia
It has to be a rice bird
I heard
You went hunting last night
how do you know
What did you hit?
shot a dog
Are there wild dogs in Helan Mountain?
hounds brought
Why did you shoot it?
Missed the shot
I almost forgot
This kid, Mi Qin, is worried about you.
Talk about you these days
Either hunting or sleeping
I'm afraid you'll be depressed
Let your mother talk about you
I am now under your command
Just a few teams of soldiers
This time the sacrifice
In name, I am in charge of the army.
Generals who can lead troops
Some of them listen to me
Let’s talk about the court
I don't even have an errand
I don’t hunt and sleep every day
What else can I do
Right
It's right that it can't be
You have to find the opportunity yourself.
There is an old saying among the Han people
What an old saying
Sit down and taste courage
Taste the courage of lying down
Survival from desperate situation
Mi Qin, tell him yourself.
Your Highness
You are the prince of Daxia
Although the king is brave
But one day
you will replace
Before that
You must not be depressed or slack off.
This will replace your head with a beheading
If you can wake up His Highness
I will die without regrets
You get up first
stand up
Rice poultry
There is an old saying among the Han people:
It’s called hiding one’s strength and biding one’s time keeping a low profile.
You can't keep it up all the time.
Father is too strong
This rumor about the goat-keeper
have you heard of it
heard
Hasn’t it been spread all over the past few years?
Gods walk in the lower world
It's not ordinary.
yes
Frequent appearances of sacred sites
Although most people believe in Buddhism
But now look
This goat-keeper
In Daxia
There are also believers
Worse
They are from beginning to end
Keep telling the public
The father is blessed by the gods
He is good at fighting
Now I have the support of gods
His title of Qingtianzi
Now in Daxia
No one questions it anymore
That’s all
How can I fight?
Those angels should die
Damn it indeed
Divine protection
No taboos
If things go on like this
There is no way to survive
This time the sacrifice
The Sheep Guardian is also on the mountain
of course
Now worship
How to avoid the goat god
His Highness came to Helan Mountain this time
Could it be that he wants to take action against the divine envoy?
It turns out that His Highness is not depressed
Very good
Attack the angel
So bold
This is my prince of Daxia
What's the use of just having courage?
Now the left wing army is watching closely
I'm hunting
Everyone is staring at them
tied hands and feet
Not to mention killing the angel
go
Let those two commanders
Please come back
Don't you mean to tie your hands and feet?
Queen mother will help you to persuade them.
What's the use of persuading?
Try your best
Didn’t you just meet me?
Why are you summoning me again?
Who is this person?
The Queen's Guards
Looks like a young man from the Yeli tribe
Empress's family
No wonder
What is he carrying?
Who knows?
Let's go
After all, it was the Queen who summoned
Still have to go
Let's go
see queen
His Royal Highness the Crown Prince is also here
Invite two commanders to come
Also for my son
The Prince Has Ordered
We shall obey
Brother Ning Ling
I feel like the goat-keeper said
Maybe someone is pretending to be a god
He wants to eliminate traitors for the country
Eradicate those so-called angels
I don’t know what you two think
Qing Tianzi explained
The envoys of the sheep guardians should be honored with national courtesy.
Never take action
Orders from the Queen and the Crown Prince
Don't you listen too?
It’s really hard to disobey the king’s order
It seems hard to persuade
Queen Mother
I have the order from my father.
It’s not good to embarrass others
Thank you for your understanding, Prince.
OK
Then let's not talk about it.
look
These fresh fruits and meats
We can't finish eating either
Would you like to come over and try it?
I wouldn't dare
We don’t have so many rules in Daxia
It's fine
Moreover
Our mother and son
I still have to rely on the support of the two of them.
Eat some meat and some fruit
What does this mean?
You're welcome
Then obey.
Eat
Eat it
If it’s not easy to persuade, then don’t persuade.
Go Go Go
What should I do now?
or
Eat some more
It's time
We Daxia people
Not wasting food
Didn't you say that you were tied up?
it's good now
No more
You can't just go the other way, right?
That's definitely not possible.
Lead troops in war
Who can win over your father?
This is neither big nor small
There are also two commanders
How should I explain when I return to Xingqing Mansion?
Just say
They were the ones who made the first move
Kill the angel
Such a big thing
We definitely can't let it go
According to the law
Kill them
Revenge for the angels
how
People who believe in the Goat God are everywhere in the government and the public
Such a big crime
We can't bear it
But those soldiers outside
what to do
They all saw it
people die here
It's up to you
Two commanders died
The soldiers of this battalion
They're leaderless
or
Just accept them
If you can accept them
None of this is a problem
If you can't conquer
Let’s go back to Xingqing Mansion
All must be finished
I think you can do it
Queen Mother
I'll use the knife later
You still have to tell me in advance
Haven't you forgotten this?
Try your best to
Come and eat meat
The camp at the foot of the mountain is a bit messy.
Ning Lingge has been silent for three years
After all, I couldn't bear it anymore.
Do you think it was Brother Ning Ling who seized power?
pretty close
this is a good thing
Apart from Yuan Hao, we can’t do it without him.
How about we go down the mountain to meet him?
Wait for Qizhai to come
Will Yanei come too?
possible
What's wrong
He saw me
Will you be afraid?
Helan Mountain
Three years later
revisit old places
Or just a few of us
I don’t know Chu Niao and the others
Are you still there?
We can get there today
I'll go there first
I'm here too
See Helan Mountain
Why are you still holding a sword?
I have to watch over you when you sleep
Why do you need to guard it yourself?
Isn't there one beside you?
The young guard of the Nori clan?
Going up the mountain
The God of Killing cannot hesitate
Rice poultry
He is also busy
seize military power
You believe him.
You can sleep peacefully here
Aren't you here?
I've already placed someone
By his side
A slight movement
Heads on the ground
But I have to say
He did a good job indeed
He has been good
I told you
Can't do it wholeheartedly
to trust someone
I know
You've always taught me this
This is your father's way of life
Mother, you say
Can I really defeat my father?
He is a human
As long as it's human
Everyone makes mistakes
You these three years
Aren't you pretending to be depressed?
Didn’t I also deceive him?
yes
He is also a human being
Make mistakes too
The left wing army went up the mountain
murderous
Mr. Wen, look
let's escape
That is
Xue Ying
Xue Ying is so strong now
It used to be great
It's even scarier now
good
What do you mean by okay?
Can you beat him?
Yanei
What are you asking for?
Can you beat Xue Ying?
Can't beat
Just admitted it
Is there a problem
I thought you were going to say something
Animals are stronger than humans
People need to rely on wisdom and so on
Ridiculing Xue Ying?
Why should I mock him?
Don't you often mock me?
When have I ever ridiculed you?
You don’t always talk about me
Fighting is not allowed
Reading and fooling around
Are you mentally retarded?
I said
so
What I'm asking is
When have I ever ridiculed you?
Isn't this what it is?
never mind
Forget it
wait
Do you have any talents?
Why forget these two words?
come out of your mouth
So irritating
Yanei, don't be angry
Young Master Wen has always been like this
Aren't you angry too?
got used to
It won't be easy for you either
Should we go first?
right
The chief of my family is coming soon, too.
Let's go
I was just about to ask what you were carrying
Stronger again
Where is that old Tang from your Bazhai?
Very strong
The one who can carry rocks
What's wrong
died
How did you die?
die in battle
Aren't you just pretending to be a ghost?
How could he die in battle?
After becoming famous
Someone keeps checking our details
Old Tang accidentally found himself in Xingqing Mansion
Revealed
he thinks
We keep the goat god
It’s not easy to pretend to this stage
Don't give up halfway
He rushed into the government office alone
Bring the few city guards who know the information
Kill them all
That you
when something goes wrong
Mr. Wen and I are not in Xingqing Mansion
The bones were buried
No
Why
Old Tang was furious when he was about to die
He burned down both the government office and himself.
All burned
No one knows it was him who did it
Mr. Wen and I are here
It's safe
When did it happen
More than a year
Young Master Wen even cried
I didn't cry
He cried
Crying while hiding from others
Yanei
have you already seen
Thank you Yanei
no need thank me
You even pretended not to see it
Didn't ask me either
Very attentive
This is
Injuried
blind
fake miracles
Being spotted by Shiboyuan
Shibuyuan
Here in Xixia
The First Divination Garden is in charge of divination.
Do you think it’s funny or not?
Ruling the country by divination
Young Master Wen leads us to create miracles
They definitely can't figure it out.
Isn't this embarrassing?
Just keep an eye on us
They suspect that you are not the messengers of God
That's not true
They're quite superstitious
Especially believe that we are
God's Messenger
Then I'll take action against you
Matters about wealth and future
God wants to kill too
Comments from Wen Shao
Everything in the world is for profit
Those guys don't dare to face the enemy head on
They're all using smoke and poison.
I got a poisonous needle
Would have died
Then I will
dig it out yourself
save your life
It hurts, right?
Very painful
I kept crying
I fainted once in the middle
Luckily I woke up quickly
Young Master Wen was besieged at that time
So it's just me
he's fine
He killed all the poisoners
Shi Bu Yuan was later frightened by him
I didn't dare to take action again
If it weren't for Wen Shao
The Sheep God cannot enter Xingqing Mansion
Yanei
sorry
Why are you apologizing suddenly?
last time we met
what I said
Do you think I'm okay?
Waiting for you and me
Get everything done
Think again
Do you want to spend time together?
I will consider it carefully
this answer
I take it all back
Why
I'm so disabled now
I don't deserve you.
The wind is so strong
My eyes are blinded
actually, I
Yanei
Go quickly. There are people behind you.
Prince
The whole army conquered
Willing to serve the prince
So fast
Yes, it went well
After all, he is the elite of the Left Wing Army.
Unexpectedly, there were quite a few
People who are greedy for life and afraid of death
If I weren't trying to win over the military,
I'll have to chop off a bunch of his heads again
Let's chop off the head later.
Right
Before we go back to Xingqing Mansion
Need to be screened again carefully
certainly
We still need His Highness the Crown Prince
Giving both kindness and power
so
Even if we are in the left wing army
Put a nail in
This strength
In front of the Father
Simply not worth mentioning
Still have to take it slow
Still have to spend time finding allies
Can't slow down
You didn't see it
Your newly born brother
How much his father likes him
All the civil and military officials of the entire dynasty also saw it.
If you lose your position as crown prince
who will follow you
So can't wait
Take action quickly
Otherwise there will never be a chance
Not enough troops
One knife is enough to kill someone
Guarding the palace gate
But they are all soldiers of hundreds of battles
The prince can carry a sword when he enters the palace
Queen Mother
Could it be that you want me to
Do it yourself
He is my biological father
That is also my biological husband
but it doesn't matter
There is an old saying among the Han people
What's coming
Kill relatives for justice
right
They have all kinds of sayings
and can be used in any situation
But do we have righteousness?
who cares
coming
Wen Shao
Chu Niao
Do you know Brother Ning Ling?
So ungrateful
Just say it directly
No polite words
have you eaten
hello
Do you know Brother Ning Ling?
know
very good
Let’s go see Brother Ning Ling
And Queen Yeli
Do you really want to convince Queen Yeli?
Betray Yuan Hao
They are a couple after all
Flowers
What about the soldiers?
Throw it away
Long time no see Hua Cishu