Do you know me yet?
I must know you then
You Bazhai
There is no time limit for the deputy director’s article.
Mi Ge Shi Zhai
You are the only one who has eight fasts and no fasting chief
two deputy chiefs
Still not dealing with each other
It's famous
It turns out that you are pretending to be a ghost.
You still here
I am very pleased
What
There was a bet in Secret Pavilion back then
Everyone in Gambling Secret Pavilion
Who will take the first step
Yanei
You are at the top
See you persist till today
I feel a little happy
What does it mean to take the first step?
Do not misunderstand
Don't bet on life or death
indeed
Who will be kicked out of the Secret Pavilion first?
That's not a good thing either.
etc.
I do not know how
Is there such a bet?
no one told you
You guys worked together to hide it from us Qizhai
This bet
But your family Yuan Zhongxin did it
he
The village where he sits
He also bet that I would be removed first
No
he bets on himself
I said
He was so noisy at that time
good guy
This guy is too weird
This kind of bet is possible
Quiet
sit
Are you training me like a dog?
Don't make any noise
You've had enough
Don't be angry, Yanei
Mr. Wen has been training birds recently
He didn't mean it.
He tamed those cranes
is not that right
why
The God of Sheep has the ability to herd cranes
Cranes accompanying them
It was daytime just now
everyone saw it
Or maybe it was domesticated from childhood
Crane is a noble bird
How dare you raise
The crane is a noble bird in Xixia
There is a saying
Have you heard of it?
Emperor of the World
Thousands of blackheads are lucky
on land
Wan Chi has different opinions
Can't understand
This is a Xixia proverb
Black heads in the world and red faces on the ground
Where are the blackheads?
Refers to the Xixia party aristocrats
The red face is the ordinary people
And blackhead also means white crane.
party nobility
Considers himself a descendant of White Crane
To them
Cranes are regarded as noble birds by gods
Why is the crane called Blackhead?
Just the top of the head
red
Isn’t that Hedinghong?
A bit dark brown
So the crane herder
Only God
But what is red face?
Refers to macaque
You all know this
We are in Xixia
Been here for a long time.
Read a lot of books again
I also read a lot of books
I do not know how
Yanei
Think it over before you speak
Okay I'm sorry
I can't read
I have a strange disease
I get a headache when I read
what
sit
People cannot be tamed
Wenwuqi
Get rid of the gas, get rid of the gas
Wen Shao
You should also restrain yourself.
Just by this sheep head
and tame cranes
You can pretend to be a god
There are two more preparations
The Appearance of the Goat God
should be accompanied by two visions
First, the gods of Helan Mountain are spiritual
Cliff Light
I did see the light on the cliff.
It's pretty.
What's the principle?
What is the principle
look
mica
Mica in bright light
Can stimulate light
That light just now
Just because of this
Someone is on the cliff
Inlaid with this stone
What about the second vision?
resurrection of the dead
It's me
I lay on the women's shed to load the body
It was preparation
Resurrection in public
For everyone to see
did not expect
Met you in Yanei
Cliff Light
It's embedded with mica
yes
You can see it
Where did you find all that mica?
Hard to find
Not from this mountain yet
It has to be shipped all the way here
It’s not convenient for horses to climb up this mountain.
carried up
How heavy is this?
The footprints are pretty deep
Looks like the same person
do you remember
Are we Bazhai Laotang?
Remember
The one who is strong enough to carry a stone mill
He was the one who carried it
Then embedded it
It's really impossible without him
Then you Bazhai
Everyone comes to Helan Mountain
Just the three of us
The other three are not here
Then you pretend to be the goat god
Any functions
The tasks we took on
It’s to kill Yuan Hao
But this has nothing to do with gods
What does it matter?
The gods appear during sacrifices
Explain that the Sheep God bestows blessings on Yuan Hao
No one is afraid of him now
In fact, this may not be a good thing
Backed by gods
Why is it bad
given by gods
Naturally, you can also take it back
You know the party members
Where does it come from?
Guqiang
I seem to have heard of the ancient Qiang people
The ancient Qiang people performed sacrifices by wearing sheepskin
Wearing sheep bones
Why do Xixia gods have sheep heads and human bodies?
This is also the source
Wen Shao discovered
Although the ancient Qiang clan has long since disappeared,
But check carefully
In fact, many ethnic groups now
All originated from ancient Qiang
Coming from the same lineage
yes
Maybe in tens of millions of years
people will find out
all different races
In the end, they all come from the same origin
All different wars
Until that day
Maybe they will all disappear
because of different languages
different customs
Return to one at last
Destiny is born together
But this is different from eradicating Yuan Hao
what is the relationship
The Dangxiang clan believes in gods
Yuan Hao is the king of Xixia
Claim to be a vulgar
That is Qing Tianzi
Ordinary slander or even power struggle
Can't even touch his foundation
yes
What to do?
Unless the gods are angry
Take away the title of Wuzu
Xixia fears gods
Then start from the most fundamental point
Destroy Yuan Hao's foundation
Millions of soldiers
Machiavellian
Nothing can withstand the wrath of gods
Guardian God Ascension
It seems like a blessing
In fact, we have to wait until the time is right
Using superstition
Let all Yuan Hao rebel against their relatives and leave their relatives
this is my plan
Conferred God
alright
Let’s not talk about God for now.
Let’s talk about people
How are you doing now?
It's really hard for me
Speaking of which, we can be considered allies.
Especially Miss Zhao
You and I are even more in love with each other
Logically speaking, I should really let you go.
Get out of here
You're confused when you sleep
If I let you go
I can't explain it.
I won’t let you go
You can confess me later
also affects
The relationship between my father and son
Actually, there are other ways
Please enlighten me
kill us
There is no way to interrogate a person after he is dead.
You'll be safe
You are not afraid of death
afraid
But do you dare to kill me?
Yuan Hao asked you to interrogate us
It's obvious that this is a test
If you kill us
Wouldn't it be a guilty conscience?
actually
There's only one thing I don't understand
Why doesn't my father kill you?
According to his character
It's impossible to leave anyone alive.
What did he say to you on stage?
Does it have anything to do with you?
Headache
What to do with you?
What should I do?
Father
what's the topic
Return to Father
Asking who is the mastermind behind the scenes
Do you even need to ask?
I guessed it all
Sons and ministers are dull
Unknown
Who did the father guess?
Not Song Dynasty
They are Liao people
It can’t be one of my own
Want to kill me
What do you say?
What my father said is absolutely true
You guys go down
I want to talk to them alone
Father
around you
Leave no guard
No need
yes
How could he be willing
Stay alone with Song people
What about Lu Nanshan?
Can't find it
He must be hiding something
Now it seems that this assassination
Unpredictable intentions
Lu Nanshan comes to Helan Mountain
Came to find you
Right
When the cliff shines with light
He also chased after her
Then won't you see him?
Master Wen said
He only trusts the president.
Lu Zhangyuan passed away
Lu Nanshan now takes over as the new head of the academy
For me
There is only one branch
Do you think there is something wrong with Lu Nanshan?
Your assassination this time
did he ever tell you
Yuan Hao's strength
That means he didn't think about it
you will succeed
Then why did he
Will they arrange this assassination?
have no idea
you can ask him
Chu Niao
Send him down the mountain
Lu Nanshan should be looking for him
good
What about you?
Our mission is not finished yet
What should Xiao Xue and the others do?
Just ask Lu Nanshan
He should make his own arrangements
What if he doesn't save people?
If this is true
I will take action when the time comes
Wenwuqi
Lu Nanshan said
Sanzhai's entire army was annihilated
You should also be careful
Everyone is mortal
Let's go Yanei
I'll take you down the mountain
Does Brother Ning Ling want to kill me?
yes
Whoever you say is who
We help with certification
Just let us go then
Want to go
Yes Yes Yes
Search for a solution
I really want to kill you
You can't get off the altar
honestly
Do you want us to help you?
Identify Brother Ning Ling
We can get things done
You and your brother are really different
when you are during the day
Mentioned Yuan Da Ge
What's the meaning
Yanei
What's wrong
Ask you something
you say
your dad
Have you got engaged?
Why are you asking?
Just ask
deal
Whose family is it?
The daughter of a household minister
Deputy Envoy of the Three Departments
A wealthy family
Is it done?
The marriage was called off
Why
You knew me at that time
The first of the four great dandies in Beijing
bad reputation
That is not bad
What do you mean by okay?
Do you think I'm okay?
The Battle of Qichuan Village
Only your brother is left behind
Why
Because you want to use him
There were so many generals in the Song Dynasty
Why did you choose him?
Speak directly if you have anything to say
Can they listen to these things?
They all know about me
good
Come and sit
Have a drink with me
Let's go
what is he going to say
Let's just go on
Pretty little girl
Come and sit
how do you
not talking
Why do you suddenly ask that?
Of course it's to express your feelings
Don't play tricks on me
why do you think so
Do you think I am capable?
Not really
Could it be
Just because I'm handsome
Actually
Quite cute
Neither capable nor handsome
Where did the intention come from?
Because you are honest
What
honest
I
The first of the four great dandies in Beijing
honest
It can't be considered honest.
How do I put it?
Can see clearly
What does it mean to be able to see clearly?
All over the Quanmi Pavilion
Can be seen clearly
It’s just you, Yanei
what are you thinking
Almost everything can be seen through at a glance
Just looking at it makes you feel at ease
no
what do i think
You seem to be cursing someone
And your family’s educational background
I'm envious
How can I have a homeschool?
Your family is rich
The house was raided
do not you know
I know
But your talent for making money is still there
future
It will definitely be no problem to settle down and start a business
Hire some maids then
Cleaning and cooking at home
Leave it all to them
Then eat every day when you are hungry
Go to sleep when you feel sleepy
Don't worry about anything
How beautiful such a day must be
Looking around the Secret Pavilion
Can do
It’s just you, Yanei
Just like you
Why are you still in the Secret Pavilion?
I was sold here
The family suffered a disaster
A family fleeing
Lost on the road
Almost robbed by bandits
Then what
Then he was rescued by the commander
Lu Zhangyuan
Didn't you find your family members?
found
when found
Everyone is gone
I see you are in the Secret Pavilion
Laughing all day
Seems quite happy
Yes, what's wrong?
did not expect
Have you ever encountered such a tragedy?
Everyone in the family is gone
I have to live happily for them
My dad
My mother
two sisters
a younger brother
I have to live up to the laughter of five people
It's even
Then you follow the leader
Back to Kaifeng
Later, the head of the court took charge of the secret pavilion.
I joined
But you said
You were sold into the Secret Pavilion
I sold it myself
The abbot saved my life
I can't forget this kindness
So I entered the Secret Pavilion
I just want to do more things
Pay off the debt to the Master
Lu Zhangyuan is dead
You don't have to pay anything back
That won't work.
what do i owe
Remember in my heart
Then how long do you want to pay?
Soon
Wait till Yuan Hao dies
It's almost paid off
then go
Go live my little life
I quite like what you said too
I have to work harder
Wait till I get my dad
Picked up from Lingnan
I can get through it
The day I want
Waiting for you and me
Get everything done
Think again
Do you want to spend time together?
I will consider it carefully
this answer
Below is the Youzhou Army Camp.
They are now teaming up with Lu Nanshan
I won’t embarrass you
how about you
Young Master Wen doesn’t trust Lu Nanshan
We Bazhai do things
He doesn't care.
I won’t see him anymore
your business
I won't tell him
We must meet again
Everyone has to live well
of course
That
I am leaving
I see you go
who
Do you know who I am
be honest
tap tap tap
Xiaolu Zhangyuan
where do you come from
I
I ran all the way down the mountain
Daytime assassination, no sign of you
I thought you had an accident
I'm timid
Escaped to the mountain
Who did you meet?
no one
I hide myself
What should Yuan Zhongxin and the others do?
You don't care about them anymore
You saw the daytime assassination, too.
Yuan Hao didn't kill him
what do you want to say
Yuan Zhongxin
Maybe he has already joined Xixia
You fart
Do you want another drink?
Let's talk business first
Good
Then I'll say it straight
The Battle of Qichuan Village
Only your brother is left
It was predetermined.
Must be your brother
other people
Leave no one behind
Why
After all, the love between father and son is deep.
What's the meaning
your dad
Serving under my command
You don’t know yet
Yuan family surrenders to Xixia
do you have evidence
After Yuan Bo's fin incident
Jingxi East Road
Yingtianfu Yuan clan
overnight
disappear
No trace
People are missing
Why did you say you came to Xixia?
My guess
Guess
Can this kind of thing be guessed at?
Yuan Hao's surname is Yuan
Yuan Zhongxin also has the surname Yuan
Isn't it a coincidence?
are you crazy
What does this mean?
Your surname is Lu
That Lu Gui is also named Lu
Are you a family?
do you know
Yuan Hao's original surname was Tuoba
Now this Yuanzi
where does it come from
How would I know
Tuoba clan of Northern Wei
I changed my last name to Yuan
Just to tell the world
My Big Summer
It is the Tuoba inheritance of the Northern Wei Dynasty
Noble blood
Have the ambition to conquer the world
Put gold on your face
Little girl, don't talk nonsense
This inheritance is no lie
Yuan Zhongxin
Your clan is the Tuoba inheritance
Now understand
Why did your father surrender to me?
You are not a Song
You and we are of the same origin
All are inherited from Xianbei
One spirit and one branch
That
Even if it is Yuan family
It is the inheritance of Tuoba lineage
It doesn't necessarily mean that they will surrender to Xixia.
So the assassination is the test
Yuan Hao will not kill Yuan Zhongxin
It proves that I guessed it right
so what
It shows that Yuan Zhongxin can no longer be trusted
Family name and bloodline are so important
Of course it's important
This is for people
The foundation
I originally wanted your father to persuade you
But unfortunately
He is not in Daxia
If he is not in Xixia, where is he?
He has his own things to do.
do what
test
What do you say about your father?
Even if it's him
Lead the entire Yuan clan to join me
I still can't
Trust him completely
Give him a job
Let him prove himself
So you don't kill me because of him
That's right
Then do you think I will surrender?
You and I are of the same race.
Why did you come to lower the word?
Does my brother know about this?
After Qichuan Village
Your father wrote him a letter
Told the truth
Advise him to serve Xixia wholeheartedly
but he refused
I also do not understand
why did he refuse
Because he is a fool
I kind of know now
Why did he want to die?
own biological father
Let him betray the Song Dynasty
How desperate this must be
If it weren't for revenge for my colleagues
presumably
He doesn't necessarily
Can I last until then?
But even so
He still protects me
Didn't tell me those secrets
Going to a dead end alone
Actually he
There's no need to do this
You won't understand at all
Even if my brother knew
I am of Xianbei bloodline
He will still not hesitate
Choose to be loyal to the Song Dynasty
that kind of loyalty
It's engraved in his bones
That's right
Born in Song Dynasty
Growing up in the Song Dynasty
Song people
Achieve a person
It's the path he took
It's not his blood.
why are you laughing
I am telling the truth
Our Song Dynasty is a big country
vast territory
All ethnic groups have
That's not what I'm laughing at
Little girl, you have to think clearly
you
Can accept him
What about other Song people?
I am a Song
Don't even listen to your father's words
I only have my brother
I thought that with your temperament
Can you pretend to surrender?
Fake is fake
But you have to believe it.
That's true.
That
What do you want me to do
What to do with you three?
people
In times of drastic changes
what is the most important
choice
I'll give you one more night to think about it
Will you kill me again tomorrow?
won't kill you
I have to take you back to Xingqing Mansion
Give your dad a surprise
If you don't serve me tomorrow
I killed both of them
That really scared me
Otherwise, lower it.
There must be some benefit, right?
Otherwise, I will treat you like this
The location of Qing Tianzi
Let me sit
sure, no problem
The premise is
You have to kill me
etc.
What's wrong
Yuan Family surrenders to Yuan Hao
Let’s not talk about whether this is true or not.
What to do with Zhao Jian and Xue Ying?
After all, Zhao Jian is of royal blood
She won't be complicit
But they were both caught too
I thought Yuan Zhongxin
Will take into account old feelings
did not expect
He is so cruel
It was you who planned the assassination
He can keep you from having to interfere
nonsense
If Yuan Zhongxin didn't know
What about the Yuan family?
What if you wronged him?
The result is the same
What do you mean the result is the same?
I say it again
Yuan Zhongxin is eighty-nine out of ten
Will serve Xixia
What about Zhao Jian and Xue Ying?
Zhao Jian is the princess
Even if it's just a branch
She is royalty after all
do not worry
This hatred
I, Da Song, will never forget
No one is dead yet
Yuan Hao
Zhao Jian will never be spared his life
The ending is decided
Waiting to return to the capital
I will ask for it personally
Begging the officials
Send troops for revenge
war again
What's wrong
You don’t want to avenge Zhao Jian?
You can save them now
How to save
Yuan Hao's camp is not far away
Be strong and tenacious
Tell me how to save
Don't take it
Then I took it
I'll ask you again tomorrow
Father
The people were locked up in the tents
yes
I will personally guard it
No need for you
Hold the camp
yes
It seems that the Song people did not betray us
But they are still alive
There's always a contingency for this kind of thing
Then we still have to silence them
Is there anyone available in the camp?
have
There are a few more in the camp
Brothers who grew up together
Comparable to brothers
Then call them over
yes
it's useless
We are in the enemy's military camp
Even with a weapon in hand
Can't get out either
What should I do?
coming
Don't you want to take action?
Keep silent
They are all allies, so what are they talking about?
I can't silence my mouth, right?
Even if you can catch me by surprise
Kill the guard at the door
The three of us are not dumb
Really take action
we shout loudly
None of you can escape
Why does Miss Zhao have to be so transparent?
Since there is no way to silence
Afraid of us again
Shake you out
How to do it
It's better to save people
No trial
There is no mastermind anymore
In fact, there are emotional factors involved.
I really want to explain
But the timing is wrong
or
I'll send you out first
there
Everyone
I hope you don't forget
Our cooperation is not over yet
Yuan Hao is not dead
This matter is not over yet
I thank you on behalf of my father
Miss Zhao
do not forget me
Really let them go
fine
There aren't many of them
we have a chance
haven't seen you for a long time
uncle
Aren’t you in Lingnan?
Escaped long ago
You have joined Yuanhao
Could it be
Let me be trapped in Lingnan for the rest of my life
But you are not using yourself as bait
Achieve the strategy of car and gun
Are you plotting against Xixia?
people like you
How could he serve Yuan Hao?
Counterfeit cars and guns
do you really think
Used several times
Damaged car and gun
It can really shake the morale of Daxia’s army
You can really deceive Yuan Hao
But your cruel plan at that time
We are all watching
Car and gun strategy
what is the end result
Yuan Hao's siege failed
Retreat
At that time, Daxia
Already at the end of the crossbow
Car and artillery
Just a reasonable excuse to retreat
actually
The result of this bitter plan is very simple
One of them, I was laid off
Many positions are vacant in the Imperial Guard
one more
My house was raided
All the money goes into the treasury
Up and down
From king to minister
All good
The Wei family was targeted
if not
Uncle, you
Why did you agree then?
that time
Wei Yuan has entered the Secret Pavilion
I disagree
What should he do
So the yamen went to the Secret Pavilion
To threaten you
Make a so-called bitter meat plan
At least save your life
Wei Yuan can also stay in Kaifeng
As for me, last
You can also give him one
A stalwart figure
Why not?
Yuan Hao heard about this
Personally send people to Lingnan
Save me here
I
Just got a chance to be reborn
So you really surrendered to Xixia
Song Dynasty
gave me such a result
What would you choose instead?
If Yanei knew
It should be quite sad
my business
Don't tell him
Just let him think
He also has an amazing father, right?
here
I thank you too
Always taking care of Wei Yuan
uncle
How about you come with us?
Let's go back to Song Dynasty together
It's all reached this point
Where is the chance?
It can be said that it is you
Saved us back
There is always a turning point
Thank you for your kindness
only
The prince passed away
Only rely on the princess
I'm afraid you can't save me
You know about my dad.
Of course I heard about it
Condolences to the princess
you two
Take care of yourself
What's the meaning
nothing
Leave the horse to you
Go with peace of mind
never come back