Tomorrow's camp
You mother and son
Come with me to the Rikyu Palace.
Stay for two days to enjoy the mountain view
That's great
this child
Always hope
I am being filial under your knees
This time I got my wish
It's good to be filial
Just don't try your best
Become a send-off
Father
You can't say such things
My son's heart will hurt when he hears this
You didn't make a move on the wooden platform
done right
I think he is basically
Playing cat and mouse game
enjoying the moment
He is indeed strong
but it doesn't matter
as long as you live
There will definitely be a chance
I see
Mi Qinmubei's corpse
Just hang it outside
Warn me?
He can be considered loyal
How about I find a reason?
Buried him too
No
Mi Qinmu Bei is indeed loyal
But it’s meaningless when people die
Who would risk a dead man?
what you up to
Set fire to the wooden platform
Let Chu Niao return to heaven and earth
What are the consequences?
I'll be more careful
Just don't let anyone see it
Why did Yuan Hao put the corpse
On wooden table
Destroy the morale of the troops
anything else
Say I know you can guess
Miqinmu has been a leader in the North for many years
There will always be people loyal to him
Yuan Hao hopes to use rice bird's body
Fish these people out
I know I'm going to die even though I know it
You can't hang around like this
Your identity as a Yeli clan member
Will be of great use in the future
So you can't die
Even if you can't bear it anymore, you have to endure it
More than one Chu Niao died in Bazhai
Now there's only two of us left
for what
Kill Yuan Hao
So you are not qualified to take risks
If the mission fails, you have to live.
where did you go
You can't control me
Put down the torch
Please keep your voice down
Didn't you say the mission failed?
Do you have to live?
I've been showing up too much over the years
Since Yuan Hao wants to get rid of the divine envoy
I don't have a chance
Return to Xingqing Mansion
But it's okay
Become a god these years
In fact, it all relied on Qizhai's help.
It's perfect to leave it to them
The ones from Qizhai
Although not as smart as me
But it's okay
They have friendship with Brother Ning Ling
I also know Yuzhou Army
Things I haven't done yet
You can also rest assured
entrusted to them
So you're a loser now
No matter what, I'm better than you
Since there is nothing to do
Just leave Xixia honestly
Return to Song Dynasty
I brought Chu Niao to Xixia
I brought it
I have to send it away
You don’t have to look at me like this
I don't have to die.
No one noticed after lighting the fire
I turned around and ran away
But I warn you Hua Ci Shu
If things change
You must not take action
I know my identity is useful
Yuan Hao is not dead
i must live
Have you ever regretted it?
What do you regret?
Join Secret Court
Join Bashai
there has never been
That's not it
you
Have you ever regretted it?
Bring Chu Niao and the others to Xixia
If there is no war
they should be able to
Keep living
Become an old man and an old woman
The way those guys are getting older
I can't imagine it at all
quite funny
Chu Niao after today
You are no longer a member of Bazhai
What you call kindness
Already paid off
The overall situation has been determined
I don't need you here anymore
then where should i go
Go the way you like
Didn't expect that
There really is a pair of rice birds in the north
So loyal
This person is dead
hung there and burned
What's the difference
Just for this fire
Put yourself in it too
Opponent
no the same
You will be dead soon
Are you stupid for doing this?
A bit silly indeed
But it does not matter
What's the meaning
I have been smart for so many years
Be silly once in a while
Understandable
This answer is interesting
Unexpectedly, Mi Qin Mu Bei
There are also subordinates like this
give you a chance
kneel down
I'm considering not killing you
Come
I won him over
This means you are ignorant
No matter what, I am too
The Lord of Daxia
Do everything yourself
what is your name
What are you looking at
fine
Let's continue
How about I give you another chance?
No
good
I just do not understand
What's the point of this?
because you are stupid
Know it earlier
No more cranes
In the end, I don’t even know what your name is.
Too busy too busy
That's just a little time
Sorry, sorry.
Are you hungry?
Eat freely
Where is this
You guys go down first
This is the palace
Qingtianzi's palace
Tired of staying in Xingqing Mansion
Just have fun here
Who are you
No hidden lies
Current Prime Minister of Daxia
correct
My sister
He is the owner of this palace
now
Qing Tianzi's favorite woman
The widow married by Yuanhao
That's her
Do you have anything else to ask?
why brought us here
Of course I will save your lives.
Yuan Hao deployed heavy troops
Guarding Helan Mountain
Direction to Xingqingfu
If I hadn't arrived early
at this moment
I'm afraid you're all dead
rest assured
I put three corpses in the carriage
Qing Tianzi should also feel at ease.
why do you want to save us
you are dead
Who killed Yuan Hao?
I do not know what you're talking about
This is boring
you see me
Always so honest
Then you might as well be more honest
Can
I know you are from Song Dynasty
Also know
You cooperate with Brother Ning Ling
The purpose is to assassinate Yuan Hao
Eat quickly
Otherwise it will get cold
I'm saving you
Just want to help you
You help us kill Yuan Hao
That's what it means
You are the Prime Minister of Xixia
No hidden lies
Your sister is Yuan Hao
The most favored concubine
I just gave birth to a son for Qingtianzi
To tell you the truth
Now Qingtianzi spends most of his time
stay here
The Royal Palace of Xingqing Mansion
Almost deserted
then why do you
Help us kill Yuan Hao?
I am kind by nature
What
Brother Ning Ling is the prince
But Qingtianzi was on guard against him
Lift military power
He did nothing wrong
But was treated like this
I really can't stand it
People always have to be reasonable
Be humane
Otherwise, he would become a beast, right?
You want to kill Yuan Hao for Brother Ning Ling?
Do you think we will believe it?
Otherwise, what would I do to save you?
If I harm you
Take you directly
If you leave it to Qing Tianzi, it will be over.
Isn’t that true?
Not surprisingly
these two days
Qingtianzi will return to the palace
I'll make arrangements then
Let you assassinate Yuan Hao
Believe it or not
We won’t know until then
what chance
you
How do you plan to kill Yuan Hao?
A reminder
Qingtianzi's fighting power is unparalleled
It's not okay to use force
Use poison
good idea
I'll give you the chance to poison
Arrange for you to sneak into the apse
Wait for the poison to take its toll and kill it
Then we should thank you
Then don't bother me
To show sincerity
I have withdrawn all my guards.
If you don’t want to assassinate Qingtianzi
You can leave on your own
Candid enough?
farewell
The guards are gone
This should really be the palace
There seems to be no poison in the food
Prime Minister of Xixia
Fight the injustice for Ning Lingge
Do you believe it?
Do not believe
It must be fake to defend oneself
Maybe it was a borrowed knife to kill someone
power struggle
possible
Not quite right
If he is really the prime minister
Want to keep position and power
The prerequisite is that Yuan Hao is alive
No matter how hard we fight
Nor will you dig your own grave
That's right too
Then his identity is lying
Too little information to judge
What the Prime Minister just said
None of it is credible
Go or stay
Leave
That's right
This may be the one who killed Yuan Hao
great opportunity
But we can't completely
Follow his arrangements
Let’s eat first
Really hungry
Yanei
I've never heard of it in my life
Words that make people happier than before
another
woke up
So anxious to die
You are still useful
Come and check
come over
You pushed this car
Scared my beast, you
Take care
Is this this?
Yes, this is it
okay
No money, no money, no money
I'll give you money
Let me ask you something
Officials of the Song Dynasty who served the Qing Emperor
Where do you usually live?
The west side of the city
All the people from Song Dynasty lived there
Go forward
Just turn around and you'll be there
Are you okay?
just in front
You go ahead
Where is my wallet?
Is this yours
Picked up on the road
thank you
Please ask about that
Where did the officials of the Song Dynasty live?
In the west of the city
It's just past three alleys
Song people
Basically everyone lives there
Yuan Zhongxin
Save Yanei
what on earth are you going to say
Come
Where are my things?
How long have I been unconscious?
Three days
what happened
There is news from Helan Mountain
Yuan Hao killed the Sheep Keeper
This news is like a bolt from the blue
Today's Xingqing Mansion
It's an undercurrent
Everyone has their own agenda
Isn’t Yuan Hao very prestigious?
No higher than gods
three years
The Sheep God spreads throughout Daxia
Although Daxia mainly believes in Buddhism
But the sheep god
Some foundation
Moreover
White Crane Throws Fire
There are signs of divine punishment
Believers in God
Why not be afraid
White Crane Throws Fire
A divine envoy died in battle in Yuanhao camp
Died in fire
Immediately
A white crane cries sadly and descends from the sky
Throw yourself into the fire and die with it
Wen Shao
The white crane is a noble bird in Daxia
Died in fire
It became even more clear that the gods were in trouble
wrong
Why did Yuan Hao want to
The crime of killing the angel
Take it to yourself
The news travels too fast
He couldn't stop him even if he wanted to
Things like white cranes throwing themselves into fire
Unless you see it with your own eyes
Otherwise it would be difficult to spread the word
There is someone around Yuan Hao
The news leaked
should be
Who is the one
There are so many people who believe in God
God knows
How should Yuan Hao cope?
Now it’s not just Xingqing Mansion
News that Qingtianzi killed the divine envoy
Has spread throughout Daxia
There are people everywhere whose hearts are floating
Passed pretty fast
But until now
Haven't found who it is
spread the word
What about the prince and queen?
Guarded by personal guards
The prince shouldn't have a chance
spread the word
This situation now
Should we still stand still?
Why move?
Is it possible that people who have heard of it
Kill them all
Wait a little longer
Are you saying that Yuan Hao went to the palace?
Never showed up
he did nothing
He is waiting
Yeah
What are you waiting for?
Someone around me leaked the news
Waiting to find out who it is
It’s easier to deal with it
Provoking the Gods
Panic
Be quiet and wait.
Let time eliminate fear
Right
Kill the Guardian Angel
It doesn’t necessarily mean disobeying the gods.
Wait for a while
Everyone looked at the gods and never got angry
Divine Punishment did not appear either
panic
It will slowly fade away
yes
Everyone will think that the gods are not angry
Maybe the messenger really made a mistake
And Yuan Hao killed him
It was really the order of the gods.
Will the gods be angry?
There is no god
That means there will be no response
Although there is no god
But someone
God is not angry
I'm angry for him
God does not punish
I'll punish
I have no control over whether you are punished or not.
Yuan Zhongxin
you asked me so many questions
I replied the same thing
Now it's my turn to ask you something
Where is my son?
I thought you were going on a hunger strike
I have to survive
want revenge
Good
Only when people have desire can life be lively
why don't you kill me
nonsense
You are still useful
You eat and drink well first
Let's wait for the news together slowly
What news are you waiting for?
Or put him in a dungeon
Need not
They are guests
Treat well
Don't worry, King
Good wine and good meat
Where's your sister?
Guarding the prince
After all, I'm still young
or
I asked her to come down and accompany the king
No need
It's fine for me to drink alone.
No need for anyone to accompany you
I didn't even panic
Why are you sighing?
I am guilty.
these three years
Chen also spread the news
The Grace of the Sheep Guardian
If not
There won’t be any disaster like today
This has nothing to do with you
these three years
I also use the Sheep Guardian
Only then did he establish the name of Qing Tianzi
spread the word for them
That's what I mean too.
Now it seems
It's drinking poison to quench thirst and bind oneself in a cocoon
The methods of these young men
It's really ok
It's a pity that it was too late to kill
It's already like this
I happened to take a look too
Under this disaster
Who is hiding evil intentions
The king is wise and far-sighted
Must be fine
Okay, get up quickly
Add wine
As merciful as the king
I don't believe it.
Someone really has a bad conscience
Conspiracy to rebel
My brother brought you here to watch
Just to make you believe
His identity
It's not a lie
Yuan Hao's son
Look at his eyes
Looks so much like him
Yes or no
That's your child's father down there
your husband
He is also the king of Daxia.
All your futures, brothers and sisters
All bets on him
I do not understand
Why do you want to help us kill him?
What did my brother say?
He said he was kind-hearted
Is this a bad reason?
You are brave enough
let us in
Not a single guard was left around.
kind person
You will feel that others are also kind
When to take action
Wait a little longer
Don't you want to poison me?
Yuan Hao is a very careful person
If you want to poison
You have to wait for the big banquet
There is opportunity for chaos
He is in the palace every day
No one is seen
How to throw a big banquet
He won't stay like this forever
When do you think he
There will be movement
Then we have to see
What is he waiting for now?
what am i waiting for
I'm just asking casually
Your Majesty, don’t take it seriously
I'm waiting for something to happen
Waiting for transfer
Waiting for mountain flood discharge
Waiting for someone to kill
There must be a follow-up to this divine disaster
This is the follow-up I'm waiting for
or
Arrange some cronies to join the army
after all
Stabilizing the morale of the military is the top priority
No need
What news is there from the Yuzhou Army?
these days
But I didn’t see the Youzhou Army.
What happened?
The death of Liang Gewei
It's just so silent
The Yuzhou Army is now stabilized
This is quite rare
The Liang family has no male offspring
He had already thought about it
Let me take over the Yuzhou Army
You have to think about the consequences
This mourning hall is so big
Your soldiers and horses
Can you squeeze in?