Long time no see Hua Cishu
haven't seen you for a long time
As the chief of Hachisai, I
Representing Bazhai
Welcome to Helan Mountain
You can't represent
I am the chief
The surname is Wen
You are just the deputy chief
okay
You two deputy chiefs of Bazhai
It's like no one knows
Funny
It's my turn to say this
Talk about something serious
ok
Our Bazhai is in the hands of Lu Zhangyuan
Picked up and sneaked into Xixia
The mission to kill Yuan Hao
we know this
Then wenwuqi
Come up with the plan to become a god
Want to borrow the will of God
The foundation of the bad Yuan Hao, the Lord of Xixia
We also know this
Then what else are you asking?
you
what's wrong with you
I ask you
Wenwuqi's plan
Do you think it's okay?
Not bad
Xixia people are quite superstitious.
No wonder you can't be the chief of the meal
What does this have to do with anything?
Zhao Zhaichang
What do you think
Do you think this plan won't work?
have a look
This is the vision of our chief priest
exactly the same
Yanei
Do you want to come to Bazhai and be the deputy chief?
Can I do that too?
This guy can do it
why can't you
The surname is Wen
Can you speak well?
It's not meant to be insulting.
etc.
Why is it insulting?
Wait a moment
Don't be impatient, everyone.
Let’s talk about business first
I don’t think it’s possible to become a god
Just take the people with lofty ideals in Bazhai
Made a new plan
Isn't this just a quarrel and separation?
Then six people are divided into two teams?
Go on
What's your plan?
Joining the WTO
Yuan Hao's power is overwhelming
If you want to kill him, you have to get close to him
How can I get close to him?
Of course they are from Xixia
To be fair to you all
Now I am
Queen Yeli's bodyguards
That's okay too
I took on the identity of the Yeli clan
People of the same race are easy to talk to
If i remember correctly
Xiaoluo and Jinnian from Bazhai
I should be following you
They both also have new identities
People are gone
Bazhai
There are only three of you left.
That's about it.
What's almost the same
he means
sad regret
That's about it.
We don't have that much time to be depressed
Yuan Hao is still there
The task is not completed
Before coming to Xixia
we all know
what will be the result
How could it be possible to escape intact after killing Yuan Hao?
It’s just who comes first and who comes last
At that time we
Just tell ourselves
There is no need for tears in Yashi
Just keep moving forward
you two together
Must be the best chief
impossible
With him and without me
honestly
Listen to their names
One becomes a god and the other joins the world
Put these two together
A match made in heaven
Not a vegetarian
It's better not to talk nonsense
After all, my eyesight and ability are still lacking.
Can I hit someone?
Separate Separate
They are all classmates and old classmates
When I was in the Secret Pavilion
The two of them are the ones I want to fight the most.
I know I know
Who comes first and who comes last?
What
Do you want to hit me or him more?
I want to fight you both
tied for first
After all, he's not the chief
Limited vision
Not as good as Yanei
What does it have to do with me?
Separate Separate
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
Still need to cooperate?
You've always been by Queen Yeli's side
There is a chance to assassinate Yuan Hao
never seen
Why
Queen Yeli has two brothers
Wild profit is prosperous, wild profit meets beggar
Yeli meets beggar
Yuan Hao killed Yeli Yuqi brothers
From then on, the twelve captains led the army
Only these ten are left
The left wing army and the right wing army
Now he has become Yuan Hao's personal guard
Yuan Hao killed
The Queen's Brother
Queen Yeli has since lost power
Yuan Hao rarely sees her either
Only her position as queen remained
No wonder you want
Persuade Queen Yeli
Assassination of Yuan Hao?
not only that
The concubine that Yuan Hao loves now
Born into the Wuzang clan
Just gave birth to a son for Yuan Hao
The position of Prince Ning Lingge
Precarious
Brother Ning Ling's life isn't that good either.
That one has no Zang family
It was still before
Yeli Yuqi's Wife
What
Wait a minute, let me sort it out.
It's a bit messy
Yeli Yuqishi
Queen Yeli's brother
Yuan Hao killed
And then married this widow
That is to say
This Muzo clan and Queen Nori
Since we are sisters-in-law,
And they both married Yuan Hao at the same time
That's it
This is too messy
Have everyone been killed?
Brought back to camp
brought back to camp
I didn't tell you everything.
Do all people have to be eliminated?
They said they were familiar with His Highness
Familiar with me
Subordinates do not dare to do whatever they want
So he was escorted back
Bring it here and see
yes
So many people
meet again
Why are you
you know
Of course I know
Especially this girl Zhao
We're already engaged. Don't think about it.
Pity
Princess
I chose this one
What are these?
What kind of person
Yeli Langlie, you should go down too.
Persuading Queen Yeli about this matter
I think it's feasible
But the flower tree
Your identity
There is no need to disclose it for the time being.
In case everything goes wrong for everyone
You will be the last chance
What is the name of the identity you bought?
Noriyoshi
So ugly
I can’t pick one that sounds good.
Can I choose this?
Separate Separate
You two, please don't quarrel later.
OK
Just think of it as giving
Chief of Qizhai
a face
You are from Song Dynasty
absolutely true
The matter of guarding the sheep god
It's the Song people's conspiracy
Not a conspiracy
Isn't it a conspiracy?
it's for him
for you
I don't understand this at all
you forgot us
The agreement made three years ago?
You two still have an agreement
Very good
Everyone is here
Let me introduce it first
Song Dynasty
Want to kill my father
Xiaren
I also want to kill my father
You actually cooperated with Song Ren
sincerely
Lessons from the sun
We agreed then
I'll kill your father for you
But you failed
Sheep Guardian
It was our second assassination
Wrong?
Three years ago you
First time visiting Helan Mountain
The Apparition of the Sheep God
Already appeared
Did you remember the wrong order?
good
Let me introduce to you
this
Deputy Chief of the Secret Pavilion Bazhai
Wenwuqi
This Chu Niao Chu girl
The Sheep God is originally the layout of Bazhai
But now I think
we can totally
Let's work together
Anyway, everyone has the same goal
Kill Yuan Hao
Different paths to the same destination
Temporarily deputy chief
Soon he will be the chief
There's really no need to explain this
besides
Guarding the Sheep God
I made the layout alone
It has nothing to do with Chu Niao
Chu Niao
after today
You are no longer a member of Bazhai
What you call kindness
Already paid off
The overall situation has been determined
I don't need you here anymore
then where should i go
Let's go back to Song Dynasty
Go the way you like
your affairs
I have no interest in listening at all.
Since it is a Song Dynasty
Why did you kill my father?
It’s true that God’s blessing is true
With divine power
This will make everyone fear Yuan Hao
But the other way around
given by gods
Nature can also be deprived
Makes sense
but not enough
Of course it's not enough
Don't hide it from the queen
We have united the army with the capital of Youzhou
forge an alliance
Conspiracy
Now it’s up to you, the Queen
You mean Liang Gewei?
It was Liang Du who commanded the army
Do you mean Liang Gewei?
Cooperate with you guys
I knew the Queen wouldn't believe it.
To be fair to you all
Liang Du's army is already here
On the way here
True or False
The queen knew in a blink of an eye
Queen Yeli
Already in alliance with you
Exactly
Queen Yeli and us
Feel like old friends at first sight
Immediately join forces to work together for great things
Now it's you
Queen
It’s so easy to get involved
The queen's tent is just ahead
True or False
Liang Du's army knew in a blink of an eye
Horse exploration report
Liang Gewei, the commander of the Youzhou capital
Approaching the camp
It's actually true
You actually convinced Liang Gewei
Prince
Queen
Youzhou Military Supervisory Department has strong combat effectiveness
Can be a helping hand
Come
Quickly untie these young heroes
Have a banquet
the door is open
Someone came out
Why did the Dutong Army come?
The queen has already set up a banquet
Waiting for you
It's actually true
He actually convinced the queen
All the troops have arrived
Du Tongjun
Her Imperial Highness the Empress
His Royal Highness
Liang Gewei
late
Please get up quickly, the Tongtong Army
Dutongjun is loyal and courageous
All the troops are here
My young descendant
I have someone to rely on.
Seeing this scene of yours
My death is worth it
One is better at acting than the other
Okay, okay.
Don't say it anymore. Don't say it anymore.
Congratulations Queen
Congratulations Prince
Congratulations to Du Tongjun
The weather is finally sunny in Xixia
Her Imperial Highness the Empress
Yeli meets beggar
Have a grudge against Liang
pity
The benefactor died young
Fortunately, the queen is still alive
This is ok
I can finally apply
This happened
Brother Yeli and I are like brothers
But
My two brothers
Already returned to the Holy Mountain
Qing Tianzi
too harsh
Summer
What is needed is His Highness
Such a king
son
Queen Mother
Liang Du commanded the army
Be like brothers with your uncle
There is a brotherly love
According to that
They can also be considered your parents.
I would like to worship Tongjun as my adoptive father
Your Highness
This old minister can't bear it
Calling foster father shows how close he is to you
Your Highness
Your Highness is the Prince
The prince has a foster father
this
this is inappropriate
Murphy
Liang Du commanded the army
Do you dislike me?
Not this or this
This this
this
It’s okay to have individual righteousness
How about the foster uncle?
Ashamed Ashamed
Father-in-law
Your Highness
Brother-in-law
Sister-in-law
No, I'm going to vomit.
Hold on a little longer
Brother, please take a seat quickly
Participate in the grand event
uncle
please
Everyone
Please take a seat too
Finally let’s talk about business
I won't talk anymore.
Where are you going?
I have something to tell her
Go ahead
take this as faith
There are no taboos in the tent
You can go wherever you want
Is there a quieter tent?
The tent over there is piled with luggage.
With it
Just go in directly
thank you
What did Wen Wuqi say just now?
I don’t want you to be in danger again
I didn’t really drive you out of Bazhai.
I know
you know
The Death of Old Tang
Mr. Wen is more sad than me
He is thinking about all the dangers that will follow
I carried it all by myself.
Actually quite good
look
Now there are so many people in the alliance
On the army side, there is the Yuzhou Military Supervisory Department
Where is the court?
There is the prince Ning Lingge
Tribal side
The Yeli clan still has some power left
In addition, the Sheep God rebuked Yuan Hao
Four parties work together
Eradicating Yuan Hao is no longer a big problem
so
The big thing is settled
You don't have to take risks anymore
Just like Wen Wuqi said
The favor you want to repay
It has been paid off long ago
I am
I don't know where to go all of a sudden
what to do
I now
Have your own business
If you really have nowhere to go
Don't dislike it
You can come to me in the future
Help me with the accounts
Didn't you say
your favorite
Just clothes to reach out
The kind that opens your mouth after eating
Leisure days?
Actually I like it too
But I'm already disabled
It's alright
Mr. Wen also said that I was mentally immature.
This counts
I'm pretty handicapped too.
You see we are all disabled
Then
That's quite appropriate
Wen rarely says that people are mentally retarded
Not talking about you specifically
I'll pay for some thugs
Turn around and beat him up
OK
That's settled
Wait till Yuan Hao dies
We all went back to Song Dynasty
I'll just spend some money to buy some thugs
If nothing happens, beat Wen Wuqi
Let's have fun
Don't let Hua Shao go either
Don't let the two deputy mayors go.
Both of them are quite annoying.
no problem
Fight together
Thank you Yanei
I am serious
Don't because
You feel sorry for yourself when you see me hurt
this is not good
Not a grievance
really not
I don’t know what to say either.
Anyway, I'm serious
Is your business profitable?
Quite profitable
It's OK to eat meat every day
You will never be poor if you eat for the rest of your life
But I’m not very good at accounting.
It doesn't matter
Looking for a cashier?
Just name it
Is that appropriate?
Suitable
Is there anything inappropriate?
You are the hostess.
Let's get there
Eat delicious food and drink spicy food every day
Traveling around
Be as happy as you want
sounds great
That's settled
OK
good
What's wrong
This halberd
I have seen
I've seen it too
This is Yuan Hao's weapon
How could it appear in
Baggage camp tent
Yuan Hao has been hiding in the camp
how come
He deliberately let Brother Ning Ling
Queen Yeli
Coming to Helan Mountain
quick
Reminder
After all, she is her own queen
Another biological son
Why did I come secretly with you?
Because I value feelings
Sheep Guardian
Youzhou Army
All ready
Good
Yanei
I've never heard of it in my life
Words that make people happier than before
This man loves my concubine.
another
Chu Niao
You idiot
How can I ask for it if I don’t know how to manage accounts?
Except for you.
You're welcome
You all have been following me for many years
go through fire and water
No more nonsense
things are simple
Someone is plotting rebellion in the camp
You follow me and fight in
Except for the Queen and the Crown Prince
You can kill them all
yes
If it becomes a big thing
Daxia Military and Political Affairs
Divide and conquer with uncle
Don't dare
what happened
The king appears in the camp
Leading the team to attack here
Yuan Hao
Isn't he in Xingqing Mansion?
How many people did he bring?
Dozens of armor
I checked the tent many times
There's no way we can hide so many people
Imperial villa
He is from the palace
They sent people and horses here
That seems to have been planned.
Just dozens of people
Have the opportunity
The soldiers in the camp saw the king
Throw away your armor and lose your fighting power
To advance or to retreat
Make your decision early
Isn't this a good opportunity to kill him?
let's go
uncle
He's right
This is a good opportunity to kill Yuan Hao
Walk
Aren’t you contradicting yourself?
The entire camp is filled with Yuan Hao’s old troops.
Can't stop him at all
Good thing it's around here
I have a Yuzhou army
It turns out that Liang Du commanded the army
Always have military horses on hand
Why didn't you tell me in advance?
Taking precautions before they happen is a matter of course
Nothing to say hello to
Yuan Hao left the army
This is a good opportunity to kill him
I'm going to mobilize my troops and come back quickly.
Take this opportunity to change the national destiny of Daxia
etc.
uncle
Go through the back door
I left a way out
The wooden fence behind the tent
There is a gap
Can leave camp directly
Uncle is right
I hold my father back
Come back as soon as possible
His Royal Highness
You can't stay here either
i must stay
No
Why should those who do great things regret their lives?
Everything depends on
Liang Du took over the army
I stay too
Queen Mother
You might as well go together
I am still the queen of Daxia
Stop dawdling and leave
Yanei and Chu Niao haven't come back yet
The two of them went to the supply camp
Go find someone
The king came from that direction.
can not go
Save Yanei
We can't all be stuck here
Walk
You are not afraid
Life and death
This is the boy from the Nori family
Noriyoshi
Follow me soon
Can be of great use
take it easy
If you really want to kill me
We won’t just take dozens of people with us
wait for him to come
Where to go now?
advanced mountain
etc.
Current situation
The Youzhou Army plays an important role
I'll keep an eye on Liang Gewei first.
OK
Let Xue Ying go with you
good
Xue Ying
let's go now
This is definitely not to leave the office alone.
I understand the chief
Wait for the Youzhou army to come back
can save Yanei
current situation
The most taboo is hesitation
Must make a prompt decision
Going up the mountain
Walk
Liang Du commanded the army
I told you to disperse earlier
what to do with me
Are you afraid that I will break my promise?
We want to help the capital unify the army
A helping hand
Keep up
The barracks is not far from here
Walk
The shouts of killing in the camp have stopped
After all, it is the left wing army
My father has been in charge for many years
As soon as he appears
In all likelihood, it will drop.
He did this on purpose
Let’s come to Helan Mountain
Where is the father?
He's not in the camp
Kings
Brother Ning Ling looks like me
ambitious
After all, he is my son
Liang Gewei
stop looking
just me
How long have we not seen each other?
a year or two
you always refuse to leave
The camp of Youzhou Army
It’s really hard to meet you
Being involved in military affairs
Also helpless
What a coincidence today
I am in Helan Mountain
I learned that the Queen and His Highness were also there
Just wanted to say hello
what hello
how to fight
All of them
commonplace
What I hate the most is ordinary speech
People should be blazing and crazy when they are alive
commonplace
Just nonsense
Liang Gewei
between the two of me
Why not be frank?
Kings
How to confess
I am going to kill you
Youzhou Army
It has always been my biggest worry.
I want to kill you directly
There is no good excuse for civil unrest
I think about it day and night
I finally figured it out
I will release Brother Ning Ling
This is the best fishing bait
That's your son
biological fishing bait
Very easy to use
Yuan Zhongxin
meet again
Thank you
Bring Liang Gewei to me
If I conspire with him
He can't say this
I set up camp
Not far ahead
Let's try it first
It's best to kill
Xiao Xue
If you can't kill
The two of us hold Yuan Hao down
Let Liang Du lead the army to mobilize troops
Have you finished talking?
Xiao Xue
Return to camp and move troops
quick
you become stronger
Have you been seriously injured before?
What are you doing here?
There's something hidden in there
Who is buried?
have no idea
Whatever you choose
You really don't believe in ghosts.
I said hello
what hello
I burned incense
I said it was love that had to be done
If there is really a bad ghost that is alarmed,
The wrongdoer has his head, and the debtor has his owner
Secret Pavilion Bazhai of the Great Song Dynasty
The life of the flower tree
They just take it
Is this appropriate?
fine
usual flower tree
I swear on my life too
Come and help
Kid
Who prompted you?
Made a lot of progress
Not quite right
He didn't try his best
Just a few people
There are a little less people
As long as you can see and speak
Liang Du commanded the army
You should know
Battlefield Capture the Flag
most important
Why
Once the battle flag falls, the morale of the army will be in chaos
That's right
Military morale
most subtle
But the general of an army
Heavier than a military flag
He did it on purpose
What
He just wants to
In front of the Youzhou Army
kill you
Let the Youzhou Army see him from now on
Feeling fear
That's right
Xiao Xue
father
Dad, I'm here
Daddy
father
Pity
Not a long sword