Did you believe this?
More than you believe me?
I see.
I did it for you.
I can explain everything.
Jun-u.
Why did you do it?
Didn't you know the truth would be
revealed eventually?
Didn't you think of
how Soo-bin would think of you?
Why do you think she got confused
over a simple text message?
It's because she can't trust you.
The fact that you're a troublemaker
who was forced to transfer
is always in her mind.
Know your place, Jun-u.
You don't deserve Soo-bin.
Don't you feel...
sorry for Soo-bin?
You hurt someone that you like.
Isn't Soo-bin
the only person you opened up to?
How could you do that to her?
Shut up. Shut your mouth, Jun-u.
What do you know?
Stupid.
You should've believed him.
O-je,
do you know where Jun-u lives?
What if he asks...
What if he asks why I'm here?
No.
-Choe Jun--
-Jun-u.
What are you doing up there?
Hey, Mom.
-Give that to me.
-Okay.
What is all this stuff?
I need to make some side dishes
for tomorrow.
For the restaurant you work at?
Why do you make them yourself?
I'm learning some cooking secrets
there lately.
The chef gave me some homework to do.
I should study hard
until my restaurant's renovation's done.
Jun-u.
Is something wrong?
What's wrong with your face?
It's nothing.
Don't lie.
It's written all over your face.
"I'm having a terrible day.
Don't bother me."
That's not true.
Let's go inside.
Are you at Chan-yeol's house?
Do you know what time it is? Hurry home.
Jun-u, I'm sorry for not trusting you.
It's my fault.
For not being someone you can trust.
No. I should've asked you first,
but I didn't.
Because...
No matter how much I think about it,
I don't think I deserve
to go out with you.
I DON'T THINK I DESERVE TO GO OUT WITH YOU
Are you okay?
What about you?
I think I'll need some time.
Can you understand?
Please don't take too long.
I'm sorry.
The total amount of mechanical energy
of a moving object remains constant.
-Do you guys like roller coasters?
-Yes.
Roller coasters are a great example
of the transformation
between kinetic and potential energy.
Even though a roller coaster
does not have an engine,
it can move up and down the track.
-It's thanks to...
-What's going on?
-...energy transformation.
-No idea.
As a roller coaster
moves down,
its potential energy decreases
while its kinetic energy increases.
Let's see.
"A 10kg object resting on the ground..."
Soo-bin.
Why are you not getting mad at me?
You know that I lied to you.
Getting angry at you now
doesn't change anything.
Right now,
I'm trying my best to understand
from the perspective
of my old friend, Little Boy Hwi-yeong.
"He probably couldn't help it."
That's what I'm telling myself.
Soo-bin.
Hwi-yeong.
I want...
you to give some thought...
to how you feel about me.
How you really feel about me.
Whether you did it because you liked me...
or there was another reason.
I was almost suffocated to death.
What's going on between you guys?
Exactly.
What's going on?
We decided to go back to being friends.
Really?
I understand.
It'd be practically impossible
to slip under your mom's radar.
I think it might be better
for Jun-u's sake.
So-ye, haven't you made up
with Gi-tae yet?
How could she forgive him?
He chose friendship over love.
What friendship? What love?
He just decided to fulfill his duty
as Hwi-yeong's butler.
What are you guys doing?
Are you guys officially leaving me out?
Did you just find out?
We looked for you,
but we couldn't find you.
It's over between you and Jun-u, right?
I guess it is.
Gosh, what should I do with her?
This is so tasty.
-Hwi-yeong did that?
-Yes.
Isn't it unbelievable?
Isn't it so childish?
Well, it is shocking
and extremely childish,
but I guess it is understandable.
He probably lost his reason
for a second...
-O-je.
-I'm just saying it could happen.
Just go talk things out with Soo-bin.
There's no need to complicate things
by overanalyzing--
-Pil-sang!
-Gosh, Pil-sang.
Didn't I tell you to stop?
Pil-sang, Jun-u has eyes
in the back of his head.
You should stop, okay?
Pil-sang.
Instead of doing this to me,
go talk to Ro-mi.
-Go ask her out.
-Am I crazy?
She'd kill me.
Would you rather die or go out with her?
Pluck up your courage.
You're not dead yet.
Ro-mi.
I like you.
I know. Stop liking me.
I want to go out with you.
-No.
-Don't say no just yet.
Please think it over for a few days
about letting me be your boyfriend.
I beg you.
Please answer
before the end of the school trip.
Gosh, Pil-sang is pretty impressive.
Jun-u, good job.
"Pluck up your courage.
You're not dead yet."
I thought it was a scene from a drama.
You're exaggerating.
I can't believe myself.
Who am I to give advice?
When I can't do that myself.
So? Did you keep calling Mr. Kim
to find out about this?
What were you trying to dig up?
The number you have dialed does not exist.
Please check the number again.
Mr. Oh, someone is here to see you.
Me?
Hi.
Oh, okay.
I wanted to bring it over sooner,
but I had a job interview.
Thank you for coming here yourself
when you're busy.
-I'm not busy.
-I see.
The interview must have gone well.
You look happy.
-I failed it.
-I'm sorry.
Bye, then.
-Wait, Ji-min!
-Yes?
-The other day
-Yes, I called a cab for you then
and brought your bag today.
If you want to thank me
with food or drinks, there's no need.
-Then what about...
-What about
a cup of coffee?
I'm a little busy.
Have a nice day.
That's not it.
Food, drinks, coffee... None of that.
"I'm interested in you.
I'd like to ask you out."
If that's what you want to say,
my answer is an even bigger no.
That's not it either.
The other day,
you seemed to be having a hard time.
I want you to hang in there.
Everything will be all right.
Thank you for bringing my bag. Bye.
It doesn't have to be today.
Gosh, dragonflies.
Guys, I have some good news.
Our class vice president, Jun-u's idea
has been chosen as the main event
of the 2nd-grade school trip.
Give him a big hand!
-Why is he so excited?
-I don't know.
Well...
While we're at it, let's prepare well
and become the winner of the event.
The first prize is an air purifier.
Let's do this, guys!
He must want an air purifier so badly.
He startled me.
An air purifier...
I knew it.
All of Dad's clothes are gone.
Why would I keep old clothes?
I've thrown them all away.
I still need them.
Then buy one.
How can I buy
clothes filled with your fond memories?
My goodness.
Let me take a look when I get home.
I wish you cared as much
about your studies as this.
Hello?
She hung up on me. Unbelievable.
-Is it for the school-trip costume?
-Yes.
-That idea was my Jun--
-I wonder who came up with the idea.
I'm sure it's a kid
who doesn't care about studying.
You didn't have to do this. We could
have eaten at a restaurant.
You eat out all the time.
As you can't use your hand...
Thank you.
I'm sure you were popular with guys
when you were younger.
Not at all.
I've had only one boyfriend.
It was Jun-u's dad. He was my first love.
Really? I see.
Have you not dated anyone else
after you broke up?
Well, I dated a few guys,
but I didn't like any of them.
No one came close to Jun-u's dad.
-Thank you.
-Sure.
What will your son do
about the school-trip outfit?
He has his dad's clothes.
I left one to remember him by.
To remember him by?
It's what your dad wore on our first date.
He looked so dashing that day.
Still, they must have loved each other
back then, at that moment.
May I come in, Mom?
Just a minute.
What is it?
What?
You don't have time to waste on that.
Soo-bin's in charge, isn't she?
So you're trying to help her?
No.
I'm the class president,
so I should at least help
the kids prepare for the event.
Go up and study. I'll get it ready.
What if your father finds out?
Hi, Mr. Park. It's me, Park Geum-ja.
Make a suit for Hwi-yeong.
Yes, good. A retro style.
-I can't wait.
-I'm so excited.
Right?
Da-huin, are you going on your honeymoon?
Of course.
-Seriously, don't overdo it.
-Wait.
Ro-mi, looking good.
What's this now?
Seriously. What's with everyone?
Hey. Good morning, everyone.
Is everyone here?
Hwi-yeong, Jun-u, please do a headcount.
-Sure.
-Good.
You look great, Mr. Oh.
-Hey, isn't that Sang-hun?
-You're right.
-Didn't he go to Singapore?
-What?
Hi, guys.
Sang-hun, what are you doing here?
Hello. I wanted to go
on the school trip too,
so I hopped on a swan boat in Singapore
to come here.
What? What's going on?
I'll tell you later.
-Hey.
-Hi, guys!
-Sang-hun.
-Hey!
Okay. Let's get on the bus.
Don't get on another class's bus.
Okay. Where should I sit?
I'll sit here.
Go.
Pil-sang,
just grab a seat. Accept it.
Let's go.
Jun-u, sit here.
Look at that witch.
I'll sit in the back.
What's this?
You have nothing to fear?
Let's keep moving.
Hurry up, you punk.
I'm going.
-When are we leaving?
-Soon?
What's this? Sang-hun didn't transfer out.
He never filed the papers.
-Really?
-Yes.
-It's true.
Yes.
So excited
-Yes.
-And we're off.
Be more animated.
-Yes.
-I'm so hungry.
I'm so excited.
And we're off.
And we're off!
I'm sorry.
I'm hungry.
I skipped breakfast.
Hey. I have food.
You do? Let me have some.
Look how pretty.
Oh, my god. I can't eat this.
What is that?
Jun-u, what is that? I want one too.
Okay. Here. Take one, Ro-mi.
Hey, me too.
Why do yours look the same?
Let me see.
-They're the same.
-What's this?
They are.
Here, take this.
-What is it?
-My driver made them.
Thanks.
See? These are pigs, and so are these.
Share these with your friends.
I made them last night.
I haven't had your rice balls in a while.
Thanks.
Hwi-yeong, Jun-u, check on the kids.
-Bring your luggage.
-Where do we get the keys?
There. Over there.
What?
So, is this where Ro-mi and I
are staying tonight?
Take your bag.
You came.
Don't get too excited.
I didn't come because of you.
Don't smile. Punk.
What a great view.
Look at this.
It's not that good.
When do you plan to wear all of them?
I can wear them all.
How many did you bring?
Just make up with him.
He's walking on eggshells around you.
Look who's talking.
But we didn't fight.
Neither did we.
Cheonbong High School students,
please come to the main hall.
WELCOME
CHEONBONG HIGH SCHOOL TRIP
Five!
-Hurry!
-Chan-yeol!
Yes, we made it.
Okay, you guys are out.
Separate. Again.
Ready? Start!
Two!
Two people!
Those who are left alone, please step out.
Those who are left alone,
you're out of the game.
All right, great job.
Who is still standing?
Hi.
Da-huin.
Here you are.
I was looking all over for you.
O-je. Give me this hat.
This is totally my style.
Hey. How could you flirt
with every single guy?
What?
Da-huin.
Give me that.
Did you just hit me?
No, I was just trying to take off
the hat--
Hey, Ro-mi.
You little...
-Guys!
-Let go of me!
What's wrong? What's the matter?
-Hey!
-Let go!
-Ro-mi!
-Stop it!
Move!
Hey, cut it out.
-Hey!
-Stop it!
Hold on. Time out!
-Come over here!
-Hit me instead.
Hey, stop it.
-Please, stop it!
-Hey!
Get lost!
Guys, let's go have dinner.
-No.
Da-huin, open the door.
It's O-je.
Don't open it.
Da-huin.
Da-huin. I know you're in there.
What if O-je gets caught
inside the girls' wing?
Da-huin.
Sorry, O-je.
So-ye.
Soo-bin. Shall we go have dinner?
-I can carry it now.
-Okay.
You don't have to come tomorrow.
I have a business trip to Japan.
Okay, have a nice trip.
-Goodbye.
-Bye.
Song-hui.
Why are you here?
I know Soo-bin's on a school trip.
How could she be so cold to me
for three days straight?
Her daughter isn't like her.
Oh, this.
-Hello, Ms. Yoon.
-Hello.
I'm not getting a divorce.
I won't let that happen.
How many times do I tell you?
You know how important this period
is for Soo-bin. Are you crazy?
Soo-bin will understand.
In order for me to move
to the States next year,
I need to take care of the documents now.
Why? To get married to that wench?
Song-hui.
Let's stop putting on a show now.
Pretending to be warm parents
in front of Soo-bin,
and a couple in love
in front of everyone else.
I hate putting on a show too.
Who said that I liked it?
But I won't get divorced.
I will never get divorced
until Soo-bin goes to university.
Stop using Soo-bin as an excuse.
Why don't you just beg me
to come back to you?
What on earth...
You act like you're so much better
than others
and act so cool.
I'm sick and tired of it.
Beg who? Do you think I still love you?
You spent the money I made
to get your degrees.
Do you feel confident now?
It's you who should be--
Gosh, seriously...
You're the one who should be more honest.
You feel better when you live
with a woman who's less smart
and less competent than me.
Why can't you be honest and tell me
that's why you're leaving?
Why are you asking if you already know?
Make your decision by next week.
If you don't,
I'll file a suit for divorce.
Seriously... Why?
What are you doing here?
You should go inside, Ms. Yoon.
No, I'm fine.
Da-huin.
It's a misunderstanding.
I'm not interested in Ro-mi.
Then why did you stare at her?
I didn't stare at her.
And about the hat,
Ro-mi just took it from me.
She always acts as she pleases.
I really mean it.
I'm not interested in any other girls.
You're the only one I'm close with.
Really?
Yes.
Then do you like me the most?
-What?
-Do you like me?
It's the PE teacher.
That was close.
-Da-huin.
-You're so cute.
I love you, O-je.
I know how pathetic I am.
All I do is follow Hwi-yeong around
and worry about what he thinks,
believing that
I could become someone like him.
Gi-tae.
I know I'm a loser.
I'm such a loser, so maybe
I don't have the right to like you,
but I still do.
I really like you.
I really like you, So-ye.
But when you treat me so coldly like this,
I can't stand it, So-ye.
Get up. Come on, get up.
I'll change from now on, So-ye.
Make sure each class takes
their snacks and beverages.
-Class One. Over here.
-Take one box each.
Hwi-yeong.
Are you disappointed that I came back?
-I don't care.
-I know you do.
You must be terribly afraid.
What?
I'm joking.
I feel so thankful to your dad.
He gave my dad a promotion
and let me stay here.
What an angel.
How could I repay his kindness?
Let's have fun, my friend.
I'm looking forward to it.
Let's go.
Are you happy? Do you feel satisfied now?
What do you think?
Soo-bin is still having a tough time.
Hwi-yeong.
I'll help you.
You should've called me earlier.
Never mind.
Hurry up, guys.
We're here.
Hurry up and grill the meat.
My family has a villa in Santa Monica.
Santa Monica? You're so cool.
I remember throwing a barbecue party
in the garden there.
Did you do nothing but blabber
in your villa in Santa Monica as well?
Not helping out at all?
Hey, Ro-mi. You're just
a big fat liar, aren't you?
Didn't you say your dad is
the director of Jaeyoung Hospital?
Hey.
Come here.
Your dad is the director's driver.
How dare you tell such a lie?
You almost fooled all the moms too.
I knew it.
You said your mom travels abroad
for conferences all the time.
Is your mom being a professor also a lie?
Pil-sang, this is your chance. Go to her.
What?
He doesn't want to embarrass Ro-mi.
Seo-jin, don't do this here.
-Talk to her some other time.
-Let go of me.
Isn't it funny?
Her dad is not even a doctor.
Hey!
Her dad is a doctor.
-What?
-The last time my mom got sick,
she was treated by Ro-mi's dad.
Why are you making a scene
with some nonsense you heard?
Cut it out, Da-huin.
I don't need your help.
You're right.
My dad is not a hospital director.
I made it up.
What's the big deal?
Saying I was pretty and smart
like my hospital director dad,
you were the one who envied me
and sang my praises.
-Am I wrong?
-You shouldn't have lied.
You shouldn't have been fooled.
Blame yourself for falling for my lies.
Ro-mi!
Don't follow me.
You woke up.
Have some porridge.
Please just leave it here.
I'll eat it later.
-Okay.
-Thanks.
I'll be going now.
Okay.
Yeon-u.
Well...
You don't have to work for me anymore.
But your hand hasn't recovered yet.
I'll help you a few more days
when you get back from your trip.
I can take a cab.
I'd be too embarrassed to see you.
Don't say that.
Please do as I say.
All right.
What we're going to do next is...
Truth Hearing! And we're off!
Well...
Let me see.
Gi-tae! Let's start with Gi-tae!
Come sit here.
Come on.
Guys, ask him anything you want, okay?
Well, you disappeared for a moment
right before dinner.
Where were you?
I had a talk with So-ye.
Then, what did you two talk about?
I made a big mistake.
Hey, what are you doing here?
Come join us.
I'm okay.
Tell me when you need me. I can help.
-Are you sure?
-Yes.
I actually need you right now.
I mean, it's so boring without you.
So boring.
Let's go. Come with me.
Come join our Truth Hearing.
The most humiliating thing
that's happened in my life?
Back in elementary school,
I peed my pants in class once.
-What grade?
I was in fifth grade.
-Fifth grade?
-Really?
Unbelievable.
Are you in love with anyone right now?
-Gosh.
-Seriously.
Hold on. It doesn't count.
The answer is already decided.
It doesn't count.
Come on.
Are you in love with someone
who you shouldn't love?
Let's move on, guys.
Why? Let's hear his answer.
Forget it. Let's move on.
-What is this?
-Are you crying?
What's wrong?
Ro-mi!
-Ro-mi!
-I'll do it instead.
Why? Go back to your seat.
-What are you doing?
-Leave Ro-mi alone.
-Fine.
-I'll do it.
You do it.
Pil-sang, come back.
Go back to your seat.
You all saw earlier, right?
I'm a big, fat liar.
I don't deserve to participate
in this game.
So I refuse.
-Da-huin.
-I'll pick one.
-Gosh.
-What happened?
Soo-bin.
Soo-bin!
Do you still like Jun-u?
That was straightforward.
Do you?
Answer right now!
All right then.
There's no exception.
-Five, four, three, two, one!
Gosh.
I ate too much today.
She's a real sociopath.
After being humiliated like that...
Chan-yeol.
I can hear you.
I'll never try to defend her again.
Exactly.
Never try to defend me again.
Gosh, are you serious?
Calm down. Leg exercise.
She's so annoying.
My stomach hurts.
JUN-U
Soo-bin, sleep tight.
-Gosh.
-What's this?
Pil-sang, please don't.
-It's not me.
-Just don't!
Who is it? Come on!
-Come on!
-Please stop.
It wasn't me!
Can't you guys fall asleep?
Why are you still up?
Maybe it's because I'm away from home.
I can't sleep either.
It's driving me crazy.
Ro-mi, are you crying?
Cry all you want.
I take back calling you a sociopath.
So you do have a conscience.
Seo-jin or whatever her name is.
Forget her.
Hey!
CHEONBONG HIGH SCHOOL
Okay. Next up is from Class Three.
Here's the outsider, Yoo Pil-sang.
-Come out!
-What about Dong?
Did he join at the last minute?
Hello. I'm the most desired guy
in Cheonbong High,
Yoo Pil-sang.
-You're so cute!
-I'll do impressions.
First, Cheonbong's vice principal.
-Let's go.
-Hey.
-Are you nervous?
-No, that's not it.
-What's going on?
-I feel diarrhea coming on.
But you're next.
Hold it in. You can do it.
-You can do it.
-I can do it.
I can do it.
I can do it. I can't do it.
I don't think I can. I can't do it.
I'll go while singing.
You can sing, right?
You're good, right? I hope you're good.
Good luck.
Dong.
Okay. Next up is Go Dong.
He will finally take the stage.
-Please give him a big hand!
-Come out, Dong!
Come out!
-Hurry up!
-Come out!
Dong!
-Are you not ready?
-Why aren't you coming out?
-Go Dong is coming--
-Come out, Dong!
Why is Jun-u coming out?
-It's Jun-u.
-That's not Dong.
-Is that you, Jun-u?
-It's Jun-u.
-What?
-Jun-u? Why?
-Why is Jun-u...
-In Go Dong's place,
-Choe Jun-u will take the stage.
-What's going on?
-Okay. Give him a warm hand!
-Yes.
Jun-u!
Why am I nervous?
Dance for us!
From far, far away
She comes to me
What do I do about my trembling heart?
How do I describe it?
You
Stole my heart
From the start
And gave me
An incurable disease
I want to be
A plant
I will be a plant
On your small windowsill
Even if I can't say a word
Even if I can't wish for anything
Every so often I will receive
Your smile and your touch
And watch you as you sleep
As much as I want
Nice!
Excuse me! You in the checkered shirt...
Are you all right?
Don't you resent
being a nobody?
I like you too.
I will be a plant
On your small windowsill
Even if I can't say a word
Even if I can't wish for anything
Every so often I will receive
Your smile and your touch
And watch you as you sleep
As much as I want
DANCING IN THE RETRO NIGHT
Pil-sang, come with me.
If you haven't decided yet,
you can tell me later.
No, I'll tell you now.
Pil-sang.
You're not my type.
Totally not,
so stop dreaming.
What must I do...
What must I do to make you like me?
I... I'll try. I'll do anything.
Don't try.
You can try for 10, 20, 100 years...
No, even if we meet again
in another lifetime,
you'll never be my boyfriend.
Find someone else.
Gi-tae.
Let's end things here.
What?
Let's break up.
Why?
You will never change.
And I'll keep hating that.
Hwi-yeong.
I want you to give some thought...
to how you feel about me.
How you really feel about me.
Whether you did it because you liked me
or there was another reason.
I don't care what that feeling is.
What's important is...
I won't let Jun-u take anything away
from me.
I can't.
Jun-u.
I'm sorry for not trusting you.
I'm sorry for making you not trust me.
Stay beside me.
You guys were all happy, right? Dismissed!
Shall we go?
I miss you more,
and also,
I keep wanting to know more about you.
Don't worry about Jun-u,
and rest in peace. I'll look after him.
I'm doing well. I'm happy.
What has changed for you
since we started going out?
I keep looking in the mirror.
My reflection looks so excited.
Like stroking your hair.
I think we should pull Soo-bin
out of the private lesson team.
-Ms. Park.
-What are you doing?
Did you do something to offend Hwi-yeong?
I asked my mom
to pull you out of the team.
I thought seeing you at every session
would be too hard for me.
Guys, you're here.
Aren't you...
Hello, ma'am.
Even if we're friends, this seems wrong.
Why don't you come inside for some water?
My mom is at work now.
Hey! Hey, hurry.
Come over here!
Subtitle translation by Wayne Ryu