I like you.
I like you too.
What...
Jun-u...
I like you.
-That's hot!
-Are you okay?
What is wrong with this?
Soo-bin.
Are you okay?
Yes. I'm feeling better now
after taking medicine.
What about the test?
I finished it. In here with Jun-u.
I'm sorry. I wanted to bring you
to the nurse's office.
Don't worry, that's fine.
If you got a question wrong because of me,
I'd have to leave school.
Your mom will kill me.
Come on. That's not true.
Thanks, Jun-u.
You can go now.
-Ma'am, his hand--
-Ma'am, her hand--
I'm sorry.
Mom.
Hello, ma'am.
Soo-bin suddenly had stomach cramps
during the exam.
I heard.
Why did it have to happen
during your math exam?
She lost a lot of time because of it.
So it must've been hard
for her to focus on the exam.
It's such an important exam.
Why math of all exams?
What should we do now?
Hwi-yeong. My gosh, I'm sorry.
Did you ruin your exam because of Soo-bin?
It wasn't me.
He carried Soo-bin here.
Thank you.
Then did you come here after the exam?
Good. You did the right thing.
My goodness.
Hello.
-Are you all right, Soo-bin?
-Yes.
I couldn't come sooner
because I had to supervise the exam.
-Oh. Hello, ma'am.
-Hello.
Mr. Oh, what do we do?
I'm not sure.
What about the time she lost
on her way here from the classroom?
It's not like she wanted to fall ill.
That should be taken into consideration.
I know she took the exam here,
but I'm sure she couldn't focus.
This is crazy.
It's such an important exam.
I'll make sure she's not put
at a disadvantage...
Are there rules for situations like this?
I'm not sure. I'll have to look into it.
-But you said you'll make sure...
-Let's talk outside, Mom.
Were you able to focus?
-Yes, I... I tried my best.
-Gosh, okay.
-Thank you.
-I'm sure she couldn't focus.
What should we do?
What can we do about this?
-The exam is already over.
-Let's go, Mom.
Gosh, I heard you! Yoo Soo-bin.
You seem totally fine.
Did you actually feel sick?
Why don't we talk outside?
-Let's go talk outside.
-All right.
Are you all right?
Ma'am, did you get an appointment
for a checkup at such short notice?
Yes.
My friend from Seoul National University
runs the clinic.
I'd like her to go through
her answers before we leave.
Don't worry about that.
I'll send you the answer sheet
as soon as it's out.
I'm going to go through the answers now.
Oh, right. We have Hwi-yeong.
He always gets a perfect score
on every exam.
You should do it for her.
Okay, then.
-Soo-bin! Are you all right?
-Soo-bin.
-Hey.
-We were so worried.
I wondered why I kept getting
the Moon card.
I always get this card when I have
a bad feeling about something.
She's at it again.
She talks like an expert, doesn't she?
Hey, can't you predict these things
before they happen?
Guys, let's go.
Hey.
Let's go over the answers
for the math exam before we clean.
We can go into detail together later.
Goodness, what a diligent class president.
What's the rush?
I mean, we should do it.
Okay, let's have a look.
Question 1 was easy, right?
The answer is number 3.
-Gosh, I got it wrong.
-I got it wrong.
Number 3 for Question 2.
-Number 3?
-Number 4 for Question 3.
-What's the answer to Question 3?
-Number 4.
Focus, guys.
What was that? What's the answer?
-Number 1 for Question 4.
-Okay!
Number 2 for Question 5. Next...
Mr. Oh, I think I've seen that boy
somewhere before.
His name is Jun-u. He transferred
to our school recently.
The one who was forced to transfer, right?
Well, that's...
No, it was just a regular transfer.
Jun-u, where are you going?
You don't want to know the answers?
I have to take care of this.
Why did a boy like that carry Soo-bin?
I mean, you were there too.
I was supervising the exam
in another classroom.
This can't happen.
Soo-bin can't be close to that boy now.
I mean, with the random draw too.
-Jun-u isn't a bad kid.
-He was forced to transfer here.
Mr. Oh, please keep
a watchful eye on those two.
Okay, I will.
I did as well as I had expected.
Well, Soo-bin seems to be okay now.
-Let's go sing some karaoke.
-Karaoke? Sounds good.
I did better than last time.
I scored about the same.
I really don't like math.
Soo-bin.
Did you get number 15 right?
No, I picked number one.
How many did you get wrong in total?
What? Soo-bin did much better
than you did.
Hey, Ro-mi. What was all the fuss about?
"Even Soo-bin passed the test.
How could I fail?
Gosh, I feel dizzy."
She took Son Jae-yeong's class!
He must've predicted all these questions.
All the questions are so dumb.
Come on, Ro-mi.
How could she say such a thing
to someone feeling sick?
Hey, Chan-yeol.
Gosh, what the...
-Watch your mouth, will you?
-Mind your own business.
Pil-sang, be quiet.
He carried Soo-bin here.
Thank you.
Did you get this one wrong too?
This too? Even such an easy question?
Hey, even I can solve that question.
How will you get into the top tier
at this rate? It won't happen now.
Why did you quit Mr. Son's math class?
What makes you so confident?
Mom, you're more worried
about the exam than me feeling sick.
Stomach cramps go away
if you take medicine.
It's not like you have
a terminal illness, Soo-bin.
You really need to make yourself
mentally stronger.
How will you survive in this
battlefield with that mentality?
I'm sorry that I'm mentally weak.
Hey, I heard the boy who carried you
is a troublemaker.
Jun-u isn't a troublemaker.
Anyway, it's the boy
who was forced to transfer here.
The handsome boy we saw
in front of the academy, right?
He was with that young woman
who seemed to be his mom or aunt.
She had a knockoff purse.
It's that boy, right?
Why did he carry you earlier?
Why does he keep coming up?
Is something going on?
Are you interested in him
because of his looks?
-Don't you dare hang out with him.
-You got the wrong idea.
Don't even go anywhere near him.
You shouldn't befriend guys like him.
-Don't get close to him.
-We're just classmates, I swear.
Lower your voice.
The math exam was quite hard, right?
Even I found it pretty hard,
so don't be too discouraged.
I bet he got a perfect score again.
Let's do better on the final exam.
I'll help you guys.
Moving on. Oh, Question 15.
The math teacher
set up a trap in this question.
Hey, Hwi-yeong.
Did you tell my classmates that
the answer to Question 15 is number 4?
Hey, how could it be the number 4?
Number 4 is the correct answer.
Hold on a second.
Sang-hun, this is so unlike you.
You fell for the trap.
No, you're the one who fell for the trap.
If you do this...
T squared is... nine T... minus K...
That means T is this.
And K equals zero.
See? You totally got tricked by this trap.
Hwi-yeong fell right into the trap.
In conclusion, K...
is included in zero.
Hence, the answer is number two.
You dummy. You idiot.
Mr. Son, can you solve
a math problem for me?
I'll be at the academy soon.
I'll call you back.
No. You have to solve it right now.
This instant.
I'm driving.
Okay. I'm pulling over
because of your enthusiasm for math.
Your teacher apparently made
the problem extra tricky
so that you guys would fall into his trap.
It can have different answers depending on
which aspect you base your solution on.
So which number is it?
Fine. Give me a second.
The answer is number two.
Are you sure?
That question was rude.
If T is a positive number
and larger than zero...
Damn it!
No!
In that case, it won't be finished
in the first half.
Which part is being delayed?
Okay.
Then I'll attend
the training session this time.
I like you too.
I like you.
Why isn't he doing anything
after saying that he likes me?
Could it be that it all happened
in my imagination?
This feels weird.
The whole thing feels so unreal.
You're done.
Hello?
So she doesn't have a disease or anything?
No. It's probably stress-related.
Cut your daughter some slack.
I am giving her enough slack.
It's just that she's too sensitive.
Excuse me for a second.
Hello, Director.
I can't believe your mom.
She's a little difficult, isn't she?
She was famous for being
a tough one back in our school days.
-Doctor.
-Yes?
Well...
Can an illness cause hallucinations,
delusions, or anything like that?
Get some rest today.
You failed to get
into the top tier in math,
so you have to listen to me
from now on, okay?
I have to get back. I'm swamped with work.
Eat the porridge.
Okay.
Thanks, Mom.
CHOE JUN-U
When you're under extreme stress,
you're mentally unstable,
which can cause confusing experiences.
For example, you can mix up
your wishes and reality.
That...
I did secretly wish
something like that would happen.
You're heavy.
You were so heavy when I was carrying you.
I thought I was going to break my back.
Right.
People only see what they want to see
and hear what they want to hear.
Was that self-justification?
It must've been self-justification
to forget the shame.
No. What about this?
-That's hot!
-Are you okay?
What happened? It's completely gone!
My gosh!
Soo-bin, are you home?
If you're feeling better, come over.
To our crazy after-exam party.
Gosh, I went overboard.
My stamina isn't what it used to be.
Soo-bin, what's with you today?
Is it because you failed
to get into the top tier in math?
So what? Forget it.
Did O-je leave?
Yes.
He has to help out at his dad's snack bar.
Guys, I have to go to the bathroom.
-So-ye.
-Yes?
Again?
Who would believe
this pretty girl has bowel problems?
What do you care?
Soo-bin, are you really not feeling well?
Do you want me to take you home?
Wipe harder.
Over there. Here too.
Do you see how much trouble
your mom caused us
while she filled in for you?
Do you?
She's too old for me to boss around,
so I had to do all the organizing
and carry all the heavy things.
My arm still aches.
She did her best.
Her legs were all swollen.
She used two packs of pain relief patches.
You punk. Do you have a problem? Do you?
You need a lesson. I'll call our boss
and tell him all the things
you've done wrong.
-Yes, I'm really calling him.
-No, wait.
I'm sorry.
Let me go organize the storage.
So you do have a conscience.
Eat first. You need energy.
You just can't stay out of trouble,
can you?
You're such a troublemaker.
Should I have talked to Soo-bin?
What is it now? Why are you frozen again?
Are you so touched
by the triangular gimbap?
You're so innocent.
Hey.
Well...
After telling someone that you like her...
Did you?
Who is she? Who?
It's not me.
There's this boy in my class.
His name is O-je.
He...
doesn't know what to do...
after telling a girl that he likes her.
How can he not know that?
It's so obvious.
Obvious? What should he do?
After telling a girl that you like her,
the next step is...
to kiss her.
-Someone said he likes you?
-To you?
-Who?
-Hwi-yeong?
Why would he? There's no need
for him to say that. It's obvious.
It's not me.
It's a friend of mine from middle school.
Middle school? Who?
Min-seo? Yu-ri?
No. It's someone you don't know.
Anyway, a guy told her he likes her.
But the guy hasn't called her since.
Nothing.
They didn't make plans to meet
or anything?
No.
But... I heard they had
a very hectic day at school or something.
What about a text message?
But... I also heard
that the guy is usually very busy.
Come on. No matter how busy he is,
that's wrong.
He just told her he liked her.
Right, it was their first day as a couple.
First day as a couple?
Of course.
After I asked O-je out,
we had pasta together that day.
Over there, at the mall.
Gosh, I already miss my O-je.
-It's you, isn't it?
-What?
-No.
-Come on, it seems like you.
No way!
I knew it, it is you.
It isn't! Seriously.
I was joking.
Of course, it isn't you.
What is Ro-mi doing?
She didn't even come to the karaoke bar.
She said she was going
to a luxury spa with her mom.
Hotel spa.
Of course, it isn't me.
Ro-mi, where are you?
I'm going to dinner with my mom
after the spa.
You guys can go ahead.
Okay. See you tomorrow.
-How much did you say it was?
-It's 2.5 million won a month.
It costs that much?
It's a one-on-one coaching lesson
that includes consulting. That's why.
Would you like to enroll?
Let me think about it.
Why is it so expensive?
Dad.
-Why aren't you coming?
-I'm sorry, Ro-mi.
I have to drive the hospital director
to the countryside for urgent business.
Sorry.
What a terrible day.
MATH EXAM
Hwi-yeong,
you didn't go home yet?
Oh, that math problem?
I heard from your math teacher.
It's just one question.
Don't worry so much.
Since the test is over,
go home and get some rest.
One question?
My life may change over that one question.
Just one question?
Hey, man. Stop overreacting.
What do you mean, your life may change?
It's because you keep thinking that way
that your arm doesn't heal.
Do you know that?
You should know
how to let things go sometimes.
If you obsess about small things
like this, you won't get anything done.
What do you know?
You didn't graduate from
Seoul National University.
You didn't even go to a university
in Seoul.
What do you know?
Hey, Hwi-yeong. Ma Hwi--
Hey!
That punk has no manners at all.
Hey, Ma Hwi-yeong!
Where are you? Come home.
We need to come up with a plan
for your math score.
Trying to recall what happened again
and again makes me even more confused.
You should go and check
if it was real or not.
Go.
Good job today.
After telling someone that you like her,
don't think that's it.
You should kiss her
as a meaning of celebration,
or if that's difficult, you should
at least keep sending her messages.
To confirm that she accepts it.
"Hey, you. What I said just now,
I really meant it.
As of today, we're a couple.
Got it?" Something like this.
When a girl hears a guy say he likes her,
everything is suddenly
so out of this world to her.
"Is this real?
What if it's a dream?"
She becomes like that.
She starts to feel so confused
all of a sudden.
She literally loses her mind.
Soo-bin, what I said earlier...
Soo-bin, how are you feeling?
No, let's just ask straight out.
Soo-bin, what I said to you earlier
in the nurse's office...
I heard your bike's name is Bumbi.
Hi.
Can you give me a ride on Bumbi?
I feel so gloomy today.
I have a flat tire,
so it doesn't go properly.
I'm sorry. Bye.
Then can I borrow your
transportation card?
I left my wallet at school.
That won't work.
Jun-u, I have something to ask you.
Is the person you like Soo-bin or me?
-What?
-I think that you like me.
My friends think so too.
But last time, it seemed like
you were interested in Soo-bin.
Is it because I kept ignoring you?
Is it like
"something is better than nothing?"
Stupid.
Hey. Did you think it'd be that easy to
go out with the queen of Cheonbong High?
-Hey, Moon Chan-yeol.
-It's Hwang Ro-mi.
Stop making lame jokes.
Oh, Hwang Ro-mi.
Let me make it clear.
-I--
-The bus is here.
He turns all red whenever he sees me.
How cute.
Right. How could I forget that?
-Sir, one person.
-Two people.
-No, one person.
-Hurry up and get in.
-Two people.
I'll get off.
I want to get off.
Sir, I'm sorry, but can you let me off?
Bye.
Hey, Jun-u!
What is wrong with her?
What?
Darn it, Jun-u...
What do you know?
You didn't graduate from
Seoul National University.
You didn't even go to a university
in Seoul. What do you know?
Darn it. That's exactly
what my mom said to me
ten years ago. My goodness.
Hold on.
Has he been possessed by my mom?
Is that true, Mom?
Why Ma Hwi-yeong of all people?
I still miss you, Mom.
You've never dated anyone.
What were you thinking, giving him advice?
THANK YOU FOR APPLYING
FOR OUR JOB OPENING.
UNFORTUNATELY, YOU DID NOT
PASS THE INTERVIEW.
I've failed the interview again.
I'm doomed.
My nose is all stuffy.
I'm depressed enough already.
Why do you have to cry and be so annoying?
Hey, mister.
If you're going to keep crying,
can you go outside and cry, please?
Mister.
I'm not crying.
I'm sadder than you right now!
Go outside and cry, please.
Do you know that I want to cry
a lot more than you do?
I should still ask him
and check what really happened.
Why?
Because I hate being
in a situation like this.
I should get it sorted out
as soon as possible
so that I can focus on studying again.
Well, you know.
Who cares if it was just my imagination?
It's not like I'll be fined
or get marks deducted.
I am Yoo Soo-bin, a confident girl.
You got this, Yoo Soo-bin.
This is so hard.
CHOE JUN-U
IT'S OKAY
"It's okay"?
Who is this?
IT'S OKAY
Hello?
Is this Jun-u?
Soo-bin.
It's me, Soo-bin.
Jun-u.
Can you hear me?
What's going on?
Hello?
Did he just hang up on me?
What? He hung up on me.
It got all messed up. Totally messed up.
But today isn't over yet.
Why didn't I think of this sooner?
LOG IN
ENTER THE CODE IN YOUR TEXT MESSAGE
Darn it.
Right.
But where does Soo-bin live?
Jun-u, what is wrong with you?
Do you even know anything?
It was bad timing.
I shouldn't have told her today.
I could've waited until tomorrow
or the day after.
Today wasn't the only day
I could say it to her.
Jung O-je, this jerk.
He ghosts me whenever he wants.
Are we really dating?
Gosh. Don't be so clingy, Da-huin.
Guys get sick of things like that
very quickly.
What did I do?
Well, don't all girlfriends do this?
-O-je.
-Yes.
Let's talk.
About what?
-Go away, lovebirds.
-You didn't call me last night.
Oh, I had to work last night.
-Where?
-You know, at the snack bar.
-But you didn't have a shift yesterday.
-I did. I had to work.
-Let's...
-Let's go!
Well, about yesterday...
Well, thanks for taking me
to the nurse's office yesterday.
I actually called you last night.
Why?
I thought about it and realized
I never thanked you properly,
and I felt bad because you probably
ruined your exam because of me.
That's why I called you.
It seemed like someone picked up,
but I couldn't hear anything.
It's okay, though.
Sometimes, you don't hear anything
even if the call gets connected.
It happens.
Anyway, thanks and sorry.
Thank you.
I have to go. Bye.
She called me.
You really don't have any friends.
Not even one person called
or texted you.
One person did call.
Who is "It's okay"?
I picked up, but there was no answer.
Your phone is a piece of junk.
Get a new one.
Why is it that nothing is going my way?
As if the entire universe
is working against me.
-Soo-bin.
-Hi. What?
-Hey, did you do your homework?
-Did you think you lost your phone?
-You dummy.
-Hey!
-You couldn't find it?
-That's not it.
Look at her all chipper
while completely ignoring
my confession yesterday.
It's so weird.
Don't tell me my dear Ro-mi
has a crush on that newbie.
Gosh, no way.
It's possible.
In any case,
weird questions like Question 15
shouldn't be on exams in the future.
That's why I asked you
to meet me at this early hour.
-Ma'am, the question wasn't weird.
-Enough.
Mr. Park wanted to come up
with high-quality questions
that were more original,
and he got a little too enthusiastic.
-That's why...
-Yes, sir.
-Mr. Oh, there you are.
This is Hwi-yeong's mother.
I see. I've heard a lot about you, ma'am.
I'm Hwi-yeong's new homeroom teacher.
Mr. Oh Han-gyeol, right?
Yes. It's nice to meet you, ma'am.
You see... Please don't take this
the wrong way.
I'd like to make a suggestion.
Pardon me?
An open class?
We already had one
at the beginning of the semester.
Yes, I'm aware.
I'd like another one just for Class Three.
For your English class.
I see. You'd like to know
how competent I am as a teacher.
You're as smart as I expected.
I'm afraid I can't do that.
I am actually planning
to hold a meeting with the parents
and introduce myself
as the kids' new homeroom teacher.
But I don't think my competence
has to be verified by the parents.
One more thing.
I heard that you put the brakes
on Hwi-yeong's plans every time.
I put the brakes on his plans?
The former homeroom teacher, Mr. Kim,
let Hwi-yeong have control
over his study plans
as far as I know. I mean, full control.
That's why the average scores
of Class Three could be
at the top of the whole year.
So I'd appreciate it
if you could actively support
Hwi-yeong's study plans.
Nullifying the question?
It doesn't make sense.
Sang-hun, the question itself...
I'll be the top student
if it's not nullified.
-Fine, let me explain inside.
-Gosh.
-This is driving me crazy.
-Let me explain. Come.
Ms. Park, see you again.
Good morning, everyone.
Let's start our morning assembly.
Did something good happen?
Hwi-yeong is the top student again.
Really?
Hwi-yeong, congratulations.
Thank you, Mr. Oh.
If it wasn't for Question 15 in math,
Sang-hun would've been
top of our year, right?
I think so.
Is it true all the answer choices
for Question 15 are considered correct?
That's what I heard.
-That's a relief.
-That must drive Sang-hun crazy.
He got it right in the first place.
I got it wrong, but Hwi-yeong saved me.
Thanks, Hwi-yeong.
All right.
There's something we need to do
before the morning assembly.
To fill the vacancy,
we'll elect a class vice president.
-What?
-Suddenly?
-Really?
-Why?
-This is sudden.
Don't worry, Mr. Oh.
I can handle it alone.
Right. I'll help him out too.
I appreciate it, guys.
You guys are so reliable.
Still, let's do it.
Hwi-yeong has too much
to deal with. It hurts me.
-Either Gi-tae or Soo-bin--
-We don't have much time.
You can either volunteer
or recommend someone else.
But it has to be someone
who doesn't have any role right now.
Come on, guys.
-Volunteer or recommend.
-Kwon Da-huin.
Me!
-Yoon So-ye.
-All right.
-Lee Yun-jin?
-So-ye, Da-huin...
-Me!
-All right.
Either volunteer or recommend.
Me?
-No way.
-Why?
-I can't do it.
-Me!
I won't do it.
Hurry up, guys.
All right. Pil-sang. Who else?
-Does he have a desire for power?
-No one else?
All right. Who wants Pil-sang
as our class vice president?
That's not a good idea.
I'm against it.
Pil-sang put your hand down.
Unfortunately, everyone is
against it, Pil-sang.
Okay. Who else?
Jun-u, what is it?
I'd like to recommend someone
for the position.
You're not volunteering?
Jun-u, you better not recommend me.
Who do you recommend?
Mr. Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm not interested at all.
I'll...
do it.
-What?
You?
You recommend yourself?
-I approve.
-Me too.
Me too.
This is very unexpected. Okay.
Mr. Oh, he's definitely better
than Pil-sang.
-I approve.
-Me too.
-Really?
-I approve!
-He's better than Pil-sang.
-Who approves?
Choe Jun-u for the class vice president.
It's decided.
Congratulations.
Jun-u became the class vice president?
Yes. And what's more surprising is
that he volunteered.
Jun-u is doing well in school.
You don't have to worry too much.
Mr. Oh, thank you.
Thank you so much.
Jun-u became the class vice president?
The class vice president.
Rock-paper-scissors!
Jun-u wins. Pick one.
-Soo-bin.
-Soo-bin. Come.
What about you, Hwi-yeong?
-Ro-mi.
Ro-mi, stand behind Hwi-yeong.
One more time. Ready.
Rock-paper-scissors. Hwi-yeong wins.
You can attack anyone
whether it's a boy or a girl.
You get hit, you're out, okay?
-Okay.
First... Team Gi-tae, get ready.
Let's do this.
-Gosh!
-Yes!
-Oh, my.
-Let's go!
Gosh, that would hurt.
Guys, what are you two doing?
Give the ball to someone else.
Soo-bin!
-Here we go!
-Ro-mi, here.
Hey!
Da-huin! Here you go!
Here we go.
Over here!
Go!
Hurry up!
Oh, my.
-Hold on.
-Come here.
Yes!
Jun-u.
Soo-bin, you're like a pea.
A tiny pea.
Jun-u is out!
I can't believe what Jun-u did.
Why did he overprotect you like that?
I'm sure he just wanted to catch the ball.
Now that he's the class vice president,
does he want a brand-new image?
Gosh.
Then again, what I really can't
believe is what that girl did.
She attacked you pretending to attack me.
Gosh, it hurts so much.
Sorry, Da-huin.
Put that halibut away.
Halibut?
By the way, O-je was amazing.
I guess.
As always. It's no surprise.
What are you doing? You're so annoying.
-Move over.
-I love you, Da-huin.
-Over there.
-Watch out!
Good!
-Over here.
-Good job.
-Let's go!
Do I have a parasite or what?
-Why am I always hungry?
-Darn you.
We're going to be late.
Stop messing around.
MEN'S LOCKER ROOM
I took care of the math test issue.
-How?
-You worthless idiot.
How could you humiliate
your father like this?
Why do I have to kiss up to someone
because of you?
For what?
I'm sorry.
It's going to be concluded that
there was a problem with the question.
But Mr. Jo's son, Jo Sang-hun,
solved that question without any trouble.
But what about you?
I've spent my precious money
for your education.
Is that all you can do?
Is it?
Honey, wait. Don't do this.
Hwi-yeong tried really hard this time.
-Honey, please.
-Was that him trying his best?
-Honey, please...
-I told you to move.
Move!
Go upstairs, Mom.
No.
No. You can hit me instead.
-Hit me.
-Right.
You're responsible too.
I'll teach both of you a lesson today.
Hey, Jun-u.
Do you want me to clear your name?
You know, about stealing that watch.
I'll prove you're innocent. How about it?
There's no need. You missed the chance.
I'll clear your name for you.
Don't you want that?
Is this because you're angry at Hwi-yeong
about the math test?
Take care of it on your own.
Instead of trying to use me.
Hey, Jun-u. Hey!
Hwi-yeong.
Hey.
-Hey.
-You shit.
You fucking coward.
How could you use your mom
to coax the math teacher?
I was going to be top of our year.
How could you rig the exam?
Rig what?
The math teacher admitted that
the question itself was wrong.
You're not at the top because you couldn't
beat me in other subjects. Don't blame me.
This is unbelievable.
Hey. Your parents made such a fuss,
and the math teacher eventually
gave in. You think I don't know that?
Did you see it?
Do you have proof?
Do you have proof, you bastard?
Well, I guess it's not your fault.
You're just your parents' pet.
It'd be better for me to ask them myself.
You just wait, Hwi-yeong.
I'll fix this by all means
and be top of our year.
Right, I guess you are guilty
of something.
Of not being as bright as me.
You little...
Well, I guess it's not your fault.
You're just your parents' pet.
-Of course, I did.
-Gosh, you must be proud.
I do feel proud.
Who wants to come to Soo-bin's house
to hang out today? Me.
-Soo-bin, you have to come.
-Yeah.
-I'll let you hang out with us.
-Be quiet.
Let's go eat tteokbokki.
-Okay.
-Tteokbokki!
Yes, let's go eat tteokbokki.
Here you go, I brought your fried squid.
Enjoy your meal.
-They're so big.
-Thank you.
Welcome. Come sit over here.
Hello, sir. I'm O-je's friend.
You sit next to O-je. Was it Choe Jun-u?
Yes.
You transferred, and you're good
at drawing. Am I right?
Yes.
It's nice to meet you. I'm O-je's dad.
You're even better looking than I heard.
You're almost as handsome as my son.
O-je.
-Yes.
-Jun-u is here.
-Oh, okay.
-Hold on.
Jun-u.
-Whose baby is that?
-It's my brother, O-dong.
Isn't he cute?
Hang on. I'll get you
some tteokbokki and fries.
Later. I came here because...
-O-je.
-Yes?
-This is an emergency.
-Why?
The delivery orders are pouring in.
Oh, boy.
-Don't cry, O-dong.
-Welcome.
-Hello.
-Take a seat.
-What should I do?
Mom won't be back for a while.
Don't cry, O-dong. Don't cry.
You need some help with the delivery?
I'd be grateful, but there are
so many orders.
Instead of that...
Is that his baby?
He looks so young.
Oh, my. He looks just like his dad.
How handsome.
He's not my son.
Looking good.
Thanks. Let's go.
O-je. I have something to ask you.
Let's go and talk. It's hot.
Let's go get some tteokbokki.
Yoo Soo-bin...
What?
Where is Soo-bin?
Do you know where Soo-bin lives?
What?
So that's how everything went wrong.
No.
That was just an excuse.
I didn't know how to react
since it was my first time.
But...
I really meant what I said.
I really meant it.
Da-huin said Soo-bin will be home
if you go now.
But what is it that
you have to give her yourself?
Jun-u.
Why do you walk so fast?
We ran into each other again.
-I guess.
-What are you doing here?
I'm here to see Soo-bin.
I'll see you at school.
I'm on my way to Soo-bin's house too.
Why do you want to see her?
You could just send a message.
Well, Ro-mi. It's...
I have something important
to tell Soo-bin.
Can I meet her first?
What is it?
I want to say something
since I ran into you.
All right,
I'll accept your feelings for me.
This is our first day as a couple.
I know you have feelings for me.
I've been thinking it over,
and I guess I'll accept you.
Let's go out. You and me.
Ro-mi.
It looks like there's been
some misunderstanding.
I don't have any feelings for you.
What? Are you playing hard to get?
Don't lie to me.
I saw you staring at me all the time.
Did you think I wouldn't know?
I have feelings for Soo-bin.
You probably thought I was looking at you
because I was staring at Soo-bin.
I'm sorry if I gave you the wrong idea,
but I should still tell you the truth.
How could you have a crush on her, not me?
She is Hwi-yeong's girlfriend.
No, she's not.
I've confirmed it with her.
I have to go.
I wonder if they'll make you
take another level test.
Soo-bin.
Hello, I'm Choe Jun-u.
I'm Soo-bin's classmate.
Yes, I know.
And?
-I...
-Hey, Jun-u.
We're in a bit of a rush,
so let's talk tomorrow at school.
Let's go, Mom.
Wait.
May I talk with Soo-bin for a moment?
Soo-bin, do you want to go to the movies?
-Another couple?
-Congratulations, Soo-bin.
I can do it. I got this.
Welcome to the English open class!
Does anyone have a different opinion?
I...
disagree with that opinion.
Make things go back to how they were.
Then I'll keep my lips sealed.
I'll try to persuade Sang-hun again.
Please have mercy, sir.
Sang-hun, let it go for my sake. Please?
Gosh, you're only 18 once.
Subtitle translation by Wayne Ryu