What?
You bastard.
Did you just call me trash?
Yes. Since you're blaming me
for what you did.
Be honest...
and tell me what happened.
I'm sorry. I was a bit harsh.
I was just taken aback.
No one has ever misunderstood me
like this.
It's nothing.
That punk, Jun-u.
What's taking him so long?
I need to go home.
Jun-u,
you can be honest with me.
Actually, I knew.
Have you seen Mr. Son's watch here?
He probably took it with him.
He didn't have it on.
Did you see him? You should've told me.
I just wanted to pull a prank on Mr. Son.
I was going to hide it.
It must be that guy.
The delivery guy.
I'm sure he stole it.
-No way.
-Trust me.
I saw him rummaging around
when he was cleaning up.
That thief.
Sang-hun, I'll go talk to him.
Let go. I'll go ask him.
I'll go see what's going on.
He's in my class.
Jun-u, just a second.
That's when I thought this.
"It already happened, so I shouldn't
let things get out of hand."
I thought I should find a way to help you.
You idiot. Did you really think
it'd still be there?
I'm sure he's already stashed it
in his pocket or underwear.
Jun-u would never do such a thing.
What are you talking about?
I heard he was forced to transfer
to our school because of theft.
Everyone knows.
I knew it. I knew he was up to something.
That's what Jo Sang-hun said.
And it looks like
he already told all the teachers about it,
along with the fact that I know as well.
Sang-hun, that jerk...
I'm sorry, Jun-u.
I didn't know it'd turn out like this.
But...
-seeing how you're suspecting me--
-"Suspecting"?
It's not just suspicion.
I saw it.
What on earth are you talking about?
I thought maybe you had your reasons.
And there must be a reason
that you're acting this way too.
Hey, Choe Jun-u!
Is that you, Jun-u?
You need to submit your apology letter.
Why didn't you come by?
And why aren't you picking up your phone?
Come on.
Hurry, get back here!
Are you going to tell Mr. Oh?
About what you're thinking.
I'm not sure.
LEE GI-TAE
Please leave a message after...
Why isn't he picking up?
Are you all right?
That must've hurt.
You didn't go to the academy?
How could I?
Knowing what you're going through.
LETTER OF APOLOGY
I thought about it,
but I did nothing to apologize for.
My goodness, you're...
I'm surprised.
You have a talent. You did
a great job of drawing this ladybug.
But we do need to submit
your letter of apology,
so please write another one.
If I submit this one,
I'll get in trouble. Here.
I really have nothing to write about.
Also, don't think about
transferring again just yet.
Hey, Jun-u.
As you know,
I'm just an assistant teacher.
If these big problems come up
while I'm filling in,
and a transfer student
gets transferred to another school,
and if the kids get even more
out of control as a result,
what do you think will happen to me?
Just try to think simply, sir.
A new kid is moving again
because of personal reasons.
No, I can't think like that.
The situation we're in is different.
Jun-u. First, the letter of apology...
Jun-u, you need to write something
instead of doodling.
Why did I get this?
Hey, write one as soon as--
Jun-u. Hey, Choe--
Gosh, this punk.
Choe Jun-u!
Jun-u! Wait.
Write a letter of apology. Please?
Come on. Get back here.
Hey, no! Wait!
God, it's so hot. My feet are killing me.
Good, you made a wise decision. Here.
Yes, great. Come here.
Good. Gosh, I can't wear these. Hey.
What's Oh thinking?
He's just an assistant teacher.
Hey, Choe Jun-u! Hey!
Sang-hun, do you know what happens when
you count on your brain and don't study?
You'll become stupid.
I'll still beat Hwi-yeong in math
even if that happens.
Hey, still...
Stop making fun of Hwi-yeong.
They were easy questions.
He shouldn't get those questions wrong.
Hwi-yeong.
Are you all right?
By the way, wasn't
what Hwi-yeong said earlier so cheesy?
"We shouldn't be biased against Jun-u.
We should trust Jun-u and be on his side."
Hey, Da-huin. Soo-bin will punch you
if you keep that up.
Why would I punch her?
I told you Hwi-yeong and I aren't dating.
We just went to the same kindergarten.
But I do agree
with what Hwi-yeong said earlier.
I think maybe we should've tried
to find a way
to help Jun-u.
Look up.
Why am I so pretty?
-Girls, look at Soo-bin.
-Why?
Wow, Soo-bin looks so pretty.
Wait, what time is it now?
Soo-bin, are you going to keep this up?
Do you know
how much the tutor charges per hour?
If you miss the session today,
we can't book that tutor again.
Soo-bin. Hey!
My mom is too much.
Is something going on?
Do you have a tutor now? A math tutor?
Who's this tutor? How much?
I really don't want to do it,
but my mom keeps...
Girls, I've got to run.
-Bye, see you tomorrow!
-What?
-Bye, Soo-bin.
-Bye.
Stop bumping into things!
What's this?
Getting good grades makes your life
so difficult, don't you think?
My mom's totally given up on me.
She'd be awfully grateful
if I didn't miss any classes.
I'll get going too.
Ro-mi, you don't have
any tutoring session today.
I'm going to a spa with my mom.
Bye.
Mom, please. I really don't want a tutor.
I'll study hard on my own. Please?
And what's the result?
Until when will your math grades
hover around Second Tier?
Mom, please.
If you keep this up, I'm going to
go talk with Hwi-yeong's mom.
I'll ask her to help you join
his math class.
No, please don't. I'll go. I'll go now.
Get there in ten minutes.
Don't even be a minute late.
How can I get there in ten minutes?
Why can't you?
That building is
right in front of your school.
Are you not at school now?
I am. I am at school.
I'm on my way. Okay, bye.
Gosh, I really hate this.
Everyone who studied with that tutor
got into Seoul National University.
Having a good career
is so important to her.
Oh, no! I'm in trouble.
I can't get there in ten minutes.
Darn it.
You again?
Yes, it's me again.
Oh, right! Hey, where are you going?
-I'm going to work.
-Where? Is it far?
It's right there.
Then let's turn this around.
I'm in a big rush now. Let me borrow this.
No, you can't. I live far from here.
I'll make sure to bring it back.
I'm sorry!
-I'm borrowing this!
-I have to go home later.
I live far from here.
Hey!
Sorry!
My place is really far from here.
Your mom said your goal is getting
into Seoul National University.
That is what my mom wants.
I don't care which school I go to.
I just want to choose the major.
Right. So you should study harder
and aim for SNU like your mom's hoping--
Well, I know that's not going to happen
even if I try my best.
I'm not that smart.
And I don't want to get stressed out
from such an unreasonable goal.
But I've already discussed this
with your mother.
Ma'am.
I heard all the students
that you've taught so far
entered Seoul National University.
I've heard a lot
about how amazing you are.
So I'm afraid
I might leave a stain on your reputation.
I'll talk to my mom and persuade her.
Thank you for your time today.
Yes! Soo-bin, you did a good job.
Has he already left?
Gosh, you startled me.
What are you doing here?
You were looking at something.
This.
Oh, my bike...
Thanks for the bike.
I was hanging out with my friends
after skipping the after-school study.
And I suddenly got a call from my mom
and had to be somewhere in a hurry.
Thanks for returning it.
Bye.
You didn't think I'd return it?
I was going to return it tomorrow
at school if not tonight.
I'm not coming tomorrow.
Didn't you say you're coming
to school until tomorrow?
Well, I decided not to come.
Right.
Is this what you call research?
I did my best.
A reference list needs more
than just book titles and author names.
I wrote down the publishers too.
You have to specify
where exactly each quote is from.
Haven't you done this before?
Anyway,
do it again by tomorrow.
I told you, I'm not coming tomorrow.
That's your problem.
Shouldn't you do your duty
before you leave?
Just like I came here to return your bike.
Don't tell me you're disappearing
after putting our group in trouble.
That'd be so irresponsible.
You heard that I'm the queen
of performance assessments, right?
Now that I've accepted you into our group,
shouldn't you at least show some--
Here.
Eyes.
Do you have something in your eyes?
Let me see.
Let me take a look.
No. Not mine.
Here.
Gosh, why didn't he tell me earlier?
Hey, I want to ask you something.
Well...
A pack of One Day, please.
I'll get going.
Thanks for your bike.
What is it? What do you want to ask me?
Well...
Did you really...
steal that academy teacher's watch?
I guess you didn't.
Bye.
Why?
Why do you think I didn't steal it?
I thought maybe you had your reasons.
And there must be a reason
that you're acting this way too.
Hwi-yeong is studying.
Father, you're home.
What were you doing?
-Pardon?
-Why are you standing so awkwardly?
Is it still so hard to stay in your seat?
No. I was looking for a workbook.
Are your mock exam results out yet?
-I'm getting them tomorrow.
-He did a good job again.
What was his name?
That son of Mr. Jo at my company.
Jo Sang-hun. In Class One.
Yes, Jo Sang-hun. That smart kid.
Beware of kids like him.
Kids who have nothing
but their good brains.
They're the scariest.
I'm one of them.
I had nothing but my brain to rely on
while struggling to climb this high.
I don't ask for much.
Just do as well as your big brother, okay?
Okay.
Open the door.
Open the door. Open it!
Open it right now!
Hey!
You know how hard it was
to make an appointment with the teacher.
You do know, don't you?
How could you do that?
I don't feel comfortable
with one-on-one tutoring.
What did you...
Does it even matter
if you feel comfortable right now?
Think of your grades.
What's so wrong with my grades?
I came 28th in my year. Is it that bad?
Other kids with my grades
would have been complimented
and become their parents' pride.
Are you like other kids?
Is it okay for you to enter
just any university in Seoul
like those kids?
Soo-bin, do you have any idea
what a difficult place
this society is for women?
Do you think you can stand
at the same starting line as men? No way.
That's why,
from your family, parents, wealth,
and education to looks,
all those things count
as your weapon and asset.
You have everything.
What do you lack, really?
Tell me what it is that you lack.
All you have to do now is study.
Work hard for two years
and enter Seoul National University,
and you can do whatever you want.
I'll leave you alone.
What's the problem?
Have I ever asked you for anything else?
All I ask of you is to study.
How hard can that be?
Am I asking you to make money?
Women can't live like men in this society!
Soo-bin!
We have to work a hundred times harder!
Do you have anything to say?
I'll study harder.
Go study.
-When is Dad coming home?
-Why? What about him?
You call him every day. Why are you asking
me? Maybe when this semester is over.
Do you think you can study less
if he's home?
Don't be ridiculous.
Don't take too long in the shower.
It'll make you drowsy.
I'll be checking on you at 1 a.m.
Okay.
Here.
So what?
Thanks for returning it.
Bye.
What's so precious about that bike?
It was a piece of junk.
REFERENCE LIST, REORGANIZE LIKE THIS!
She has nice handwriting.
Why do you think I didn't steal it?
For two reasons.
First of all, you seem a bit
too slow to steal something from others.
More importantly, I think you'll
find stealing itself so bothersome.
Did you almost smile again?
What was your name again?
Gosh, should I go to school tomorrow?
I really don't want to.
CHOE JUN-U
I really don't want to go.
I really, really don't want to go.
THE NAKED TREE
Hurry up, Jeong-hu!
My mom isn't home today!
Jun-u, wait for me!
CHEONBONG LIBRARY
Jun-u.
You're here early.
I have something to do.
-What is it?
-Some research.
For the performance assessment.
What for? You're leaving tomorrow.
I might not go tomorrow.
Then when?
I'm not sure.
This bastard is toying with me.
I see.
Hwi-yeong.
What?
-Don't worry.
-About what?
I won't tell anyone.
Hey, Jun-u.
You're here early.
Good morning, Hwi-yeong.
I have to check for tardy students today.
-Take care of the class for me.
-Okay.
Jun-u, don't you have something
to say to me?
You little punk. How could you
just run away like that yesterday?
Hwi-yeong, you can go. And you follow me.
-Over there.
-What?
-It's the vice-principal.
Hey, Jun--
See you later.
Your payment has been settled.
Thank you.
Hey.
Near the school.
Now?
No, okay. I'll be there right away.
Okay.
Gi-tae.
-So-ye.
-What are you doing?
I was getting a book rebound.
Sorry, but something came up,
so I have to go.
-I'm sorry.
-What is it?
Hwi-yeong?
PHILOSOPHY, LITERATURE, LINGUISTICS
LETTER OF APOLOGY
Could you write this first
before you study?
And during this important era
appears a great figure.
Let's finish this part next time.
-Okay.
-Thank you.
-Thank you, teacher.
-Have a good day.
I'm so hungry.
Why don't you go eat some grass?
Like a goat.
-Do you want some?
-No.
Da-huin is stressed out lately.
She gained 500 grams.
Goodness, Da-huin.
Why are you living like that?
What's so important about
looking pretty to others?
It's not just anyone. It's O-je.
O-je's ideal type is
extremely skinny girls.
O-je, do you...
No. Don't say anything.
Soo-bin, what?
Oh, it's nothing.
He's so good-looking.
What are you looking at this time?
-The newbie isn't coming.
-Choe Jun-u?
What if he got arrested or something?
He said he was transferring.
I guess he already left.
He's really a man of his word.
He kept his promise.
Shouldn't you do your duty
before you leave?
Hwi-yeong.
Yes, Chan-yeol. What?
Did the newbie really leave?
Is he not coming?
Jun-u?
I don't know.
He should've at least told us
that he was really leaving.
Choe Jun-u, that loser.
I thought he understood me.
He really didn't come.
You came.
Oh, right. About the list of references...
THE NAKED TREE
I checked all the cited parts,
but I couldn't for the life of me
find some of them.
My gosh! Choe Jun-u, this rat.
Move. Let me see.
Goodness.
The newbie was a thief after all.
Wow, I'm impressed.
Oh, my. The newbie's got some nerve.
My gosh, you dirty thief.
You're really something.
Hey, where's my watch?
Oh, here it is.
Jun-u, didn't you transfer
to another school?
I thought you did.
Gi-tae, what's going on?
We opened Jun-u's locker thinking he had--
I asked him if I could use this locker
because the corner one is uncomfortable.
But we found...
Gosh, how much would this cost?
You didn't have to open it
in front of everyone.
I didn't expect to find this
in his locker.
How did you know I wouldn't be here today?
-What?
-I...
only told Soo-bin.
I didn't tell anyone.
You guys were told
that today would be my last day.
We didn't see you in the morning,
so we thought...
Gi-tae, you were misinformed.
Jun-u's leaving tomorrow.
I see. I guess I was confused.
-Guys.
-Let's go. They're coming.
My goodness.
You've already decided
to leave our school,
so I don't even know
how we should handle this.
In any case,
Mr. Oh, handle it well
so it doesn't get out of control.
-As for our students,
-Yes, sir.
make sure they don't spread any rumors.
-Sir.
-Understood, sir.
Yes? Hi, Hwi-yeong.
I just spoke with Mr. Son on the phone.
He said he'll just let it go.
-Really?
-Seriously?
Yes. And he asked me
to bring the watch to him.
Hwi-yeong,
you're such a skillful negotiator!
Oh, my. He should become a diplomat.
Yes, you're right.
That'd be perfect for him.
Jun-u.
It's all sorted out now, so don't worry.
Hwi-yeong never lets us down.
He's the pride of our school.
What's been sorted out?
We haven't even figured out
who put it in my locker.
Goodness, Mr. Son said
he'd kindly forgive you.
He doesn't need to forgive me.
Jun-u, what are you doing?
I've done nothing...
to be forgiven for.
What...
My goodness.
Ma Hwi-yeong.
Did you really have to do this?
-What?
-I'm leaving this school anyway.
You could've just let me go quietly. Why?
What are you talking about?
You're out of line.
I think I've done my best to help you.
Right, there's nothing to expect
from people like you, right?
Today, we'll be learning
about the coastlines of Korea.
As you guys already know,
each of the three coastlines
has different characteristics.
First of all,
what's the eastern coastline like?
It's relatively simple, right?
Then what about
the western and southern coastlines?
They're complicated. Very complicated.
Why? Because all the mountain ranges
point toward...
Next, you can see it here.
Ma'am, I have a question.
Yes. What is it, Hwi-yeong?
From the last assignment...
The last assignment?
The one about volcanoes?
In the case of basaltic lava,
it has low viscosity,
which means it's more fluid.
Therefore, basaltic volcanoes
have gentle slopes.
Okay?
Great. Now, let's take a look
at the questions below.
-Go!
-You got this!
-You can do it!
-Faster!
-You got this!
-Run faster!
Where's Jo Sang-hun?
Sang-hun? He's over there.
Sang-hun! Jo Sang-hun!
-Go, team!
-Faster!
-Jo Sang-hun.
-What are you doing here?
-Did you really see it?
-See what?
Me stealing the watch.
-What?
-Did you see it?
-Go!
-Go for it!
All right. Now, let's learn
-about Ulleungdo and Dokdo.
-Hey!
-You, over there!
-Ulleungdo is...
-It's the newbie.
-The lava from...
Guys, what are you doing?
Hey, isn't the one
in the white T-shirt Jo Sang-hun?
And isn't that the newbie?
-The newbie?
-It's the newbie.
Guys, go back to your seats!
-Go!
-Go for it!
Hey, Sang-hun runs super fast, right?
He was the fastest one
in my middle school.
Right? He's super fast.
Hey, look at that.
-What's with them?
-Should I get the baton?
Hey, stop. Hey!
-Hey, Sang-hun!
-Hey!
You need to pass the baton to me!
Guys!
Stop chasing me! I'm exhausted.
I asked you if you saw me
stealing the watch.
How fast can you run?
Hey, what are they doing?
The PE teacher is watching.
Get back inside.
I think they're fighting.
What are they talking about?
-Hey!
-Ma'am.
I think they're fighting.
I should go stop them.
No, you shouldn't. Go back to your seat.
-It's dangerous.
-Guys, go back to your seats.
Hey, Pil-sang and Dong.
Did you see me doing it?
Is that what Hwi-yeong told you?
Yes.
Hwi-yeong, that jerk...
Hey, Choe Jun-u!
Get me a popsicle on your way back!
I want a popsicle!
What are they doing?
-We're not sure.
-Guys! What are you doing?
My gosh, the PE teacher.
The PE teacher saw us.
All right, guys.
Let's get back to where we were.
What do we do about them?
Where were we?
I'm sorry, ma'am.
It's okay, Hwi-yeong.
All right, next page.
In winter,
the cold air mass from Siberia...
Come here.
Hey!
Gosh, I'm so forgetful.
Hwi-yeong.
That newbie is quite something.
He's super fast.
What did he say?
Did you tell him that I saw it?
Yes.
Interesting.
Why are you here?
I can't play with you anymore.
My legs are killing me because of you.
Don't you remember what I said?
What do you mean?
I saw it too.
Are you happy now, newbie?
Didn't I do a good job?
Here I go. Gosh.
Are you leaving?
You haven't changed your mind?
Yes.
You were running around the field
so fast earlier. What was that?
You were going to leave anyway.
I was curious
why they did that.
Saying they saw something they didn't.
Saying they didn't do something they did.
Is that it? You were curious?
Curious, my foot.
You were angry.
All the treading made you turn.
Am I wrong?
You're running away right now.
Fine, walk away trying to look
all cool. But you don't!
Hey!
Jun-u!
You're only running away!
I'm in front of the school gate. Come out.
Soo-bin!
-What's going on?
-Let's go.
-Where are we going?
-Let's go!
Did you find another tutor?
Another one already?
Why are we at Hwi-yeong's house?
Soo-bin, carry this.
God, what is all this?
-What are we doing right now?
-Just follow me.
Who is it?
Hello, I'm here to see Ms. Park.
-"Ms. Park"?
-Stay, or you get no allowance.
Pick it up. Right now.
Sorry for making you wait.
Why do you bring so much every time?
-Come on in.
-Okay.
-Have a seat.
-All right.
I was talking to my eldest son
on the phone.
-He's in the US, remember?
-Of course.
I'm sorry for showing up so suddenly.
Don't worry. I understand.
You must feel anxious
with the midterm coming up.
By the way, Soo-bin,
you've become so much prettier.
I'm worried.
When the girls become prettier,
the boys can't focus on their studies.
Thank you.
So, Soo-bin wants to be
in Mr. Son's class?
Yes.
No matter how hard I look,
I can't seem to find
a better math teacher than him.
That's true.
I talked to Mr. Son,
and he said we need your permission.
My goodness. He's exaggerating.
Why would you need my permission?
If she's good enough, she can join.
You're aware that you need
to pass the level test, right?
Of course.
I...
-Even after that...
-Even after that?
Without your permission,
Mr. Son won't accept her. We know that.
Please think about it.
Let me talk to Mr. Son.
-Thank you. I appreciate it.
-I'm home.
Hi, my son.
Soo-bin and her mom are here.
-How have you been?
-Hi, Hwi-yeong.
You've become so handsome.
Your son is perfect.
No way. He has a long way to go.
I love your dress.
I bought it recently...
What a bitch.
She thinks she's the queen.
She's nothing
without her husband and sons.
How obnoxious.
If we had met 20 years ago,
she wouldn't have even dared
to talk to me.
She graduated from a university
no one has heard of.
I'm sorry I didn't tell you beforehand.
Hey, humiliation doesn't last long.
I had no choice.
Without some special measures,
-you would have--
-I'm sorry, Mom.
What?
I'm sorry I'm not a top student
like Hwi-yeong.
I made you beg that lady.
Hwi-yeong.
I'm glad you're here.
You'll probably never see Mr. Son again
after this.
But still, you should settle it.
The thing you said earlier...
"People like you."
What did you mean
by that?
That?
Well...
Which school are you transferring to?
I'm moving to Onyang. My mom works there.
"People like you."
People like you are nothing special.
You are living and breathing,
but even if you keep on living like this,
you have no hope.
You're okay no matter
how badly other people treat you.
You just live.
Just because you were born
even if no one welcomed you.
Just because you still are alive.
Just because you don't even have
the guts to disappear.
I pity
people like you.
What about you?
Don't you pity yourself?
Why would I?
I'm different from you.
Go now.
You asked one more thing.
Why did I have to do that to you
when you were leaving anyway?
Because you were out of line.
You started to raise doubts about me
instead of getting lost quietly.
How dare you do that...
to me.
Does that answer your questions?
All of them?
-Yes, Mom.
-Did you pack up your things?
You should pack lightly for now.
I'll go over there on Sunday
and get the rest of your stuff.
I visited the school
you'll be going to this afternoon,
and it seemed really nice.
Just forget everything,
and when you come here,
you should just focus
on your studies, okay?
You have to go to a nice university
and succeed
so that you can be a proud son
when you meet your dad later.
Dad?
Where does he live?
Do you even keep in touch with him?
Of course, I keep in touch with him.
Didn't I tell you?
He lives in Pohang or something
because of his work.
Do you know how much he worries about you?
Mom.
I have to go.
I'm on my way home.
Jun-u--
Mom, you think I don't know
where he lives, don't you?
I know
where his house is.
Now that I'm leaving soon,
I think I have the courage.
The courage to see him once
before leaving.
The man who brought me into this world
without any blessing.
Choe Myeong-jun.
Who is it?
-Excuse me...
-We're not done
with our noodles yet.
Tell him we'll put out the bowls
in 30 minutes.
We'll put out the bowls in 30 minutes.
Can I help you?
Don't you...
Don't you know me?
What?
I think you came to the wrong house.
-Daddy!
-Did you have fun today?
I want this.
By any chance,
are you Mr. Choe Myeong-jun?
No, I'm not.
Okay.
By any chance,
are you Mr. Choe Myeong-jun?
Choe Myeong-jun? No.
I thought I had finally found you.
I always thought about
what I should say if I meet you.
But...
-Yes.
-Hey.
I was wondering if you got home safely.
I did.
I'm packing right now.
Jun-u.
I'm sorry about earlier.
I just meant...
Don't worry about it.
I'll try harder from now on.
No, there's no need. When you come here,
you don't have to try so hard.
I'm just happy as long as you're with me.
The ladies in this town are
looking forward
to meeting my handsome son.
Do you know my friend Hye-yeong?
She even made
radish kimchi to give you when you arrive.
Also, do you remember Seon-mi? She--
I'm sorry, Mom.
What?
For getting in trouble again.
I wanted to do better this time.
What are you talking about?
It's not your fault.
It's because of those mean jerks.
They think you're a pushover
since you don't live with me.
Who can I blame?
It's all my fault.
I should've always stayed
right by your side.
But I have no choice
because of that darned money...
Mom.
Are you crying again?
No. Why would I cry?
Crying means that I've lost.
Don't let it get you down.
You're not running away
from that place, okay?
You're coming here since I'm living here.
To be with me.
Let's live happily here, Jun-u.
I am...
I'm truly happy right now.
Since I can live with my son.
I can make breakfast for you every day now
and even iron your school uniform for you.
I feel so happy.
Okay.
Good night.
You're running away right now.
Fine, walk away trying to look
all cool. But you don't!
You're only running away!
I'm running away.
Why do I keep running away?
Why must I keep running away?
Because I don't care
however my life turns out?
I pity
people like you.
"People like me"?
I'm sorry, Jun-u.
Because of me... It's all my fault.
I'm sorry, my son.
Don't cry, Mom. I can see you crying.
I'm not crying.
I'm already in bed.
My mom is still young and immature.
But she didn't run away from me
even back when she was much younger.
She didn't run away.
THE MIDTERM
D-19
Guys, I have great news.
On the mock exam, Hwi-yeong...
ranked in the First Tier...
on every subject.
-Awesome!
-Amazing!
-We're proud of you.
-Nice!
-We're proud of you!
-Ma Hwi-yeong!
-How does he get such good grades?
I know, right?
-That's amazing!
-All right.
-Hwi-yeong.
-Ma Hwi-yeong.
-Well done!
-You should say a few words.
-Thank you, Mr. Oh.
-Don't mention it.
Thanks, guys.
I think I got good grades by luck
this time, so I'll study harder.
Let's all do better next time.
All right. Give him a big hand!
You're so cool!
You're cool!
Hwi-yeong, don't mess with me.
You'll converse freely in pairs
for three minutes.
The study leader will
randomly pick your partner.
That was a good call too.
Not running away. Good.
If you face any problems,
you can talk to me openly about them.
-Yes, sir.
-That sounded so insincere.
If her performance assessment
and English exams are ruined...
I don't think it's something
you can sort out.
For Soo-bin, not for you.
Why are you concerned about me?
Because I was forced to transfer here
and seem like a loser?
Right, it's just how Jun-u is.
Subtitle translation by Wayne Ryu