Have some more water.
I'll go get my phone.
Okay.
Hey! Hey, hurry.
Come over here!
It must be our housekeeper.
It's okay. It's all good.
Jun-u.
Mom.
Come here.
So... You two are...
Is that why you asked me
about my first love last time?
Are you two...
-You know...
-Yes.
Yes, we're...
Hello, I'm Yoo Soo-bin.
Yes, hi.
Of course I know you,
Soo-bin.
I was about to tell you,
but it hasn't been long...
since we started dating.
Right. And some stuff
happened recently as well.
Congratulations, guys!
Congratulations, Jun-u.
So you two are actually going out, right?
Right?
Congratulations.
Huge congratulations to both of you.
Let me have a good look at you, Soo-bin.
My son Jun-u's first love.
Thank you for being Jun-u's first love.
My gosh, why am I tearing up?
Gosh.
I can't believe such a cool girl
like you is my son's girlfriend now.
This makes me so happy.
Thank you.
By the way, what happened, Mom?
What?
Why do yours look the same?
Let me see.
At first, I wasn't going to do it.
Soo-bin's mom was also
uncomfortable with it.
But if you think about it,
it's just a job, you know.
I figured it'd be better than doing
nothing during the renovations.
But I should've thought more
about it from your perspective.
I made such a rash decision, didn't I?
And if Soo-bin is your girlfriend now...
What do we do?
You're uncomfortable with it, right?
No, I'm fine with it.
I'm just worried that it might
have been hard for you.
No, not at all.
You know I like to drive, cook, and clean.
It's perfect for me.
My gosh, I should get going.
-I have to go pick up Soo-bin's mom.
-Okay.
She doesn't know that you guys
are going out yet, right?
No, she doesn't.
Just tell her.
I don't want you guys
to hide it from anyone.
I feel bad that I know about it
when she has no idea.
We'll tell her.
But maybe not right away.
Right?
You'll need some time
to mentally prepare yourself.
But don't take too long, okay?
Okay.
I'm off.
I hope your shift goes well today.
Drive safely, Mom.
-I will.
-Good.
Bye.
Once again, huge congratulations
to you, Jun-u.
My son's first love!
Oh, my! She's his first love.
Bye, Mom.
Mom.
You couldn't come with me
because we ran into my mom.
My mom just left.
Are your hiccups completely gone?
Yes. They're gone.
I can see that.
Soo-bin.
I was on my way to the convenience
store because I was worried,
but you're here.
I'm sorry. I really had no idea.
Why are you sorry?
My mom
just works for your mom.
Are you uncomfortable with it?
I'm really okay with it.
No, I'm fine if you're okay with it.
I'm glad that my mom is fond of you.
Although I knew she'd be.
By the way, your mom is so nice.
She's like a girl.
Right?
My mom thinks we should tell your mom
about our relationship.
She feels bad that she knows
when your mom doesn't.
Right, I understand.
Let's go.
Thanks for walking me.
Take it easy.
I will. I'll think about you.
-I'll be off, then.
-Okay.
Get going.
All right.
Bye.
-Get home safely.
-I will.
What took you so long?
Where have you been?
I was at the library because of
the performance assessment.
You should've called me.
I would've sent the driver over.
Are you tired?
-Hey.
-Hey, you need to see this.
Someone posted something strange.
I THINK MA HWI-YEONG IN CLASS THREE
RIGGED HIS GRADES
What is this nonsense?
Is this rumor about Hwi-yeong true?
CHAN YEOL:
IS THIS RUMOR ABOUT HWI-YEONG TRUE?
Come on. Why would he?
He always gets the highest grades.
Maybe that's why
he always gets the highest grades.
Do you think it's true?
I have to say,
it doesn't sound like a mere rumor.
I'll find out!
Ro-mi.
RO-MI LEFT THE ROOM
Gi-tae, is it true?
We don't know anything for sure yet.
Let's just study.
I'm just curious.
-Yes, ma'am.
-Right.
-We're looking into it.
-We're not sure...
-Please don't worry.
-Say we're looking into it.
We're looking into it now, ma'am.
Don't be too concerned.
Hello, ma'am. Right.
-I see.
-We're looking into it now.
-My gosh.
-That's right.
Mr. Oh, did you see this?
Yes, just now. I was in the classroom.
Ms. Bae, what are you waiting for?
Delete the post immediately.
Oh, hold on.
We shouldn't just delete the post.
We have the full right to delete any posts
that contain false information.
Yes, I'm aware. But I'm afraid
it might stir up more suspicion.
We should post something official
explaining the situation
before deleting the post.
-Or--
-The kids are so fast.
They've already reposted it everywhere.
-This is crazy.
-All my friends know about it too.
The rumors will quiet down soon.
This happened last year too.
My grandma said a rumor is
usually true if you keep hearing it.
Hey, what did Hwi-yeong say about this?
Oh, right.
You guys aren't on good terms now.
What did Gi-tae say?
Right, you're in the same boat.
Then what about O-je?
Gosh, you too.
What is the matter with all of you?
Da-huin, go home.
You're bringing everyone down.
My house is really hectic right now
since my relatives visited.
I just want to stay here.
Do you think my house is
some kind of care home?
HWI-YEONG
SCHOOL BULLETIN BOARD
COMMENTS
Stop looking at it.
There's no need.
Did something happen?
-Something I don't know about.
-No. Nothing happened.
So don't worry about it.
And keep studying.
You shouldn't worry either.
And stop drinking.
I didn't drink.
It was just juice.
You should study.
Yeon-u, did you wait long?
Did you bring what I asked you?
Yes.
Did you see the post?
The moms are going crazy.
Leave them be.
Once Hwi-yeong gets
the highest grades again,
they'll compliment him
like it never happened.
You had your cast taken off.
I did. That's why I came late.
Well, I guess you won't need me anymore.
Why? We still have some time left
on our agreement.
Still, you're well now.
I still feel a bit uncomfortable.
Why don't you help me a little more?
It turns out that my son
has a new girlfriend.
-Oh, my god!
-No, a rat? Where?
It's not a rat.
How could your son start dating so soon?
He's a senior next year.
This is a big problem.
I feel so bad for you. Goodness.
Yes, it is a big problem.
Did you get off work?
Yes.
Are you coming from the academy?
You must be tired. I'll see you tomorrow.
Okay.
But...
You're pretending not to know.
You probably saw the post.
There's no reason for me to bring it up.
To be honest,
I can't be nice to you.
See you.
That punk acts tough,
but he's actually more vulnerable
than anyone.
You're a true teacher.
You were so furious about Hwi-yeong's mom,
but you're still worried about him.
Do you know that's all you've been
talking about since earlier?
Have I?
I'm sorry. You must've been bored.
A little bit.
A little bit?
My mom
always told me to become
the top student as well.
How could you not get a perfect score?
Look at me.
Look at me!
You must get a perfect score
and become the best.
Didn't I tell you
that's the only way you can survive?
Oh Han-gyeol!
She was such a frightening
and hysterical mom to me,
and whenever I looked at her,
she seemed unhappy.
So I tried my best to make my mom happy,
but things didn't turn out well
in the end.
Later on, I had trouble attending school,
so I dropped out
when I was in eighth grade.
Eventually, I didn't get
into the university my mom wanted.
I blamed my mom so much
while I was growing up,
but she passed away from an illness
when I was in university.
After that,
I felt a huge sense of regret,
and I felt so sorry for my mom
who devoted her life to me.
I felt sorry for the Han-gyeol
back then as well.
I'm sorry. I suddenly ruined the mood.
Mr. Oh.
Your mom must be truly happy
since you've become
such an amazing teacher.
You think so?
Of course.
"Oh, my. My Han-gyeol,
I'm so proud of you."
That's what she'll say.
I really hope that's true.
It's probably Hwi-yeong's
previous homeroom teacher.
We've done more than enough for him.
What more does he want?
Maybe the person who posted that
is Mr. Oh Han-gyeol.
We need to change his homeroom teacher.
How can we change it again?
Is that all you can think of
after going through that mess?
-What are you talking about?
-How have you been behaving at school
for something like that to be posted?
Did something happen
between you and Mr. Kim?
Is that why he was injured...
Don't be silly.
And what is this about Mr. Oh?
What have you two been up to?
What? Don't you know
everything was for your sake?
If you just did well on your own,
do you think I would've
been humiliated like that?
Honey! Don't.
Hwi-yeong, let's go upstairs. Let's go.
There's someone else I'm suspicious of.
Who?
You know, that genius you like so much.
Hwi-yeong is probably experiencing
a mental breakdown by now.
My mom thinks we should tell
your mom about our relationship.
She feels bad that she knows
when your mom doesn't.
Hey, you know that guy?
No,
you know my driver, right?
Her son has a girlfriend now.
Does that make sense?
He's so thoughtless.
His mom is working her butt off right now.
I guess he doesn't care
about getting into college.
Hey, Soo-bin.
You better study really hard this time.
You have to do good on the finals.
You better not forget that Hwi-yeong's mom
kicked you out of the private lesson team
because of your grades.
Never forget that sense of humiliation.
Okay?
Why? Do you have something to say?
Something to say?
I'm just feeling thirsty.
Go get some water.
I hope the post
about that rat's son is true
so that she gets humiliated really hard.
Soo-bin.
-Let's go.
-Okay.
Hi, Hwi-yeong.
That means exams are coming up.
Oh, right. The finals.
"Oh, no, the finals!"
You're suspecting me, aren't you?
It wasn't me.
Why would I post something like that?
My dad got a promotion,
I didn't have to transfer,
and I even joined an exclusive
private lesson team
that I could never afford.
Why would I betray
such a grateful friend...
Oh, gosh.
Sang-hun.
What do you want, Gi-tae?
Didn't you quit being Hwi-yeong's butler?
Hey, Gi-tae.
Don't mind us, and just go.
What is this?
Some sort of broken friendship?
This is quite interesting.
Hwi-yeong, I'll be your best friend
from now on then.
Why? I'll be nice.
I'll be a good friend, Hwi-yeong.
Don't worry.
I bumped into Hwi-yeong last night
on the way home from work.
He said it wasn't bothering him.
Let's go.
Are you doing what Jun-u did?
This worked for Jun-u.
What the... Are you giving up on Ro-mi?
Is that a fish?
You bastard.
I'm serious right now.
I doubt she'll like that
if you give it to her.
Your drawing isn't really screaming
that you're serious.
Pil-sang, let me see.
Hand it over.
HWANG RO-MI
You need to draw an outline first.
Like this.
Now, you have the outline.
-Then...
-Oh, my god.
Jun-u, you can really draw.
Now, you have to highlight her features.
How'd you describe her face?
She has a small face and beautiful eyes.
-Like this?
-Oh, my.
-It looks just like her.
-Gosh, Jun-u!
What else?
Her under-eye bags look cute.
-Under-eye bags?
-Yes.
And her bangs look like mine.
Okay, got it.
Da-huin, let's go have some food.
You'll really faint at this rate.
Da-huin, are you this distraught
because of a boy? Don't be such a loser.
Get back at him by going out
with someone better than him.
Yes, I am a loser.
Do you know what love is?
All you do is lie.
You have no idea what true love is!
-Girls, I'm hungry.
-Who do you think you are?
-Calm down.
Hey, O-je.
-What's your problem?
-Ro-mi.
How dare you make Da-huin starve herself?
Who do you think you are
to give her such a hard time?
Hey, why are you hitting O-je
out of the blue?
Take it up with me. Why hit O-je?
You saw that, right?
You need to take responsibility.
Give back all the love
you've received from her.
How could you end things like that?
Have some manners.
Da-huin.
Da-huin clearly
still has enough energy left.
She won't die.
Mr. Oh.
I'd like you to be honest with me.
-About what?
-About my parents' faults.
-What?
-I'm sorry about the petition
for a new homeroom teacher.
Don't worry about it.
The mothers did that
because they want you guys
to get better grades. That's all.
And they withdrew it right away.
You must be bothered by the post
on our website.
Are you suspicious of me as well?
No.
I trust you.
Hwi-yeong, you see...
It's very unlikely,
but even if something unexpected
did happen,
I'm sure you wouldn't have
anything to do with it.
I never cheated or rigged my grades.
I'm aware. I know that, of course.
Hey, have you eaten yet?
-Shall we go eat something?
-No. I should get back.
Mr. Oh is in a meeting,
so I'll give you guys a few updates.
There isn't anything special.
I've posted all the updates
regarding the performance assessment.
Hwi-yeong. The rumors about
rigged grades aren't true, right?
There's another post?
What do you guys think?
I'm just curious. That's all.
Let's get ready for the next class.
We must quell the rumors
before they spread further.
I really hope
things don't get out of hand.
Shouldn't we release
an official statement?
No. Why should we
when it's not true at all?
Mr. Oh, please do your best to make sure
your students aren't distracted
by the rumors.
All of you should make sure
your students don't spread
the false rumors.
You'll have to firmly warn them, okay?
Yes, sir.
Da-huin's Breakup Project.
It begins now!
Hello, everyone. My name is Kwon Da-huin.
My boyfriend and I broke up
a few days ago.
How's Da-huin holding up? Is she okay?
All my friends are distraught now.
It's stressing me out.
Let's cheer up.
Here, it's red ginseng.
I usually drink this when I study.
I brought it for you.
Thanks.
STUDY PLAN FOR FINAL EXAMS
This is pretty intense.
But I must follow this plan.
I have to improve my grades even though
we're going out. Then I can tell my mom.
I have to do very well on the exams.
Don't be too stressed out, though.
Things don't go your way
when you try too hard.
Don't say that. I have to do well.
We promised your mom
that we'll tell my mom
about our relationship.
Yes, let's do that.
What is this?
We can't even tell people
that we're going out.
We have to hide all the time.
Are we living in the Joseon era or what?
It's because we're 18.
What's wrong with our age?
Is being 18 a sin?
Are we not allowed to like each other?
Maybe it is a sin.
Why?
We learned about the most brilliant thing
at the most brilliant time of our lives.
I guess you could call it a sin.
You're actually from the future,
aren't you?
You're about a million years old,
and you realized
this was the best time of your life,
so you traveled back in time.
Gosh, I'm in trouble.
Why? What's wrong?
How did you know...
that I'm from the future?
Sit down.
Sit.
What should I do with you?
Should we just
be reckless?
How about we just tell everyone
that we're dating?
We'll stop running away or lying.
"We're dating.
We're in a relationship." Like that.
No, I don't want you to do
anything reckless.
And I don't want to see you intimidated.
You're always hiding behind
the trees in my neighborhood.
I'm not intimidated.
Hiding is fun.
Still...
I'm sorry.
I feel bad.
I'm happy, but it feels weird.
How so?
It makes me sigh.
Same here.
My gosh!
It's my dad.
I'm glad. You should say hi to my dad.
Right now?
Yes, my dad isn't like my mom,
so he'll understand everything.
Wait.
Wait, I missed the call.
I'll call him back.
Hi, Soo-bin. I'm--
I told you not to call Soo-bin
without my permission.
Goodness, how could you be so inflexible?
I don't have time.
What is it you wanted to talk about?
Here. I brought the divorce documents.
I'm not getting divorced. Are we done?
Hey, Song-hui.
Let go.
We don't love each other.
What did you say?
For goodness' sake.
Are you 18?
To bring up love in this situation?
What should we do then?
Keep living like this?
Keep living uncomfortably like this?
Unlike you, I'm not uncomfortable at all.
Don't you think
you're paying for what you did?
Hey, Song-hui.
The more you do this,
the more exhausted you'll get.
I hope you get exhausted
in the process as well.
Mr. Yoo Jong-su.
Good luck living a nice life like that.
And if you file a divorce lawsuit,
you know that it's unfavorable
for you, right?
Since it's your fault our marriage failed.
You should have some dignity
at least, as Soo-bin's dad.
Okay? Goodbye.
Your meeting ended early.
Yes.
He came with her.
Should I run them over?
What are you doing?
Wait. Hey, stop!
No, what are you doing?
Are you crazy?
Hello, my daughter.
You're studying hard.
I made a promise with you.
Cookies?
Yes. They're from the driver.
Isn't your arm okay now?
Do you still need a driver?
I wanted to pretend it still hurt
to keep her,
but she quit.
She'll return to her previous job now.
You must've gotten really close
to your driver.
Yes. She makes me feel comfortable.
We've decided to be friends.
Really?
Yes.
Keep studying then.
Okay.
I think your mom and my mom
became friends.
This is good news for us, right?
It is.
Now, all you have to do is
do well on the final exams.
Let's study hard!
Okay. Don't worry.
STUDY PLAN FOR FINAL EXAMS
Good. This is good.
The caller is not available...
What is Ji-min doing?
I can't reach her all day.
Does she have another test today?
Hwi-yeong, how are things going?
If you have anything to discuss,
you can call me anytime. Okay?
Thank you.
Gosh, that emotionless punk.
He should at least use an emoticon.
Bro.
What do I do?
I'm afraid.
Yes.
I'm on my way home from work.
What about you, Mom?
Did you arrive safely?
You must've had a lot of work to do.
Don't worry, I'll do fine.
Mom. Are you crying again?
No, right?
Don't worry.
I can do well on my own.
Okay.
Do you still sleep with the lights on?
Well...
You should practice sleeping
with them off.
You can fix it.
Then...
Imagine that I'm next to you.
Next to me?
Yes.
Imagine that I'm by your side,
protecting you.
Did you turn the lights off?
Yes.
Do you feel sleepy?
Not that much.
Even when I said I'd protect you?
That's what's making it harder.
Why?
Because imagining you lying beside me
makes my heart flutter.
Don't worry. I'll help you go to sleep.
All right.
Close your eyes.
You're feeling sleepy.
It's okay.
You feel comfortable.
You're doing great.
You got it.
My gosh, I'm really proud of you.
Well done. You make me so proud!
I'm sorry. I got too excited
because you did so well.
Why does this
remind me of the story about
the princess and On Dal the Fool?
Gosh, come on.
I'm just really proud that you solved
the question we studied together.
Right, but are you proud of me
because I'm like On Dal the Fool?
You know what?
That should be your nickname.
Jun Dal.
Jun Dal, not On Dal.
I'm Little Pea,
and you're Jun Dal.
Jun Dal, it is. Jun Dal!
Isn't it such a cute nickname?
Jun Dal. Hey, Jun Dal.
Jun Dal.
I love you.
Okay.
That's not fair.
He contacted me out of the blue
when we were cleaning.
Then you should've told me
right after that
so that I could prepare myself mentally.
I was worried it might distract you
while you were studying.
We were able to study
for two full hours, you know.
You really are like the princess
in the story.
I'll go catch up with my dad first
and text you.
You can come in then. That's okay, right?
Yes.
Let's go.
Hello, I'm Choe Jun-u.
How have you been, Soo-bin?
-Good.
-All the studying must be stressful.
It is. And Mom makes it
even more stressful.
Oh, dear.
Soo-bin.
I have to
tell you something today.
What is it?
Your mom and I...
are getting a divorce.
Dad...
I thought I should be honest with you.
I'm sure you already know
that your mom and I aren't on good terms.
Gosh.
I'm so ashamed
that I can't even look at you.
But you see,
I no longer want to pretend we get along.
I don't want to put on an act anymore.
That's why I've decided
to divorce your mom.
But she's against it because
she's worried that it may shock you.
Soo-bin.
You're not
a kid anymore.
You're 18.
I think you're old enough
to understand the situation.
I mean, you'll be an adult soon.
Right, Soo-bin?
What?
Aren't I right?
You understand everything, right?
It must be
so easy for you adults.
What?
Sometimes,
you tell us
that we know nothing
because we're too young
and that we should do nothing but study.
But other times, you say,
"You're all grown up now.
You're old enough
to understand everything."
You change your words
whenever you want to suit your needs.
No, Soo-bin. Let me explain.
It's just that you've always been
so mature and thoughtful
since you were little, unlike other kids.
No, Dad.
I just
acted mature, that's all.
I had to react that way
to make it easier for you and Mom.
So that you'd feel less guilty.
But you know what?
To tell you the truth,
I didn't want to be like that.
You're back.
Let's go. My dad is busy today.
You can meet him another time.
Okay. Did the talk go well?
Yes.
You have a shift today, right?
But shall I just skip it
and hang out with you today?
No, you shouldn't miss your shift.
Just today. Let's hang out just today.
Come on. Please?
Jun-u.
Yes?
What is the one thing you regret
the most in your life?
I'm not sure. There are so many things.
Just one thing.
One thing that you've kept
bottled up inside your heart.
Not being able to tell him that it was me.
A while ago,
when I was about to transfer
from here to another school,
I went to my dad's house.
I always knew where he lived
but didn't have the courage to go there.
But I finally plucked up
my courage to go there to see him
since I was about to leave.
But my dad...
Don't you...
Don't you know me?
What?
He didn't recognize me.
That's what I regret the most.
Going to see him?
Not being able to say...
that I was Choe Jun-u
at that moment.
It felt like I had been erased
from his memory.
I regretted it all the time.
But I couldn't go there again to tell him.
Let's go there again and tell him.
So you won't regret it anymore. Okay?
You want me to do that?
If it's something you regret.
Okay.
Can you take a look at this first?
You even drew a drawing?
Yes, just a little one.
That's good.
Let's go.
I hope all your regrets are gone now.
Do you feel better?
What?
Since I got rid of my regrets.
You had something you regretted,
so you were trying to feel better
by making me do this.
Did you know?
Something must've upset you
when you met your dad earlier.
You did this to make me feel better?
I was thinking of doing this
one day anyway.
I guess today is that day.
And I wanted to make you feel better
as well.
Aren't you hungry?
I'm having such a hard time
without you, Yeon-u.
I mean it.
You must miss your son.
I have no choice.
We've always lived like this.
I miss Jun-u, and you too.
Come if you miss me,
I'll treat you to something good.
Okay. Get back to work.
It's a railroad.
Isn't it beautiful?
It's like another world.
It is another world.
The world I live in.
I came here before.
What?
Last time, when I didn't trust you.
I wanted to come up here.
It's nice.
Is that your room?
Yes.
I want to see it.
No, wait.
You can see my room later.
It's a total mess.
Take a seat here.
Here you go.
Thank you.
-Enjoy your meal.
The thing I regret most right now
is when
my mom and dad said
they would get a divorce,
and I stopped them.
Mom, wait!
Mom, don't go.
Don't go. Don't go, Mom.
Mom.
You said you'd understand
even if we got divorced.
No. I can't understand.
I don't want you to split up.
Don't go, Mom.
Even if we get divorced,
your dad and I will still be friends,
and you'll be our daughter,
whom we love the most in this world.
No. Don't go, please.
Mom, I'll be a better daughter.
I'll study harder
and become a better daughter.
Dad promised me too.
He promised to change.
Mom, don't go.
Mom, please don't go.
Please stay.
Don't split up with Dad.
Don't cry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, Soo-bin.
We won't split up.
I'm sorry, my daughter.
I'm sorry.
Back then, I thought
I was doing the right thing.
I didn't know they were just
living together because of me.
And I made them pretend
that they were happy and in love.
I found out later.
That what I did then was wrong.
But what can I do now?
I can't turn things back.
It's because of me.
It's not your fault.
You didn't know back then.
You thought that was for the best then.
Why didn't I know that back then?
I feel so bad...
for both Mom and Dad.
What are you guys doing?
So your girlfriend is Soo-bin?
-Well...
-Mom.
I was going to tell you
after the final exams--
Soo-bin.
What is this now?
What is happening here?
What are you two doing?
Don't touch her!
What is this?
What on earth is happening?
What are you thinking?
Can I ask you something?
That...
never happened.
I won't meet Soo-bin outside of school.
Even at school, I won't talk to her.
But please give her some freedom
in return.
Please.
This place is not a prison.
And I'm not a prison guard.
You suffocate them
and intrude into their lives.
You even censor and judge their emotions.
Soo-bin, let's get through this
even if it's hard.
At a time like this,
we should focus on our school life.
That's what I'll do.
I hope you'll do the same.
I'm here for you.
I don't think
I can get the highest grades.
So I was wondering...
I'll need your help again.
I'm counting on you and Dad.
Could you please drive a little faster?
Hello, I'm Choe Jun-u.
Subtitle translation by Wayne Ryu