It was in my pocket.
It's clean. It's just a little crumpled.
What a surprise
to see you carry this around.
Since I live alone, I should carry it
around to look better.
That's what my mom told me.
It'll make you look worse
if you carry it around like this.
You should iron it or something.
I'm usually good at ironing,
but my mom took the iron with her.
She's living in the countryside
because of her work.
That explains it.
That's why your uniform and clothes
always seemed all wrinkled up and dirty.
Since you don't have an iron?
It's not that dirty.
They said it looked okay.
Who said that?
What?
The people at school.
The girls.
Gosh, you pretended not to know
anything and be indifferent,
but you were actually enjoying
what the girls were saying, right?
No, that's not what I meant.
I didn't want to hear them,
but I couldn't help overhearing.
And they all have loud voices, you know.
So that's why...
How come you're not asking?
What?
About what's wrong.
Why I was walking around like this.
How come you're not asking me?
Why I'm such a mess?
You probably got into a fight again.
Again?
I don't go around fighting and stuff.
If you didn't fight, then what?
Did you work out? Play a game?
Let's just say
it was some kind of matchup.
Are you sure you weren't beaten up?
What do you take me for?
I can't get into detail right now,
but anyway, that's what happened.
Aren't you going to answer that?
Oh, right.
-Yes?
-Hey! Where are you?
Hey, how could you forget
to go to your part-time job?
I was caught up in an emergency.
Wait, why are you taking me with you?
It's too far to walk,
and it might rain again.
Hold on tight.
Okay.
Why did you send me an unfinished script?
"Not because I'm afraid of ghosts..."
What comes after that? Tell me.
Aren't you going to answer me?
Hello.
What are you two doing?
Yeong-bae, are you late
because you were flirting with...
What's wrong with your face?
Who did that to you?
-Did you do it?
-What?
No, I fell off my bike.
Both of you?
-No.
You two are dating, aren't you?
Soo-bin.
Hey, Hwi-yeong.
Where were you?
Your mom was really worried.
Did you go to my house?
Yes. To go to the academy together.
Congratulations on passing the test.
Do I have to go today?
Of course. You need to start right away.
Jun-u, did you get into a fight again?
Right? I was right.
Tell me if you're in trouble. Anytime.
Why?
Since we're in the same class.
We should help each other out
whenever we're in trouble.
I'm not sure. I don't want to.
Suit yourself. See you tomorrow.
-Let's go, Soo-bin.
-Okay.
Jun-u.
Send me the last part of the script, okay?
Hey, Yeong-bae.
Those two are dating, right?
No.
What are you talking about?
That little girl is so lucky.
Hey, go and get changed now.
No, I didn't walk in the rain that much.
I just walked around here and there.
Okay, Mom.
I brought your clothes. Change into them.
What's wrong with my mom?
She didn't have to ask you.
I asked her first.
She was worried you might be
walking in the rain.
Is there somewhere you can change?
Oh, it's okay. I'm fine.
Go and change. What if you catch a cold?
Look.
It's dry, right? I don't have to change.
But the thing is, Hwi-yeong...
Don't do things like this.
It makes me a bit uncomfortable.
Why do you feel uncomfortable?
I brought it because I wanted to.
Well, we'll be late. Let's hurry.
Let's go, Hwi-yeong.
Don't forget your stuff.
CHOE JUN-U
I told you to send me the part after
this. Why haven't you sent it yet?
And translate what you wrote earlier
into English and send it to me.
I won't say anything even if
it's not good, so just send it.
It'll help you study.
"It'll help you study"?
Right, she's in the top tier in English.
All right. As you guys just saw,
we can prove that the sine rule
is always valid for acute, right,
and obtuse-angled triangles.
In summary, this is the formula
you guys will have to use.
The length of one side divided by
the sine value equals the diameter
of the circumscribed circle.
Okay, let's put it to use right away.
Who wants to solve this question?
Hwi-yeong, do you want to try?
-Sure.
-Were you distracted?
What's with you today?
Mr. Son, I guess he's having
a hard time concentrating
because his girlfriend
has graced us with her presence today.
Gosh, it's a big problem.
This is no good.
What should we do about this?
Mr. Son. Instead of him,
since I don't have a girlfriend,
I'll try solving it.
Okay, give it a shot.
Why do you think
that you don't have a girlfriend?
-Never mind. I'm sorry.
-Ro-mi, Soo-bin is at our academy.
Erase this first.
I'm back.
I'm home.
Yes.
Did you have a good day?
Was the class okay?
Yes, it was all right.
Mom, what happened?
Did you hurt your head?
I bumped my head
when I was running after you earlier.
I'm sorry.
It was quite upsetting for me to see you
being like that
in front of Hwi-yeong's mom.
Soo-bin.
I know...
that I pester you so much.
I also know that I shouldn't.
I always tell myself to let go
of my greed, but it's not easy.
You're my one and only daughter,
my baby whom I love the most
in the whole wide world.
"What if she graduates
from a mediocre university?
And what if people look down
on her because of that?
What if she can't get a nice husband?
What if she can't afford
to live in Gangnam?
What if she struggles?"
I can't stop worrying.
Mom.
Gosh, lie on your back.
This is why your shoulders
are always so tense.
I'll study hard.
Don't worry too much.
I didn't get hurt for nothing after all.
Gosh.
Sent you the English version.
Revise it for me please.
About the part at the end...
I'm still thinking.
My gosh.
Jun-u's English is seriously bad.
What do I do?
Oh, my goodness.
I can see that he tried his best.
It's relatively good.
I made a few changes.
This isn't "a few."
How embarrassing.
Memorize the whole thing.
We'll go over it together tomorrow.
You can't sleep until you memorize it.
That explains it.
That's why your uniform and clothes
always seemed all wrinkled up and dirty.
Since you don't have an iron?
TO REMOVE WRINKLES WITHOUT AN IRON
It was in my pocket.
Why is Mom calling so early?
-Hi, Mom.
-Good morning, Jun-u.
-Are you washing up?
-Yes, my eyes are burning. Hurry.
Okay, Jun-u.
Don't forget to eat breakfast.
-Breakfast, okay.
-Put on the uniform,
-and don't forget the handkerchief.
-The handkerchief? Got it.
Mom, I have to go. My eyes are burning.
All right. I love you, my baby.
-Okay, bye.
-Have a good day.
Okay.
Jeong-hu, are you all right?
Please leave a message after the tone.
Hi.
Jun-u?
Choe Jun-u. Come here.
Choe-- Hey.
I bet you weren't expecting this.
What's up with that mask?
You're such a great actor.
Are you in a boy band or what? Come here.
Stand still. Take that off.
What happened to your face?
-Mr. Oh!
-Hello.
Hello.
He caught a cold in this heat.
-Great.
-Okay.
Have a nice day.
Hey. What happened?
Did you get in a fight?
When? Where? With whom?
No. I fell off my bike.
You fell off your bike
and got these small wounds
on your eye, lip, and cheek?
You don't want to say, is that it?
Fine. Well, nothing was reported
to the school,
so it must not be anything big.
Are you sure you're okay?
Yes. I'm sorry.
Cover it up well and cough a lot.
Okay. Hi, Hwi-yeong, Gi-tae.
-Hello.
Why did you have to catch a cold?
They got scared when the cops showed up.
They'll do it right next time.
They won't do anything stupid, right?
I don't think they will. Don't worry.
What if they will?
Don't worry.
You have me.
SEARCH
BYEONGMUN HIGH SCHOOL
Are you having carrots for lunch again?
That's right.
You'll turn into a rabbit.
-O-je. When are we going to practice?
-Oh, hi.
Later.
Why? Can't we do it now?
Hi.
Hey. Hi.
That will draw more attention
from the teachers.
That must hurt.
Not at all.
Did you practice English a lot?
A little.
A little won't be enough.
I washed it. Thanks.
If you do that, it'll be wrinkled.
I ironed it nicely.
Good.
Well... You said you had no iron,
but you ironed it nicely.
Hey. So...
I worked on our test a little...
Pil-sang. Get lost.
Okay. I will.
What are you doing?
Darn it. Just go back to studying.
Jun-u. Your face...
-Are you okay?
-Are you all right?
Hey, Jun-u.
You must have gotten into a fight.
Who was it?
Our neighborhood has been quiet lately.
Right, Pil-sang? Pil-sang...
Hey. Jun-u must have been beaten up.
Right? That's why he's wearing
a mask, right?
-Yes.
-I'm not even surprised.
I don't think so.
I heard he fell off his bike.
No, no.
I doubt that.
Soo-bin.
Yes, Ro-mi?
I hear you're taking Mr. Son's classes.
-For real?
-Did you pass the level test?
I knew it.
I hear it's not easy
to get a chance to take the test.
How did you get to take it?
What happened was...
I recommended her.
I thought she was qualified.
Did you even take the level test?
I did. Ro-mi, let's talk--
Hwi-yeong, can we have a word?
Later. I need to do this now.
Later.
No, let's talk now.
Hey, Ro-mi. You little... That's so rude.
-Stop it.
-Do you want a beating?
Hey. Respond when someone talks to you.
-Ro-mi.
-Okay.
Let's get ready. Take your seats.
Why does the mood seem so dark?
Pil-sang? Why do you look the darkest?
It... It wasn't me.
Ro-mi.
Why didn't you tell us that day?
When you came from somewhere
when we were at the cafe,
you took the level test that day, right?
I felt awkward telling you then.
You felt awkward because you felt guilty?
In a way, yes.
Since Hwi-yeong recommended me.
And since I could've failed the test,
I didn't think I had to tell you.
But you passed anyway,
thanks to Hwi-yeong.
I did pass.
I think I passed
because I was good enough.
I went over the test questions
when I got home,
and I did pretty well on the test.
It's so annoying.
All this favor and preferential treatment.
-It's not like that.
-That's enough.
I don't want to talk to you.
Ro-mi.
Did you two fight?
Do you think I'm like you?
Yes, we fought.
Did you win?
That means you won.
Losing is winning.
That mask looks so bad on you.
Yes.
If possible,
I'd like to meet
Jun-u's previous homeroom teacher.
Yes.
Hello?
Please give me a call--
What's his problem?
Mr. Oh. A student asked me
to bring this to you.
-Thank you.
-Sure.
SHIN JEONG-HU FROM BYEONGMUN HIGH
"Shin Jeong-hu from Byeongmun High"?
Excuse me. Did you just get this?
Hey, Shin Jeong-hu!
Hey!
Jeong... Jeong-hu!
Okay. Today, we will learn about cities.
In our country, Seoul...
Gas.
Pil-sang, open the windows.
What was that?
Jeong-hu! Hold on.
-Hey, Shin Jeong-hu!
-Hey.
What is Mr. Oh doing out there?
-Why? What is it?
-Hey.
Hey. Shin Jeong-hu!
Hey! Shin Jeong-hu! Hold on. Wait.
-Hey. Shin Jeong-hu!
-Jeong-hu?
Hey!
Jun-u! Where are you going?
We're in the middle of class!
What will I do with him?
Teacher.
Jeong-hu! Oh, cramp...
Jun-u! Jun-u, Jeong-hu!
Jun-u!
Hey!
Thank you.
Can you lend me the bus fare?
Don't you have to go back?
I do.
I'm in trouble now.
You'll get expelled
if you're caught again.
How will you handle it?
But it's the first time for me.
Don't you even feel angry?
I just put the blame
for everything on you.
Jeong-hu.
Let's start over.
At another school. Okay?
I quit school.
I'm just going to work instead
for the time being.
Jun-u.
I'm sorry for everything.
You were falsely accused because of me
and even forced to transfer.
I'm sorry.
I'm okay.
I'm doing well here,
so that's enough for me.
-Jun-u.
-What?
Why?
Is your new school okay?
Yes, don't worry.
Watch out for bullies at your school.
You never know.
I'm not afraid at all.
You better call me
if someone else bullies you again.
Don't talk like my big brother.
I'll go to see you during summer break.
You'll let me sleep over, right?
Go back to school now.
Jeong-hu.
Our lives are not that messed up
after all.
No. Who cares if we were born
a bit miserably?
We can overcome it. Don't you think so?
-I'll see you again.
-Bye.
EXPRESS BUS
SEOUL TO UIJEONGBU
And if you look here,
their ownership of land was increased
to contribute to their wealth...
-Did you meet Jeong-hu?
-Yes.
Jeong-hu gave me a letter.
He said you were falsely accused
and forced to transfer because of him.
My goodness.
-What are you doing?
-Oh, yes, sir.
I was having a word with Jun-u.
He caught a cold without my permission.
Keep coughing.
The aristocrats consisted
mainly of high-ranking officials.
And their government positions were
inherited from one generation to the next.
They enjoyed their wealth
and lived extravagantly.
However, as time passed,
they began to place more importance
on the National State Exam,
and it started to change their lifestyles.
Shall I change my seat?
Thank you, Hwi-yeong.
See you at the academy later, Soo-bin.
-I'll call you later.
-Okay.
Ro-mi, aren't you going to practice?
No.
Ro-mi, I checked our script
one more time--
Just memorize what I gave you.
Ro-mi, watch your temper.
You look like a bride
about to get married.
Are you that happy to be
partners with O-je?
Look at her lips.
O-je, see you later.
Okay, see you.
Are you happy now?
Yes.
What did you talk about with Mr. Oh?
You almost skipped the class.
We didn't actually talk.
Was it another matchup?
No.
Let's just say he protected me in a way.
He covered for me.
What are you talking about?
Let's practice our English.
Why don't we do it over there?
What is that?
The sentences you wrote down for me.
Okay.
Read them out loud.
I'm embarrassed.
Hang on. "So me"?
It's "Some." Look carefully. S, O, M, E.
Oh, right.
I know this word.
You know, but what?
I'm a bit nervous.
Okay. Read it again.
Look at this word, "slept with."
You need to remember this.
"Slept with." Don't pronounce it as
"sleep with."
Just memorize these together.
Don't forget to add "with" at the end
for the correct meaning.
I knew that, you know.
Is that so? What was "So me" then?
"So me people"?
The weather is great.
But is this really your dream?
Then what is your dream?
Let's read it again.
Since your part is more important
right now.
All right, let me begin.
You even added a touch of emotion.
It seems like we're making some progress.
I see a glimpse of hope.
-To the academy?
-Yes.
Bye.
You have to practice that
really hard today.
-Especially the spots I marked.
-Okay.
You should go now.
Wait.
Look. Every time you finish reading this,
color in one grape, okay?
Grape?
One, two, three, four...
Fifty times?
You know 50 times isn't enough, right?
Do you want ten more?
This is enough.
-You should get going.
-Okay.
Study hard! Stay up all night!
Hi, Mom. What's up?
Soo-bin, is it true?
-What?
-Did you partner up with the guy
who was forced to transfer recently?
What is wrong with Mr. Oh?
Does he think
that the test is a joke or what?
How could he partner you up
with a guy like that?
It wasn't Mr. Oh.
We did a random draw.
A random draw?
It was my idea, Mom.
It's a test. How could your partner
be decided like that?
Hey. Soo-bin?
Hello.
Jun-u.
Jun-u...
I knew it.
I bet you were pretending to be
washing your hair to cover this.
Let me see.
Gosh, my goodness.
Mom.
How did you know?
Hey, Yeong-bae. Don't you know
that all moms know everything?
They have crazy instincts.
They can practically read your mind.
Gosh, you shouldn't have lied to your mom.
What are you going to do now?
Gosh, this is so upsetting.
It's okay. It wasn't a big deal.
You're sure, right?
Nothing serious is going on?
Yes, I'm sure. It's all been sorted out.
I went through hoops
to get you out of that situation.
Trust me, Mom.
You said I'm the only person
you can trust in the whole world.
Nothing bad will happen. Trust me, okay?
Okay.
You should go.
You'll be late for work again.
I dropped off side dishes at your house.
Make sure you never skip breakfast, okay?
Okay, I'll catch a cab for you.
I'll just take the bus.
Listen. Don't ever fight with anyone.
And do not let anyone hit you, okay?
Promise me, okay?
Okay, don't worry.
I'll be off, then.
There's soup in the freezer.
Heat it up in the microwave.
Okay. Gosh, be careful.
-Bye.
-Okay, bye.
-Be careful!
-All right.
Soo-bin.
-Let's go together.
-Sure.
Is something bothering you?
Hwi-yeong, I want to quit
Mr. Son's math class.
Don't take what Ro-mi said to heart.
Well, it's not that.
I just don't like feeling this way.
What's the matter, though?
I recommended you to Mr. Son
because you're my friend,
and you got in
because you did well on the test.
And Hwi-yeong...
Well...
It's okay. Go on.
I'd appreciate it if you could stop
talking to your friends
that I'm your girlfriend.
I know that you're doing it
to help me out,
but it makes me uncomfortable.
Soo-bin.
Yes?
Why do you always
feel uncomfortable around me?
You said I made you uncomfortable
when I brought you clothes
when you got soaked in the rain.
And you don't like to be my girlfriend.
You're always uncomfortable around me.
Hwi-yeong.
You were never like this before.
We were good, close friends.
Hwi-yeong, that kid...
I feel so guilty now.
MA HWI-YEONG
I know that you're doing it
to help me out,
but it makes me uncomfortable.
You know...
that's not why I do it.
Why are you so late?
Didn't your class end hours ago?
I went to do some exercise.
Son.
I hope you're not distracted
from your studies
because of Soo-bin.
Mom, please.
I'm going upstairs.
I trust you, son.
This is pretty good.
Now, I understand
why they say Mr. Son is really good.
-Seriously?
-Yes.
I'll check my level test
and quit the class
if I didn't get in with my score alone.
Can I take the test for the class
if you quit?
Yes, of course.
But let's not get awkward
because of something like this.
We're friends, you know.
Mom, about Mr. Son's math...
What is it? What did Mr. Son say?
Can I just...
It's nothing. Never mind.
Also, about the free-talking test...
I hope you won't say anything about it.
Yes, I'm going to keep quiet about it.
What if I complain
and get on the wrong side of the teachers?
But don't be friends with that kid, okay?
I'm sure you won't anyway.
You have to be careful of kids like him.
What about this part, though?
"However, I still sleep
with the lights on.
Not because I'm afraid of ghosts..."
Then what? What's after this?
You need to tell me the rest
to complete this script.
That part...
Because you don't want it to be dark
when your parents get home.
Right?
Then why?
"It's not because I'm afraid of ghosts.
It's because I'm terrified of zombies."
-Gosh, zombies...
-What?
That's basically the same thing.
I was just kidding.
It's just a habit of mine.
I guess it's become a habit.
I can't really fall asleep
with the lights off.
Choe Jun-u...
You should practice sleeping
with the lights off starting today.
I mean, you're not a baby.
Be honest with me.
You're just scared, aren't you?
You're afraid ghosts will show up
when you turn the lights off.
No, I'm not.
Come on. I think you are.
Just sleep with the lights off
starting today.
Your electricity bill must be very high
if you always keep the lights on
all night.
Don't be so wasteful, okay?
So he's been sleeping like this
since he was a kid.
It must've been so uncomfortable.
It's not because I'm afraid of ghosts.
It's because keeping the lights on...
helps me feel less lonely.
Hey.
-What is that?
-Isn't he cute?
His name's Rice.
What kind of name is Rice?
It's cute.
You're so cute.
My phone was blowing up
with texts all night long.
Some parents are
still complaining fiercely.
Scrap the English free-talking test.
Sorry?
But... I can't do that.
We can't cancel a test
just because the parents complain.
As a teacher, that's so...
We have our pride.
Mr. Oh. Are you refusing to do as I say?
No, sir.
Right? Okay.
Yes, sir.
Okay. I'm going to the Education Office.
Mr. Oh. Are you okay? Mr. Oh.
Did he leave?
Yes. He has a meeting
at the Education Office.
So? What will you do?
What else? Just do what you want.
Okay.
This is the moment everyone becomes happy.
The English free-talking test...
will now begin!
Okay. I've prepared this myself.
-The long-awaited first couple...
-Did you memorize everything?
Drum roll...
Kwon Da-huin and Jung O-je!
Come out here.
No touching. I'm docking points.
I'm docking points, O-je.
Okay, let's give them a round of applause!
Was Da-huin that good in English?
It's the power of love.
Mr. Oh. I have another dream.
-What?
-Da-huin, we're done.
My other dream...
What was that?
-You should date!
-Hey, hey, hey.
-Yes.
-You should date!
Hey, guys. Quiet down. Quiet.
Nice.
What's this?
You listened to me right away.
It's not like I'm Hwi-yeong.
Mr. Oh.
Oh, my god.
Mr. Oh. May we speak?
I'm in the middle of the class.
Study on your own for a bit.
-Hwi-yeong, take care of the class.
-Yes, sir.
Mr. Oh.
Okay. Study on your own.
Okay.
-What was that?
-Quiet.
Mr. Oh. Didn't you hear me before?
Well, the kids worked hard
to prepare for it,
-and as I said earlier--
-Come to my office.
Yes, sir.
Da-huin hit the lottery.
-You got the most out of this.
-Right?
I'm so happy right now.
I think Mr. Oh is in a bad mood.
Hwi-yeong will be
wrapping up today's class.
Who keeps pressuring the vice-principal?
It isn't my mom.
I have an idea who's behind this.
-Me?
-What?
I never said it was you.
-Is it the guilty conscience?
-Why you--
-Hey, hold on.
-What?
Are you going to hit me with that?
-Hit me.
-Come on. Stop it!
-Stop it.
-Hold back!
-Hey! Stop it!
-You little...
I'm upset too!
You didn't even do the test.
Why are you upset?
Because you couldn't be partners
with Jun-u?
That's right! Do you know
how hard I worked
to teach that fool?
-It was useless.
-Exactly.
Isn't it better
that you didn't do the test then?
Whatever! Regardless, you guys
don't fight. Seriously.
You're so noisy!
-What's her problem?
-She said not to fight.
What is this? Why am I disappointed?
It's because I wasted all that time.
Regardless, you're no longer
teaching Class Three.
It's what all of the parents,
the homeroom teacher,
and I want.
I'm sorry.
That rolled here all by itself.
You're right.
Why? Is something wrong?
It's the kids from your old school, right?
-Those jerks. Lead the way.
-No, I...
had a question.
What?
What's wrong with you?
I just wanted to know what your dream is.
I guess it's a secret.
I don't understand English very well.
Right? My dream is...
unboxing limited editions all day long...
No, no. Not being cheap
and waiting for off-season sales,
I want to make big purchases
without hesitation?
I'm a shopaholic.
I doubt that's it.
No, right?
What was my dream again?
I'm not sure, actually.
Why?
You're a lot like me.
You've lost your dream.
What? I am not. I...
I drink a lot because of you kids,
so my memory
got slightly bad, that's all.
-That's not true.
-You talk a lot now.
Mr. Oh!
What is this? We worked so hard
for the English test.
Soo-bin. Sorry. I...
-We want to do it here.
-What?
It was super hard training him.
It's unfair.
Did you say you trained him?
Hold on. Then...
Okay. This teacher of yours will grant you
a special test.
He forgot. I should dock some points...
No, wait. Time out.
-You can do it.
-Okay, I'll try again.
Soo-bin is...
smiling.
Yes!
Jun-u, no, I mean you did a great job.
-Soo-bin, great job.
-Thank you.
All right, then.
Although it's unofficial,
both of you receive
100 points!
To congratulate your perfect score,
why don't we go get some pizza?
-Deal.
-Deal! Great.
Let's go.
I have to go to work.
Come on. I know you have some time left.
-Deal.
-Deal. Come on, let's go.
You did such a great job.
Hello?
Yes.
Sorry?
EMERGENCY MEDICAL CENTER
I thought you might be scared.
Hey, Jeong-hu.
Jun-u. I'm sorry for everything.
Jeong-hu. Our lives are not
that messed up after all.
No. Who cares if we were born
a bit miserably?
We can overcome it. Don't you think so?
FUNERAL HALL, MORTUARY
LATE SHIN JEONG-HU
Jun-u.
I brought your classmates.
Are you okay?
Why don't we wait outside? Let's go.
I guess he has no family.
He has a father,
but we can't reach him yet.
His grandmother is at a nursing home
due to Alzheimer's.
Jun-u probably hasn't had anything to eat.
Shall we go get something to eat?
-Shall we?
-I'll go.
Get it over with and come back out.
I think they're the assailants.
What is going on?
Let's go.
I guess that bastard didn't come.
Do you know Lee Gi-tae? In your class.
He paid us money to get you expelled.
I was going to quit after just one time.
Geon-hyeok, let's go.
Because you were out of line.
You started to raise doubts about me
instead of getting lost quietly.
How dare you do that...
to me.
Jun-u, stop!
Did you give them money? Are you crazy?
Do you think he'll have your back?
My friend died because of you guys.
I'll get on my knees.
Your life is already ruined,
but mine is different.
Why didn't you hit him back
when Jun-u was hitting you?
Were you upset that I beat up Hwi-yeong?
I wanted to help
in case you were treated unfairly.
Why would you help me?
Out of pity?
You can say exactly what you saw, right?
Thank you, Geon-hyeok.
Mom, help me.
-Are you embarrassed?
-Did you give birth to me
just to brag to others?
I won't make it to SNU.
-Are you okay?
-And why do I want to help you?
Is it out of pity?
Subtitle translation by Wayne Ryu