And why do I want to help you?
Is it out of pity?
I know it isn't. That's why I...
It's because I like you. What are you...
going to do now?
Hey! Jun-u!
Hey! Are you... Are you okay?
Are you okay?
I'm fine,
but Bumbi's a mess.
Bumbi?
Is that its name?
I'm surprised. I see. This is Bumbi.
Hi, Bumbi. I'm Soo-bin.
No, it's not.
What? Let me introduce myself to Bumbi.
No, that's not it.
-Isn't this your friend?
-You misheard. You're mistaken.
-Soo-bin, is that what's going on?
-I want to say hi.
This isn't Bumbi.
Why did I...
You've lost your mind, Soo-bin.
I should really say something.
What do I say? Think, Jun-u.
Think.
-So...
Good, Jun-u. Tell me. What's your answer?
You go first.
What? What happened?
Was I just rejected?
About what I said earlier...
I was just kidding.
I was in a bad mood today,
so I was just...
What are you saying, Soo-bin?
I was kind of offended by what you said,
so I wanted to see what you'd do.
Bye.
Are you really...
Are you really
going to leave home?
That's what you said
to your mother earlier.
It's none of your business.
Hey.
Soo-bin. Seriously...
What's wrong with you, Jun-u?
Are you mute or something?
Hello.
That's right.
Relationships are all about timing.
If you miss that timing,
it's "Welcome to hell."
Timing.
Yeong-bae.
Did something happen again?
No.
Hey, Yeong-bae.
Be careful of that kid.
She looks all naive and innocent,
but she's wicked inside.
You know,
the girl who biked here with you.
The one with the super hot boyfriend!
Hey!
Soo-bin.
Soo-bin?
Don't be so hard on yourself.
How did you know I was hard on myself?
Did you guys hear...
We know you're like this
because you regret arguing with your mom.
My mom. I forgot.
What?
Did your mom hit you on the head
or something?
Maybe she has short-term memory loss.
Hey. Call your mom right now.
You should beg before it's too late.
Or you'll lose your allowance
and extend your sentence.
I'm not going home today.
What?
Not until my mom apologizes to me
and gives in. Never.
Who will put me up tonight?
We're redoing our kitchen
starting today, so it's a mess.
Sorry.
Da-huin?
Chan-yeol?
Hey. Do you think Ro-mi
is doing well on the level test?
That's right. It's today.
I'll ask.
SON JAE-YEONG MATHEMATICS
I'll do whatever it takes
to get Soo-bin back,
so please forget what she said
about quitting.
But ma'am, I don't think
Soo-bin wants to take my class.
Why don't you respect her wishes?
No. She doesn't know anything.
She's acting all self-righteous.
She's just acting out.
Hello.
I'm Ro-mi. Soo-bin's friend.
Okay. Hi.
I gave my answer sheet to the proctor.
Okay. Sure.
Soo-bin, that idiot.
Thanks to Soo-bin quitting
Mr. Son's class,
I was given an opportunity.
Thank you.
Soo-bin didn't quit.
What? That's what I heard.
You heard wrong.
My driver's here.
Goodbye, ma'am.
Okay. Bye.
Did you quit
just to give it away to that brat?
Darn it. That stupid moron.
Seriously.
Seriously. That idiot. Seriously!
You loser.
It's because I like you. What are you...
going to do now?
Does Soo-bin want to have it all?
That's ridiculous.
Welcome.
Jun-u, do you work here?
Yes.
That's kind of romantic.
How are you preparing for the midterm?
Welcome.
Which chapters
did you study at your old school?
Do you want to borrow my notebooks?
I don't usually let anyone see them,
-but you can--
-Well...
Moon Chan-yeol, right?
I'm kind of busy right now.
"Moon Chan-yeol"?
Sorry. Jung Da-huin?
No. Kwon Da-huin?
Here.
It's 13,600 won.
Here you go.
Are you trying to be funny?
Yoon So-ye?
Ro-mi. Hwang Ro-mi.
Say it. Hwang Ro-mi.
How much is this?
I'll have to scan it. Just a second.
Sorry.
It's 7,000 won.
What? He didn't even know my name?
How can he not know my name
if he likes me?
Then again, boys are like that.
Names are not important to them.
Still, he's pretty weird.
Ro-mi, how did the level test go?
Why are you so late?
I've been waiting for so long.
Hey.
You forgot this.
Thanks.
Are you Ro-mi's friend?
I'm her dad.
-Hello.
-Nice to meet you.
What are you waiting for? Let's go.
Okay. See you again.
Is he in your class?
What a good kid.
Working part-time and everything.
Why did you talk to him?
You shouldn't have.
Does he think I'm your driver too?
Oh, I made a mistake.
-What should I do?
-Forget it.
Yes. Okay. I'll deliver it right away.
Yeong-bae, I have to deliver
something to the academy.
Please stand in for me.
-I'll go.
-What?
-Would you do that?
-Yes.
Here.
Thanks.
Gosh, that was close.
Jun-u.
Did Hwi-yeong's mom send
something here again?
Yes.
Aren't these amazing?
I had to work my butt off to buy these.
What? Do you have something to tell me?
-About Mr. Son's watch...
-Sorry.
No comment. I don't want
to get involved in that.
I know that you're not
going to tell anyone.
Although you saw
Hwi-yeong steal that watch.
You'll just use it to tease him,
while waiting for the right time
to reveal it.
You're pretty smart.
That day,
what exactly happened?
Right before Hwi-yeong stole that watch.
That day?
That day...
That day, Mr. Son complimented me
on my math skills.
That must have driven Hwi-yeong crazy
and made him want to steal
Mr. Son's watch.
He's done that a few times before too.
He completely loses his mind
when he's upset.
Every time, his mom stepped in
and covered up for him.
I wish I had a mom like her too.
Hwi-yeong, I'll have to reveal
who you really are.
I have to put things right.
Soo-bin, are you crazy? How dare you?
You told me to get out.
I'm listening to you.
Oh, really?
Then you can live there forever.
Okay, I will.
I'll live my own life. I'm 18 now.
Soo-bin, don't you think
you're going too far?
I think I can do this.
You should live your own life too. Bye.
I don't know.
My fingers are out of control.
I must be crazy.
That feels better.
Aren't you going to send it?
-Here we go.
-Hey!
That was fake.
Man, you're such a coward.
If you can't even say harsh words
to your mom, why did you leave home?
You'll never be able to beat her.
Look at this card I picked.
Last time, you said
that meant I could beat her.
You said I should push forward.
Did I say that?
Ta-da!
What are you guys doing here?
You said you didn't have time today.
I said we couldn't be at my place.
I have Mom's permission too.
God, my house is tiny enough as it is.
Whatever.
This is so exciting! A pajama party!
Be quiet. A pajama party?
The exams are coming soon.
What are you guys thinking?
The exams are around the corner.
-You're right.
-Seriously.
Gosh, you guys.
Hey! Give me mine.
It's late, and my grandma needs to sleep.
So let's keep it down.
What if your grandma comes upstairs?
Play some music.
We'll just play some music, okay?
Here we go.
Stand up, guys. Right now.
Hey! Stop!
-Stop it.
-Be quiet.
-Calm down.
-Here we go.
-Hey!
Get up!
-Seriously. It's late at night.
-You'll get in trouble.
-Be quiet.
-You started it.
So-ye, join us. Come on.
So-ye, are you still angry?
I'm in front of your house.
I'll wait until you come out.
Keep it down for grandma.
Yes.
-Yes.
-Why aren't you dancing?
It's okay.
-It's protein.
-It is.
Go. Go do what you want.
Go and live as you please now.
Did you think I wouldn't go?
Thank you for letting me live as I please.
You didn't run away from home, did you?
Should I not have sent it?
What are you up to?
-O-je.
-Yes?
-Go home now.
-Okay.
Why?
I'm delivering something
to Chan-yeol's house.
I wanted to give you
some tteokbokki if you were up.
My father's tteokbokki is phenomenal.
A delivery?
I hear the girls are there.
You know, Soo-bin's gang.
It's Ms. Da-huin's order.
What's with you, Soo-bin?
Did you really run away?
I'll take a rain check on tteokbokki.
Is Soo-bin staying out tonight?
Would she?
No. I'm sure she'll go home.
But it's dangerous to walk alone at night.
Maybe she's sleeping over.
I go walk her home.
I don't.
People usually take this as a yes.
That's right.
This means that I should go.
Where is Chan-yeol's place?
Good. Jun-u, you got this.
I'll respond properly this time.
I really will.
Just leave. I'm going to sleep over
at Chan-yeol's place with the girls.
Chan-yeol's place?
Soo-bin is at Chan-yeol's place.
Soo-bin, this girl...
LEE GI-TAE
REMINDERS
I haven't finished everything for today.
I'm in front of Chan-yeol's place.
I'll wait for you.
Until the morning if I have to.
-Right over here.
-Yes, I see it.
My baby whom I love the most
in the whole wide world.
"What if she graduates
from a mediocre university?
And what if people look down
on her because of that?"
So-ye, are you leaving?
Yes.
My mom is here to pick me up.
I'm off. I'm sorry.
Gosh, am I going overboard?
I think she'll go home, though.
What if she asks me why I've come?
Soo-bin, you should go home.
-Hey, Soo-bin.
-Gosh! You scared me, Hwi-yeong.
Did I scare you?
I'm sorry. You came out
when I was about to message you.
-What brings you here?
-I came to walk you home.
My mom asked you to bring me home, right?
No. I heard your mom visited
the school today,
so I figured you'd throw a fit
to rebel against your mom.
-Let's go.
-No, it's okay.
I can go home alone.
It's dangerous.
And that alley is too dark.
-Let's go.
-It's really okay.
You're too late, Jun-u...
Since it's midterm season,
you must be really stressed out.
By the way, I wanted to ask you something.
What is it?
Did something happen
between you and Jun-u?
Why do you ask?
You guys went to the counseling office
together the other day.
And you two seem a little...
The counselor wanted to know
how Jun-u was doing at school.
She also asked if Jun-u hit me
for any other reasons.
Do you think I'm hiding something
from you?
No, it's not that.
Did I upset you?
Come on. I think you're a little upset.
-No, I'm not upset.
-Gosh.
You probably have no idea
how much of a jerk I am.
Come on. Don't get upset over
a tiny thing, Little Boy Hwi-yeong.
I'm really not upset.
Really?
I liked it when I used to be
your Little Boy Hwi-yeong.
When I could tell you everything.
You used to scold me
and slap me on the back.
What? Then shall I give you
a big slap on the back now?
-It's all right.
-It's nothing hard. I'll just...
Forget it.
It's getting late. Let's hurry.
Shall we run? It is quite late now.
You can't keep up with me.
Hey, Soo-bin. Wait up!
Bye!
Mom, I'm back.
I'll do well on my midterm exam, okay?
I'll get into the top tier in math.
So believe in me just one more time.
Soo-bin, we can't afford
to observe the situation
in a relaxed manner,
go through trial and error,
and reflect on our mistakes
at the moment.
You're in 2nd grade, for God's sake.
For you, every second of the day
should be exam season.
Even the slightest mistake
can push you off the steep cliff.
Gosh. Come on, Mom.
Why are you so negative?
Don't think like that, please.
Give me one more chance, okay?
Please? I'll do a good job. Okay?
I'll study hard.
Oh, right.
After you came to school earlier.
After you left, my arm
became like Ma Dong-seok's arm.
-What? My goodness.
-The actor, Ma Dong-seok.
Along with the Gods.
You saw the movie, right?
Gosh, my arm swelled up this much earlier.
-My gosh!
-I hit your shoulder, not your arm.
No, it was right here.
-You hit here.
-Hey, Ma Dong-seok's arm is...
Ouch! My gosh, it hurts so much.
It hurts so much!
I'm in pain! Anyway, I'm going to study.
I'll go study!
Good night!
Where have you been?
I just stepped out to get some fresh air.
You keep getting distracted
because you're not focused.
You feel frustrated and itchy all over.
I'm heading upstairs.
Your homeroom teacher
can't return to school
because he's hospitalized, right?
How did you know?
The assistant teacher has
officially become our homeroom teacher.
Mom,
again?
It's midterm season.
Sit down.
You'll never be able to see Soo-bin again
if you step out again like you did today.
I love you.
You didn't run away from home, did you?
Is that all he sent? What is he doing?
I mean, if you're worried,
ask more questions.
But then again, why would you
be worried about me?
I'm sure he was just bored.
Soo-bin. Why did you have to say that?
Seriously. This whole day
has been humiliating. God...
Also, I'm not Hwi-yeong's girlfriend.
Liar.
Soo-bin, you're a liar.
About what I said earlier...
I was just kidding.
I was in a bad mood today,
so I was just...
I was kind of offended by what you said,
so I wanted to see what you'd do.
She was really kidding?
Hey, Jun-u.
-Hi.
-Hi, O-je.
O-je!
-Hi.
-Did you have breakfast?
-Of course.
I made tuna salad. Do you like tuna?
Hey.
Hi, Jun-u.
Hey. Hi.
So... Why didn't you reply
to my text yesterday?
That... I did see
the text, but...
Hey, Soo-bin!
Hi.
Never mind. Bumbi's all better.
Bum... What's Bumbi?
Well... Jun-u's bike...
That's a secret.
You're close enough
to share your bike's pet name?
What's this about?
It's not like that.
Let's go. Okay. Let's go.
See?
He turns all red whenever he sees me.
How cute.
Now I know.
It wasn't her.
It was her.
Ro-mi. How did you do
on your level test yesterday?
Obviously.
Your mom came to the academy yesterday.
She seemed really angry because of you.
Yes.
So-ye. When did you leave yesterday?
Sorry. My mom wanted me home. Sorry.
You traitors.
You made Da-huin and me
the sacrificial lambs.
She and I couldn't study at all.
Did you go home too?
Yes.
Bring this to the classroom,
and pick up the printouts.
Okay.
Change your seats back to the way
they were.
I made myself clear, so...
Gosh. Okay.
Good morning, everyone.
Let's begin...
What's with the seats?
We'll stay in these seats.
-That's what everyone wants.
-Everyone?
Did you take a vote in that short time?
No, but...
Everyone says this is good
for the exams coming up.
That's right.
I like this.
-Me too.
-That's right.
It's only good for them.
Is that unanimous? There isn't
a single person who doesn't like it?
I don't like it.
Okay.
Me neither.
Me too. I don't...
Okay, then.
How about we do this?
What is this?
My goodness.
Gosh.
That's Class Three again, isn't it?
Okay, everyone who agrees with
the class president sits up front.
Everyone else, sit wherever you want
in the back.
-Begin.
-Okay!
-Let's go, O-je.
-Who wants to sit with me?
-Da-huin, O-je.
Soo-bin, So-ye. Where do you want to sit?
I'm going there.
Okay.
-Jun-u.
-Hey.
Ro-mi. Where's your seat?
Yun-jin. Sit here.
Okay.
But Ro-mi. I may be uncomfortable
sitting way up front...
But then again...
-Hey. Pil-sang.
-Don't do it.
Wow, Pil-sang.
Pil-sang has changed.
You're sitting up front?
Welcome.
Okay, are we done?
Mr. Oh.
This will make it too distracting
to study.
Why? It's nice.
Pil-sang is sitting up front,
trying to study hard this time.
Isn't this nice?
Yes! It's nice!
See that? It's all about perspective.
Hwi-yeong, you should relax
a little too. Relax.
That stupid Oh Han-gyeol.
New teachers always do that to stand out.
It's so annoying.
Why did our homeroom teacher
have to get hurt again?
He shouldn't drink so much.
But Mr. Oh's our official homeroom
teacher now.
We have to listen.
He's totally in power now.
He has the student council
in the palm of his hand too.
-Look closely.
-I don't know.
I had to work my butt off
to buy these from a reseller.
-Aren't they awesome?
-Let me try.
Don't touch.
You're not supposed to touch them.
Just look. Aren't they awesome?
Hey. Hwi-yeong.
Are you studying hard for the midterm?
He ignored me.
Just wait, Hwi-yeong.
I'll beat you in the midterm.
That clown Sang-hun. What's with him?
Don't mind him.
Look. As you can see, the lengths
of the two diagonals
are five and eight. What does that mean?
This has to be five.
And this has to be eight.
Okay. The angle between the diagonals
is 60 degrees.
Then figure out the area
of quadrilateral A, B, C, and D.
-Let's see.
-Look at them.
All lovey-dovey.
A', B', C',
D'... The area is...
Jun-u couldn't look happier.
Kids said they saw him
staring at Ro-mi all the time.
I can see that it was true.
Boys are all the same.
-Except for my O-je.
-...20 times the square root of 3.
-So...
-Ro-mi
doesn't usually smile so much, does she?
This is new.
I know.
Ro-mi, the ice queen,
is smiling from ear to ear.
Study. Let's study. Exams, remember?
Jun-u, are you so happy?
Soo-bin.
Why did you say that to him?
Pil-sang, cut it out.
Okay.
Did you doze off?
Doesn't it hurt? Are you okay?
Yes.
I think we've become in charge
of more and more areas.
Gi-tae decided who cleans which areas.
It might be because of me.
Maybe.
Let's just accept it.
The math teacher must be
really scared of Hwi-yeong.
Sang-hun is the math teacher's favorite.
They have to meet in secret
because he's so jealous.
Come on, you're good at this.
Give that to me. I'll go in.
Hwi-yeong, let me do that.
You should study.
Thanks.
No problem.
Do you know where Ma Hwi-yeong is?
Hwi-yeong? Why?
Hwi-yeong, the math teacher
wants you to come to the math office.
Sang-hun, as always,
you understand what I teach you so fast.
This is why I like you so much.
I know your favorite is Hwi-yeong.
My favorite student is you.
Don't you know that?
You should really switch
to the natural sciences track.
Then you'll easily become
the very top student.
You're a math genius.
That'll be much easier for you.
Sir.
I'll make sure Hwi-yeong doesn't
get the highest grades here.
You're joking, right?
No. I mean it.
You have no idea how fun it is
to trample on Hwi-yeong.
I'm saying this because I care about you.
Hwi-yeong.
Did you want to see me?
Me?
No. If I wanted to see you,
I would have messaged you.
I was asking him about a math question.
You're already finished with it, right?
That's why you're the best student
in our year. Shit, I'm so jealous.
Come on. Watch your language.
Excuse me.
All right.
My favorite student is you.
Don't you know that?
I'll make sure Hwi-yeong doesn't
get the highest grades here.
You have no idea how fun it is
to trample on Hwi-yeong.
Just wait, Hwi-yeong.
I'll beat you in the midterm.
Your heart is about to explode, right?
Jealousy.
Anxiety.
So this is the issue you have.
If someone gets on your nerves,
you have to get rid of the thing that
person treasures most to feel relieved.
What are you talking about?
This is just a prank.
A prank?
Was stealing your academy teacher's watch
a prank too?
And then you framed me for it
and came up with a plan
to kick me out of this school.
Were those pranks too?
You're just making all that up.
Do you know why you do this?
It's because
you only care about yourself.
You look down on everyone else.
When people you look down on
get on your nerves,
you can't stand it.
You're very imaginative.
So? What are you planning to do?
What if you spread that made-up story
as if it's my weakness?
Do you think that'll humiliate me?
No.
I will make you feel sorry
for those who you've looked down on.
I will make you feel
genuinely sorry for them.
You're just a pathetic little...
Hwi--
I told him to come here.
You have to plant that too, right?
Just like how you planted
that teacher's watch in my locker.
That little...
God... The midterm...
It's time for my appetite
to be out of control.
Shoot, I suddenly feel so lousy.
-Me too.
-Soo-bin!
I failed that level test
because of you, right?
-What?
-Did you fail the level test?
Didn't you see me
tell Mr. Son I was quitting?
Then is it your mom?
She said you weren't quitting
Mr. Son's class.
Ro-mi.
Are they fighting?
Don't you think you're out of line?
Why else would I have failed?
Even you passed the test.
How could I fail?
-Maybe you did badly on the test.
-Why would I?
Ro-mi, stop. Why are you fighting?
-Stop fighting.
-Move, O-je. Move.
-O-je.
-Gosh, I can't believe this.
Why would I fail that test?
Gosh, I feel dizzy.
-What?
-Stop putting on a show.
Soo-bin. Hey!
Hey!
Put her down.
Soo-bin!
Try to understand.
You know that's just how Ro-mi is.
Gosh, I knew Ro-mi would do this.
She's the one who did badly
on the level test.
What's wrong with me?
-What's the matter with me?
-Come on. Don't take it to heart.
We all know how ill-tempered
and rude Ro-mi can be.
-I regret it.
-What do you regret?
Quitting Mr. Son's class?
No.
Fighting with your mom?
I don't even know.
I have so much on my mind now.
I have too much on my mind.
Just let it go, okay?
STUDENT RECORDS, MA HWI-YEONG
ACADEMIC AWARDS AND RECOGNITIONS
Because the one controlling Gi-tae
is Hwi-yeong.
CLASS THREE, MR. KIM
Hello, ma'am. This is Oh Han-gyeol.
I'm sorry I keep calling you.
I was just wondering
if Mr. Kim is still too unable
to talk on the phone.
Is he still very ill?
I just wanted to ask a few things
about the kids of Class Three.
Sorry? Hello?
Yes. I'll call you again
some other time, then. Thank you.
CHOE JUN-U
Hwi-yeong is here early,
so it's obviously exam season.
I feel suffocated.
I organized what you need to memorize.
You already got all this done?
Give it to me when you're done.
I have one too.
I made another copy while working on mine
to give it to you.
Really?
-So-ye.
-Yes?
Let's do well on the midterm.
-Thanks, Gi-tae.
-Just a second.
-What are you looking at?
-Pil-sang.
I can't concentrate because of you.
Oh, sorry.
Hello.
-Mom.
-Jun-u.
-Mom, why...
-What?
And why are you wearing...
Your exams are starting tomorrow.
You should study hard.
Your mother will cover your shift.
She pestered Boss for three hours.
Hey, you need to do very well
on the exams.
You have to get good grades
and prove you can do well too.
Yes, of course.
What about the restaurant?
Well, I'm using
the rest of my vacation days.
Jun-u, you should just go home
and study hard.
No, how about you sign up
for a cram academy?
Yes, that's a good idea.
Aren't there ones that are
specifically designed to help you
prepare for the midterm?
Let's go. Let's just go
to the academy and find out.
Wait, ma'am! Your shift is about to begin.
For now, just go home and study. Okay?
Go. Go on.
Bye.
All right, bye for now.
What shall I start with?
-Shall we try this again?
-Sure.
-Let's go over it again.
-Sounds good.
Gosh, my mom's too much.
Yoo Soo-bin,
good luck.
YOO SOO-BIN, GOOD LUCK!
Have some red ginseng.
You promised me
that you'll get into the top tier in math.
Gosh, she's all focused.
Gosh, math...
Top tier.
Check your answers before you submit
your answer sheet.
Those in the back row, collect the sheets.
Hwi-yeong, what are you doing?
Just a moment, please.
-I have to--
-I told you to wait.
We need to collect the answer sheets.
Just a second, please.
-Hwi-yeong, you must submit yours.
-Give me a second, please. This is...
MA HWI-YEONG, MATH
For God's sake, I said wait!
Dad.
I said I'd kill you if you didn't
get the highest marks on the exams.
Hwi-yeong.
How could you fall asleep?
How will you manage to be top of your year
if you sleep this much?
Hwi-yeong has been studying hard.
He was just taking a short break.
You pathetic good-for-nothings.
I work my butt off so that you two
can enjoy this comfortable life.
How dare you sleep as much as you want?
Right outside our house
are a ton of people
vigilantly awaiting an opportunity
to take what belongs to us.
Aren't you going to focus?
If you don't get the highest grades
in the midterm,
I'll kick both of you
out of the house naked.
Hwi-yeong. No, don't.
Don't scratch, please.
Don't scratch.
I need to ace the math test.
I need to prove myself
to Mom and myself.
What's wrong with you, Soo-bin?
You need to focus.
Soo-bin, do you feel sick?
I'm sorry, but may I go
to the nurse's office?
The nurse's office? Let's go.
-Soo-bin. Oh, no.
-Oh, my god.
Quiet. This is a test. Stay in your seats.
-Soo-bin?
-I'll carry her.
Get back to the test.
I'll be right back.
Okay, quiet. Focus on the test.
My test...
What about her test?
She probably didn't finish.
I know. We still have 20 minutes left.
Can she take the test
in the nurse's office?
I heard that was allowed.
That will work. I'll get her test papers.
-Go ahead.
-Okay.
Don't worry. You'll feel better
if you take medicine.
You can take the test.
Jun-u's back is warm.
I didn't think it would be, but it's warm.
Ma'am. Soo-bin.
What's wrong?
Do you feel sick?
Let's see.
Hold on.
It looks like acute stomach cramps.
Jun-u, here's your test.
I'm fine.
You're a student too.
Did you finish?
Jun-u.
Soo-bin.
I'll turn them in
to the math teacher, so wait here.
Are you feeling better now?
Yes. Thanks.
I'm sorry you lost time for the test
because of me.
Sorry.
It's okay.
I had no idea how to solve
the problems in the back anyway.
You can go now. I can stay by myself.
I will once the nurse gets back.
Am I making you uncomfortable?
I'll go then.
Hey. Your hand.
Was it from earlier?
I didn't know.
You should have the nurse treat it.
It may get infected.
It's okay.
Get it treated.
Maybe I should.
Hey.
About what I said the other day.
Which part?
When Bumbi...
When your bike broke. I mean...
What I said right before it broke.
Please forget it.
Me too.
What?
I was going to say this then too.
Exactly.
I know what you're about to say.
What?
I wanted to get some water.
-I'll get it.
-No,
it's okay.
So... That is...
Don't feel bad...
Just... forget... everything...
I like you.
I like you too.
Mr. Oh, I think I've seen that boy
somewhere before.
-He was forced to transfer--
-It was just a regular one.
Why did he carry you earlier?
Why does he keep coming up?
Don't even go anywhere near him.
The answer is number two.
It's just one question.
Don't worry so much.
What do you know?
I've been thinking it over,
and I guess I'll accept you. Let's go out.
Rock-paper-scissors!
Soo-bin, you're like a pea. A tiny pea.
Soo-bin.
Hello, I'm Choe Jun-u.
Subtitle translation by Wayne Ryu