Jun-u,
Hwi-yeong is leaving today.
He wanted to leave
when no one else was around.
Mr. Oh.
Thank you for everything.
And...
I'm sorry.
I was rude
and disrespectful to you.
Even my parents were so rude to you.
And I only cared about myself,
being the selfish guy I am.
I apologize for everything.
For what I did
to Jun-u as well.
Hwi-yeong.
You got through the worst part.
You'll probably have to go through
more ordeals,
but don't resent anyone.
Just stay strong and live your life
of your own accord.
I will.
Gosh. I have to say,
I'm sad that you're leaving.
Take good care of yourself,
and stay in touch.
Yes, I will.
Soo-bin.
You'll be fine, right?
Take care.
Bye.
You said I'm dropping out
because I want to run away.
So I thought long and hard about it,
but I think this is
the only thing I can do for now.
Going to school
with students who have been studying
so hard and honestly...
makes me feel too guilty.
I'll pay
for all the bad things that I did to you
and repent for the rest of my life.
Jun-u.
Thanks for forgiving me.
Goodbye.
Do you want to ride my bike with me?
Sure.
Choe Jun-u! I'm sorry.
Soo-bin, I feel happy.
NAME: CHOE JUN-U
2019 HIGH SCHOOL DESIGN
AND ART COMPETITION
Jun-u!
Soo-bin.
Why did you come here?
I can do this alone.
No, I...
I wanted to get here early,
but I have to go to the academy later.
Okay, that's fine.
-You're sweating.
-Gosh, don't.
I'm all sweaty.
Today is an important day, you know.
Gosh, you can't even run that well.
Thank goodness you didn't fall.
Jun-u, today...
Today...
I'll do a good job. Don't worry.
You'll do great.
Best of luck.
Thanks.
-I should head in, Soo-bin.
-Okay.
-Break a leg.
-Get back safely.
Okay, you'll do great.
Thanks.
Go on in.
MINJOK ART UNIVERSITY ART COMPETITION
WATERCOLOR PAINTING
Look for your applicant number
to find your seat.
You can only use the given tools,
and you cannot change your seat.
2019 HIGH SCHOOL DESIGN
AND ART COMPETITION
Find your seat
according to your applicant number.
Those of you who just came in,
find your applicant number.
You can only use the given tools,
and you cannot change your seat.
You got this, Jun-u.
Soo-bin.
What's wrong?
I have to retake the course.
Again?
What do you mean?
Why? What happened?
I'm not the only one
that has to retake it.
-Everyone has to do it?
-Of course.
Gosh, I studied so hard.
Why do I have to retake it?
Just forget about it.
Why don't we go have lunch?
Okay.
I heard the food at the cafeteria here
is very good.
Let's eat off campus.
Shall we?
That will be better, right?
-Yes.
-All right, then.
SHELTER PSYCHIATRIC NURSING HOME
How have you been, brother?
Mom and Dad couldn't come
because they're a little busy.
They're doing well.
Also, I dropped out of school.
I need some time to think...
about how I should live.
I LOVE YOU, SON
You know what?
You've always been my idol
since I was a kid.
You were smart,
and you were a straight-A student.
You were even good at sports
and good-looking.
You were Mom and Dad's favorite.
They couldn't be prouder of you.
They always told me
to try to be as good as you.
Just as good as you.
But I'll stop trying to be as good as you.
I'll be as good as I can be.
Just as good as I can be.
I'll find what I should do...
on my own.
Someone taught me that.
I wonder how Jun-u is doing.
Soo-bin.
-Mom.
-Get in.
We haven't been
on a date like this in ages.
I'm sorry. I've been too busy.
Don't apologize.
I think what you do is cool.
Soo-bin.
I've given it some thought.
From now on,
I'll try to trust you more.
But right now, I can't be
entirely happy about you two going out.
I know.
But I'm sorry
I reacted so emotionally.
Mom.
Can I ask you a favor?
What is it?
I want you to stop
caring about Dad,
be strong, and live your own life.
You've been doing your best so far.
Don't care about what other people think.
If you're worried about me,
I'm really okay.
I want you to continue to be
the confident, cool woman you are.
Not just Yoo Soo-bin's mom
or Yoo Jong-su's wife.
The fabulous career woman, Yoon Song-hui.
Like you've always been.
Okay?
Soo-bin.
Do you think we can eat
more food after this?
-More after this?
-This is...
-Hi, Mom.
-Jun-u, did it go well?
I did my best, but I'm not sure.
The other kids were so good.
I'm sure you did better
than everyone else.
Good job, son.
Where are you, by the way?
There's an echo.
I'm at a big supermarket.
We ran out of ingredients.
I see.
Mom.
Should I come today?
What?
Why are you so surprised?
Go home and rest.
Why would you come here?
All right.
Don't skip meals.
Okay. You too.
Bye.
Isn't Aunt Hye-yeong there?
She's not feeling so well these days.
You don't seem very well either.
Are you sick?
No. I'm in perfect health.
I'm sure he did well.
Soo-bin.
I'm with Mom. Can we text instead?
Soo-bin, everything went well.
Good job. Are you going home?
No. I'm on my way to my mom's.
I'm going to surprise her.
She'll be so happy. Have a safe trip.
I went on a date with my mom.
JEOKSEONG SNACK RESTAURANT
Mom.
Are you home?
We just closed the restaurant
and are finishing up.
How was it at the restaurant today?
Was it okay?
Yes, of course.
All right.
AUNT HYE-YEONG
The phone is turned off.
Please leave a message.
You'll be charged after the beep.
AUNT SEON-MI
Aunt Seon-mi.
It's me, Jun-u.
Have you been well?
I'm wondering...
if something happened
to my mom's restaurant.
Please tell me.
I see.
Jun-u, are you asleep?
Did you visit your mom?
Yes, I did.
Can I call you?
Hey.
Jun-u, was your mom happy to see you?
Was she surprised?
Yes.
But you sound a bit worried
about something.
No, I'm not.
Don't lie. I already knew something was
on your mind when I saw your text.
What is it?
It's nothing.
I guess I was too nervous today.
Yes, I know.
It must've been a long day for you.
Yes, I'm a bit tired.
Then,
I'll sing you a lullaby
so you can sleep well.
Okay.
Ms. Lee! Hurry up and get in.
-I'm sorry I'm late.
-Why are you so late?
I'm sorry. Hello.
-Don't be late tomorrow.
-Okay.
Good night.
I'm so sleepy.
JEOKSEONG SNACK RESTAURANT
Hey, Jun-u.
Mom, what are you doing?
What do you think?
There are so many customers
right now. I'm really busy.
No, you're not.
Mom.
Tell me the truth.
What kind of situation we're in.
How difficult it is.
Don't worry. I'll take care of everything.
How can you call this taking care of...
Mom. I'm not a kid anymore.
If there's a problem,
you should discuss it with me.
It's just you and me in our family.
I'm your guardian too.
Why are you trying to carry
the weight of the world alone?
I feel so guilty and stupid for
not being aware of this all this time.
Jun-u, don't think that way.
I hid it from you
because there was
a good reason I couldn't tell you.
You did nothing wrong.
Mom.
Tell me everything.
I want to know.
To tell you the truth, Aunt Hye-yeong
took the money we needed
for remodeling this place,
but I can't reach her.
It's quite a large amount
that took me a lot of time to save up.
I thought it would be better for me
to work part-time for now,
instead of running this restaurant
without remodeling.
I'm going to take care of everything.
Don't worry, Jun-u.
I'm going to reopen this place as well.
So you just concentrate on
preparing for art school.
Do you understand me?
Mom.
I'm sorry.
Monthly expenses.
Electric bill, food expenses,
transportation expenses,
and my academy fee.
The total is...
73,000 WON
Jun-u, what are you doing?
I'm at the academy.
Are you learning well?
Yes, I am.
Have a good day.
Shall we run away?
I was too busy to call you yesterday.
Jun-u.
Do you remember the day we got
soaked in the rain right here?
Yes.
By the way, why did you do that?
Did you think you'd be able
to block all the rain like that?
I don't know.
What I felt that day
was something I had never felt before.
What did you feel?
I felt as if
the rain we were soaked in
was washing away all the hurtful
feelings I had inside my heart.
Jun-u, what do you plan to do
during the summer break?
I'm not sure.
The summer vacation is finally...
-It's back!
No one looked excited when we were
talking about the school trip.
Are you that excited
about not having to see me?
-Yes.
-Pil-sang.
I was joking, of course. I'm actually sad.
Mr. Oh, how am I going to
get through the summer without you?
Pil-sang, stop putting on such a show.
Don't forget to check your homework
for each subject.
I hope you all stay productive
and healthy during the break.
And don't call me too often
even if you guys miss me.
Mr. Oh, can I follow you on social media?
Me too! Please follow me back.
I'm already following you guys.
-I see.
Oh Han-gyeol.
You just got through your first semester
as a homeroom teacher.
Well done.
All right, guys.
Let's wrap up. Enjoy your summer break.
Off I go!
-Bye, Mr. Oh!
-Bye!
What's with Mr. Oh today?
He's being so corny.
Guys, how about we party it up today
to celebrate?
-Good call!
-When will you keep your promise?
I have to ask my mom first.
You can join us if you want.
Okay, I will.
I should join you girls, of course.
O-je and Jun-u.
Hang out with us. Go, let's go!
Pack up.
-Pack up your stuff.
-Pack up.
What should we do?
You look so excited.
Mr. Oh!
Ji-min, this is...
We're on school grounds now.
Please calm down.
I...
Gosh, it's okay.
There's always a next time, you know?
Do you want to go shopping today?
Or shall we go have some meat?
I passed, Mr. Oh.
I passed!
Seriously? Ji-min!
Wait, hold on. Ji-min.
Let's get out of here first. Come on.
Wow, Gi-tae.
Look at you volunteering at school.
Oh, just a second.
Throw out your own garbage, will you?
But this is right here. Sorry.
By the way, did you see Hwi-yeong leave?
No, I didn't.
He'll probably get in touch with me
after he pulls himself together.
Gosh, make sure to pick up
all the garbage, okay?
Go away, Sang-hun.
Take it easy.
-My gosh.
-What just happened?
You're good.
Pil-sang, you're pretty good at bowling.
Of course. I'm good at everything else
but studying.
And I'm very good to you.
Cut it out. All right, Pil-sang.
Let's go to the movies this Saturday.
-Seriously?
-But
all of you have to come with us.
Otherwise, I won't go.
Guys, help me out just this one time.
I'll buy all the movie tickets.
Hey!
Pil-sang, do you think
we're broke or what?
Thanks!
Guys, let's go!
-Let's go.
-Just one more.
Go, Soo-bin!
That was so close.
Gosh, too bad.
I know.
Gosh, this feels like a dream.
I can't believe Ji-min finally passed.
She said she was going
to the ladies' room.
What's taking her so long?
Ta-da!
What's all this, Ji-min?
Mr. Oh, thank you for waiting for me.
And thank you
for always being there for me.
I'm going to formally ask you out today.
Please be my boyfriend.
Okay.
Jun-u, is something bothering you?
O-je.
-Yes.
-To tell you the truth,
I'm thinking about
going to live with my mom.
Did something happen to her?
I think I should be by her side.
She's...
going through something at the moment,
and I'm the only one she has.
I want to see if there's anything I can do
to help unburden her.
But still...
This thought struck me
when I saw my mom the other day.
I've been feeling lonely,
thinking that I'm all alone in the world.
But perhaps my mom is lonelier
than anybody else at the moment.
I now have Soo-bin,
you,
and Mr. Oh in my life.
Are you hesitant because of Soo-bin?
Mom, I'm going to the academy.
Study hard even during the break.
Okay, I will.
Hello?
Yes.
Hello, thank you for making time
to meet with me.
What's up?
I heard you did much better
on the exams this time.
And I've decided on my major.
I want to go to art school.
I started going to an art academy too.
Art school? It'll be tough.
That's okay.
What did you want to talk to me about?
If you're going to ask
for my permission to date Soo-bin,
you won't get my answer.
I hope you understand.
No, it's not about that.
I have
a favor to ask of you.
That's why I called.
What is it?
Please allow me...
to hang out with Soo-bin for just one day.
Why not just hang out with her
without asking me?
Please give her your permission
so that she can hang out with me
without feeling bad.
I plan to move back to where my mom is...
so that I can be by her side.
Which means I won't be able
to see Soo-bin for a while.
Why all of a sudden? Did something happen?
She has a bit of a situation now.
But...
I'd like to tell Soo-bin myself.
I'd appreciate it
if you could keep it from her until then.
Please don't tell her.
All right.
I won't tell her.
Thank you.
Jun-u.
Thank you so much
for comforting Soo-bin back then.
And I think
I reacted too emotionally.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry.
I'll be going then.
Okay.
Hi.
Where are you?
I'm at the academy.
Are you on your way home?
Yes.
Is something wrong?
Well...
It's just that we don't
see each other as often.
And the break began,
so we can't meet at school either.
You should go home.
Jun-u, it's a bit tiring, isn't it?
Let's hang in there until the day
my mom approves of our relationship
and we can meet freely.
Actually, it doesn't matter to me.
Should we meet now?
No.
Until the day.
Go home now.
Okay.
Bye.
-I'm home.
-Did you study hard?
Have you been somewhere?
What? I just stepped out for a moment.
Hey.
You...
It's summer break now.
Why don't you meet him once?
Who do you mean?
Jun-u.
Why are you saying this?
You asked me
to trust you.
Also, your grades went up.
You said he's been working hard too.
I'm not saying you can go out with him.
Just meet him and get some fresh air.
Thanks, Mom.
Meeting him with your permission
even for a day would be great.
You don't seem too excited.
I am. Thank you.
Jun-u, the thing you asked for
the other day.
Thank you.
He gives private lessons around there.
-Give him a call.
-I will.
I really hope you'll win a prize.
I don't think I will.
All the other kids were so good.
Jun-u.
Choe Jun-u.
I'll make you an offer you can't refuse.
Jun-u, will you go
on a date with me? All day?
I have my mom's permission.
Okay.
Are you at the academy? Focus.
Let's talk later.
Okay.
Thanks. I'll talk to you later.
Good. Like that.
He's painting.
Jun-u.
Jun-u, your skills have improved so much.
What did I tell you?
I'm good at recognizing talent.
So why?
I heard you're quitting the academy.
Well...
I should've told you first.
I think I should go to my mom.
What do you mean?
Are you saying you're transferring?
My mom is in a bit of a situation.
I think I should stay with her
and help her as much as I can.
Jun-u.
I hope this doesn't hurt your feelings.
Will you let me help you?
Mr. Oh.
I appreciate
your concern.
I mean...
You're all settled now.
You found what you want to do,
and you're going to a good academy.
To me, it seems like
everything is finally in place.
That's why I'm going.
Now I know I can do well
wherever I go.
You're running away right now!
Fine, walk away trying to look
all cool. Well, you don't.
Hey!
Jun-u! You're only running away!
All right, Jun-u.
Go.
Go to your mom
and be with her.
I think you can do that now.
Without you, I would...
I'd feel a little empty.
But I think you can do that.
Soo-bin.
You look pretty.
Do I look okay?
You look very pretty.
See you later.
Okay?
Soo-bin.
One more thing.
I've given some thought to what you said.
A lot of thought, actually.
Thank you so much...
for giving me courage.
Soo-bin, I'll try to do as you said.
I love you, Mom.
I love you so much.
I'm sorry.
-Hi.
-Like this?
-Yes.
One, two, three.
One more time. One, two, three.
Pil-sang.
Do you want to go out with me?
What?
I'm saying it just one more time.
Let's go out.
Goodness.
-What are you doing?
-Sit down!
-Gosh.
-Are you crazy?
-Sit down.
I can't see the screen.
This feels nice.
Yes.
Soo-bin.
Yes?
I have something to tell you.
I know.
I kept having this strange feeling,
so I called your mom.
Since you visited your mom last time,
something's been bothering me.
She said
you're insisting on coming to live
with her
even though she told you not to.
I'm sorry for telling you too late.
What do you think I said?
Hello, this is Yoo Soo-bin.
Yes. I've been doing well. Thank you.
Well... I was wondering
what's up with Jun-u lately.
He seemed down lately,
so I got worried and called you.
It's okay. You can tell me.
No matter how much I try to stop him,
Jun-u's insisting that
he should come here to live with me
because he's too worried about me.
So I eventually agreed.
You must be very upset, Soo-bin.
Right? I feel so bad.
I'm really okay on my own.
I'm sure
Jun-u thought about it a lot.
No matter where Jun-u lives,
what's important is for him to feel
at ease.
He can keep studying hard
and focus on his art studies.
That's what's important.
I'll be staying in touch with Jun-u,
so don't worry.
Jun-u, it must've been so tough for you.
But Jun-u,
although I said that to your mom,
I...
still feel...
Soo-bin, to be honest,
you're the one that worries me the most.
But,
just because I go live with my mom
doesn't mean it's over between us.
Let's do what we have to do for now
and wait
a little longer.
Okay.
From now on,
let's never wear sad or depressed faces.
Promise me.
I promise.
You're so kind, Soo-bin.
You're so kind, Jun-u.
YOU HAVE WON SECOND PRIZE!
Hey, Jun-u. You won second prize...
You won second prize?
Congratulations!
I feel so proud of you.
-Soo-bin.
-Congratulations.
Congratulations, Jun-u.
Thank you.
-Great job.
-Thank you.
That was so fast.
How about another lap?
That was already our seventh lap.
You should go inside now.
Okay.
Good night.
Soo-bin.
I have a favor to ask you.
What is it?
When I leave,
I don't think you should come.
Why not?
I don't want you to see me leaving.
I'll come back to see you.
I'll be even more handsome when I return.
Go.
You'll see my mom when you get there.
Thank you, sir.
Jun-u is leaving today, right?
Yes.
Shouldn't you go see him and say goodbye?
I have to do this.
I have a test at the academy today.
All right.
It's like another world.
It is another world.
The world I live in.
-Happy birthday to you
-Blow them out.
Many happy returns.
Jun-u.
I'm going to the academy.
Soo-bin.
Have a good day.
Bumbi.
Password, Soo-bin's birthday.
You, again?
Yes, it's me.
No...
Jun-u.
Choe Jun-u!
Choe Jun-u! Jun-u.
Jun-u.
Choe Jun-u!
Jun-u!
Soo-bin.
Even though we have to say goodbye now,
this goodbye isn't forever
because all the moments we've shared
are still shining so radiantly
and the dazzling moments
I'm having at the age of 18
are truly beautiful.
THANK YOU FOR WATCHING MOMENT OF EIGHTEEN
Subtitle translation by Wayne Ryu