Sir, please take me to this address.
Your destination has been set.
Unlike yesterday,
the sky looks very clear today.
It's been raining for the last few days,
and on my way...
I'm leaving, just like this.
Summer seems just around the corner.
Just like this, I'm on the road
once again to someplace else.
Time didn't wait for me
and just passed me by,
with all those moments.
You are approaching your destination.
Sir, this way.
Anyway, I'm at this moment.
Anyway, I'm 18.
Take a left 300 meters ahead.
Go straight.
Take a right 100 meters ahead.
That crazy--
Is he all right?
Shouldn't we get off and check?
He seems okay.
He didn't even fall off.
Let's go.
Wait, even if he didn't fall off...
Hey, kitty.
Where's your mom?
It's dangerous here. Play somewhere else.
Bye!
CONGRATULATIONS
MOST IMPROVED SCHOOL
-Yoo Soo-bin!
Hi!
Hey, this has grown quite a bit.
Did you buy this?
-My gosh, it's so cool.
-It's pretty.
My mom bought it for me
on her business trip.
I was going to get this too.
-Isn't this a knockoff?
-There are knockoffs of this?
What if it's really a knockoff?
I walked here all the way from home.
-My legs hurt so much.
-What?
Good, I hope you'll lose some weight.
I'm so exhausted.
My legs are all wobbly.
Hang on. Just a moment.
What's going on?
Excuse me! You in the checkered shirt...
Are you all right?
Pardon me?
Oh, you almost got hit by a car earlier.
That was my mom's car.
Try doing this.
Good. You seem all right.
If there are any issues,
find me at school.
My name is Yoo Soo-bin.
I'm in the 3rd class of the 2nd grade.
Soo-bin, what happened?
Is it okay to give out your name?
He nearly got hit by my mom's car earlier.
We should take responsibility
if we have to.
Still, you don't even know who he is.
By the way, isn't that guy so handsome?
Not at all. Da-huin, don't look at him.
I think he is.
Hey, Soo-bin!
My hair looks so bad!
-Look at my hair.
-What happened?
No, it looks okay.
-It doesn't look okay.
-What's that? Your lunch?
No! I'm not giving it to you.
Yoo Soo-bin?
Look at what he's wearing. Hey, you!
Yes.
-Hello.
-Yes, hello...
Mr. Nam.
Excuse me.
Good morning, everyone.
-Hello.
-Hi.
-Yes, hi.
-Excuse me, sir.
-All right.
-Hello.
Let's see.
Excuse me, sir.
I'm a transfer student.
-Are you the one from Byeong...
-Yes, from Byeongmun High School.
I see. You're here.
Mr. Oh.
Mr. Oh?
Mr. Oh Han-gyeol isn't here yet.
My gosh, I'm sorry I'm late.
Follow him. Go on.
Hello?
Hi, how have you been?
His homeroom teacher is giving him
an orientation at the moment.
Yes, I'm aware.
Oh, you can leave it here.
Well, I'm sure nothing will happen.
Yes, right. Please don't worry.
Yes. Take care.
TRANSFERRED ACCORDING TO ARTICLE 17.1
OF THE SCHOOL VIOLENCE LAW
So this is... It's a case of forced...
A forced transfer, sir.
You should never talk about that openly.
And... I understand.
Things happen, you know?
Let's do something
about your clothes first, okay?
Ms. Bae, where can we buy
the school uniform?
At the school uniform store, obviously.
Right, obviously.
There's a store that sells uniforms
at the nearby intersection,
so get changed
into the uniform first and...
CONGRATULATIONS, YOU'VE WON
THE EVENT FOR LUXURY SNEAKERS...
Hang on. Why is this already...
Well, hey.
I mean... First, you should...
-Hi, Hwi-yeong.
-Oh, see that guy?
He's the class president.
You can follow him.
Just follow him.
Go with the class president.
-He's a transfer student.
-I see.
Let's go.
Yes, go on.
Yes, ma'am.
I'm with your son now. Yes.
He's very mature for his age.
Yes, he'll do well here. That's right.
Go on.
-See you in a bit.
-Yes, sir.
PAYMENT COMPLETED.
YOUR ORDER WILL BE SHIPPED SOON.
Isn't Mr. Oh cute?
He's our assistant teacher.
Our homeroom teacher is hospitalized now.
I'm Ma Hwi-yeong. It's nice to meet you.
-I'm...
-Choe Jun-u?
The vice-principal told me
about you yesterday.
You don't have the uniform yet, right?
-Hey, Hwi-yeong.
-Hi, Gi-tae.
Let's go.
LEE TAE-HO
These pants will be better.
I'm fine with anything.
You shouldn't be fine with anything.
Put them on.
Thank you, ma'am.
They're practically new.
I made sure to find the best ones
since you asked.
-You know it's usually not free.
-I do, of course.
I have the summer uniform ready too.
Thank you.
This is for today's morning assembly.
Introduce the transfer student
and submit the evaluation sheets.
Classes begin at 9 a.m.,
but we often have to be here
by 8:10 a.m. for supplementary classes.
And the midterm's coming up soon.
I'm not sure if you've covered
the same chapters.
The lockers are here.
Look for Lee Gi-tae,
the student life leader.
He'll tell you which one to use.
DID YOU MEMORIZE 50 ENGLISH WORDS?
Let's go.
You'll learn this soon,
but all the teachers here are great.
They're all highly qualified as well.
I bet they're better than most
top-notch instructors at academies.
Everyone talks about
special-purpose or private schools,
but I think this school will be more
helpful for us to get into good colleges.
Oh, the after-school studying hours.
It's not compulsory, but everyone
does it during the exam times.
There's a separate performance
assessment group for each subject.
And about the practical evaluation...
It must be confusing
to hear about all this at once.
First, go over the notices
in our class group chat.
They'll give you an idea.
If you have any questions, ask me anytime.
Wait here.
-Goodness.
-Hey!
Someone left this for you.
What is it? Does it mean something?
The wheel of fate is turning.
I hear the creaking noise.
Didn't you say a waterwheel
was spinning last time?
-Let's go.
-There's a ton of people at NW.
Where is NW? North, south, west, or east?
North. It's north, you idiot.
-Okay, north.
-Hey, where's the bulletproof car?
-Where is the bulletproof car?
-No idea.
You idiot, you should know where it is.
-It was amazing!
-I know.
This is crazy.
Guys, be seated.
Get your act together.
Yoo Pil-sang, be seated.
It's time for our morning assembly.
-Yoo Pil-sang.
-Yes, what's up?
Hey.
You punk.
-Something's come up for Mr. Oh.
-Every day?
I'll introduce the transfer student first.
Jun-u.
Didn't we see him earlier?
Hey.
Isn't he...
Jun-u, please introduce yourself.
I'm Choe Jun-u.
What's with him? That's all?
Hey, let me ask you a question.
Pil-sang, don't.
Can you tell us a bit more?
He's from Byeongmun High School.
Byeongmun?
Where is that?
It seems like a lousy school.
Jun-u had to move here
because of his parents' work.
That's why he transferred to our school.
Let's get to know him better later on.
It wasn't because of my parents' work.
-It wasn't?
-Then what was it?
Something personal?
I transferred because...
He's new here. We should all help him out.
He'll sit...
Sorry.
O-je is here.
O-je, can you move?
To the seat next to Pil-sang.
Jun-u is a new student.
What's up with him?
Does he think
I'll bully the newbie or something?
Won't you?
You little...
Well...
-Sure.
-Thanks.
Jun-u.
God, you stink of sweat.
Welcome.
I have some announcements to make.
Some groups haven't turned in
their assignments yet.
Be sure to submit them by Friday.
Also, Pil-sang, please be quiet.
Sorry, guys.
-What's with you?
-I can't believe you!
How could you be so late?
I said I'm sorry. Okay?
-Are you done?
-Not yet.
I covered the new student part.
I see. Good job.
Where is he?
Oh, there he is.
All right.
The midterm's in three weeks.
What are we supposed to do?
I'm Lee Gi-tae.
-Welcome.
-Mr. Oh, she thinks you have a cold.
Me? How did you know?
Let's get started. Be quiet.
When it won't open, do this.
Jun-u, you got a good spot.
You didn't have to do that.
What?
You said I transferred
because of my parents' work.
I just thought you seemed to feel
a bit uncomfortable.
That doesn't mean it's okay to lie.
What's the big deal?
Our class president was
just being thoughtful as always.
Hey, checkered shirt!
We're in the same class.
No way.
Again? This morning,
you were on your bike and...
In front of the school gate.
Yes. So you do remember me. That's good.
Do you know each other?
Kind of.
Well, this is Yoo Soo-bin,
our study leader.
And Ma Hwi-yeong's girlfriend.
No way. We're just friends.
Right, Little Boy?
Yes.
We went to kindergarten
and elementary school together.
By the way, Jun-u has to join
an assessment group.
Right?
Ro-mi, isn't your group kind of small?
But we're already finished.
We'll submit our assignment today.
Really?
Too bad. My group is already too big.
Then maybe another group...
He can join my group.
We're one person short
since the vice president moved away.
Soo-bin.
I'll tell you what you need to do later.
Lucky you.
You're in the same group as Soo-bin.
She's super good at performance
assessments.
She's really meticulous.
You're on the bus now.
Enjoy your ride.
What should I make him do?
You didn't have to let him
into your group.
What can I do? There's not much time left.
I feel a sense of responsibility
as the study leader.
Still, don't you need a good grade
in Literature this time?
Soo-bin, how could you?
What about So-ye and me?
Don't you need our consent first?
Only in a situation like this?
Who has done all our assignments so far?
Also, who hasn't sent
her part of the assignment yet?
I did a little this time.
I was going to send it to you tonight.
Really? Good for you, Da-huin.
Let's be nice and help each other.
Why were you disciplined
at your previous school?
Well... Sir, it's written
on the first page.
I asked just to confirm it.
I see.
Is it true that you were
forced to transfer
because you repeatedly committed
theft and assault?
Well...
Tae-ho, you can't get away
with things like that anymore.
This school is fundamentally
different from your previous school.
It has history, tradition, and class.
If you show any unacceptable behaviors
like these,
in the worst case,
you might be advised to drop out.
Can't I drop out
right now?
Pardon?
Can't I drop out?
You're surprisingly unpredictable.
Getting on the vice-principal's nerves
would only make your life here harder.
Listening to his one-on-one lecture
once is enough
to make you want to drop out
right then and there.
Well...
Tae-ho.
I'm Jun-u. This is second-hand.
I mean Jun-u.
The thing is, those teachers and I
are the only people who know
that you were forced to transfer.
There's no need to say unnecessary things
and make things awkward.
I mean...
Why don't you make a fresh start?
Forget all your past.
Okay? You can do this.
Let's do this.
Here.
Is the new student
from another planet or something?
I can't find anything about him online.
Stop it, Da-huin.
What?
We should find out what he's like.
Because of you, he's suddenly
in our group.
You're interested in him, aren't you?
I could see he's your type.
What are you talking about? He's not.
Fine, I admit
that he's pretty good-looking.
-Still, he's not my type.
-Agreed.
Da-huin's type is Jung O-je.
-O-je?
-Gosh.
Guys, the new student is unbelievable.
What did you find?
CHOE JUN-U IS BEING FORCED TO TRANSFER
Gosh, "assault and theft"?
Does that mean he stole something?
See? What are we going to do now, Soo-bin?
So-ye, what should we do?
What do you mean?
It's not like
he's a gangster or a criminal.
Who knows?
There are many good-looking
psychopaths these days.
Gosh, you're going too far, Da-huin.
Isn't this the new student?
Is this his?
Yes, that's his bike.
Welcome.
Hello. You're hiring, right?
Oh, yes. Are you a student?
Well...
I'm in my second year of high school.
Not in middle school?
I'm not.
I'm just joking.
What are you good at?
Do I have to be good at something?
Of course. Otherwise, you can't work here.
To those who answer correctly,
we will send various gifts.
We look forward to your participation...
I knew it.
Hey! That thief! Hey!
Hey, just take it! Darn it.
What's wrong with you?
Here, take it.
There is something you're good at.
Running.
Great job.
What?
Put them back where they belong now.
-Hurry.
-Okay.
Excuse me,
then does that mean I can work here?
Depending on how you clean up.
Hurry up. Over there.
Yes, sir.
Why does that lady always ask for favors?
Okay. Yes.
Park Yeong-bae.
I have a little errand for you.
"Park Yeong-bae"?
PARK YEONG-BAE
Now, I will explain exponential functions
to you for about 20 minutes.
Why are we doing something so easy?
To go over the basic concept.
In principle, you need to input
all the numbers one by one,
but you already know this, right?
I know you're all smart kids.
First of all, let's take a look
at when A and B are bigger than one.
This is X.
I told you not to do that.
All right. Let's review
what we've learned until now
and take some time
for checking by yourselves.
You should check
why you got this question wrong.
Hwi-yeong, you keep making a mistake.
You got this wrong. Do you see?
It's strange.
I thought you'd be good at this.
Hwi-yeong, when you set a range,
you must never get it wrong.
I'm so hungry.
Hwi-yeong.
Isn't your mom buying snacks today?
I'm starving.
She'll come soon.
-I told you to check.
-Okay.
Let's take it step by step.
What is this question asking?
Hwi-yeong. Did you get this wrong?
This one is so easy. Hold on.
Sir, this is really bad.
If you keep this up,
I'll beat you on the exam.
-If you keep--
-I'll tear your ear off.
Stop bothering us and go away.
Okay. Let's see.
Where were we?
-Put that down.
-Yes, sir.
Look. I think this part is
where you made a mistake.
Why did you come up with this number here?
You little...
Sang-hun, are you solving it right now?
Yes.
Good.
Is that how you solved it?
My goodness.
Hey, that seems like a faster way.
Although this method is correct too,
don't you think his method
looks more efficient?
Why is it so hard to solve
such an easy question?
Don't you think, Hwi-yeong?
Mr. Jo Sang-hun.
Not everyone is a genius like you.
Okay.
I'm starving.
He'll be a perfect student
if he just quits smoking.
Anyway, you shouldn't miss that.
Don't make a mistake.
Okay.
It's just a mistake.
Guys. Why don't we all take a short break?
-Go outside and get some fresh air.
-Okay.
Jo Sang-hun.
I have a delivery for Class 1.
Oh, Hwi-yeong's mom?
-Over there. It's Classroom Two.
-Okay.
Oh, wait.
Can you take out
the recyclables in the classroom?
-They're from your store too.
-Okay.
Thanks.
Jun-u.
What are you doing here?
Oh, I came here for a delivery.
-The teacher told me to throw this out.
-Gosh, how could he make you do that?
-Give it to me. I'll throw it out.
-No, it's fine.
Give it to me.
Hwi-yeong. Hey.
What are you doing?
Hey, it's our delivery. Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Your mom is a savior.
I'm hungry. Let's go.
Jun-u, wait.
I think I threw something away by mistake.
Are you looking for something?
No, it's nothing.
Thanks. See you.
-Are you looking for something?
-No, it's nothing.
Thanks.
Welcome...
Are you the newbie? Park Yeong-bae?
Hi. I'm the part-timer
for the night shift.
I came early to study.
Hello.
For goodness' sake.
Stop with the flattery.
I didn't do anything.
Hwi-yeong practically set everything up.
Yes.
I'm telling you. Just treat me
to something good later.
You're home. Your mom is on the phone.
Talk about some great timing.
Yes. Of course.
Stop singing my praises, Ms. Yoon.
Yes.
Did you?
Did you get this wrong?
Mr. Jo Sang-hun.
Not everyone is a genius like you.
It's just a mistake.
Yes, ma'am.
I'm so grateful for your consideration.
Yes, okay. Have a good evening.
God, she's so obnoxious.
Was that Hwi-yeong's mom?
What does she want now?
What else? It was because of you again.
I'm trying to get you
into Hwi-yeong's math class.
-Mom, please.
-What? Cut it out.
Hey, they don't let just anyone
take a level test for that class.
She said she'd try,
so get ready for the test.
Gosh, I really don't want to do it.
Why do I have to practically beg
Hwi-yeong's mom
just to get into that class?
Do you really... My gosh, I'm speechless.
Do you really not know
why you need to improve?
Hwi-yeong is top of his year,
whereas you are the 28th.
And you barely managed it.
Do you think you're at his level?
I am studying hard,
and I will get better grades.
How long will it take you
to get better grades, then?
I don't know.
Anyway, I'm not taking that class.
What? Don't be ridiculous.
I'm dead serious. I won't take it.
Hey, then let's get you a tutor at least!
Why do you keep saying
you want to study on your own?
Do you think you're a genius?
God, she always does
whatever she wants to do.
I just sent you my part
for the performance assessment.
I'm no longer a nuisance.
All right. I'll have a look.
What will you make the newbie do?
Don't let him be a nuisance.
Which task should I give to Jun-u?
It's me, Soo-bin.
For the performance assessment...
Gosh!
"Assault and theft"?
Forget it.
This time, you can get a free pass.
It didn't seem like
he could do such a thing.
Are you all right?
Sorry about that.
Are you all right? Try doing this.
Mom.
Son, did you have a good day at school?
How's the school? I bet you're
the most handsome guy there.
Make sure you eat well and study hard.
I have to leave before you get home
because of the restaurant.
I'm sorry.
-Enjoy.
-Thank you.
Mom, did you stop by?
I told you not to rush.
What if you trip and fall again?
I thought you'd be out
of all the side dishes by now.
I couldn't even be there
when you were moving. I'm sorry.
Excuse me. Could we get a bottle of soju?
Sure.
I'm working now.
My baby, Jun-u. I love you.
I love you too.
Hey, newbie.
Shall I let you in on some information?
See that girl?
The prettiest girl in our class.
She's mine.
Don't you dare look at her.
If I ever catch you doing that,
I'll teach you a serious lesson.
And that girl over there.
Hwi-yeong has a crush on her.
As for the rest, I don't care
whether you hit on them or not.
Although you'll have a hard time
with that face.
Nice, bravo!
Excellent job, Hwi-yeong.
-Play "Let It Go" next!
-All right, quiet down.
What's the matter?
Well, could you please spare me a second?
Sir, Choe Jun-u is here.
You know who I am, right?
What is the most famous
of Beethoven's sonatas?
It's the "Moonlight Sonata."
The "Moonlight Sonata" consists of
three movements in total.
Out of the three movements,
the first one, which Hwi-yeong
played for us just now,
is the most famous one.
All right, let's look at the printout.
Ma'am.
Yes, Hwi-yeong. What is it?
May I step out
to go to the nurse's office?
Are you going to keep
playing dumb like this?
You stole my watch.
No, I didn't.
Sorry to interrupt. Sir.
Jun-u.
Oh, hello.
Apparently, Jun-u stole his watch.
Pardon me?
As soon as he's transferred here...
My gosh.
Mr. Son.
Hey, Hwi-yeong.
This punk stole my watch
when he came for the delivery yesterday.
Was it an expensive watch?
What kind of watch costs 25 million won?
You said 25 million won?
Jun-u, why did you do that?
-I didn't do it.
-Right?
He says he didn't do it.
Who else would have done such a thing?
You were the only person to enter
my classroom besides my students.
Hwi-yeong, you should know.
I've been wearing that watch
every single day,
but nothing like this has happened before.
I see.
Well, are you sure
you didn't lose it somewhere else?
There's no way Jun-u did such a thing.
Jun-u, wait.
I think I threw something away by mistake.
How can you be so sure?
He only transferred here yesterday.
He was forced to transfer here,
to be precise.
Sir, there is no evidence yet.
Why don't you go home
and take a look under your bed
-or in your bathroom cabinet?
-Look.
I considered settling,
but I don't think I should.
I'll ask the police to investigate.
-Look, sir.
-Please try to calm down.
Can we talk for a minute?
No. I have to go shoot an online class.
I'll be leaving then.
-Wait.
-Just a second.
What are you waiting for, Mr. Oh?
Well, okay.
Sir, can you...
Stop him.
Can we talk?
Hwi-yeong, why are you doing this?
What are you doing? Hurry up.
Sir, please think again.
I've already given it a lot of thought.
Go change your shoes.
Have a seat.
Ro-mi, drink this yogurt.
Ro-mi.
You don't like yogurt? I see.
Are you sure? Did Jun-u really steal it?
I'm not sure. I hope not.
But it seems so.
He doesn't seem to be that kind of person.
-How do you know that?
-What?
Soo-bin, our group is doomed, aren't we?
I hope this doesn't leak out.
We already have enough troublemakers
in our school.
It already spread everywhere.
This is not good.
Haven't you guys lost anything?
I should check.
Right. My earrings.
I got them for my birthday present.
Do you mean these?
-Gosh.
-Oh, right.
Da-huin.
We can't be too careful.
Eat up.
Hwi-yeong, it seems like
your class is in big trouble.
I heard Son Jae-yeong
came and made a scene.
He bragged so much about his watch.
Serves him right.
Sang-hun, we're eating.
You have something to say?
Hwi-yeong, here you go.
Oh, thanks.
Sim-bok, did you just get Hwi-yeong bread?
-Does your mom know about this?
-She does.
What about your dad? You...
I asked him for a favor.
I'm leaving.
-Sim-bok, have my yogurt.
-Thanks.
I'm leaving too.
Gosh.
Stop it.
Thank you for everything.
Salute!
-All right.
All right.
Bye.
Mr. Oh, how did it go?
There's not enough evidence,
so nothing will happen to Jun-u.
-There are no cameras either.
-No.
-That's good, I guess.
-"Good"?
The vice-principal is furious.
He wants Jun-u
to be transferred to another school.
But he came here yesterday.
We can't send him away so soon.
The vice-principal wants to see me.
I have to go. Talk to Jun-u.
Okay.
You skipped lunch, right?
Eat it.
Thanks.
There's no evidence.
And the school is doing its best.
I'm sure everything will be fine.
The academy teacher is not
that cold-hearted either.
Do you also think I stole it?
Of course not.
You're scratching yourself again.
Mom.
Poor boy.
Never scratch even if it itches.
Your atopy will get worse. Okay?
Okay?
You're in a good mood today.
Your brother came out on top
in his department again.
How can he be so perfect?
He beat all those smart Western students.
I'm sure Dad is happy.
You have no idea.
You know he never smiles.
But now, he's grinning from ear to ear.
You're happy too, right?
Totally.
I wish every day were like today.
I'm happy if you're happy.
Study hard. That'll make me happy.
Sorry for interrupting you.
Study hard.
Just do as well as your brother.
I love you.
Drink this.
Jun-u.
Can you bring your mother tomorrow?
Good evening, Yeong-bae.
-You can leave now.
-Okay.
Okay.
"I'm Yeong-bae's dad.
Yeong-bae would never do such a thing."
-Is that what I should say?
-Yes.
It must be hard to go to school
and work at the same time.
You could take the high school
qualification exam instead.
My parents passed away early,
so I went through a lot too.
-Sir.
-Yes?
My name isn't Park Yeong-bae.
Right. It's the name on the vest.
That was a long time ago.
I should have known.
"Lee Tae-ho."
"I'm Tae-ho's dad."
That's not my name either.
What? Then...
Jun-u, where were you?
I've been looking everywhere for you.
-Well, my dad...
-Your mother is here.
-Pardon?
-Your mother.
Mom.
Your husband is here too.
Well...
Hi, honey.
Well... As I said...
With the Education Office
Comprehensive Inspection coming up,
this is a critical moment for us.
Also, in my opinion...
Tae-ho...
It's Jun-u. Choe Jun-u.
Okay.
Your son seems to be rather soft-hearted.
I'm worried the rough kids at this school
will take advantage of him.
I'm afraid there's a possibility
that he'll get picked on.
-I didn't--
-I'll make him transfer.
I'm working in the countryside anyway,
so I'll take him with me.
I see. That sounds like a good idea.
From what I've experienced,
it's best for emotionally
unstable kids like him
to always be with their mothers.
-Sir, do you also agree with her?
-Yes.
I see.
Wait.
Ma'am. Ma'am, wait.
You don't have to take
such drastic measures.
I don't think the vice-principal meant
for him to transfer to another--
Do you think I'm avoiding filth
because I'm afraid?
Sorry?
She's avoiding it because it's dirty.
Jun-u is not someone who steals things.
-I know.
-What is a school supposed to be?
It's a place that embraces students
in crisis with a warm hug.
His previous school was no different.
Schools like this that don't trust
nor embrace students are trash...
I mean, schools like this are really...
This is totally annoying.
We'll just leave.
But I never suspected Jun-u.
I have to look for a house
near my workplace.
So I'll take Jun-u with me
in about two days.
Until then, please take care of him
for me.
-Ma'am...
-Jun-u.
I have to get to work now.
Don't be discouraged.
I won't tolerate that.
-I'll call you.
-Okay.
-See you.
-Bye.
Let's go, honey.
-Okay, honey.
-Wait, ma'am.
Ma'am? Can you please reconsider?
Watch your step.
Goodbye.
Your mother is quite feisty.
You don't take after her, do you?
Hey. I heard the transfer student
is transferring again.
What's his issue? Is it his hobby or what?
He's lucky he's not going to Juvie.
He stole an expensive watch.
Are you sure he's the one who stole it?
Who goes to that academy?
Hwi-yeong and Sang-hun? Who else?
-Hello.
Where did we leave off last time?
Mr. Oh.
About Jun-u.
I don't think it's right
to just send him away like this.
Well, nothing's been decided yet, so--
I don't know about the faculty,
but we shouldn't be biased against Jun-u.
He's our friend.
Right.
We should trust Jun-u and be on his side.
Jun-u, you shouldn't just leave like this.
I'll talk to the vice-principal
again tomorrow.
I'm not leaving now.
He's going the day after tomorrow.
Since we still have time,
why don't we start studying?
The midterm is coming up.
We haven't made any progress!
-It's your fault.
-What should we do?
-He's so lame.
-Boo!
Where did we leave off?
Page 93.
This is our group's presentation material.
Can you look into books for reference?
I marked the quotes on the back.
You're in our group. If you want to join,
you should at least do this.
-I'm leaving--
-Even if you have to leave,
I still wrote down your name
in our group list.
You can go to the library for research.
You know where the library is, right?
Aren't you going to take off
that name tag?
It's hard to take off.
What? What do you want?
Hey. You guys can go on ahead.
Will you be okay?
What do you think?
Let's go.
Here.
You're already finished?
You can do it by tomorrow.
I'm not coming tomorrow.
Didn't you say you're coming
to school until tomorrow?
Well, I decided not to come.
You just do as you please, don't you?
LEE TAE-HO
I'm going to return it now.
Bye, then.
-Wait for me.
-Stop following me.
Wait for me.
My bad.
You have to get ready
for Seoul University?
Sorry.
Where are you?
Over here.
GROUP 4
SOO-BIN, DA-HUIN, SO-YE, JUN-U
REFERENCE LIST
What's taking you so long?
I'm on my way.
-Where are you?
-Wait.
I'm on Level Four.
Level Four? My gosh.
LETTER OF APOLOGY, CHOE JUN-U
You're pretty good at drawing.
That ladybug looks cute.
Can you stand there for a second?
Why?
Stay still.
I won't kill you.
Hey, newbie.
Are you a ghost?
You're barely visible.
Don't you resent being a nobody?
It's done.
All right. Look, okay?
Thanks.
Wait! I'm not done yet.
What was your name again?
Choe Jun-u.
So you do know how to smile.
Bye, newbie.
I wish you all the best.
Keep being a nobody.
CHOE JUN-U
Is it necessary to be a somebody?
I've never cared about
things like that my whole life.
Why should I change now?
Seriously?
Are you sure Jun-u stole it?
Yes, I think so.
Come on. No way.
I don't want to believe it either,
but Sang-hun said he saw it.
You mean, Jo Sang-hun in the other class?
Yes.
Jun-u, are you going home?
I explained everything to Mr. Oh.
Let's wait and see what happens.
I have a tutoring session.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Do you have something to say to me?
What is it?
Jun-u, I'm running late.
Let's talk tomorrow. I'm sorry.
Ma Hwi-yeong.
Yes?
Jun-u, you see...
Why are you putting on an act?
What?
What are you talking about?
It was you.
-You're the one who stole it.
-Stole what?
You mean, Mr. Son's watch?
Jun-u, don't be so anxious.
I said I'll help you.
-So calm down and--
-That day,
when you followed me down the stairs,
you found the watch
inside the garbage bag and took it.
Did you think I didn't know?
What are you talking about?
Hey, Hwi-yeong!
You shit.
What will you do?
What will you do if I did it?
I want you to be honest with me.
Why are you pinning it on me
when you're the one who did it?
What will you do about it?
What will you do if I did it?
You piece of trash.
"Piece of trash"?
Shouldn't you call yourself that?
What?
You bastard.
Did you just call me trash?
Jun-u, you can be honest with me.
Actually, I knew.
It must be that guy. The delivery guy.
Did you really have to do this?
You were angry.
All the treading made you turn.
You're only running away!
Shouldn't you do your duty
before you leave?
Dad? Where does he live?
I'm running away. Why do I keep...
running away?
You're okay no matter
how badly other people treat you.
I pity
people like you.
I'm sorry, Mom.
Subtitle translation by Wayne Ryu