What are you guys doing?
So your girlfriend is Soo-bin?
-Well...
-Mom.
I was going to tell you
after the final exams--
Soo-bin.
What is this now?
What is happening here?
What are you two doing?
Don't touch her!
What is this?
What on earth is happening?
What are you thinking?
Mom.
Go home.
I'll be downstairs.
Go home. Just go.
I told you to go home!
Sit down.
Can I ask you something?
Yes.
Did you...
sleep with Soo-bin?
Be honest with me.
Only then can we prepare
for the worst-case scenario...
as soon as possible.
Right?
Did you?
That...
never happened.
Thanks.
Thanks for not being immature.
You probably know
what I'm going to say to you.
Don't go out with Soo-bin.
Don't even talk to her from now on.
Yes, just pretend you don't know her.
Nothing happened between you two, right?
Nothing whatsoever happened
between you, right?
Hey, Soo-bin is not a girl
someone like you can go out with...
Jun-u.
Your mom is such a good person.
You're probably a good person as well.
I'm sure of it. Right, Jun-u?
Jun-u.
Yes.
Jun-u, I beg you.
Please?
Mom.
He said he won't go out with you anymore.
He promised me.
This is it.
Okay?
Come down.
Soo-bin, are you all right?
Tell your mom that you're sorry.
I'm fine.
You don't have to give them up
if you don't want to.
Keep them.
But if you do that,
I'll pack up and leave.
I'll quit my job too.
I'll quit everything.
Once I decide to do something,
I always do it.
I don't need these things.
Go study.
Mom.
Yes.
Is it that wrong...
that I'm going out with Jun-u?
Yes.
Why is it wrong?
Because you're my everything.
You're...
Because you're my everything,
and I cherish you even more than myself.
You're the last bit of pride
that I have left.
And you're going out
with a boy like that...
I can't even believe that my daughter
hung out with a punk like him.
Does that answer your question?
Had I gone out with someone else,
would you have been okay with it?
Take them. Just take them
if you don't want to give them up.
Suit yourself.
Do whatever you want if you don't need me.
I'll go study.
-Mom.
-Yes.
Your threats...
Forget it.
Mom, I wanted to tell you
that I'm not obeying you
because I'm afraid something bad
might happen to you or you might walk out
of my life, and I wanted to say
I'm sick and tired of your threats.
But that might make you
hate Jun-u even more.
-Hi, Mom.
-Jun-u, did something happen?
You seem upset.
No, I'm not upset.
Is it because the light is dim?
You must be exhausted
from studying for the final exams.
My poor son.
I can't even be there to look after you.
-Were you washing the dishes?
-Yes.
I'm fine.
-The restaurant is busy, right?
-Yes, of course.
We've been busy. Maybe it's
because of the renovations.
We had a big group earlier.
Twenty people came together.
Isn't it amazing?
All right, Jun-u.
You should get some sleep.
-Okay.
-Great.
Good night. Cheer up!
That...
never happened.
Thanks.
Thanks for not being immature.
Sleep tight, Soo-bin.
Don't think about anything,
and sleep well.
See you tomorrow at school.
Hey, Soo-bin. Say hello.
She'll accompany you everywhere
starting today.
Mom.
Wait for her in front of the school gate
around the dismissal time
-and come home together.
-Yes, ma'am.
Call me right away if she doesn't
come out by the time I told you.
-I'll let her homeroom teacher know.
-Okay.
And you don't have to go
to the academy from now on.
I'll find a live-in private tutor for you.
But for now, focus on studying
for the exams.
Get going.
-Take good care of her, please.
-Of course, ma'am.
Mom.
Mom, who is she?
Are you doing this so I can't see Jun-u?
Don't you think this is too much?
-I can take care of myself.
-"I can take care of myself."
You can take care of yourself?
Look what happened
because I believed that.
I don't trust you anymore. Go.
It's been five days since my breakup.
I'm on my way to school.
I'm so hungry that I can't think straight.
But I think I do look
thinner and prettier.
-Stop it already.
-What are you doing?
She's been posting videos on the internet.
What's it called?
Da-huin's Breakup Project?
Really? Wait, what's going on?
Soo-bin!
Soo-bin, what's going on?
Are you debuting as a singer?
I knew this would happen.
What do you mean?
What else? Her mom must've found out.
I bet my beauty that Jun-u will
transfer within a week.
Someone please make her shut up.
Let's go.
Did she find out?
I mean Soo-bin's mom.
You should have listened to my advice.
I didn't want Soo-bin to get hurt.
So what are you going to do now?
What's your plan?
What else can I do?
I'll keep liking Soo-bin.
I didn't have my phone,
so I couldn't talk to you.
Mom took it.
My mom hurt your feelings, right?
Did it hurt a lot?
I should have known better.
I shouldn't have brought you to my place.
It's not your fault.
I'm the one who suggested it.
I wanted to see where you live.
Still...
You were only trying to comfort me.
I was in a lousy mood
after meeting my dad.
I wanted to comfort you,
but I ended up hurting you.
Sorry.
Please don't apologize.
Because that really hurts.
Soo-bin.
Let's get through this
even if it's hard.
At a time like this,
we should focus on our school life,
study even harder,
and stay cheerful.
That's what I'll do.
And I hope you'll do the same.
Jun Dal, you sound so mature.
I'm here for you.
Even if I can't
be of much help to you...
Still, I'm here for you.
I'll always be by your side.
You'll always be
the one I like.
No matter how hard it is.
Okay?
Ms. Yoon, I don't think that's...
No. I beg you, Mr. Oh.
Please make sure Soo-bin doesn't
hang out with Jun-u.
I was supposed to be at a really
important meeting this morning,
so I thought I'd talk to you on the phone,
but I ran here in the end.
Ms. Yoon.
Jun-u and Soo-bin
are in the same class
and have been really good friends.
How could I stop them from hanging out?
Did you know they were going out?
As their teacher,
as their homeroom teacher,
how could you not do anything about it?
What was I supposed to do then?
What if Soo-bin's grades fall?
What if she fails
to get into a good university?
Don't you care
if something happens to her
while hanging out with a boy like him?
Ms. Yoon, Jun-u is not that kind of boy.
He is kind and hardworking.
Have you been encouraging
the kids to date like this?
How could an irresponsible person like you
become the kids' homeroom teacher?
How are the parents going to trust
you and send their kids to school?
Why? I mean, why?
Why do you mothers
have to do this?
I lost my temper.
I'm sorry if I crossed the line.
No.
No need to apologize to me.
Apologize to Jun-u and Soo-bin,
to the kids.
Children are not the property
of their parents. Am I wrong?
"Study.
Get into a good university.
Win by all means.
Hang out with that kid.
Don't hang out with that kid.
Dating?
That's out of the question."
You suffocate them
and intrude into their lives.
You even censor and judge their emotions.
This place
is not a prison.
And I'm not a prison guard.
When are you going to stop
telling me to monitor and control
those beautiful and kind-hearted kids?
You're losing your temper. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry too.
Hi, Ms. Yoon.
Soo-bin is in the science room.
Should I get her for you?
No. That's fine.
Bye.
Hello.
Let go.
You'll only make things worse.
Do you have something to tell me?
I won't meet Soo-bin outside of school.
Even at school,
I won't talk to her.
But...
please give her some freedom in return.
Please.
Why should I do that
just because you ask me to?
It all depends on how Soo-bin behaves.
I think I'll just focus on studying now.
That seems to be the only thing I can do
for Soo-bin right now.
Why am I so stupid?
Is Soo-bin stupid too?
What are you talking about?
Of course she's not.
Then you're not stupid either.
Soo-bin is not stupid at all,
and who does she like?
It's you.
Right?
Yoo Soo-bin.
Is your mom Sherlock or what?
It's painful.
I don't know how else to describe it.
It's just so painful.
For now, focus on the finals.
If you do well,
your mom might change her mind.
Even if Jun-u becomes a topper
in school, there's no chance.
Her mom prioritizes bloodlines
and stuff like that.
Bloodlines, my foot. Is she a dog or what?
You're okay as long as
you don't open that mouth.
You're not okay even with your mouth shut.
Likewise.
Chan-yeol, are you sick?
Why are you so down all day?
-Guys.
-What?
I like Mr. Oh.
-Who?
Oh Han-gyeol.
Gosh, why him, of all people?
This school is packed with guys.
Why does it have to be Mr. Oh?
What? Mr. Oh is handsome.
What's wrong with him?
He's the stud of Cheonbong High School!
Is it wrong for me to fall in love?
You, you, and you!
You guys are all in love.
Okay, we didn't say anything.
He's quite all right.
Why are you crying?
-Are you crying?
-Don't cry.
What do we do?
Let's begin today's class.
Let's see, where were we...
Page 106.
Everyone, let's go outside.
All right.
This feels so nice.
Oh, boy.
The sky looks so beautiful, doesn't it?
Have you guys ever looked up
at the sky lately?
-I don't think so.
-I knew it.
If someone's up there
and looking down at us,
they'll probably think we're so pitiful.
Annoying each other all the time
over our greed,
and hurting those who are precious to us.
Let's stop doing that!
I'm so tired.
Jun-u. Do you have a second to talk?
Tell me what's on your mind comfortably.
I know it's late,
but I want to apologize to you.
What you did
makes me angry,
but I know you didn't mean to hurt me.
I shouldn't have done that to you,
but I guess kissing up to Hwi-yeong
was so important to me back then.
I was so stupid.
But since that day,
I've always been feeling guilty.
I'm really sorry.
I mean it.
I don't know why I did it.
I really regret it.
I'm sorry, Jun-u.
To be honest, I blamed you a lot too.
It was really tough for me.
I'll accept your apology
for what you did wrong.
You know we're starting
a mentor-mentee program, right?
If there's anyone who wants to join,
give me your application form by today.
You can be my mentee.
I'm not becoming a mentor because of you.
I just need more points
for volunteer work. I don't have enough.
Oh, yes. Of course, I know.
If you don't do the homework I give you,
I'll quit right away.
Okay. I mean, yes, ma'am.
Study hard.
If you come within 200th in the finals,
I'll watch a movie with you.
Wait, Ro-mi.
What if...
I come within 100th?
What? Within 100th? Don't worry.
That will never happen.
I know it's very unlikely. But still,
what if I come within 100th?
I may go out with you.
Hey! How did it go?
-Go... Go out...
-Go outside?
This is low in calories.
It's just rye bread with vegetables.
This is the jerk who dumped me.
He made me a sandwich.
Is it the carrot and stick approach?
Come on, Da-huin.
That will be all for today.
Bye.
-So-ye.
-What?
-Well, I...
-Hi.
I have a favor to ask of you.
Your dance club's doing
the autumn performance, right?
Can you get some tickets for me?
Please, I'm begging you.
What is it, Sang-hun?
Is something wrong?
-What?
-Why are you bothering So-ye?
Since she's in the dance club.
By the way, is it totally over
between you and Hwi-yeong now?
Why? Because he's about to be humiliated?
Gosh, what happened to your
everlasting friendship or whatever?
-It's not like that.
-Don't try to fool me.
Or are you looking for
a new informant or something?
Should I do it?
Goodness, you should reflect
on yourself, Gi-tae.
That's why you need to be careful
who you meet.
Hey. Who are you to say that to Gi-tae?
He's regretting what he did wrong,
so don't worry.
Worry about yourself.
She's quite feisty.
Then you're not stupid either.
Soo-bin is not stupid at all,
and who does she like?
It's you.
You're pretty good at drawing.
That ladybug looks cute.
THE NAKED TREE
By the way, that was a good call too.
Not running away.
Very good.
"Yoo Soo-bin, good luck!"
I doubt that. I'm sure she was happy
because her son, Choe Jun-u, was born.
SUSEONG SAUNA
Darn it.
Gosh.
Oh, boy. This is...
Darn it!
It was you, wasn't it?
No, it really wasn't me.
Why would I post that on the website?
Why would I dig my own grave...
Right? There is something.
Gosh, I totally knew it.
Mr. Kim, please tell me the truth.
If you don't,
-I won't let you go.
-Gosh.
He's in trouble, isn't he?
His OMR sheet...
I tampered with it.
Just for two questions though.
That's huge for Hwi-yeong, you know.
I happened to find out
he made a mistake on the exam.
I didn't want to do it.
I know I shouldn't have done it,
but my family was struggling
financially at the time.
That's why
I cut a deal with Hwi-yeong's dad.
How...
Even if you were
in a financial bind, how...
-How could you?
-That's why I have to lie low.
I can't even sleep or eat these days.
What about the vice-principal?
Does he know?
No, no one knows. I did it alone.
Even Hwi-yeong doesn't know about it.
He probably thinks he marked
the correct answers by mistake.
You have no choice, then.
You need to step in
and explain what happened.
Then Hwi-yeong's parents and I
will be doomed.
If you don't do anything,
Hwi-yeong will be doomed.
You need to right the wrong.
Don't ruin his bright future.
Fix things, please.
The adults who did it
should confess to it
and pay for what they did.
Then give me some time, Mr. Oh.
MY DEAR JI-MIN
Hi, Ji-min.
Hello?
Mr. Oh, there's something
I need to tell you.
Are you all right? Are you feeling sick?
Did something happen?
I...
need some time.
Time for what?
I'm not sure if we can keep dating
and if I deserve a man like you.
What do you mean? Why wouldn't you
deserve to be with me?
I don't think I'm good enough for you.
I'm sorry.
Ji-min?
Hello?
Your drawings are quite nice.
Your grades will determine the type
of portfolio you have to prepare.
Considering your grades,
I think you'll need
a basic design portfolio.
For the schools that accept
basic design portfolios,
your portfolio and drawing test score
can take up 60 to 100 percent.
There are many art schools
you can get into
if you improve your grades
and start working on
your portfolio and application right away.
Could having a bad student record
affect admission decisions?
If I was forced to transfer, for example.
It'll put you
at a disadvantage, of course.
But every school has different
admission requirements, though.
If you're aiming
for one of the top universities,
you'll need to improve your grades more.
But there are schools
that have their own admission tests,
so those schools can be your options too.
I see.
How much do the lessons cost?
Well, that's...
Would you like a quote then?
Yes, please.
Give me that. I'll do it.
No, don't waste your energy.
Just go over there and study for the exam.
This is great
for improving my concentration.
It's because of Ji-min, isn't it?
You knew?
She told me about you.
She said you're a wonderful person,
but she doesn't feel ready yet.
What? Ready for what?
Is she going fishing?
Is she going hiking or what?
I know it's hard, but give her some time.
Like you and Soo-bin?
I know it's hard.
God, liking someone
can be such an ordeal, right?
Whether you're 18, 28,
or 38 years old, it doesn't matter.
Mr. Oh.
Are you 28?
Whether you're 48 or 58,
whether you're 68 or 78,
Whether you're 88, 98,
or 108 years old...
Jun-u, eat as much as you want.
Here, eat up.
Thank you.
Hey, I'm excited to see
how well you'll do on the finals.
You've been studying hard.
Will your grades go up this time?
Have you decided
to totally focus on studying?
I'm hoping Soo-bin's mother
will become fond of me
if I do well on the finals.
So I'm studying hard,
but I can't help wondering this.
"Even if I manage to get higher grades
or even get the highest grades,
will Soo-bin's mother ever approve of me?
Why am I making all this effort?
Is this really the best thing I can do
for myself?"
Something like that.
Come on. You need to stay strong.
Who cares about
what her mother thinks of you?
Do it to make yourself proud.
Make Choe Jun-u proud.
"I'm doing so well.
I'm making this much effort.
I'm doing great."
But what comes after that?
After that...
A new story will unfold.
Jun-u, think about the time
when you first came to our school.
You met Soo-bin and this amazing teacher
because you didn't run away back then.
Don't you agree?
Yes.
Jun-u, don't think too far ahead.
Just do it.
Now. Don't leave any regrets.
Okay?
Okay.
Good. If you were a grown-up,
I'd drink soju with you right now.
Let's at least drink some water together.
All right. Bottoms up.
It's just water.
CHEONBONG HIGH SCHOOL
ANONYMOUS BULLETIN BOARD
YOU RECEIVED AN E-MAIL FROM JOSEPH.
HWI-YEONG.
DO YOU THINK YOU GOT TO WHERE YOU ARE
ALL ON YOUR OWN?
LAST YEAR, YOU GOT A PERFECT SCORE
ON THE MATH FINAL
EVEN THOUGH YOU GOT TWO QUESTIONS WRONG.
IT'S BECAUSE YOUR HOMEROOM TEACHER
TAMPERED WITH YOUR ANSWER SHEET.
COME CLEAN ABOUT IT
AND GET WHAT YOU DESERVE,
OR YOU AND YOUR PARENTS' LIVES
WILL BE DESTROYED.
REPORT CARD
Good morning.
-Good morning.
Why isn't Mr. Kim picking up?
I'm getting worried.
Mr. Kim, you promised me
that you'd explain the situation yourself.
Mr. Kim, as a fellow teacher,
I trust you.
CHEER UP, LITTLE PEA
God, you don't want to
go to the movies with me, do you?
How could you say that?
That's what I live for.
Solve it.
COME CLEAN ABOUT IT
AND GET WHAT YOU DESERVE.
CHEER UP, LITTLE PEA
STUDY PLAN FOR FINAL EXAMS
-Mom.
-Did I wake you?
-I tried to be quiet.
-When did you get here?
I stayed up late.
I came early in the morning
to make breakfast for you.
Your exams start today, right?
I meant to come last night,
but customers stayed late
at the restaurant.
I eat well on my own.
Then why is your face so thin?
Anyway, I'm glad you're up.
I have to get going soon,
so I thought I'd leave before you wake up.
-So soon?
-I have to go open the restaurant.
Isn't Aunt Hye-yeong there?
She's not feeling so well these days.
You don't seem so well either.
Are you sick?
No. I'm in perfect health.
Let's eat.
-Eat up.
-Okay.
Start with fish. It's good for your brain.
Is Soo-bin doing well?
Is her mom very busy?
I haven't heard from her in a while.
I thought we're like sisters now.
She hasn't found out
that you two are dating, right?
No.
Tell her if you get good grades
on the finals.
Even though she might look
a tiny bit aggressive
on the outside,
she's actually a really cool person.
We might look like
completely different types,
but we get along pretty well.
I shouldn't miss my bus.
Jun-u, do well on your exams.
I'll send you some good energy
while working.
Okay. Thanks.
My son. I love you.
-I'll be going.
-Okay.
Oh, right. Say hi to Soo-bin for me.
Good luck.
Stick with the same answer for
every question you're not sure about.
I get it, Mom.
-Mom.
-Yes?
Is everything all right with you?
Yes.
-Okay. Get home safe.
-I will.
-Let's do this.
RED GINSENG WILL GIVE YOU ENERGY.
DO WELL ON THE EXAM! SOO-BIN
She's been using it.
It smells good.
It suits her.
COME CLEAN ABOUT IT...
Gosh!
Ro-mi, I got more than 50 points.
-You got 51 points.
-Really?
-Please always be my teacher.
-Be quiet.
I messed up.
It's your fault.
It's all your fault!
Did you get everything right?
I knew it.
You only got four questions wrong?
I know, right? That's strange.
What's with you? How did you do so well?
That's not okay.
I got so many wrong.
Da-huin, are you okay?
-I'm okay.
-Should I do it for you?
I'm done.
Did you do well?
Kind of. You?
Let me see.
-I'm done. You're heavy.
-Me too.
Hwi-yeong, did you get
a perfect score this time too?
See you.
-Hwi-yeong, you got a perfect score again?
-Will you be top of our year again?
-I envy you.
-Tell me about it.
Hello, son. Did you do well on the exam?
You got the highest grades
this time too, right?
Great job, my son.
Mom, what do I do?
I don't think
I can get the highest grades.
What? My goodness.
You know how to crack a joke too?
That's not funny at all, though.
I really mean it.
I got five math questions wrong.
What? Five?
So I was wondering...
if you could take care of it
this time as well.
Take care of what?
I heard you and Dad asked to have
my grades fabricated last year.
I'll need your help again.
Who said that? Hwi-yeong, who said that?
Who? Mr. Kim?
Help me.
I'm counting on you and Dad.
Hello? Hwi-yeong.
Why isn't he answering?
Hello? Honey.
The thing is...
Hwi-yeong has...
Oh, no...
Really? You got a perfect score?
Oh, my gosh!
You really got a perfect score?
Hold on. Then...
What was your score for the midterm?
Are you in the top tier
if you add those two scores?
I'll know when the rest of my grades
come out,
but I think I might make it.
I can't believe it, Soo-bin!
You did a great job.
Thank you, my daughter.
I knew you could do it if you just
grit your teeth and try your best.
Soo-bin. What do you want to eat?
I'll buy you anything.
No, let's go shopping.
I'll buy you clothes.
You wanted to go. Let's go to the mall.
I'll buy you... Oh, right.
Darn, I have a meeting this evening.
What should we do? What do I do?
It's okay, Mom.
I'll just go home and rest.
You want to rest? Okay, then.
Get some rest. I'll call you
as soon as my meeting ends
and head straight home.
Let's eat something good. Okay?
Soo-bin, I love you so much.
You need to keep going forward like this.
And get into SNU.
Do you understand? Let's go!
-What's the matter?
-I can't believe this.
-What's wrong?
-She suddenly fainted.
Hey, O-je. This is bad.
Da-huin fainted.
-I think it's because of malnutrition.
-What?
Follow me.
Da-huin!
She fell asleep.
We'll be outside.
You can go home.
I'll take Da-huin home.
Will you?
Let's go after she wakes up at least.
-Chan-yeol.
-What?
Read the room already.
Let's go, guys. Come on.
Gosh.
Leave, O-je.
I don't want to see you.
You weren't sleeping?
I told you to leave.
Leave.
Then I'll go call your friends.
It's not because I don't like you.
There you go again.
Stop saying ridiculous things.
-I'm sick and tired of it.
-To be honest...
I like someone.
Forget it. I don't want to hear it.
It's not a girl.
I'm also flustered
that I feel this type of emotion.
But there's nothing I can do about it.
I keep thinking about
what's wrong with me too.
I'm sorry, Da-huin.
It's Hwi-yeong, isn't it?
That person you like.
Leave.
I'll take you home.
-I told you to leave.
-Da-huin, let's go.
Come on, let's go home.
Are you okay?
-I can walk on my own.
-No.
Hey, O-je. What is this?
What?
That brat!
Da-huin.
Da-huin!
Hey!
What do we do?
-Oh, no...
-Da-huin.
-What do we do?
-It's okay, Da-huin.
No, but she...
-She wrote in the chat room...
-It's okay.
I didn't know she was here. I'm sorry.
No, don't be.
JUNG O-JE
Hey, O-je. Do you...
Yes.
Well...
Is Da-huin okay?
Yes, she's okay.
Okay. I'm glad to hear that.
Let's talk later.
Make sure Da-huin gets home safely.
Okay.
-Talk to you later.
-Bye.
Hello?
Is this Jun-u?
Yes.
Then I'll send you an address.
I'll see you there.
Soo-bin.
Get home safely. I need to go.
Where are you going?
Our favorite cafe.
Why are you going there?
I'll tell you later.
Soo-bin.
Keep looking forward.
Use this.
It's okay...
MA HWI-YEONG
The person you are trying to reach...
What?
Hello, I'm Choe Jun-u.
Yes, I know.
You came to see me a while ago.
Have a seat. What do you want to drink?
Did you think...
I didn't recognize you back then?
No, it wasn't like that.
How could I not recognize you?
I can tell at a glance.
Is that why you wrote me the letter?
So I'd recognize you?
I couldn't do it for a long time,
but my friend helped me
muster up the courage
so that I wouldn't have regrets.
Your girlfriend?
Yes.
I used to always run away from reality,
but I've changed because of her.
She gives me courage.
What a great friend.
You're right.
You should never run away.
It's not a good thing to do.
But you see, Jun-u,
I ran away like a coward.
No, you came back like this.
I came here to ask you for a favor.
Don't visit me like that again.
CHOE MYEONG-JUN
Thank goodness I saw this letter first.
It's all in the past, you know.
You're all grown up now,
and I have another family.
I think we each have
different paths to take.
Do you understand?
I'm sorry, Jun-u.
Could you please drive a little faster?
Jun-u!
Jun-u, are you all right?
Soo-bin.
My mom still thinks that the time
she spent with her first love
years ago was the most
beautiful moment in her life.
Back when she was 18.
Writing a letter like this
is the only thing I can do now,
but I'm here for you. Let's stay strong.
I miss you, and I like you.
-Can't you take care of it again?
-How dare you!
It turned out to be me. The informant.
Drawing, art, and art school.
Soo-bin.
I have a goal now.
Big news. People from the Office
of the Education came to get Hwi-yeong.
I admit all the allegations.
I'll cooperate with the investigation.
Happy birthday.
Let's go now. I'll walk you home.
Subtitle translation by Wayne Ryu