Jun-u!
Jun-u, are you all right?
Soo-bin.
You're all grown up now,
and I have another family.
I think we each have
different paths to take.
Where have you been?
MOM
Goodness, what should I do with you?
Come on, answer it!
MOM
I need to go to my friend
Chan-yeol's house to do my homework.
Please give me a ride.
Come on.
Can you throw the ball back to me? Hurry!
We're not done with our noodles yet.
Thanks, delivery guy.
-Do you...
-You came to our house last time
to collect empty bowls, right?
You have a great memory.
It's because you're good-looking.
You're the good-looking one.
I hear that often.
I hope you grow up
to become a brave man, kid.
Okay.
Jun-u.
Mom.
He picked up my ball for me.
Dad, let's eat noodles today. Okay?
Go on inside.
Let's go.
Bye, delivery guy.
Thank you.
What is this?
Why does he have the same name as me?
Why?
When I gave him his name,
I was thinking that maybe
it could be a way of asking
for forgiveness.
I was too immature when I had you,
and there were so many things
I couldn't give you.
I wanted to give them all to him
and raise him with all my heart.
As a way to make atonement.
Still, how could you use my name?
You really don't know
how to name your child.
My mom...
still thinks that the time
she spent with her first love
years ago was the most
beautiful moment in her life.
Back when she was 18.
She still misses that moment.
She always told me
that my dad was a kind person
and that he loved me very much.
That's what she always said.
That's why...
I longed for that person.
The person who is my dad.
I didn't get to say this earlier.
That's why I came here.
I'm sorry, Jun-u.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry.
I will never...
I will never come to see you again.
Goodbye, then.
Jun-u.
-Are you Mr. Choe Myeong-jun?
-No.
Are you Mr. Choe Myeong-jun by any chance?
Choe Myeong-jun? No, I'm not.
Dear Mr. Choe Myeong-jun.
Hello, I'm Choe Jun-u.
It's my birthday today.
It would've been nice to spend time
with you today, Dad.
But it's okay.
Mom said today is
the happiest day of my life.
Dad, I miss you.
I hope we'll meet someday.
Hello, I'm Choe Jun-u.
Now that I'm writing this letter,
I don't know where to start.
I'm writing you to tell you
that I missed you.
I've always wanted to know
what kind of person my dad is.
I'll watch you from afar
only once in a while.
And please remember that I'm Choe Jun-u.
Please remember just that.
The feeling of missing him.
That's all I should remember.
Just that feeling.
-Honey!
-Where the hell have you been?
You completely ruined your exam.
How could you mess it up on purpose?
You obviously knew the correct answers.
Are you out of your mind?
Can't you just take care of it again?
Will Mr. Oh not accept bribes?
What should we do, then?
-Hwi-yeong!
-You brat.
You're out to get me, aren't you?
You want to waste away all the money
I've earned by working like a dog.
You're itching to waste it all away!
-Aren't you?
-Honey! Honey, please.
Hit me instead.
-Hit me instead, please.
-All right, Park Geum-ja.
I'll teach you a lesson first.
All you do is drink at home.
How could you not pay
any attention to your son?
How dare you!
Let go. I said, let go.
Let go!
-You insolent shit.
-Yes, I am.
It's obviously because I take after you.
I'm human trash.
Why you little... How dare you!
You see,
I've always loathed you
since I was little.
I've always thought
I should never become like you.
But I've caught myself becoming like you
without even realizing it.
A monster who stomps
on those weaker than him
and only cares about his own gain,
no matter what it takes.
Human trash.
I've already turned into that monster,
and I can't undo it.
Even if I want to,
I can't go back to the time
when I wasn't like this.
I wanted to become
a better person than you,
but I can't anymore.
You shit, how dare you say
such a thing to your father?
-Honey, please.
-Let go.
-Please stop.
-Let go!
If you hit Mom one more time,
I won't let it slide.
Hwi-yeong, get out of here.
Run. Hurry.
Hey.
Isn't it her?
Gosh, it is her. Kim Ji-min.
Isn't this that place?
Why are you trying to find
Mr. Oh's girlfriend?
To do something mean to her?
No.
I have a plan you don't know.
By the way, why are we whispering?
Hey.
-Chan-yeol.
-Yes?
Can I use your phone?
Sure, here you go.
Hi, Jun-u. It's me, Soo-bin.
When you arrive at your part-time job,
check where you usually park your bike.
-This one is good.
-Okay.
Gosh, I'm so sleepy.
-Soo-bin, get some fresh air.
-Soo-bin!
Goodness, she's studying so hard.
Hey there!
Hey, my gosh.
Have you eaten yet?
Oh, I'm all right.
My gosh, my grandma's hot pot
is super delicious.
I'll be quick. Thanks, guys.
All right, be safe.
I can't believe Soo-bin is doing this.
That is true love.
What do you know about love?
Let's go.
I told you not to do it!
Don't. Don't you dare!
Stay away from Soo-bin.
Don't even call her. I have to go.
Soo-bin.
I was at Chan-yeol's place.
We did homework together.
Yes, I heard.
-I'll go wash up.
-Okay. Oh, wait.
Why didn't you tell me
about meeting your dad?
Soo-bin. I don't know
what he said to you,
but it's all a lie.
He's just mad at me because we fought.
Don't worry about it, okay?
-Okay.
-Good.
I'm serious.
Your dad and I don't have any problems.
So don't worry,
and just focus on studying.
Okay?
We need to celebrate,
but it's getting late now.
So how about we go on a trip together?
How about Jeju Island?
-Sure, if you want to.
-Okay, great.
Then I'll come up with a plan.
All right.
Go wash up.
What's he doing?
What are you doing here?
What's so funny about that?
I think it's funny
that I'm hungry in this kind of situation.
Hi, Jun-u. It's me, Soo-bin.
When you arrive at your part-time job,
check where you usually park your bike.
Jun-u, you must've been surprised
to see me earlier.
Actually, Hwi-yeong let me use his phone,
so I called you in a hurry.
And I happened to overhear
your conversation with your dad.
I'm sorry.
I know I wasn't supposed to hear it.
You must be feeling bad.
I know how you'd feel
so well.
It breaks my heart.
When I was feeling sad because of my dad,
you comforted me.
I want to be able to comfort you too.
But I can't be with you.
Writing a letter like this
is the only thing I can do now,
but I'm here for you.
I'm always rooting for you.
In the morning, during the day,
and even when I'm sleeping at night.
So...
let's try our best to stay strong.
I miss you, and I like you.
A lot.
From Soo-bin.
JEONGHO APARTMENTS
Ji-min, how was your day?
Did you study a lot?
All right.
Take your time and give it some thought.
I'll wait for you.
I'll wait
until she becomes fine.
Good night.
She's still up.
I will
try harder...
to become someone you can depend on.
Good night.
Are you on a diet?
Da-huin is on a diet these days,
and you're her boyfriend.
Hwi-yeong.
Eat.
You weren't like this before.
Why have you changed so much?
Enjoy.
Bye.
Hi, O-je.
Hey.
Why do you look so down?
I heard you and Da-huin made up.
Yes, we did.
Can we talk for a minute?
Sure.
I should have told you first.
Sorry.
You don't have to tell me.
It's up to you.
I'm weird, right?
Not really. It's just how you feel.
Yes, but...
I'm not sure what I'm really feeling.
It's confusing.
I was trying to figure it out.
Then, things turned out like this.
Hwi-yeong.
Thanks.
-Did you make a phone call?
-Yes.
I didn't pick up
because I thought it was you.
I got it yesterday.
-O-je? Really?
-Is this true?
That's so weird.
Hey. Why is it weird?
He just likes another person.
You're even weirder.
Just go back to playing games.
Wow, Pil-sang.
That's unexpected.
Hwi-yeong, did you see it?
O-JE HAS A CRUSH ON HWI-YEONG.
What page is it?
No idea.
I heard it in the nurse's office.
When O-je said that, Da-huin...
Seo-jin.
Will you shut up?
That little...
It's okay. Let her be.
She'll stop soon.
Hey, don't let her get to you.
Da-huin.
You're okay, right?
O-je.
What happened? I thought
we were meeting this morning.
You said you'd carry my pots.
Oh, sorry. I had to take care of O-dong.
Mom and Dad went to the morning market.
Come with me. There are many things
you should carry for me.
We're going to the gardening room.
-Okay.
You can go now.
-O-je.
-Yes?
Stop feeling bad for me.
You don't have to.
And stop wearing that face.
You look better when you smile. Smile.
Okay.
You should go.
Gosh, what is this feeling though?
I still get flutters.
JUNG O-JE IN CLASS THREE
LIKES MA HWI-YEONG,
THE GUY WHO FABRICATED HIS GRADES!
Hey, Jun-u.
Mr. Oh.
Is something wrong?
Why do you look so serious?
You're making me nervous.
Go on and tell me.
I...
visited an academy.
Why?
You know, that ladybug...
A ladybug academy?
What does that place teach?
Drawing.
Drawing?
By drawing, do you mean...
You're saying that you've decided
what you want to do in university?
Drawing, art,
and art school.
Hooray!
So, does that mean you're
really going to start preparing?
That's a great idea.
I knew it when I saw you
draw that ladybug.
You've got talent. Really.
Thank you. But I haven't decided
for sure yet...
No. You should hurry up and start
before it's too late.
Well, shouldn't you learn
thoroughly, from the basics?
Yes. That's why I've been
searching around here and there,
but it's quite difficult,
considering my situation.
I know.
Right, I have a friend
from my military service,
and he teaches students preparing
for art school. Do you want me to ask him?
Well, he's not as handsome as me,
but he's good.
I heard he's quite famous in that field.
I know, preparing for art school
is not an easy task.
Still,
I will help you.
Will that be okay?
Of course.
Thank you.
I'll put in a word for you,
so go visit that academy.
You need to push forward confidently
once you've made up your mind.
Jun-u, let's do this. Okay?
Soo-bin.
Did you not get any sleep last night?
I didn't get any sleep either
after reading your letter.
I was so touched.
It was nothing.
I thought about what I could do for you,
and that was the only thing
that came to mind.
Shall we do it again when
we have something to say next time?
Sometimes when it's too difficult
to talk about something.
Okay.
Soo-bin.
I have a goal now.
About what I'll do from now on.
What is it?
I haven't thought of the details yet,
but since I like to draw,
I'll set it as my goal and study for it.
Really?
I'm glad to hear that.
I really like it when you draw too.
I'll sincerely root for you.
It's all thanks to you.
You're the one who made me
want to live a better life.
And even have a dream.
You have
changed so much.
I'm proud of you.
I know.
Oh, right.
What?
I promised your mom that
I wouldn't meet you like this.
I should keep that promise.
You can go first.
Okay.
Jun-u.
You are
a really good person.
So-ye.
I came because I thought
you'd skip lunch if I didn't come.
What is it you want to say?
I wanted to thank you
for saying that to Sang-hun last time.
Okay.
See you.
So-ye.
I'm trying really hard.
To become a person
you won't be ashamed of.
So please give me another chance.
Please give me another chance.
What about the exams? Did you do well?
Aren't you going to take that?
I heard the rumor about you.
You're free to like whomever you want,
but don't get me involved in it.
Don't worry, that won't happen.
It's just a personal problem.
Sir, do you know of anyone who teaches
students preparing for art school?
Mr. Oh!
Mr. Oh, this is an emergency.
Oh, hi. You can go first.
People from the Office of Education
are here.
Darn it.
Gosh, big news.
People from the Office of Education
came to get Hwi-yeong.
I can't believe it.
It's over for Hwi-yeong now.
This is so scary.
Guys, move over.
Hey! What are you guys doing?
Go back to your classrooms. Now!
Sang-hun, go to your classroom. Now.
Yes, sir. As you wish, sir.
Hwi-yeong.
Were you aware
that your grades were fabricated
in the second semester last year?
Wait, I can explain.
Back then, Hwi-yeong didn't know--
CHANGES ON THE ANSWER SHEET
We want Hwi-yeong to answer.
I found out recently.
I admit all the allegations.
I'll cooperate with the investigation.
If it's found true that
your grades were fabricated,
yourself, the teacher who was
involved in the tampering,
and even your parents will be punished.
Lastly,
you will be given zero points
for that subject.
Hey, you must be feeling good about this.
Was it you?
What? Do you think I did it?
Oh, boy.
I should've done it.
But sadly, it wasn't me.
I'm telling you the truth.
What's with you, Jun-u?
Has the hatred turned
into friendship or what?
That serves him right.
He should be punished
for what he did.
I was just wondering if you did it.
Hello, Dad? It's me, Sang-hun.
What the...
Cut the nonsense.
Natural resources are subject to change.
The technology standards or...
Take petroleum for example.
In the past, we didn't have
any technology to utilize it,
so we just left it as it was.
But how about now?
It's a crucial natural resource for us.
That's how the values can change.
And natural resources...
Sir.
Yes, Mr. Oh.
How could this happen?
I really didn't see this coming.
God, this will ruin
my 25-year teaching career.
I won't get fired, will I?
What do I do if that happens?
I'll never become a principal.
No. That won't happen.
Let's cooperate with the investigation
and sort things out.
I've done so much for this school.
They won't do that to me.
Mr. Oh, I'd like to consult you
about something.
Oh, really?
Sure, anytime. Are you at school now?
I'd like to meet you outside of school.
Sure, sounds good. Where?
Hey, Chan-yeol.
I'm here. Are you not here yet?
Mr. Oh, did you meet her?
You little... I'm going to scold you.
Ji-min.
I don't want to see you again.
Please leave.
I will leave.
But can we talk for a minute?
Mr. Oh.
You see, I'm really
not good enough for you.
I'm working part-time jobs
because I can't get a full-time job.
And I practically have to support
everyone in my family.
You have a stable job,
and you're a good guy,
so I want to keep dating you.
But the more I let this go on,
the more insecure I'll feel.
What are you talking about?
Don't think that way.
I'm sorry. I have to get back to work.
Enjoy this drink and leave.
Ji-min.
Thanks, Chan-yeol. I met her.
Good luck this time, Mr. Oh.
Gosh, what's wrong with my eyes?
Why is that a problem?
We can just date. Why does it have to be
so complicated?
What's up?
Right. You're working, obviously.
It turned out to be me.
The informant.
It was me.
I called my dad earlier just to be sure
and found out he's the one who did it.
It's all in the past.
Why is he digging it up now?
What about your dad's job?
Haven't you been quiet about it
because of your dad's job?
He quit.
He said he can retaliate now
because he has nothing to lose.
I wish he had told me.
And why quit his job?
Had he told me back then, I would've...
God, I don't know.
Whatever, this is actually good.
I feel so much better now.
What? What is it?
You don't feel better, right?
Yes, I do.
I totally feel better now.
Gosh, it's so gratifying.
What do I do now?
You should get going.
Yes.
I should go home.
What?
Hey, Jun-u.
Gi-tae, what brings you here?
Have you seen Hwi-yeong by any chance?
This jerk's going on
about Hwi-yeong again.
It's not that.
He was acting weird earlier.
He sent me a text saying sorry,
and I haven't heard from him since.
He didn't even go to the academy.
So what?
Well, I was just wondering if he came by.
I'll be off, then.
Bye.
Ma Hwi-yeong...
Okay, let's find him.
He's probably gone home
after wandering for a little while.
-I mean, it's pouring now.
-Gosh, I'm so worried.
His phone is off too.
What if something happened to him?
I'm sure he's fine.
Don't make such a fuss.
Hey, O-je.
Hey, what are you up to?
I'm...
Hwi-yeong?
I'm sure he'll go home.
Lastly, you will be given zero points
for that subject.
That bastard. We worried for nothing.
Hwi-yeong, let's go back.
Let go. Let go of me.
Let go, you bastard!
He still hasn't come to his senses.
Now we know he's fine. Let's go back.
Just let a piece of trash like me
be smashed to bits.
What?
Are you happy watching me fall?
Is this fun for you?
Get lost, you bastard!
You guys go back first.
Gi-tae, let's go!
What are you doing here?
The guys were worried about you.
What do you care?
You're still a coward. You know that?
Are you trying to be forgiven this way?
I'm not trying to be forgiven.
You're still full of pride.
Then what's torturing you so much?
Is it so humiliating to say sorry to me?
Is it so hard to own up
to what you did wrong?
Do you know why I'm just standing by
and watching you?
It's because I feel
genuinely sorry for you.
You're suffering
because you know you did wrong.
Stop running away and face it.
Take responsibility
and put things right yourself.
Stop being such a coward.
This is your last chance.
Damn it!
JUN DAL'S REAL BIRTHDAY
Is this your birthday?
Yes.
But there was a different date
on the class bulletin board.
My mom registered my birth late.
Let's celebrate your real birthday
together this year.
Okay. I can't wait.
JUN DAL'S REAL BIRTHDAY
It's Jun-u's birthday today.
Hi.
-Did you get home safely last night?
-Yes.
Guys.
Hey.
I have something to tell you all.
I'll tell Mr. Oh that I'm stepping
down as class president today.
I don't think I need to explain
why I don't deserve the position.
And I believe Jun-u will
manage the class just as well.
I'm sorry I can't finish my term.
Hey, Hwi-yeong.
Who says you can quit?
Shouldn't you ask our opinions too?
I don't think that's necessary.
Hwi-yeong.
Can we talk?
You don't have to comfort me.
I'm not trying to comfort you.
I'm just worried about you.
You don't look okay right now.
"Little Boy Hwi-yeong."
Let's not do that anymore.
We should stop pretending we're close.
Why do you say that?
Yes, I was angry at you.
I couldn't understand you.
But we're still friends.
I can't just sit back.
It gets like this in summer.
I'm fine.
Hwi-yeong.
Thanks for your concern though.
Let him be.
Let him continue to be a stuck-up kid.
That's Hwi-yeong.
Don't worry too much, Soo-bin.
She's right.
Focus on protecting your love.
Guys, can you do me a favor?
What is it?
Actually, it's Jun-u's birthday today.
There's something I wanted to get him.
If I buy it,
can you guys hand it over to him?
You're such a coward.
Can't you even give him
a birthday present yourself?
Why don't you just
completely give up on him?
Why? Do you still want him?
That won't happen. Never ever.
I wouldn't say "never ever."
Really. Never ever.
Ro-mi is right.
It's his birthday after all.
You should give him your present yourself.
Totally.
Look, guys.
Is it time for
Chan-yeol's Special Unit again?
Please. Just this once.
-It's her boyfriend's birthday.
-That's right.
It's his first birthday
since they started going out.
We beg you, ma'am. Please.
-Please.
-You're so petty.
How much do you want? We can pay you.
-Hey!
-Hey! Seriously.
I'm sorry.
I can read tarot cards for you.
I'm very good at it.
Or is there anyone you want to find?
-We can find anyone.
-She's right.
Sorry.
Have you never been in love?
-Stop.
-I mean...
If you have, you should understand
how Soo-bin would feel right now.
She's right.
-Please.
-Follow me.
-Hey!
-I can't believe this.
-Let's hurry!
-We have only an hour.
-We don't have time. Let's start.
-Okay.
What are you guys doing?
You should look pretty
when you meet your boyfriend.
She's right. We'll make you look
so pretty that Jun-u passes out.
Hurry up.
-Oh, my.
-Here we go.
You're scaring me.
-It hurts.
-Just put up with it.
-What?
-Do this.
Why isn't Ro-mi here yet?
That unreliable girl must have bailed out.
What do you take me for?
Ta-da.
-It's so pretty.
-You have good taste.
It's pretty.
When Soo-bin comes in, he'll come out...
Why isn't O-je here yet?
-Guys.
-You're late.
Give me the candles.
-Hurry.
-Come on.
ART SCHOOL PREPARATION COURSE
-Hi, Mom.
-Jun-u, I'm sorry.
It's your birthday, and I didn't
get to make seaweed soup for you.
It's okay.
It's no big deal.
Don't worry about it.
How are you doing?
Is the restaurant doing well?
Yes, of course.
You're leaving for work early today.
Yes. I need to stop by somewhere.
Okay, Mom. I'll call you in the evening.
Okay, my baby. Work hard.
Happy birthday.
Gosh.
Two, three.
-Happy birthday to you
-Happy birthday dear Jun-u
-Here.
-How did you guys know?
-Blow them out.
-Many happy returns.
-Happy birthday.
-Congratulations.
Thank you.
Thank you, guys.
We didn't get any gifts, though.
That's fine.
However, there is one gift
that all of us prepared together.
All right, then. Come on in!
Jun-u.
Happy birthday.
You shouldn't be here.
-Let's go.
-Hold on.
It's your birthday today.
Consider it a special chance.
-That's right.
-Yes.
Jun-u, just stay with her for a bit.
Oh, boy, we should get going.
-Right.
-We should leave now.
-I'll leave the cake here.
-Let's go.
-See you.
-Hold this.
Let's go.
-See you.
-Bye.
Bye.
-Let's go.
-Hey, watch your step.
Don't worry, I'll go home soon.
Where's her bodyguard?
She said she'd be counting the time.
Did she just leave?
I guess she read our minds.
Then shall we go to my dad's restaurant?
It's my treat.
-Sure.
-Gosh.
Da-huin, don't you even feel
uncomfortable?
What's the big deal?
We're just eating tteokbokki, right?
Let's go.
Will those two be all right?
I wanted to give you a birthday gift
and cheer you on.
Thank you.
Let's go now. I'll walk you home.
Let's stay for a while longer.
I came all the way here.
Let's go.
After I see you opening this.
You promised your mom
not to come here again.
I'll put this inside.
Do you know
how hard it was for me to come here?
I felt really afraid and guilty too,
but I still mustered up the courage
to come here.
It's your birthday today.
I was worried you'd be alone.
Isn't it okay for me to be with you today?
I'll take you home.
Fine.
I can go alone.
Soo-bin.
Do you know how much
I'm holding back and enduring
this situation right now?
You know well.
But if you come here,
what does that make me?
It's really hard for me too,
but I'm still enduring it.
So...
I'm sorry.
Thank you for today.
It was the best birthday of my life.
-Really?
-Mr. Oh sent me here.
Are you Choe Jun-u?
You're really talented,
just like Han-gyeol said.
Let's split them up.
Could you transfer Jun-u
to another school?
Please do it for me.
Soo-bin, I'm having a really tough day.
I know it's tough for you now,
but after time passes, don't you think
things will become better?
Ji-min, whether you see me or not,
that's up to you to decide.
Why didn't you tell me all this time?
Jun-u.
Since I knew you'd be hurt.
How could I tell you?
Leaving you like this
until you got to this state.
That's what I regret the most.
What in the world is this emotion?
I hated him so much,
and I still can't forgive him. But...
Hwi-yeong.
Subtitle translation by Wayne Ryu