Jun-u.
You little punk.
I thought you were the vice-principal!
The back door was hard to open.
Didn't he transfer to another school?
You little rascal.
STUDENT GRADE REPORT
Is this how...
Why did you pretend you were leaving?
Come here. I'm glad you're back.
Welcome back.
Come over here. How could you fool me?
Let's give a big hand
to Choe Jun-u, who has returned!
Welcome back, Jun-u.
You said you were leaving. Were you lying?
You know, it's not cool to run away.
Jun-u, you can go sit in that empty seat.
Here you go, Hwi-yeong.
-Thank you.
-Congratulations.
CHOE JUN-U
Mom, I really don't want to go.
Then you should've gotten
top-tier grades in the first place.
Consider yourself lucky to be
taking Mr. Son's level test.
It's because of all your kissing up
that day.
You even brought Hwi-yeong's mom flowers.
What's wrong with kissing up?
I can do worse than that.
As long as my daughter goes to SNU.
You better pass the level test. Got it?
You can do it.
You can do it. You're my daughter, right?
"I'll make it to
Seoul National University." Say it.
Yoo Soo-bin! You can do it, Yoo Soo-bin!
HEY, JEONG-HU. HOW HAVE YOU BEEN?
CONGRATULATIONS
MOST IMPROVED SCHOOL
Was it that bad?
Running away.
Is that funny?
Of course it's funny.
It didn't sound like you at all.
I'm glad you found it funny.
Everyone says I'm boring.
I guess I've improved.
Hwi-yeong, don't mess with me.
What?
As long as you leave me alone,
I won't do anything.
It's too bothersome.
"Don't mess with me"?
You bastard.
What are you guys doing?
Soo-bin.
-What about the literature--
-Jun-u.
The research on the list of references
that you did, it was good.
We finished the assignment, thanks to you.
You just submitted the assignment?
I was going to look it over for you.
I even found some papers for reference.
Oh, really? You should've told me.
That's too bad.
Thanks.
Next time, tell me before you submit it.
I'll review it for you.
-Let's go.
-You can go first.
I need to go to Class Five.
Why are you so surprised?
By the way, that was a good call too.
Not running away.
CHOE JUN-U
Very
good.
Did you look into it?
Yes.
It seems like Jun-u's transfer
was conditional.
When he came here.
To leave if he gets involved
in another incident.
Really?
Then he'll have to leave
if something bad happens again.
-How?
-You should come up with that.
As soon as possible.
Hwi-yeong.
Why are you trying to chase Jun-u away?
He won't be a problem
even if you leave him alone.
He just gets in the way.
All the time.
That doesn't mean it's okay to lie.
"Piece of trash"?
Shouldn't you call yourself that?
He's annoying.
The number you have dialed
is not available at the moment.
Please leave a message after the beep.
Jeong-hu, why aren't you
answering the phone?
Is something wrong?
Do you still hang out with--
Hey, wait.
Let me see. It's not broken.
What a relief.
I just saved myself some money.
-Thank you.
-Okay.
Jun-u.
Yes?
Is everything going okay?
Are there any difficulties
or things you want to tell me?
-No.
-Really?
I see.
Hey, hold on. Well...
I know that you're not opening up
to me yet.
But still, if you face any problems,
don't keep them bottled up
and try to solve them on your own.
You can talk to me openly about them.
You know, I've had a lot more
life experience than you, right?
Yes, sir.
"Yes, sir." That sounded so insincere.
-The bell just rang.
-I know.
Who am I kidding?
I'm barely managing
to take care of myself.
S/S SEASON 30% OFF
DON'T MISS THIS CHANCE!
Season...
30% OFF
I don't have any money. Stop it.
The cold air mass from Siberia
affects us in the winter.
In the summer...
I did it.
I stole that money.
Is he telling the truth?
-Yes.
-I told you.
I said I was right.
My son would never do that.
As you said...
I will transfer to another school.
Jun-u.
Jun-u, why...
Why would you do such a thing?
It wasn't you, right?
-I'm sorry, Mom.
-I'm...
-Got it, Ro-mi?
-Yes, ma'am.
That's why this happens.
On page 68,
there's a list of the air masses
that affect Korea.
The Siberian air mass
affects us in wintertime,
whereas maritime tropical air masses
affect us in the summertime.
When maritime tropical air masses
meet the Okhotsk High,
they form...
-Nice!
-Friday?
-Hey, come on.
-Get out of here.
It's a hot mess in here.
All right, guys. The class has begun.
Pil-sang, let go of Chan-yeol.
Gyu-nam, break them up.
Da-huin, it's time to go to school.
You're always sleepy
because you starve yourself. Da-huin!
Soo-bin, wake her up.
Guys, let's study.
Guys.
Pil-sang, Mr. Oh is here.
I'm sorry, Mr. Oh.
I was so focused on my book.
That's all right. No worries.
All right, then.
Today, we'll...
Gi-tae.
I'd like you and Jun-u to switch seats.
-Pardon?
-Why?
Just for the time being.
Still, the two of us want to make
some fond memories together.
No, that won't happen.
But Hwi-yeong told me to sit here.
Gi-tae really is Hwi-yeong's minion.
The class president told you to sit there?
-Yes.
-I see.
Mr. Oh, I'll get it sorted out
next time we change seats.
All right.
As the class president, make sure
they're all evenly spread out.
-Yes, sir.
-Good.
Did we cover up to page 40 last time?
Okay. Page 40...
But you two should still
switch seats, just until then.
I just think it'll be better.
Come on, Gi-tae. Let's do it, okay?
I'm your homeroom teacher.
Show me some respect, please?
I feel so bad for him.
That's pretty pathetic.
Show me some respect, please.
-Yes, Mr. Oh. I'll switch.
-Great.
Jun-u, switch seats with Gi-tae.
-Gi-tae.
-Yes?
Thank you.
I should listen to you, of course.
All right, guys.
Then we'll start from where...
Okay. Just a moment.
He seems so annoyed, doesn't he?
Gosh, Oh Han-gyeol seems
completely bewildered.
What's the matter with me?
Why am I groveling so much?
I'm their teacher, for God's sake.
I'm an adult.
All right.
Sorry, guys.
Let's get started.
Mr. Oh, about our English
performance assessment...
You haven't told us the range
for the listening test.
Well, actually...
-No way! Why?
-Hush, the vice-principal.
What's the matter?
It is a performance assessment.
Wasn't the listening test replacing it?
That's what we did last year.
The listening test isn't the only way
to assess your performance.
We want to be original, so we'll do
a free-talking test instead.
-No.
-No way.
-Unbelievable.
-No!
What will be the topic?
The topic will be...
-This is crazy.
-Gosh, how original.
-It's so lame.
-Goodness.
It's so original.
All right,
I'll tell you how it'll be done.
You'll converse freely in pairs
for three minutes.
The study leader will
randomly pick your partner.
You're okay with it, right?
Me?
-Team up with me.
-Be quiet.
Oh Han-gyeol, be calm.
Relax. Be confident...
and graceful.
Look, he's smiling.
Gosh, he's really losing it.
I told you. We need to find
a nice lady for him soon.
Come on, guys. Just accept it.
This assessment is
not even that important.
-Sir.
-Yes.
Is my class the only one that
hasn't submitted the budget plan?
Give me a moment. I'll quickly--
It's okay. Your class president
submitted it this morning.
-Hwi-yeong did?
-Yes.
You're so lucky.
We're all swamped, but Hwi-yeong
takes care of things like this,
gets the highest marks
on exams and boosts the average,
and even looks after
all of his classmates.
I know you're just an assistant teacher,
but this must be your lucky year.
You're right.
Hey, Hwi-yeong. What's up?
Mr. Oh.
About the free-talking test...
Please reconsider.
I'm fine with it,
but three days won't be
enough time for the other students.
Plus, the midterm's
just around the corner too.
But this is a test too.
Completing the assignment
within the given amount of time.
-That's how the assessment works.
-Right.
Still, don't you think it'd be risky
to randomly divide into pairs?
This will affect our academic records.
Hwi-yeong, you'll do a great job
no matter who your partner is.
Well, it'll be great if those
who aren't so good at English
can help each other out.
Yes, understood.
Oh, Hwi-yeong.
Just a second.
Well...
Come here for a second.
As for the class budget plan,
it is my job to write and submit it.
It would've been nice
if you had consulted me about it first.
The headteacher asked me to do it.
I thought it was okay
since you're our assistant teacher.
Even so, I am your homeroom teacher
at the moment.
I'll be careful from now on.
Mr. Oh, don't complicate things
for yourself.
If you take on more work,
there will be more things
for you to fill their teacher in on
when he returns.
You're probably right.
-Yes, probably.
-Right.
By the way, when will
their homeroom teacher come back?
I'm not sure.
Hello, sir. How are you feeling?
I'm doing very well, thanks to you.
This place is like a nice hotel.
-Hwi-yeong is doing well, right?
-Yes.
About the thing I asked you
to look into a little while ago...
I'm wondering if it's coming along well.
You don't need to worry.
My gosh. Thank you, Mr. Ma.
I'll take care of the rest, then.
Eat up.
We don't even have time to study
for exams. What? Free-talking?
That's what I'm saying.
It's always the incompetent teachers
that are overly eager.
I'd say Mr. Oh is pretty competent,
don't you think?
Okay, fine.
Gosh, that newbie.
Will he be all right here?
-Because he stole the watch?
-Yes.
He said he didn't do it.
We have no way of knowing.
How can we believe what he says?
Exactly.
They found the watch in his locker.
Why are you taking his side?
-I am not.
-You are.
I am not taking his side.
Hey, Da-huin, it's O-je.
It's O-je. O-je.
Hey, O-je.
Over here.
There aren't any seats left except here.
What? We saved his seat for nothing.
Why did he sit there?
Who cares?
What do you mean, "Who cares?"
She's right.
Do you like basketball?
Yes, I do.
I'm good at it too.
You know, our class is like...
a company.
Hwi-yeong's the chairman,
and the others are his minions.
When he gets up once he's done eating,
they'll probably get up with him.
Isn't that funny?
But that's just how men are, you know.
They always want to decide
who's stronger than who.
What about you?
-What?
-Then what are you like?
What do you think?
What are they doing?
They want to see whose face is smaller?
Well... Just...
"Just"?
Just...
a nice basketball man?
Correct.
What's a nice basketball man?
I've never heard that before.
Hey, Jun-u.
I heard you were popular
at your previous school.
You must've been good
at a lot of things other than this.
Sang-hun, what's your problem?
We're eating.
Scram.
Sorry, O-je.
Eat up.
What did he say?
He said to eat my peas.
Well, he's right about that.
Are you done eating?
Slow down.
Go ahead.
You're anxious, aren't you?
About what happened.
You're scared I might tell Jun-u.
About what?
Look at this guy playing dumb.
That's right. You should.
That makes it more fun.
Sang-hun.
You know what?
-What?
-When you laugh like that,
it's really annoying.
I don't know what you're talking about,
but do as you wish.
Rat me out or whatever.
The girls' rep and the guys' rep
will play rock-paper-scissors.
The losing side puts in their names first,
and the winning side picks them. Okay?
-Hey.
There are more guys than girls.
-That's not right.
-Tough luck.
-The leftover guys can pair up.
-Darn it.
I'm getting very nervous.
Now, begin!
-You have to win.
-Good luck.
-You can do it.
Rock, paper,
-scissors!
-Scissors!
-Yes!
-Nice!
-Again!
Come on.
Rock, paper, scissors!
It's okay.
-Rock, paper, scissors!
Okay. The guys, take out a piece
of paper and put your name on it
and give it to me.
Okay. Next is So-ye.
Let's see.
Drum roll, please.
It's Gi-tae?
You're so lucky.
He's really good at English.
-Next, Da-huin.
-Next.
Hey. Aren't you going to pray?
I prayed during a gym class the other day
and got paired up with Pil-sang.
Then don't.
Anyone but Pil-sang.
Hey. I don't want you either.
-So what?
-Right back at you.
Is it Pil-sang again?
-O-je.
-Oh. It's me.
Let's do our best, Da-huin.
Okay.
Next. Ro-mi.
-Why? Who did you get? Ro-mi!
-Who is it?
-Pil-sang!
Oh my!
Yes!
-Hey!
-Ro-mi!
Ro-mi!
That's going to be so much fun!
Okay, Chan-yeol.
Chan-yeol's turn.
Darn it.
It's bad. You go first.
Okay. Then I'll pick first.
What a unique shape.
Here, for you.
It's okay.
Take it. I have a lot.
Who's in charge of recycling
in this class?
Hey. What are you doing here?
It's my turn to do this.
Aren't you preparing
for the free-talking test?
I will.
Who picked me?
I guess no one picked me.
CHOE JUN-U
When are you free?
Not now.
What? I picked him,
and he's playing hard-to-get?
Just so you know,
I'm not playing hard-to-get.
I need to get to work right now.
Well...
I'm still too new to ask for a day off
for personal reasons.
I don't have time right now either.
I have to go.
Okay.
I'll message you later.
Jun-u, what's your dream?
My dream?
I don't know.
What?
What? Then how...
Fine.
Then think of anything for now
since we have to take the test. Okay?
See you.
Bye.
Who hasn't turned it in yet?
Are you done? I'll turn it in.
If you're done, pass it forward.
Hold on.
Why is it taking so long to write a name?
Hurry up.
Jun-u is kind of cute.
He even knows how to use a secret code.
About the list of references.
I checked all the cited parts...
Hey, Hwi-yeong!
How could you just leave? We're partners.
Oh, right. I'm looking forward to it.
What should we do?
First, let's go to the snack shop
and talk over a cup of latte.
Sorry, but I have to go now.
I'll make the script by tomorrow,
including yours.
All you have to do is memorize it.
Let's check it together
on the day of the test. Bye.
Hey. How could you just leave?
Do you know what my dream is?
You don't know anything about me.
Don't worry.
I'll make you get a perfect score.
Just focus on preparing for the midterm.
Hey, Hwi-yeong. Hey!
Thanks!
Hello.
Yeong-bae, why are you so late?
She's been waiting for a long time.
-Mom.
-You're late to work.
Tell me about it.
He's always five minutes late.
Jun-u, you should know better.
You're being paid for this.
You should arrive
at least 15 minutes early,
pull yourself together,
and be ready to work.
Mom, is something wrong?
Why did you suddenly come here?
I had some business nearby,
so I dropped by.
You should've gone home then.
Why did you come here?
You're working here.
Why would I go to an empty house?
I have to go back soon anyway.
Let's go eat.
I have to work.
The owner said you can go.
Of course, I helped her persuade him.
-This is delicious.
-Is it?
Have some, Jun-u.
Hey,
you're not hanging your head at school
because of that watch incident, are you?
Don't worry, I'm not.
Good. The truth always gets revealed
one day.
Right.
You didn't hear from the kids
from the previous school, right?
How about Jeong-hu? Shin Jeong-hu.
Doesn't he call you?
No.
Well, he shouldn't
if he has a sense of shame.
You were forced to transfer
because of him.
Jeong-hu isn't a bad kid.
-You know that.
-Of course.
I adored Jeong-hu so much.
But whenever I think about that day...
It feels so unfair
and upsetting.
Mom.
You promised not to cry.
Okay, I won't cry.
Anyway, you should really...
just focus on studying from now on.
Don't get caught up in anything
unnecessary. Do you understand?
I understand.
Promise me.
I promise.
Don't cry.
Mom. You came because you were
worried about me, didn't you?
You didn't have any business here.
-No.
-Come on, don't lie.
I'm not lying.
Let's eat.
These are so difficult.
SON JAE-YEONG MATHEMATICS
You should try your best, Soo-bin.
You should go, or you'll be late.
Let me walk a bit more with you.
I told you to wear your hair like this.
So people can see your forehead.
-Like this.
-I'll do it.
-No, it looks better like this.
-I can do it.
Hi. Hello, ma'am.
Oh, is she from your class?
Hi. I'm Jun-u's mom.
Oh, hello, ma'am.
It's nice to meet you.
We're in a bit of a hurry, so...
I'll see you again.
Goodbye.
Who is that?
He's good-looking.
He's a guy who transferred to our school.
-Mom.
-Gosh, this is embarrassing.
Her handbag looked real.
That handbag was fake.
She must be embarrassed right now.
Well, everyone carries around
fakes these days.
I heard a real one costs
more than 10 million won.
Is she rich?
I don't know.
Is she really his mom? She's so young.
I don't know. Let's go.
That boy is so handsome.
Okay, whatever.
I knew it.
This neighborhood is really rich.
I should be more careful.
That's not true.
I'm really bad at English.
I'm really impressed, though.
I'm so glad I met the perfect partner.
Where are you?
I'm waiting for Hwi-yeong.
Can you believe this?
He says he's glad he met
the perfect partner.
O-je said that.
Be quiet.
Are you going to marry him or what?
-I'm here.
-Hey.
Where have you been?
What? Well...
Didn't your mom come to school earlier?
She wanted to look around
for some academies.
Gosh, your mom is so persistent.
How are you going to prepare
for the English free-talking test?
With Jun-u.
Oh, right.
God, this is so annoying.
How can I do it with Pil-sang?
Jun-u won't be an easy partner either.
-Thank you.
-Have a good day.
Jun-u. Can you send me
five sentences in English?
Anything.
Why?
"Why?"
It's a level test. To see
how good you are at English.
Does this sound too arrogant?
I want to see how you use English.
For reference.
Yeong-bae, I'm going home.
Goodbye.
Wait.
Do you speak English?
Then can you help me
write some sentences in English?
Write...
Oh, yes. Dad?
Hey, wait.
Why isn't he answering?
Jun-u?
My...
Ma Hwi-yeong?
Choe Jun-u?
Welcome--
How's it going?
Preparing for the free-talking test.
So so.
That won't cut it.
Soo-bin is in the top tier in English.
If her performance assessment,
English exams,
and academic records are all ruined
because of you, what will you do?
I'll make sure that won't happen.
Don't worry. I'll sort it out.
I don't think it's something
you can sort out.
I can help.
For Soo-bin, not for you.
Because she's my girlfriend.
Do you not scratch yourself these days?
What?
You scratch yourself on the wrist
when you're anxious.
I think you're probably very anxious now
for many reasons.
Welcome.
Hey, Hwi-yeong.
I met the guys at Byeongmun High.
It went well.
"Well"?
How?
Hey.
Check the amount.
Are you kidding us?
-Give us more.
-Finish him.
Then I'll give you more.
Hey, where are you going?
Give us a little more!
-We need more than this!
-Well...
They'll take care of it.
They promised to make sure
Jun-u gets expelled.
Well done.
What about the mock exam? Did you do well?
Me?
I'm going to start a study coaching group.
My mom's looking for good tutors
at the moment.
I'll let you join without a level test.
Really?
I really needed help.
Thanks a lot, Hwi-yeong.
I'll study hard.
See you tomorrow.
Good night.
I'm home.
Mom...
Your mom is asleep. Don't wake her up.
Mom, are you okay?
Oh, are you leaving for the day?
-Yes.
-All right.
Wait.
Did something happen?
No.
-Have a good night.
-All right.
Bye.
I can help.
For Soo-bin, not for you.
Because she's my girlfriend.
No way. We're just friends.
Right, Little Boy?
Which one of them should I believe?
How's it going, Jun-u?
Let's meet up.
Hey, are you ignoring my text?
All right, then.
CHOE JUN-U
Gosh. Jun-u, this fool...
I WANT TO SEE HOW YOU USE ENGLISH.
FOR REFERENCE. JUN-U?
Are you home?
HWI-YEONG
Yes.
What are you doing?
Judging by that question,
I'm assuming you're probably not
in a great mood, Hwi-yeong.
No, I was just curious.
I suddenly thought of you.
Right, what did Mr. Son say?
About my level test.
He hasn't mentioned anything yet.
I probably didn't pass, then.
What should I do?
My mom will be so mad at me.
CHOE JUN-U
What's with you, Jun-u?
If you're struggling with writing in
English, tell me what your dream is.
In Korean.
Dream?
My dream? To sleep with the lights off.
"To sleep with the lights off"?
Sleep?
Gosh. How childish.
What's his deal?
CHEONBONG HIGH SCHOOL
Can you believe
Son Heung-min was sent off for that?
I'm sure the referee was bribed.
Tackle.
What a sad attempt.
-Does the new kid play soccer?
-Who knows?
-He looks like he can't play.
-Should we ask?
Soo-bin is in the top tier in English.
If her performance assessment,
English exams,
and academic records are all ruined
because of you, what will you do?
Right? That's right.
No, don't you dare.
You don't need to talk me up to Mr. Son.
If I bombed the test, so be it.
That's all I'm capable of.
Don't worry, Soo-bin.
You won't fail. You always do well.
Hey, newbie!
He never responds.
What position do you play?
Are things going well with Jun-u
for the English free-talking test?
I don't know. I'm stumped.
Jun-u?
Hey. See you later.
Hey, newbie! What position do you play?
-Just be a goalie, punk!
-He's running again.
Hey! You punk.
Soo-bin.
What was that?
Your dream is to sleep
with the lights off?
-Are you kidding me?
-Feel free to change...
your English partner if you want.
-What?
-I stink at English,
and I have no dream.
Don't ruin your grades because of me,
and get a new partner.
Hey. You are so shameless. You know that?
You sent me that strange text last night
after ignoring my texts.
And now, what?
Strange?
Like the literature
performance assessment,
I'm doing this out of concern for you.
You shouldn't be like this to me.
Why are you concerned about me?
Because I was forced to transfer here
and seem like a loser?
You must feel some kind of sense of duty
towards kids like me.
Thanks, but it's okay.
You don't need to be concerned.
Why did you draw the peas then?
Didn't you mean...
you wanted help?
Because you wanted to do your best too.
I draw things like that all the time
out of habit.
Maybe I should just change my partner.
What's wrong with me?
Kim So-wol was a poet that cared a lot
about the form of poetry.
-This poem is the best example.
-Peas?
Are you craving peas?
No.
If you lay the poem on its side,
it looks like a mountain.
That is exactly what the poet intended.
For the next stanza...
If you take a look...
Here.
I wrote down my dream.
If you write it in English for me,
I'll memorize it.
Are... Are you okay?
What's with him?
What is it?
No.
Why won't you let me see it?
-Where are you going?
-To the restroom.
My dream is to fall asleep
in a dark room with the lights off.
I often had to sleep alone
when I was a child,
so I slept with the lights on
because I felt like
zombies, ghosts, and monsters
would attack me
if I turned off the lights.
And I still sleep with the lights on.
Not because I'm afraid of ghosts...
Okay, Soo-bin.
Hurry up and take your seat.
Do you want to work on English?
At the snack shop after school?
Are you preparing for the free-talk?
-No!
-Yes!
Can't we change partners?
No, you can't.
Why? I'm good at English.
Not at school. After school, at the park?
Anyway, prepare well for the free-talk.
I'll see you tomorrow then.
-Okay.
-Work hard!
-Goodbye.
Good luck.
Fine. As you want.
Hello, Mr. Son.
Do you have...
Yoo Soo-bin's level test result?
Hey! Where are you going?
Aren't you going to the library?
See you later.
Okay.
Hey, don't push!
What's wrong with me?
What's wrong with my heart?
It's because I'm annoyed.
How will I teach that fool, Jun-u?
Hello?
Sorry, something urgent came up.
He's here.
Jeong-hu.
Jun-u. Long time no see.
See? He came.
He ignored our calls, but he came
right away when his best friend called.
Jeong-hu, are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay.
Are you disappointed that he's fine
after you ran all the way here?
Hey. You're here anyway.
Let's work out a little together.
-Hey. Are you scared?
-He's leaving.
Hey, Jun-u! Aren't you going to fight?
What if I do this?
-You promised not to do this.
-I didn't.
Did you believe that, you shit?
-You wimp. You loser.
-You shit!
Your friend's dying here!
Get over here.
Now that you transferred to a good
school, you don't need your friend?
You will just save yourself, huh?
Stop that.
You fuck.
You should really
just focus on studying from now on.
Don't get caught up in anything
unnecessary. Do you understand?
Get over here, you shit!
Don't act like you're better
than us, and fight!
Your friend is going to die today.
I said to stop it, you bastard!
Stay down.
Jun-u.
-Damn it.
-Jun-u!
Move, you shit.
Do you think you're better than us?
What is that?
Run, Jun-u!
-The cops are here.
-Let's get out of here.
Hey! If we catch you,
you're dead, Jeong-hu!
Hurry up, Jeong-hu!
My mom isn't home today!
Jun-u, wait for me!
Why do you live like this?
Do you think I was transferred
for you to be treated like this?
You must've felt relieved.
After leaving like that.
You made me feel so guilty.
I told you to go somewhere else
and start anew.
Don't be ridiculous.
Start what?
It's the same no matter where I go.
For losers like us, it's miserable
no matter where we go.
Jeong-hu, why do you think like that?
You weren't like this before.
CHOE JUN-U
Do you think a new name tag and uniform
will change your life?
Never.
Our lives were messed up
from the moment we were born.
I got to go.
Hey, Jeong-hu.
Hey.
Mom. When are you coming home?
Today too?
What time are you coming home?
Choe Jun-u. Jun-u!
I thought you might be scared.
Hey, Jeong-hu.
You're not scared of the dark now, right?
Since I'm here.
No. I've always wanted to sleep
with the lights off.
Let's sleep.
You coward.
CHOE JUN-U
Right, it's just how Jun-u is.
An irresponsible
and hopeless troublemaker.
Pull yourself together, Soo-bin.
-Oh, my.
-Hey, Soo-bin!
My daughter.
Yoo Soo-bin! Come here, my sweetie.
You passed the test for Mr. Son's class.
Come here. They're here
to congratulate you. Say hi.
My daughter is home.
-Hi.
-Hello, Soo-bin.
Soo-bin, congratulations.
-Great job.
-Yes, congratulations.
-Congratulations.
-Thank you.
It's true that I tried hard,
but Hwi-yeong was very concerned
about you too.
Soo-bin, I hope you do your best
for Hwi-yeong's sake too.
She will do her best.
I'm so glad for you.
-Oh. my.
-Are you okay?
Stay still. I'll take care of it.
Oh, boy.
-Right over here.
-Yes, I see it.
Gosh, you could've gotten hurt.
-Can you lift your foot?
-Okay.
-Can you lift the other foot?
She's trying so hard.
Oh, right.
Soo-bin!
Oh, my. Ms. Yoon, are you okay?
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Hey. How could you just leave like that?
You should sit down and talk.
Are you her servant?
Did I make it to Mr. Son's class
because of her?
Of course.
You wouldn't have
if it weren't for Hwi-yeong's family.
I did okay on the test.
It's not because of Hwi-yeong.
Are you kidding me?
You know your math skills
are not good enough.
You're not even in the top tier in math.
Mom.
Seriously...
You embarrass me.
Who cares if you graduated from SNU
and work at a good company?
When I see how you act around
that lady, it's really...
embarrassing.
Look who's talking.
Who is the one that made me like this?
Who's the one who made
a proud woman like me into a servant?
Cut the nonsense and come out.
No.
Come out.
She's about to introduce more tutors
for other subjects.
You have to make a good impression.
-Come out. Listen to me!
-No.
-Come out.
-I said, no.
Be careful then.
Oh, no. She has severe menstrual cramps.
-Really?
-Yes.
She ran out of her medicine.
That's too bad.
-She must be sensitive.
-Yes.
-Right over here.
-Yes, I see it.
Why does it have to rain now?
You...
Why are you...
You don't have an umbrella?
Why else do you think I'm walking
like this?
I don't have one either.
So what?
Do you have something to say?
What happened to your face?
I have something to say.
What?
No, you don't have anything to say.
You even left like that earlier
after promising me.
Don't walk in the rain.
What?
That's what I wanted to say.
It's really bad for you
if you get wet in the rain.
It was in my pocket.
How come you're not asking
why I was walking around like this?
why I'm such a mess?
Hey.
What's up with that mask?
Are you in a boy band or what? Come here.
What happened to your face?
I'd like to meet
Jun-u's previous homeroom teacher.
But is this really your dream?
Then what is your dream?
-Fifty times?
-Do you want ten more?
Why do you always
feel uncomfortable around me?
And you don't like to be my girlfriend.
Hey, Shin Jeong-hu! Jun-u, stop Jeong-hu.
Jeong-hu, our lives are
not that messed up after all.
Subtitle translation by Wayne Ryu