Put your bags in here. Okay.
You don't have a bag?
Hey, sit here.
Choe Jun-u.
Soo-bin, did you get my message?
Your mom told you, right?
We have an orientation
with the new tutor tomorrow.
Come to my place by 5 p.m.
Let's talk about it later.
It's about our tutor.
All right, guys.
My beloved students in Class Three.
-We don't love you!
-But I love you guys.
Pil-sang, are you already asleep?
All right. The class president
and vice president.
Is everyone here?
-Yes.
-Good.
All right, then.
Sir, we're ready to leave!
Here, please drive safely.
-Thank you.
-My pleasure.
Let's go!
-Can you do that for me too?
-What?
-Here.
-It's your belt.
Gosh, they're so quiet.
I guess they had too much fun.
Mr. Oh, I'd like to meet with you
as soon as you arrive.
There's an urgent matter
we need to discuss.
This is what I was going to send you
the other day.
I should've checked with you first,
but I couldn't
because
I felt like I'd keep liking you
even if the text message
turned out to be true.
I was embarrassed
that you might find out
about the way I felt.
You guys were all happy, right?
-Yes.
-I guess only I had a great time.
You guys all did great.
Now, you all must go straight home.
All right, you're dismissed!
-Dismissed!
-Let's go!
-Thank you.
Let's go.
I'll get going.
-Congratulations, Soo-bin.
-For what?
The word has already spread.
You and Jun-u.
Be happy together.
-I'm off.
-Ro-mi, you're leaving?
Hey, enough.
We can go again.
-Here.
-Thank you.
You took it, right?
Hey, partner.
We've gotten quite close, haven't we?
Like this, one, two, one, two.
And please do a tarot card reading
for me. Promise.
O-je, do you want to hang out with us?
I have to go work at my dad's restaurant.
I'm off.
-Bye.
Bye, Mr. Oh!
Hey, are you feeling sick?
-Your face is beet red.
-It really is.
Maybe it's because
I forgot to wear my sunscreen.
My gosh, you got a sunburn.
Girls, let's go to the sauna.
My entire body aches.
Sounds good! Let's go.
Okay, let's all go to the sauna together.
-Let's go.
-Let's go to the sauna together.
I just want to go home. I'm quite tired.
-Hey, come on.
-Come on. Come with us.
Let's go!
-Let's go to the sauna.
-Let's go.
Soo-bin and I are supposed to hang out.
Well, do you want to go
to the sauna with us?
I want to spend time with just you today.
That's okay with you girls, right?
-Yes, of course.
-My gosh.
-I actually have plans!
-My gosh, me too!
Hey, hurry. Let's go.
They're gone.
Shall we go?
A moment like this is actually here.
-What?
-Just two of us spending time together.
But there were many moments
like this in the past.
Right, there were.
But I think this is the first time
that we're really spending time together
with no one else around.
Soo-bin.
Please...
be good to me from now on.
-I ask you to do the same.
-Okay.
-Isn't this so delicious?
-Who suggested this place?
-Me.
-It was a good call.
O-je! Were you out for delivery?
I thought you went to the sauna.
Oh, I ran into my friends on the way.
Say hello.
-Hello.
Is Da-huin your first love?
-What do you like about her?
-When did you start dating?
Let's take a picture.
-Da-huin, let's take a picture.
-Okay, sure.
Maybe you could lower...
Okay, one, two, three.
Let's take one more.
-Thank you.
-My gosh.
-Hey, sit down.
-Da-huin.
-Why are you mad at me?
Because I showed up
with my friends unannounced?
Well, they really wanted to see you.
I'm just a little flustered.
All my friends are hounding me now.
The photo is everywhere already.
Are you upset that everyone now
knows we're in a relationship?
-It's not that.
-Why?
Did you not want your friends to
find out I'm your girlfriend?
-Because I'm not pretty?
-Why does that matter?
And you're pretty. You really are.
What, then? Am I the only one
that's been taking this seriously?
No, that's not what I meant.
Are you mad at me?
-I'm very shy, you know.
-I see.
I didn't know. I'm sorry I overreacted.
My friends and I
will eat quickly and leave.
Try to be nice to them until they leave.
Hey, Da-huin.
What did you mean, then?
O-je...
PETITION
The parents who want a new homeroom
teacher for Class Three have signed this.
They're all in agreement
that they should have a teacher
who has more experience
with college admission.
It's not 100 percent of the parents,
but most of them--
I don't think this is most of them.
In any case,
more than half of the parents--
Let's count. Two, four, five...
Mr. Oh, the number isn't important.
Even if it isn't a majority,
the fact that most parents of
the students who get good grades
-are taking such action--
-This
was started by Hwi-yeong's mother.
Why? Because I'm against
the intensive English class?
Or because I didn't obey her?
Mr. Oh. Listen,
I understand what you think.
But can't you try to be
more accommodating?
How could you let this happen?
I'm not quite following.
All I know is that I won't falter.
Gosh, this is a big problem.
Goodness, I'm really offended this time.
I mean, right after that fun trip...
MR. OH HAN-GYEOL
Goodness.
Your call has been declined.
Declined? She declined my call?
For goodness' sake.
Do you think I'll care
if you come out against me?
I'll just persuade
the other mothers first...
I'll persuade... I can't.
Why am I becoming all timid
all of a sudden again?
Mister, I'm sad too!
Let's cry together.
That much?
I don't have that much money.
Mom, don't cry.
I'll come up with the money
no matter what. Yes.
Don't forget to take your medicine, okay?
My mom's on a business trip,
so she'll come tomorrow.
I mean, don't worry
about running into my mom.
Still, the neighbors may see.
Hello.
You should go now.
After watching you go in.
See you.
-Right, tomorrow...
-Tomorrow...
Let's think about what we'll do
tomorrow and talk later.
Did you think I was gone?
I'm really going now.
Okay.
-Bye!
-Bye.
We're going to meet tomorrow too.
And the day after tomorrow,
and the day after that.
I can like you tomorrow too.
And the day after tomorrow,
and the day after that.
I can like you every single day.
You're late.
Mom.
Why are you so surprised?
Did you do something bad?
Your school trip ended hours ago.
Why are you so late?
I'll let it slide
since you came back from the trip.
Mom, weren't you coming tomorrow?
That was the plan,
but my work ended early.
Why? You don't like me coming early?
No way. I'm glad.
-I'll go rest.
-Okay.
Hey. Did you like it that much?
The air over there must've been so fresh.
Your face is gleaming.
I envy you, Soo-bin.
I want to quit work and go traveling too.
I envy you.
That was so close.
Are you looking for a perfume?
Yes. I want to buy a gift.
Oh, for your girlfriend?
Yes.
The perfume you just chose
has a neutral scent,
and it's very popular
for couples to use together.
You can test it if you want.
Here you go.
You can spray it if you want.
Spray it in the air,
and you'll smell it in a more natural way.
Yes, I'm telling you. I give in.
I give in to your passion
for your daughter, Ms. Yoon.
But there's one thing.
I hope the other moms
don't find out about this.
They keep saying that I'm only
favoring Soo-bin.
Of course.
You should.
You better pay me back one day.
What? No way.
Okay, fine.
Ms. Yoon, aren't you overworking
yourself though?
There are so many things I want to do.
Then... Why don't we each say
what we want to do?
Let me see.
Hey, Soo-bin.
My stomach...
Why? Are you sick?
I don't know. I have a stomachache.
Again? There you go again.
Just when you have to
start studying again.
Did you hear you have to go to
Hwi-yeong's place by five tomorrow?
Yes, I know.
Hey, Soo-bin.
Do you know that my insides
are literally churning right now?
That sneaky rat...
No, because Hwi-yeong's mom
trampled on my pride.
Soo-bin, don't disappoint me
this time, okay?
-Okay.
-Do you understand?
Hello? Little Pea!
Soo-bin?
Jun-u. Did you have fun?
Yes, Mom.
How was the school trip? Was it fun?
Yes, it was fun.
Look at you.
Something good must've happened.
It's written on your face.
"I am very happy right now."
No, I'm not.
I guess it went well with her.
-Her?
-I already knew
when you asked me
about my first love last time.
Who is it? Someone in your class?
You guys hooked up on
the school trip, didn't you?
How? Tell me.
Come on, tell me.
-I don't know.
-Please, tell me!
-No, you can't go in!
Tell me now.
-What?
-Let's talk inside.
I'm going home now. Bye.
Mr. Oh, my shift...
is over.
-Cheers!
It must be tough for you too.
Is that why you cried so much last time?
Well, yes.
You should be brave. Go up against her!
But I have a tendency
to become super timid
at critical moments.
Don't be like that.
I heard from Jun-u that you're
the best teacher in the world.
No matter what the moms say,
your students will be on your side.
Believe them, and believe in yourself.
You should be brave, okay?
Ji-min, do I seem like
a good teacher to you?
Are you kidding me?
If I met a teacher like you
when I was in school,
I wouldn't have ended up like this.
Then you can meet me now.
What?
I mean, you and I can meet.
Let's go out.
Well, that's...
We've only met a couple of times.
Come on, numbers don't mean anything.
I felt it from the moment
I first laid eyes on you.
What about you, Ji-min?
See? I think you felt the same.
Wait, didn't you say you were super timid?
Why are you suddenly...
Of course not, I'm a man!
Then, let's...
go out.
From this moment on.
Okay?
Well...
Okay.
Really?
Really? Are you serious?
You're not lying, are you?
We're really going out now, right?
We're going out.
-Yes! Nice!
-You did it!
Yes!
He told us to go straight home.
I have an orientation
with the tutor at 5 p.m. tomorrow.
Really? Then I guess
I can only see you briefly.
Yes, I guess so.
Shall we meet earlier, then?
I'd love that,
but will that be okay with you?
About an hour early? How's 8 a.m.?
I can meet even earlier.
Will you be too tired?
Then how about 7:30 a.m.?
-Will you be okay?
-Yes, of course.
I mean, yes. I think so.
Then can we meet a little...
earlier than 7:30 a.m.?
Earlier? How early?
How about we meet...
at 7:24 a.m.?
What's gotten into you?
-Going to the library this early?
-Yes.
I guess you're nervous
about the orientation.
Yes.
Mom, you have to go to work today?
It's Saturday.
Right? I'll come home early
so that I can to go to Hwi-yeong's place.
You're coming too?
Of course. I went through hoops
to snag this opportunity.
See you later.
Have a good day. Study hard.
I will.
I'm sorry, Mom.
-Oh, this one is the same too.
-Yes.
This one too.
What shall we do first?
Well...
There are no good movies
playing at the moment,
and we don't have enough time
to go to an amusement park today.
Then...
let's both say what we want to do
the most on the count of three.
Okay.
In one, two, three.
-Number One.
-Doing nothing.
What was Number One?
Then we can do both of them.
You're right.
-Let's go.
-Okay.
-Hello.
-My gosh.
Yeon-u, I thought you weren't
going to do this anymore.
I checked your schedule and saw
you have another busy day today.
Don't you have to go pretty far?
It's okay. I can just take a cab.
Then please take this.
You overpaid me for the work I did.
I can't accept this.
Just accept it, please.
You made kimchi for me
and even brought lunch.
You did more than enough,
so please just accept this.
I don't want to take advantage
of anyone. Take it, please.
Do you only think about yourself?
I don't want to take
advantage of anyone either.
I know you hired me,
but I did all those things
because I genuinely wanted to.
You always skip meals,
and you're too busy with work
to do any housework.
I felt bad for you,
so I wanted to help out a little.
Sister, how could you pay me
for genuinely wanting to help you?
You're too compassionate.
Also, why are you calling me "Sister"?
Then what?
Shall I call you "Brother" instead?
So, is this how we do it? Doing nothing.
It's boring, isn't it?
No, it's nice.
I like how the scenery keeps changing.
What do you think about this seat?
I like it. I can see everything from here.
When I was little, I had to
take buses like this very often
to go see my mom.
And,
whenever I sat here because this seat
happened to be empty,
I was so happy.
I felt as if the bus was on the road
solely for me.
Just in that moment.
It does feel that way indeed.
I wanted to introduce you
to Jeong-hu before anybody else.
He would've been amazed
to find out that we're going out now.
Hi.
I'm Yoo Soo-bin.
As you can see, Jun-u is doing very well.
He's our class vice president
and very popular now.
And he even has a pretty girlfriend now.
So don't worry about him,
and rest in peace.
I'll look after him.
You'll look after me?
I have been looking after you.
I helped with your performance assessment,
and I scolded you
when you wanted to run away.
You know that I always want
to help out others too much.
That's why you helped me.
I thought you were interested in me.
You got the wrong idea.
I don't think I did.
You definitely seemed interested.
Look who's talking.
You came back using
the performance assessment as an excuse.
I just wanted to be responsible.
That's all.
Jeong-hu.
Don't be sorry for me anymore.
I'm doing well.
I'm happy.
Your mother married her first love?
I guess it can really happen.
It's like a fairy tale.
But not one with a happy ending
as it didn't exactly work out.
She had me, so she struggled a lot.
I doubt that. I'm sure she was happy
because her son, Choe Jun-u, was born.
Right.
I wanted to ask you something.
What is it?
When did it start?
From which moment did you start liking me?
Goodness. You're so certain now
that I like you, aren't you?
Am I wrong?
But I can feel it.
When we practiced
for the English free-talking test?
I thought you were transferring again,
but you came back.
For me, it was that day.
I suddenly feel embarrassed to tell you.
Why? Which day was it?
Which day?
I think it was that day for me too.
What is it?
You can't concentrate?
No.
You need to stay alert.
I heard Jo Sang-hun from Class One
didn't transfer.
Your dad isn't someone who lets
something like that slide.
I don't know what he's thinking.
Eat this and study hard.
Mom.
About Soo-bin.
Yes?
I think we should pull her
out of the private lesson team.
Why? Did Soo-bin ask you to do that?
Does she feel guilty
for being favored all the time?
Gosh, how could she be so inflexible
for a young little girl?
Do you know how much her mom begged me?
It's not that.
I just think it'll be
more comfortable with just guys.
Son.
You don't like Soo-bin anymore, right?
What?
Then you can pull yourself together
and focus fully on your studies, right?
What a wise decision, my son!
Your condition seemed to
improve because of Soo-bin,
so that's why I didn't say anything
even if I didn't like her.
Then there's no need anymore, right?
What do you mean?
Why so suddenly...
Hello?
Seriously, that rat... What do I do?
Rat?
What's going on?
Can you turn the car around?
-What?
-Make a U-turn now.
-Okay.
-Hurry.
Ms. Park.
Ms. Yoon, what brings you here?
What is this about?
Why did you suddenly
take Soo-bin out of the team?
Well, I gave it some thought,
and Soo-bin's grades
seem too low for her to be
in the same private class.
She only missed the top tier in math.
You said you'd make a special exception.
Ms. Yoon.
I'm not fond of things like
special requests or favors.
You know I like to keep things clean.
I have an appointment.
-Wait, ma'am...
-What are you doing?
Hello.
Yes.
Ma'am. There's another reason,
isn't there, ma'am?
Stop calling me like that.
Honestly,
that's bothered me all this time.
I understand that you want to flatter me,
but we're all moms here.
There's no need to be excessively polite.
You should have some self-respect.
You even graduated from
a prestigious university.
Hey.
Shouldn't you apologize to her?
You even made her drop her purse.
Since when did you two become friends?
It's been a while.
So you came all the way here together?
I envy your friendship.
Wait...
Anyway, I hope you apologize to her later.
Let's go, Ms. Yoon.
What's up with those two?
It's a gift.
My first gift as your boyfriend.
What is this?
Wow, it smells nice.
Jun-u, you even know how to buy gifts?
I guess.
I didn't know I'd be like this either.
Thank you for accepting my feelings.
This was exactly what you looked like.
The first time we met
in front of the school.
You too. You looked just like this.
I'm sorry. I shouldn't have butted in.
Thank you.
For what? I wasn't being helpful.
I know, but I still feel thankful.
I don't know why.
So are you implying that
I was the one who started
that petition?
Ma'am.
If it's because there's something
that bothers you,
you can be frank with me.
Bother me? What are you talking about?
Are you saying we fabricated grades...
or something like that?
Mr. Oh. You are aware
that this is a very serious
matter of defamation, right?
I didn't say anything about...
I didn't say anything about
fabricating grades, ma'am.
I just said that as an example.
Including Question 15
of the math test last time,
it's true that there is something
fishy going on, isn't it?
I beg you, for Hwi-yeong's sake...
Mr. Oh.
Are you saying you want to
go up against us?
Is that why you're digging around
here and there lately?
That's not what I meant.
I just want to set things right
if there's something wrong.
So what? Did Oh Han-gyeol
find out anything?
It seems so.
I'm not sure.
Unlike his looks, Mr. Oh is
quite a smart man.
I don't know what to do.
What should we do?
What do you think?
We'll do what we always do.
Make sure Hwi-yeong doesn't find out.
He's already mentally unstable.
Later. The kids will arrive soon.
Suddenly?
I don't know why she suddenly
changed her attitude.
Come sit over here.
Did you do something to offend Hwi-yeong?
What?
No.
You should've been nice to him.
Everything is ruined now.
Gosh, that sneaky rat.
I'm sure
it was her inferiority complex talking.
Seriously.
Why in the world do I have to hear
something like that from her
because of you?
Mom, I wasn't qualified to join
that team in the first place.
You keep forcing things
that aren't possible,
and that's why bad things keep happening.
Just leave it up to me.
I'm not as smart as you,
but still, I'm trying my best on my own.
Look at you talking.
Are you boxing or what?
Trust me. I can do it!
-Hello.
-Hi.
-Come on in, guys.
-Hi, Sim-bok.
-Hello.
Only today's session will be done here.
Starting from next session,
you'll be meeting at the apartment.
Remember that, okay?
-Okay, thank you.
-Thank you.
-Hey.
-Guys, you're here.
-Where's Gi-tae?
-He can't make it.
-I think he's sick.
-Really?
-Aren't you...
-Hello, ma'am.
Hey, Sang-hun. Welcome.
Hello, sir.
Honey.
My, what a nice place.
Gosh, is this real?
Oh, my!
Honey, I get it. But don't you think
this is too harsh?
Do you agree with your mom?
Do you know what it's like
to get to the top?
You must compete fiercely
like a vicious beast.
Only one person who survives
that battle until the end
can get to the top.
He's very clever.
You should compete against him.
Honey. Then like last time,
Hwi-yeong will...
If he can't get through this,
he won't survive the competition.
Like my brother?
What are you talking about?
He's so successful now.
I wish you were like him.
Don't worry, Dad.
I'll win.
I will survive.
My gosh. Thanks, Hwi-yeong.
I got to visit this mansion thanks to you.
Thank you.
-Can I ask you for a favor?
-Of course. Anything.
Don't put on an act in front of me.
Just be your usual self.
Your greedy, sly self.
Come on. What are you talking about?
This is how I always am.
I need to use the bathroom.
Where's the bathroom?
Hwi-yeong.
Don't provoke me.
You'll get hurt.
Hey, Gi-tae. Are you very sick?
I'll upload all the notes
from the tutoring session.
Thanks.
I doubt that.
I'm sure she was happy
because her son, Choe Jun-u, was born.
My gosh!
-Have you been waiting long?
-No, let's go.
Where's Bumbi?
At home.
I wanted to walk with you.
Bumbi must be sad.
It's a love triangle.
Let's go.
Why let go? Keep holding hands.
It looked lovely.
Let's go.
Then I shall...
Hi.
Gosh, you're so thick-skinned.
-Hi.
Soo-bin, I heard you got kicked out
of Hwi-yeong's tutoring team.
-No, I didn't get kicked out.
-What else would you call it, then?
Didn't Hwi-yeong say
he doesn't want you in the team?
That's what Gi-tae's mom said.
Ro-mi, you're so sneaky.
Did you peek at the moms' chatroom
on your mom's phone again?
Right, Hwi-yeong must think
you're out of his league now.
Because you ended up with him.
Hey, you little... Ro-mi! Hey!
You're one tough cookie.
You sure are the Hwang Ro-mi I know.
Let's go, guys. Come on. Let's go.
Don't mind her.
Why didn't you tell me?
About the tutoring team.
Because it's not important.
I'm happy that
I don't have to do it anymore.
Jun-u, I can see right through you.
I know you're worried that it might
be because we're going out now.
I can still see you.
Gosh, just get your books.
Did you have breakfast?
No, I didn't.
Then how about we go to the snack bar
during the break?
Okay.
Hey, Hwi-yeong.
You two should talk.
Even Sang-hun joined the team,
so there are too many people now.
Sang-hun too?
Thank goodness
I'm not in the team anymore.
It would've been hard for me
as you guys are all so smart.
I asked my mom
to pull you out of the team.
I thought seeing you at every session
would be too hard for me.
But it doesn't make me feel better.
Hi, Ji-min. Did you have a good sleep?
Did you dream about me?
Seriously?
I was just joking, but you actually did?
My gosh, thank you
for seeing me even in your dream.
Oh, okay. Study hard.
I'll message you whenever I can.
Okay, all right.
-Mr. Oh.
-Gosh!
You have a girlfriend now, don't you?
Yes. Did you see her?
What do you think?
You two looked so lovely together.
She's beautiful, and she seemed very kind.
Right? I guess I got lucky
because of all the good deeds I did.
Chan-yeol, do a tarot card reading
for my love life later. Okay?
Sure.
Gosh.
Da-huin.
What's going on?
Guys, feel free to take
this printout if you need one.
I've decided not to take
the tutoring sessions.
Why?
The thing is, I can't afford
such an expensive tutor,
but you just let me join for free.
It just makes me uncomfortable.
Hey. We're friends,
so we should study together.
Even if we're friends,
this seems wrong.
I'll just find something I can afford.
Are you saying you won't be
my friend anymore?
It's not that.
I just feel more comfortable
taking care of it on my own.
Fine. Suit yourself.
But I won't share my test notes with you
from now on.
And you'll be kicked out
of our study group cafe.
Hurry up before my face gets sunburned.
You skipped your meals again, right?
Your face looks haggard.
I won't accept your apology.
I kept so many things
bottled up all this time.
You don't have to say things like
"I'm sorry, forgive me."
Bye.
Da-huin, can we...
Can we go back
to being friends like before?
To be honest, I just wish...
you could be my good friend...
instead of my girlfriend.
I tried my best...
but it's hard.
Being your boyfriend.
You're so kind to me,
but I can't be the same,
and I always feel sorry,
and I don't know what to do.
It's not like there's another reason.
It's not like there's someone else
or you're not attractive.
-It's not that...
-Hey.
Stop talking.
Why are you talking so much suddenly?
All this time,
when I said a thousand words,
all you did was smile and say one word.
Are you being generous now?
Since you have to dump me?
How could you make me look so pitiful?
Da-huin.
In the classroom.
After school today,
I have two hours to spare.
Oh, okay. I have time too.
Do you want to go get something to drink?
Something sweet?
That place, after school?
What has changed for you
since we started going out?
The world seems...
Not some cliche like
"The world seems different."
I keep looking in the mirror.
Me too.
Why?
You're handsome.
You don't have to look in the mirror.
I know.
I'm joking.
When I look into the mirror lately,
my reflection looks so excited.
It wasn't like that before.
So whether it was a mirror
or a glass wall,
I tried not to look on purpose.
But these days, it's amazing
how much I've changed.
You know, right?
Know what?
That you're...
really...
pretty.
What?
That you're pretty.
What did you say? I can't hear you.
That you're getting prettier.
Wasn't I always pretty?
You always were,
but lately, you seem to get even prettier
every single day.
And I
miss you more.
And also,
I keep wanting to know more about you.
Like what?
It's nothing much.
"What does Soo-bin
look like when she sneezes?
Does Soo-bin sleep
with her knees curled up?
Does she lie on her side?
Or does she raise her arms?"
And also...
I thought of things like that too.
"Does Jun-u really have trouble
sleeping with the lights off?"
I guess you can sleep
with the lights off lately
since your mom's with you.
Also...
"When Jun-u smiles,
does he know that his left eye
gets smaller?"
It does?
-No, it doesn't.
-It does.
Try smiling properly.
Hey. You're squinting your right eye
on purpose, aren't you?
-On purpose.
-No, I'm not.
Who smiles like that?
Open them properly.
What are you doing?
And when I'm with you,
everything feels comfortable.
Like all the troubles in this world
have disappeared.
It's so hot.
On days like this,
after washing your hair,
if you stick your head outside
the window, it feels so refreshing.
The cold breeze blows through your hair,
and it feels like someone is blowing.
It must feel like someone is
stroking your hair.
Right.
But you can't do it in winter.
Your hair will freeze.
You know, like when it's been hit
by lightning.
I do get taller.
But it doesn't work in winter.
Of course not.
That's not your real height.
I know.
By the way, isn't it about time
that you need to go to work?
I still have 30 minutes left.
Shall I walk you to the store?
Sure.
Then let me stop by my house
for a second before we go.
Okay.
Why am I hiccupping suddenly?
Did I surprise you?
Yes.
Let's go.
Wait, I left my phone at home.
My mom said she'd call later.
You're so clumsy. Go get it.
I'll be right back.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine. It'll stop soon.
Why don't you come inside for some water?
It's okay. It'll probably stop.
Don't worry. My mom is at work now.
We talked on the phone.
Come inside for some water.
Come on in. Get some water.
Just get me a cup of water.
No one's here. It's okay.
All right, fine.
-Here.
-Thanks.
What are you doing?
This gets rid of hiccups.
I see. So has it stopped?
-Yes.
-Nice.
Have some more water.
I'll go get my phone.
Hey! Hey, hurry.
Come over here!
Oh, it must be our housekeeper.
It's okay. It's all good. We're okay now.
Jun-u.
Mom.
By the way, what happened, Mom?
Are you uncomfortable with it?
I'm fine if you're okay with it.
Someone posted something strange.
The rumors about rigged grades
aren't true, right?
What do you guys think?
I trust you.
Even if something unexpected did happen,
I'm sure you wouldn't have
anything to do with it.
Aren't I right?
You understand everything, right?
No, Dad.
I just acted mature, that's all.
I had to react that way
to make it easier for you and Mom.
Something must've upset you
when you met your dad earlier.
What is the one thing you regret
the most in your life?
Not being able to tell him that it was me.
Let's go there again and tell him.
I hope all your regrets are gone now.
It's not your fault.
You didn't know back then.
You thought that was for the best then.
What are you guys doing?
Subtitle translation by Wayne Ryu