I should make it look like the Milky Way.
It'd be so refreshing to come here
after a bath, right?
Yes.
What's wrong?
I need to use the restroom.
I've been hesitating,
but I think you should see this.
Jun-u sent me this before.
FORWARDED MESSAGE FROM HWI-YEONG
Soo-bin is the person
who's most important to you, right?
I'll take her away from you.
Soo-bin.
Is something wrong?
My mom told me to come home now.
Your mom? Let's go.
You should...
finish watching the movie. I can go alone.
There's no point watching it without you.
Let's go.
I'm sorry.
Let's hurry.
You can go now. I can go home alone.
I can't believe it.
Whether the text you sent
Hwi-yeong is true or not.
I'm afraid
I'll keep liking you even if it is true.
Do you have a fever? You're burning up.
Let me see.
You're running a fever.
Do you have medicine at home?
I'm okay.
Soo-bin, hold on. Wait here for a second.
PHARMACY
My friend is running a fever.
What are you doing, Soo-bin?
Why are you waiting for him?
Just go.
Go.
It could be an upset stomach.
So I bought some medicine for that too.
Did your mom find out
that you were with me?
No. She just told me to come home.
Go. I'll leave.
Get better soon.
Oh, Hwi-yeong.
-Hello.
-Hi.
I'm sorry.
Soo-bin went out with her friends.
Mom.
Oh, are you two having lunch together?
He carried Soo-bin here.
The one who was forced to transfer, right?
I was worried about you.
Is...
that message true?
Jun-u...
must have been holding a grudge
against me.
He thinks I'm responsible
for all the things
that have happened so far.
But that's just a misunderstanding.
-Are you sure?
-What?
Hwi-yeong,
what have you done?
Hwi-yeong, do me a favor.
I want this to stay between you and me.
By the way,
do Gi-tae and the other kids already know?
And don't tell Jun-u
that I know about this.
Because that would embarrass him?
No.
Because that would hurt my pride.
Bye, then.
I didn't get to give her the present.
I can't let him take her away from me.
I can't let that happen.
What are you doing?
All by yourself.
Are you sure you want to do this?
Why are you kicking so hard?
Take it easy.
Is something wrong?
You should go now.
What do you do when you hate yourself?
When you're angry at yourself.
Why are you angry at yourself?
Because I'm so stupid.
Never mind. Don't worry about it.
Soo-bin, are you okay?
What's with you now?
O-je.
Isn't it hot out here?
Why are you here?
So you just came home like that?
What else could I do?
Her mom told her to come home.
-Are you sure that's true?
-What?
My goodness. I can't believe you, Jun-u.
What did you even dress up
and do your hair so nicely for?
Did you even finish the movie?
We left in the middle.
-What?
-Forget it.
To be honest,
I've never liked someone this much.
Is this your first love?
So it's really your first love.
Gosh, this should be recorded.
You're right.
It's my first love.
First love.
Isn't it nice, Jun-u?
Doesn't it feel like you're floating
on a cloud?
I'm not sure.
The part that feels nice is
this tiny for now.
The rest feels somewhat...
heavy and awkward.
It's messy...
and confusing.
You can't stop thinking
that you're not good enough.
I feel like even the sound of my breathing
might bother her.
I want to do this right,
but I keep making mistakes.
Still, you're lucky
you can like someone as much as you like.
Cheer up, dude.
What's the problem?
You two like each other.
"Each other"?
Hi, I'm in the lobby now.
Building B, Room 1901.
I'm coming up right now.
Song-hui.
Do you live here?
Yes. My apartment in Yangjae-dong
is still occupied.
You should move. Soo-bin will
be tutored in this building.
Really? When does she start?
Is she here too?
She's not here, luckily.
Wait, Song-hui.
Song-hui, are you okay?
Are you okay?
Don't touch me. Just go.
Are you okay, though?
Go.
It hurts so much.
Just a second.
Song-hui, are you okay?
Tell me if you're okay.
Just go!
Are you okay?
-Gosh.
-Are you hurt?
This is humiliating. Darn it.
What should I do? My goodness.
Is she very sick?
Mom.
Did you get hurt? How?
I went to see your tutor and fell.
How did you fall?
Why did you have to
find a new tutor anyway?
It's not like the tutor pushed me.
Go to bed. I'm going to sleep.
Okay.
You're not answering.
I'm worried.
Why does it hurt so much?
I don't think I have a cold.
Did I do something wrong?
I went to the theater.
I saw her.
Was the popcorn too big?
Was it the soda?
I couldn't find our seats too.
When we left...
You were too lame, Jun-u.
Mom, are you asleep?
You didn't have dinner,
so I warmed some milk for you.
Leave it here.
Mom.
Something happened, didn't it?
What do you mean?
My arm hurts a lot, that's why.
Mom.
Do you have a fever?
Are you sick?
No.
I just don't feel too great, that's all.
I took medicine.
Then go to sleep.
In a little bit.
Don't get sick.
It's depressing.
If you're depressed,
you can't study.
Okay.
You too. Don't get sick.
Hey, Soo-bin.
How was your first date?
You ignored our texts all weekend long.
It must've been so good
that you forgot all about us.
You guys met yesterday too, right?
That's why you were out of it, right?
That's why you ignored our texts.
No. I wasn't feeling well.
And we left right after the movie
on Saturday.
Something came up at home.
What?
Did your mom find out?
That's why you're like this, isn't it?
Is a storm approaching?
That's not it.
O-je.
Oh, hey.
Sorry I couldn't call you yesterday.
I went to my grandma's farm.
You did?
Me too.
Hi.
Hey. Hi.
You look good together.
Come on. Let me join too.
I heard they help you prepare your
applications and the interview for SNU.
What is that brat Ro-mi
working so hard at this time?
Let's go.
Da-huin.
Sorry.
I felt uncomfortable
in front of the others.
Are you mad?
Don't be mad. Please?
What is this?
Did you bring this
from your grandma's farm?
It's so cute.
I can't even get mad at you.
Sorry.
So don't be mad, please?
-Please?
-Okay.
Sorry, but you have to be
in the top tier in every subject.
I'll make it into the top tier
in the next exams.
That will do.
Right?
Ro-mi, I'll introduce you
to another tutoring group then.
You know Park Si-hyeon
in Class Two, right?
-He's joining an SNU prep team--
-No. I want to be on your team.
Your team is guaranteed to get into SNU.
Ro-mi.
My mom asked when you'll deposit
the consulting fee.
I heard you requested it too.
Yes. My mom must have forgotten.
I'll remind her.
You know, I saw Soo-bin
at the movie theater.
She was there with Jun-u on Saturday.
MOM
Hi, Mom.
Yes.
I'm dead.
Hwi-yeong,
are you going to the science camp?
No.
Give me those.
-Thanks.
-Okay.
Guys, these are application forms
for the science camp.
Fill it out and give it to me today
if you're interested.
Hello, ma'am.
I heard you wanted to see me?
Why was Hwi-yeong's English
performance assessment grade
not a perfect score?
Well, the thing is, whereas Hwi-yeong
did a good job presenting,
he was lacking in
the collaboration aspect.
Still, he does much better
than the other kids,
so don't worry.
So this is when I should say this.
I'm so flabbergasted.
He has never received
anything but a perfect score.
Look, ma'am. Just because
Hwi-yeong has been receiving
perfect scores until now
doesn't mean all evaluations
must follow that precedent.
Do you think it's appropriate
to be talking about precedents right now?
Look. Hwi-yeong isn't someone
whose grades can be deducted
by teachers like you as they please.
Didn't the other teachers tell you?
I didn't deduct it as I pleased.
Ma'am. I think about it
long and hard as a teacher
and evaluate the kids' grades.
What you just said is a bit offensive.
I understand what you mean.
I finally get it.
I've been busy lately,
so I couldn't look after you.
-Pardon?
-I'll discuss it
with Hwi-yeong's dad.
Thank you for making time for me today.
Excuse me. What do you mean?
Come on, Mr. Oh.
There's more to you than meets
the eye. You're a real pro.
I got it.
I'll take good care of you.
What's she talking about?
Excuse me. Ma'am?
-Ma'am. Did it go well?
-I don't know what you mean.
Ma'am?
Really?
Didn't I make it clear that I like Jun-u?
How could you watch a movie with him?
Jun-u asked me first.
Even if he did.
Is there any reason that
I can't watch a movie with him?
We can watch a movie
as classmates, can't we?
But why does it have to be
Jun-u of all people?
Ro-mi.
I really didn't want to say this,
but I heard that Jun-u made it clear.
That he wanted to stay friends with you.
He even told you that?
Anyhow, even though he likes you,
how could you do that to me?
You even gave me advice the other day.
You knew that too?
Fine.
I'll be honest with you.
I like him too.
I used to like him.
Even if you like him,
there's no reason that I can't.
It's not like you can control
your feelings all the time.
So when we met at the cafe,
I was going to tell you everything.
But you were so serious,
so I missed the right moment.
I'm sorry for not telling you then.
Why am I making up excuses?
No, never mind.
You "used" to like him?
You don't anymore?
You don't like him anymore, right?
What about now?
You don't like Jun-u now. Am I right?
Ro-mi.
I understand how you feel,
but I hope you stop
whining about it to me.
It's stressing me out too.
You made it clear
that you don't like Jun-u.
When did I say that? I said I didn't know.
Jun-u. You're late.
Goodness, I feel so sorry for Pil-sang.
Let's go inside.
Now, a settlement is
a place where people live together.
It can be a city or a village.
A settlement pattern is
a pattern where the city and village
are closely connected
and interact with each other regularly
within the settlement.
A central area is a place
that provides goods and services
to the surrounding areas,
and the areas that receive goods and
services from the central area
-are called the surrounding areas...
-So-ye, is something wrong?
Are you sick?
To be considered as a central area,
the maximum coverage space
covered by the area
must be bigger than the minimum
amount of demand.
According to the functions of
the central area,
it is divided into sections.
It can be divided into
a high and low central area.
You made it clear
that you don't like Jun-u.
If you look below, you can see a hexagon.
That's called the Central Area Theory.
Numerous central areas are
gathered in a particular space,
and some areas overlap with
each other and cause problems...
Pil-sang, I think it's true
that Ro-mi likes Jun-u.
What? Choe Jun-u, you jerk.
Yoo Pil-sang. Go stand in the back.
I think it might rain.
Come over here. You little punk.
Pil-sang.
Hey.
Hey!
Darn, I flew like a butterfly
and stung like a bee.
-Just walk casually.
-Hey!
Are you mad at me about something?
Why do you keep avoiding me?
Gi-tae, you...
You shouldn't hang out with Hwi-yeong.
Are you his butler or what?
What are you talking about... A butler?
-You're being a bit harsh, So-ye.
-You are his butler.
Whenever he calls,
you run to him right away.
You help him with everything in class
and always worry about him.
And I didn't like
that incident with Jun-u too.
You think I want to do that?
-I have no choice--
-I know.
I know you think you can get into a nice
university if you hang out with Hwi-yeong.
But I hate it.
When you act like that.
I hate my boyfriend being
treated like a pushover...
What do you expect me to do then?
You know my family isn't well off.
How could I ever receive
an expensive private lesson like that?
How could I join the study group
if Hwi-yeong didn't let me?
I like hanging out with Hwi-yeong.
I'm sorry, So-ye.
I didn't mean to say...
I'm sorry, I didn't mean...
Make your choice then.
To be my boyfriend
or Hwi-yeong's butler.
O-je, why are you so late?
I'm sorry.
Get lost.
Come on, move.
-Don't go.
-Don't even look back and move.
Don't go.
Try all you want.
I have your back from now on.
Today, you will draw your friend.
Draw the person who's sitting
in front of you.
-You all have partners, right?
-Yes.
Draw the main outline first.
Next, draw the detailed eyes, nose,
and lips.
Come on, that looks so funny.
Seriously.
You'll notice light and shade
while you're drawing.
The parts that protrude and don't.
Look at your friend's face closely
and add some shading.
Also,
if you look more closely,
you'll know which part needs more shading.
Hey, turn your face this way.
-Hello.
Are you Ms. Lee Yeon-u...
Ms. Yoon Song-hui?
Yes.
Hello.
I have to drive to many places for work,
but I hurt my arm.
That must've hurt.
It still looks swollen.
And our housekeeper is
on vacation for a while.
So I needed someone to help me
with the housework and stuff.
I see.
The restaurant I co-manage
is under renovation,
so I was looking for a part-time job
to do until the renovation's done.
The period of this job was
just right and perfect for me.
Still, this won't work, right?
-I guess not.
-Right.
I have a client to meet.
-Please excuse me.
-Sure.
-I'll stay and finish this drink.
-Okay.
Thank you. Goodbye.
Did they withdraw the interest
for my loan?
Why isn't this person answering?
You want me to pull out your car too?
Yes. I'm on my way to the meeting
with the blockchain company.
I checked the design draft.
Why is the UI so bad?
Who would want to use this?
Today's meeting is
just to outline our plans.
Send me a new design in the meantime.
You're a good driver.
Thanks.
-We're exactly ten minutes early.
-Thank you.
I'll park the car and leave.
-Okay.
-All right.
-Thank you.
-No problem.
I should probably pay you.
Don't worry.
Our kids are in the same class.
Thank you.
No problem. Good luck with your meeting.
See you.
Call me.
Okay.
The wind is so hot.
Seriously.
-It's humid too.
-Wait for me.
The study leader has too much to do.
You finished it quite early though.
Where are So-ye and Ro-mi?
So-ye is at the dance class, and Ro-mi
obviously doesn't want to hang out
with us anymore.
Why didn't you at least ask her?
I don't want to. She's annoying.
It's so hot.
Soo-bin.
We're in a bit of a hurry.
I'm in a hurry too.
But I still want to talk to you.
We'll leave you two alone.
Good luck.
I want to know what I did wrong.
You must be like this
because I've done something wrong.
Is it because I just left
when I saw your mom?
I've given it a lot of thought,
and that seems most likely
to be what I did wrong.
That's not it.
When I met your mom
in front of your house last time,
she didn't seem
too fond of me.
That's why I avoided her this time.
But that must have bothered you.
Next time,
no matter what your mom says to me,
I'll talk to her confidently
-and...
-That's not it, really.
I just...
suddenly felt uncomfortable
going out with someone.
Suddenly
during a movie?
during a movie.
Why? Why all of a sudden?
Is it true?
Was he really
using me?
Then it's the movie's fault, I guess.
It made you suddenly feel uncomfortable.
Still, you can let me know
anytime if you remember
what I did wrong.
I'll fix it.
Here.
I wanted to give you this that day.
Mom.
-Hey.
-When did you come?
A while ago.
I'll be staying with you
for the time being.
The restaurant is being renovated.
-Really?
-Yes.
Aren't you happy?
Of course, I'm happy.
This doesn't happen a lot.
What's all that stuff?
I'm sorting through some old stuff.
Gosh, I should really throw things away
every now and then.
It's such a mess.
No way. I know you'll decide
to keep everything in the end,
saying you feel attached to them.
You're wrong. I am throwing
them away for real this time.
Unbelievable.
It's been in here all this time?
My goodness, I can't believe it!
What do you think?
It's pretty.
I wore this on my first date
when I was 18.
Was it with Dad?
Yes.
The dress is still the same,
and only I have changed.
This is 30 percent off?
But it's still expensive.
Gosh.
Are you Mr. Oh Han-gyeol?
Yes.
What's this?
Excuse me. What's this?
Excuse...
What is it?
Oh, my. What's this?
Mr. Oh, I'm over here.
-Come in.
-Okay.
-Have a seat.
Ms. Park, you caught me off guard.
Do you see me sweating here?
This...
never happened.
Mr. Oh, I really don't understand you.
Are you really that innocent
or are you just pretending to be?
No. I'm not innocent.
But...
this is not about me
being innocent or not.
You're not helping Hwi-yeong at all
by doing this.
Hwi-yeong is already doing great.
Couldn't you just trust him and wait...
Mr. Oh.
Why do you have to make
such a big deal out of it?
I really don't understand.
Why can't you just smooth things over?
Did you do this to Mr. Kim,
the previous homeroom teacher too?
Did you do this then too?
Ma'am.
If you did, I think this is
a very serious situation.
So?
Did you keep calling Mr. Kim
to find out about this?
What were you trying to dig up?
Is that what Mr. Kim said?
Mr. Oh. I have just one favor
to ask of you.
At least until Hwi-yeong gets into
Seoul National University, can't you...
Can't you please just stay quiet?
Your ridiculous sense of justice
may destroy my Hwi-yeong's future.
I don't even want to imagine that.
Please, I'm begging you.
Mr. Oh? You understand
what I'm getting at, right?
I feel like crap.
What does she take me for?
Please take my order.
This world stinks.
How could I fail again?
See? It's not bad, right?
It's a little less lonely
-when we drink together.
-Yes.
That's right. You got that right.
My mom always told me she wanted me...
to always be an upright...
An upright person.
That's what my mom always wanted me to be.
Mom...
My mom is working hard
and suffering in the countryside.
I'm sorry, Mom. I failed again.
Darn it.
Why are you crying?
You're making me cry.
Don't cry.
I'm terrible.
-No, I'm worse.
-No.
I'm so terrible, Mom...
-Mr. Oh, are you okay?
-Yes, I'm fine.
I called a cab. Wait a minute.
-I... I'll take you home.
-No.
-Wait a minute, okay?
-Okay.
What's taking him so long?
There he is. Mr. Oh, your cab's here.
-Let's go.
-Okay.
I'll take you home.
-Here. Are you okay?
-Yes.
I'm totally fine.
-No, no.
-I am...
-I'm sorry. Are you okay?
-I'm okay.
I'm okay. Go first.
-Get in.
-Okay.
Where do you live again?
Deullae Apartments on Cheonbongsan Road.
Deullae Apartments, please.
Take him home safely. Bye.
Bye.
Song-hui.
It's so annoying.
Why am I mad?
It's not like I didn't know.
He isn't worth getting mad about.
Mom.
You should've taken a day off.
How did you drive with your arm like that?
I hired someone to drive me around
and help with housework.
-What?
-That's good.
Hold on.
What are you doing? I'm not a kid.
What? Things like this
become fond memories.
There's a kid in my class
who draws these things well.
They should go to art school.
Is something bothering you?
No.
-Mom.
-Yes?
Was Dad your first love?
That's right. I was 18.
I guess first loves end easily
and become meaningless.
Listen to this kid.
Why is it meaningless? First love is huge.
It feels like
you're walking down the street,
and someone's suddenly throwing
a bucket of water at you.
It's like having some emotion
pounce on you.
That's what your first love is.
It makes you forget who you used to be
before the water was thrown at you.
Hey. That kid in your class who was
forced to transfer... The cute kid.
Is he still in your group
for the performance assessment?
No, it's over now.
Okay.
That's good.
What is that?
Peas.
Because you're not the same person
you used to be anymore.
The person you used to be
before you met your first love.
I wish I could go back to those times.
We met when we were too immature,
so we ended up breaking up,
but I have no regrets.
That's just how it is.
What am I saying in front of my child?
All done.
Wash up and go to bed.
We finished so quickly.
Come to think of it,
I can't remember either.
The person I used to be
before I met Soo-bin.
Excuse me! You in the checkered shirt...
Are you all right?
From that moment on, I stopped
being the person I used to be.
Okay. Gosh.
Did I gain weight?
I feel sick.
You're so handsome.
Hold on. Where's my bag?
My bag...
I'd like to drive you,
but I feel bad asking the driver.
It's okay. I like this better.
Are you saying you didn't like
having me drive you?
Come on. That's not what I meant.
Bye.
-Have a nice day.
-Thanks.
That's so funny.
Study hard.
Get your head on straight.
Hello.
Were you hiding there?
Yes, I felt a bit... You know.
I brought some young radish kimchi.
We should put it in the kimchi fridge
before we go.
The kimchi fridge?
You didn't have to.
You guys are still...
Math is next, right?
They still are.
-What's this?
-What?
What's wrong with this?
My gosh.
Who did this?
What is this? A wire?
Don't. You'll hurt your hand.
What is this?
Oh, no. Oh, boy.
-What are you doing?
-What?
What are you doing?
Oh, sorry.
I slipped.
You hid my math book,
wrapped that wire around my bag,
and put that ladybug
in my tray too, didn't you?
Me?
No, I didn't.
Is it because of Ro-mi?
No.
Hey. You should try harder
to make Ro-mi like you then.
Instead of taking it out on me.
How?
All she does is stare at you
all the time. What should I do?
Jun-u, you're really...
You should leave! Just transfer!
Go to another school! Get lost!
Are you laughing? Is that funny, you punk?
-Hey.
-Is that funny?
-Hey, don't.
-Let go of me.
-Do you find this funny, you jerk?
-Hey, come here.
I have some good news for you.
It's finally time for
the school trip
that we've all been waiting for!
Aren't you guys happy?
-I hate school.
-It's not just school.
It's a school "trip."
You'll be spending
two nights away from home.
I love it!
This is so annoying.
-Can we not go?
-You have to go.
This is an extension of classes.
Then why don't Hwi-yeong and Jun-u
arrange the schedule
for the school trip? Okay?
Yes, sir.
You all remember the school trip
last year, right?
There's no need for us to waste time.
People who like dancing can prepare
for the talent show.
Pil-sang, put your hand down.
And...
We go on a school trip just once a year.
Why don't we throw
some memorable event together?
Jun-u. The finals and performance
assessments are coming up soon.
And there's the mock exam too.
Let's not waste time
on unnecessary things.
Then...
Why don't those of us who want
to enjoy our school trip
prepare something fun?
Not those who think it's a waste of time.
That sounds good.
I agree.
Me too.
That sounds okay.
Then those who agree to
Jun-u's opinion can stay.
The others can go.
What do you think?
Soo-bin, thank you.
For staying.
Ro-mi, aren't you going
to the group study?
No. I'm staying.
Me too.
Guys, this is the only school trip
this year.
Why don't we all participate?
Don't go?
It's time for our study group.
Lee Gi-tae.
Don't go.
She's right. Don't go.
Gi-tae, you should join us.
You're the student life leader.
I'm sorry.
My god, this is unbelievable.
He left.
Shall we gather around?
Why don't we try something unique
and all wear hanboks?
To promote Korean traditions.
Don't you think the vice-principal
will love that?
Hey. Are we throwing a party
for your grandma or what?
Wearing the same outfit
sounds like a good idea.
Yes, it sounds good.
It doesn't sound bad.
How about this?
We can all wear old clothes
from each of our homes.
This is what I wore on my first date
when I was 18.
Our parents' clothes
that are filled with fond memories.
That sounds good.
But what should I wear?
Retro cosplay?
O-je, wear something cool.
Okay.
What is "retro"?
English.
Prepare something.
Our class vice president's idea is great.
I like it.
It will look really great
if we all wear them.
-Right.
-It will look really cool.
-Yes.
-It will look so pretty, right?
-Yes, it will.
-Hey, thanks.
She got off work around this time,
so she's probably still here.
Hello.
Mr. Oh.
Jun-u, why did you come to work so early?
Oh, the girl who works before me
said she had to leave early.
Oh, really?
Yes.
Is there something you wanted
to say to me?
Yes.
I heard your meeting
with the kids went very well.
You know...
That retro cosplay or something.
You didn't have to come
all the way here to tell me that.
I just felt so proud of you
and wanted to give you a hug.
Good job.
All right, then.
Hwi-yeong, how did your study group go?
I had some more work to do after.
What are you doing here?
Nothing much.
I'm just enjoying the breeze.
You know, our school trip event...
Can't you join us?
Everybody talks about it now.
It's a competition among all the classes.
If we win,
we'll get an extra air purifier
in our classroom,
and we each get two gift certificates too.
We came up with an idea today.
It'd be great if everyone
in the class participates.
You're our class president after all?
Fine, then. Whatever.
Suit yourself.
If you grant me my wish.
We came here often
when we were in elementary school.
After our private lessons.
Behind our moms' backs.
We did.
And whenever my mom caught me,
she practically killed me.
But I didn't know
these game machines were still here.
I know.
Shall we begin, then?
-Okay.
-Let's begin.
Okay.
The game began.
Hwi-yeong, what are you doing?
What if your mom catches you
playing games?
Just go.
What do you want now?
I told you to go.
I don't want to.
My dad told me
that if I saw a sad friend,
then just sit next to him.
Without saying anything.
That's how we share each other's troubles.
Soo-bin.
I feel happy.
I just...
suddenly felt uncomfortable
going out with someone.
Suddenly
during a movie.
This thought came to my mind.
That you must have liked me a lot.
You liked me so much
that you wanted to show me
that text from Jun-u.
Even though you knew it would hurt me.
Was that a moment's jealousy?
I'm sorry.
I was just a bit worried about you.
I'm sorry too
for making you feel that way.
We're old friends.
We're closest friends, right?
Oh, my. This playground
looks completely different now.
There was only sand
when we were little, right?
It's so much better, right?
See you.
I've granted you your wish, so you'll
prepare for the school trip with us, okay?
Bye. Good night.
I can't believe this.
What is this?
What did I walk you home for?
I'll give you another chance
some other time.
Forget it. No more chances left.
Go now.
Soo-bin.
Well...
-That day...
-What?
Actually,
the text...
Soo-bin.
I thought about it,
but it just can't be true.
That you suddenly felt uncomfortable
during the movie.
What are you doing at this hour?
I have a feeling that
there's been a misunderstanding.
Because
your eyes said something else.
What is it?
Later.
Soo-bin.
She says she doesn't want to talk.
Hwi-yeong.
Stay out of it.
Soo-bin.
Go home, Soo-bin. I'll send him back.
Did you believe this?
More than you believe me?
I see.
I did it for you.
I can explain everything.
O-je, do you know where Jun-u lives?
Don't you feel sorry for Soo-bin?
You hurt her.
I think I'll need some time.
Please don't take too long. I'm sorry.
Hwi-yeong, I want you to give some thought
to how you feel about me.
Thank you for coming here yourself
when you're busy.
Wait, Ji-min.
While we're at it, let's win!
Two!
Next up is Go Dong. He's coming--
Is that you, Jun-u?
Subtitle translation by Wayne Ryu