Hello, I'm Choe Jun-u.
I'm Soo-bin's classmate.
Yes, I know.
And?
-I...
-Hey, Jun-u.
We're in a bit of a rush,
so let's talk tomorrow at school.
Let's go, Mom.
Just a second.
May I talk with Soo-bin for a moment?
About what?
I have something I must tell her.
About the research material?
But Chan-yeol gave that to me
this morning at school.
Oh, did she?
We're in the same group
for the literature performance assessment.
So I guess he had something to give me.
Did you come all the way here for that?
Well, it's...
I was around the corner,
and I saw Soo-bin here.
So, is that all?
Yes.
-Let's go.
-Yes, we should go.
Let's go.
Goodbye, ma'am.
I guess your strategy failed.
Although I don't know what it is.
Why did Jun-u come?
Hey.
Ro-mi didn't go yet.
Wait for me.
Are they dating?
Why is Ro-mi dating a guy like him?
What if her parents find out?
They're not dating.
What do you mean?
It's obvious they're dating.
If I were her mom, I'd go crazy.
Why date a guy like him?
Hey.
Why would you be in the same group as him?
It would be bad for your grade.
Our teacher teamed us up.
Of all people...
If I were Hwi-yeong's mom,
I'd go to the school to throw a huge fit.
What were you about to say to Soo-bin?
That you like her?
In front of her mom?
It would've been funny.
Her mom would've fainted on the spot.
See you.
Why like someone if you can't even
tell her confidently?
You don't even have the courage.
You can't help but sigh too, right?
I'm so worried.
Why are all the students so smart?
What should we do about Soo-bin, ma'am?
Each student will be monitored
by several consultants,
and we'll make preparations
depending on the course.
And this is...
I have something I must tell her.
Oh, about the research material?
Oh, did she?
Asking her out, taking action, timing...
Maybe these weren't the problem.
Maybe I was just not qualified.
Why is it so complicated to like someone?
An open class?
We already had one
at the beginning of the semester.
I'd like another one just for Class Three.
For your English class.
For goodness' sake.
You can't trust me, can you?
Hold on.
I'll use this opportunity to...
Welcome.
Hello, there.
What brings you here?
MR. OH'S OPEN CLASS
What is this?
WELCOME!
This is incredible.
I can't believe it.
Mr. Oh.
Keep up the good work.
Wait, you can't step on that.
Gosh, you're really setting an example.
Seriously... Okay.
It's all set.
You can do it, Han-gyeol.
I'll impress all their moms
through this opportunity.
All right, I can do it.
I can...
No. You shouldn't rely on medicine.
You got this, Han-gyeol.
I can do this.
I got this.
Okay. I can...
I can... I can do...
I can do it.
Hello, Ms. Park.
The weather is so hot.
Shall we go?
Hold on, wait for me!
Class Three, right?
-Yes.
-Hello.
My son just transferred here.
I'm Choe Jun-u's mom.
It's nice to meet you all.
Hello, didn't we
-run into each other?
-Yes, hello.
Hello.
-I'm O-je's dad.
-I see, hello.
Are you nervous?
Ro-mi.
Jun-u!
I didn't think my mom
would know about this.
Your mom looks very young.
She's beautiful.
Where's your mom?
My mom couldn't come
because of O-dong, but my dad...
Mr. Jung!
Da-huin.
Hey, thank goodness
your mom couldn't come.
Gosh, my mom should've totally come
so that she could meet his dad.
Stop being ridiculous.
Please come to your senses, Da-huin.
Ro-mi, is your mom coming?
No, she had to go to a conference
in Stockholm.
Good morning, everyone.
All right. Hello, parents.
Well... My gosh, Pil-sang.
This is Class Three's English open class.
Welcome, everyone.
He seems super nervous.
-He's so hyper today.
-Then
let's get started.
Gosh, Mr. Oh. Just teach us
the way you usually do.
-You're being so weird.
-Yes, I agree.
I thought so too.
All right. Then let's get started.
Sang-hun, the bell rang.
You'll be late for your class.
This means this can be included here,
so number two is the answer.
You see, this is...
Number two can be the correct answer too.
But number four works as well
depending on your interpretation.
Because of the wording in the question,
it's possible for anyone to be confused.
Sir.
Just say you're sorry.
Admit that you're ashamed.
This article poses a question
regarding whether or not
our society is led by high achievers
with top grades.
In conclusion, it's important
to cultivate people of talent
in various areas--
Hwi-yeong, let's talk in Korean.
Why? I appreciate how advanced
the level of this class is.
I see. All right, then.
See? The teacher isn't
half as good as his students.
This is why I'm saying
they need an advanced level class.
-Oh, cool.
-They're all at different levels.
Oh Han-gyeol can actually speak English.
What a surprise.
Why am I still speaking English?
Does anyone have a different opinion?
Jun-u, what about you?
Oh, right.
As all of you are aware,
the class vice president position
was vacant for a long time.
But Choe Jun-u
was recently elected
as our class vice president.
Let's give him a big round of
applause to show him our support.
-Congratulations, Jun-u.
-Congratulations, son.
He's my son!
-The newbie?
-He was forced to transfer.
I...
disagree with that opinion.
Sure, one can argue that society is led
by the top one percent of the population.
However, that does not mean everyone else
who doesn't belong
to that one percent is a loser.
In fact, those standards
were set by those with power.
When you're in school, it's your grades.
After you graduate, it's how much you own
and what you do for a living.
Things like that.
So, such numbers shouldn't determine
who is talented or who leads the society.
And I think education should be made
available to all students equally
for them to discover their talents
and contribute to society.
That was good.
Then how about we try to come up
with a counter-argument
to what Jun-u just said
and write it in English?
-We're okay.
-Impressive.
That was so well put.
-I totally agree with him.
-Me too.
Look at you, Jun-u. That was impressive.
How can you speak so eloquently?
It sounded as if
you had a script or something.
I know, right?
As if I had a script.
Jun-u, I'll ask you to share
your opinion during the open class.
So...
Here.
Just say this.
"I disagree with Hwi-yeong's opinion."
What? How do we know
what Hwi-yeong will say?
I don't know. But,
I bet he'll say
the opposite of what's written here.
But what if he doesn't?
He will. Just trust me.
Seriously?
Jun-u, let's be honest.
When the mothers visit our class tomorrow,
they'll probably gossip about you. Right?
You need to show them.
Show them how amazing you are.
You're our class vice president.
Still, scheming like this is...
I don't feel good about it.
Look, kiddo. Sometimes in life,
a little bit of scheming is necessary.
Here.
Memorize it no matter what.
Okay?
Mom. This is my best friend, O-je.
-I see.
-Hello.
Hi, it's nice to meet you.
I'm Lee Yeon-u, Jun-u's mom.
-His dad has been trying so hard.
-Exactly.
-My gosh.
-Soo-bin, isn't your English good?
You guys are almost like native speakers.
Is your name O-je
because you're the fifth child?
No, it's not that.
Hey, Jun-u and O-je.
-Hello.
-Thank you for coming.
-You worked hard.
-No problem.
-May I talk to Jun-u briefly?
-Sure.
Great, thank you.
-Hey, Ro-mi.
-Move.
Ro-mi?
I'm Pil-sang's mom.
-So you're Pil-sang's girlfriend?
-Pardon me?
I heard your father owns a clinic.
We're in the same league, then.
We own a huge leasing business.
I want to marry Pil-sang off as soon as
he graduates from high school.
You're ready too, right?
Am I ready?
Oh, you must already know that
he's an only son for three generations.
-Hey, Yoo Pil-sang!
-What?
She's so feisty. Just like me.
Jun-u.
You did a good job. You really did.
That was amazing. You're the best.
It's all thanks to you. Thank you.
Well, I guess it is.
This is the beginning of
your journey to becoming a cool kid.
I wouldn't go that far.
-See you.
-All right.
I wanted to ask you about your colleague
at the convenience store you work at.
You mean the guy working night shifts?
Who came to the school the other day.
Yes. Is everything okay with him?
Well, I think so.
That's great.
-Why?
-Nothing.
See you.
-We've met, right?
-Where did we meet?
-The bar.
-The loser.
-Well...
-Loser...
Do you live around here?
No. I work part-time here.
Jun-u.
You know Jun-u, right?
I'm his homeroom teacher.
-Who?
-Jun-u.
Oh, you mean Park Yeong-bae.
I'm late for my night shift.
See you around. Bye.
Why can't I get her off my mind?
Why is she so cute?
Jun-u. You know Jun-u, right?
I'm his homeroom teacher.
Park Yeong-bae's homeroom teacher?
So that loser is a teacher?
Totally not my type.
Gosh, I'm soaked in sweat.
-Because your grandma was watching?
-I'm her precious granddaughter.
I didn't open my mouth once during
the class. She must be disappointed.
Why didn't you study harder?
I didn't expect Hwi-yeong to do that.
O-je!
Can we talk?
Maybe after lunch?
No. Right now.
-Go.
-You guys go ahead and eat first.
What's going on?
Did Soo-bin borrow money
from Jun-u or something?
-Right?
-Sorry.
I'm sure there's something going on.
Jun-u.
Soo-bin, where are you going?
Jun-u wants to talk.
The girls are over there.
Have lunch with them.
Sorry.
For what?
For that day.
No. I'm the one who should
apologize for that day.
You came all the way to my place...
That's not what I'm talking about.
That day.
What?
I'm sorry I didn't call you
after telling you I like you
in the nurse's office.
I wanted to call you,
but my phone...
So I even went to your place...
Never mind.
Anyway, it was my first time,
so I didn't know what to do.
Your first time?
What do you mean?
You...
Or anyone...
This is my first time having a crush...
Sit down. Right now. Turn around.
Look over there.
-Sounds nice.
-Yes.
Jun-u!
What does he keep looking at?
It must be that stray cat again.
An adorable stray cat
has been following him around.
Really? I'll have to ask him about it.
Do you like cats?
Of course. I have two at home.
Do you want to take a look?
This one is called Black.
-These guys--
-Sorry, I have to run.
-Sure.
-Bye.
Wait for me!
Well... Have the moms left?
Not yet. They walk pretty slowly.
Anyway, I have to go.
Soo-bin.
Later. Let's talk later.
Gosh, this is embarrassing.
Do you want to go to the movies?
This Saturday.
Let me know if there's a movie
you want to watch. I'll buy the tickets.
Oh, my.
Anyway, call me.
What about Ro-mi?
Isn't she your girlfriend?
I hate two-timers
more than anything in the world.
I'm not two-timing anyone.
She's not my girlfriend.
I'm not even interested in her.
At all.
There's only one person...
that I like.
Call me.
Only one?
By the way...
Yes? What is it?
The moms are gone now.
Maybe I should have recorded him
or something.
I'm getting confused again.
No, Soo-bin. It's real.
It happened for real.
Oh, Ro-mi.
Did something good happen?
What? Not really.
Did you already finish your lunch?
What did Jun-u say?
Ro-mi, I have something to tell you.
Soo-bin.
Something has been bothering me.
Can I talk to you about it?
After school today.
Okay.
I don't have any secrets.
The more effort you put in,
the more you see.
They say, her kid's grades
and the level of the kid's college
determine the mother's grade in life.
That's right.
Gi-tae's success is my success.
-Oh, my.
-I'm working all the time.
I sometimes wonder what I'm doing.
It's so hard to make a living.
A Seoul National University graduate
shouldn't say that.
Competent people like you
should work hard to contribute to society.
That's how Korea will become
a better country.
"Competent"? That's really flattering.
Please take good care of
this incompetent working mom.
-I'm kissing up to you.
-Oh, gosh.
You're so funny.
By the way, you look really young.
If you don't mind me asking,
what year did you graduate?
I didn't go to university.
I'm 37.
Somehow, I ended up giving birth
to Jun-u a bit early.
I guess you were young and reckless.
I think you're right.
So that explains it.
That's why your son was so carefree.
By the way, I think we need something
like a parent qualifying exam.
Just because you give birth, doesn't
mean you're qualified to be a parent.
-Right?
-Yes.
Are you saying I'm unqualified
to be a mom or something?
Why do you think that?
Isn't it time for your husband to return?
Isn't he an exchange professor right now?
-Hello?
-He won't be back until summer break.
Soo-bin's mom and dad are
both so talented.
-I know.
-I envy her.
What's the use?
She should get good grades.
Just like Hwi-yeong.
That's true.
There's an old saying.
After you become 40,
your whole life depends on
how your child turns out.
-That's true.
-That's what counts.
I knew it. There's never a day
you don't insult me, is there?
You sneaky rat.
-Such a headache, though.
-Yes, you're right.
Don't you think this cake is too sweet?
-It is.
-It's a bit too sweet.
This tea is too sweet too.
Hello.
Aren't you Mr. Jo's son?
Yes. I came here to tell you something.
Hold on. So are you saying that
we coaxed the math teacher--
I mean, that we persuaded him
to give credit
for all choices of Question 15?
Yes.
Make things go back to how they were.
Then I'll keep my lips sealed.
Sealed? What are you talking about?
Sang-hun. Mr. Jo...
I mean your father.
You know he is doing well at work
thanks to Hwi-yeong's dad, right?
-As a son, you shouldn't--
-I don't care about any of that.
Just make things go back to how they were.
Make things go back?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Forget it. Go.
I know everything.
About Hwi-yeong stealing Mr. Son's watch
and blaming Jun-u for it.
And also about you saving him
from similar incidents before.
I even gathered all the proof.
Are you
threatening me right now?
It's a negotiation.
Seeing that you consider this as a threat,
I guess you do feel guilty.
You rude little punk!
So,
please make things go back
to the way they were.
What?
My mom told me
that Jo Sang-hun met your mom.
I think it's because of
Question 15 of the math test.
Welcome home, ma'am...
That cocky little brat.
It's me. Hear me out even if you're busy.
It's about Hwi-yeong.
What a bunch of show-offs.
I can't even stand being around you!
Right. From now on,
I'll become a passionate mom too.
There's nothing I can't do for my son.
What is it you want to talk about?
I like Jun-u.
I don't know why I feel this way.
He's not even that smart or rich.
Isn't it funny?
Actually, my family is going through
a rough patch lately.
My parents are on bad terms,
and my dad's hospital is
struggling financially too.
Even my grades are dropping.
Everything is stressing me out,
but whenever I see Jun-u, I feel...
What should I say?
I feel better.
I don't know if I expressed that right.
Anyway.
It's like
walking on a rough and dirty road
in the rain and unexpectedly
finding a pretty umbrella.
I feel like it'll make me feel much better
if I walk under the umbrella.
But I don't think Jun-u likes me.
I think there's someone he likes.
Do you know?
Who Jun-u likes.
I'm not sure.
Shall we eat something else?
You'll feel better
if you eat something sweet.
Do you have something on your mind too?
What is it?
I wonder what's good here.
The brownies here are amazing.
Hey. When did you get here?
Sorry.
I didn't mean to eavesdrop.
I was just taking a nap.
But that's not important right now.
I heard everything.
-My gosh.
-Unbelievable.
-My goodness.
-I knew it. Something felt strange.
That's why you looked so uncomfortable
when you were eating that brownie.
What do I do?
If Ro-mi finds out later,
she'll be heartbroken.
What should I do?
Yoo Soo-bin.
You deserve a beating first.
How could you hide a shocking story
like that from us? You traitor.
That's right. You're a traitor
who doesn't care about friendship.
I'll beat you up first!
Guys, stop. You'll hurt her.
You might wake up her grandma.
Fine, hit me.
Hit me all you want,
so I can get a grip on myself.
Soo-bin, you're totally in love.
You're right.
Hitting her will be useless.
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
Have a good day.
Soo-bin. Do you want to go to the movies?
Movies.
What does it say?
You look like some kind of cult leader,
Chan-yeol.
Come on, what does it say?
Check that.
It's probably my mom.
-What does it say?
-Check it.
It's probably him.
I told you, it's my mom.
-Did you decide on the movie?
-Gosh.
Choe Jun-u?
"Did you decide on the movie?"
This is awesome. How did you know?
-Are you a shaman or what?
-Maybe this is the path for me.
Did you see that?
Not yet.
Take your time.
"Take your time"?
This is unbelievable.
I've never seen Jun-u
being nice to someone like this.
Are you working? Keep up the good work!
Another couple? Congratulations, Soo-bin.
No. Not yet. There's Ro-mi.
What should we do about Ro-mi?
So how did the results come out?
Oh... These cards are...
I don't know in detail,
-but they look good.
-They do look good.
These guys are dancing here,
and there are even fireworks.
Right. This is a good sign, right?
Yes... It is a good sign.
Soo-bin, congratulations.
-Congratulations.
Congratulations.
-Sang-hun.
-What do you mean?
Pretend nothing happened?
Did Hwi-yeong's dad tell you that?
Take a seat.
I'm just in a bit of a bind.
It's not a big deal if you try
to see it in a different light.
Why? Are they going to fire you
or something?
I might have to leave my job
because of it.
So please be understanding
about it just this once, okay?
Let it slide just this one time. Please?
No, I can't do that.
I don't care whether you get fired or not.
Sang-hun.
I'll clean it up for you.
Thank you. Sang-hun.
Sang-hun!
So you're saying...
I'm getting kicked out
of the class, right?
What are you talking about?
You're the ace of the class.
I'm starting another class. That's all.
I want to gather
top students from other schools
including you,
so just join my new class, Sang-hun.
Hwi-yeong's mom is so fast.
And your reaction is even faster.
Sang-hun, don't get the wrong idea.
Well understood. I'll quit.
And don't include my name
in your promotional materials.
If you include my name in the list
of your students who got into SNU,
I'll sue you.
Hwi-yeong.
Sang-hun will also participate
in the upcoming math competition.
Pardon me?
You said he wouldn't be participating.
He applied, Hwi-yeong.
Just compete fair and square, okay?
2ND GRADE TEACHERS' OFFICE
Hey, look at this.
Does someone have a crush on you?
Yes, obviously.
You know what?
A guy in 1st grade gave it to him.
-Hey.
-Keep it a secret.
-Secret.
-I'm just going to eat this.
Sir, please forgive my son
just this one time.
I'll try to persuade Sang-hun again.
If persuading him was going to work,
he wouldn't have dared to talk
to my wife in the first place.
She said he threatened her
giving her murderous looks.
How dare he...
I apologize, ma'am.
I'm sorry, sir.
Sir... I can't be shunted off right now.
You know that my eldest daughter
is studying abroad now.
This is a very important time for her.
Please have mercy, sir.
Please help us out.
Sang-hun.
You should apologize to Hwi-yeong.
Dad, are you crazy? I would've been
top of my year. He stole it from me.
Sang-hun, I'm satisfied
with the marks you got.
You know it's not about that.
This is about my pride.
It was rude of you
to do that to his parents.
Is that what Hwi-yeong's mom said?
Does she even realize
what kind of jerk her son is?
Sang-hun, just let it go.
-It's not a big deal.
-How is it not a big deal?
Dad, you have no pride?
I'll tell everyone about it.
Sang-hun, let it go for my sake. Please?
Stop talking such nonsense!
Gosh, seriously.
Every single time... Damn it!
It's all because I'm incompetent.
Dad, why are you saying
you're incompetent?
I'm sorry, son.
All right, Jun-u. I want you
to tell everyone in class
these three things
as the class vice president.
Look. "Actively encourage
each other's learning activities
and help each other out
so that everyone can improve
their grades."
It basically means
that everyone should get along
and study hard.
-Yes.
-Such big words...
Right. I'd like you to put together
a preparation committee
for the school trip.
And everyone has to submit
travel journals afterward. Okay?
What's wrong?
Well, you're talking about
managing the class out of the blue,
so my brain feels a bit overwhelmed.
Then just go and read this aloud.
Well, okay.
You can't be like this
when you're the class vice president.
Come on, you're my right-hand man.
That's a bit too much.
Anyway, I just want you to tell
these three things
to everyone in class, okay?
Good?
Oh, one more thing.
Hey, Sang-hun! Congratulations.
His dad has been promoted to
the manager of the branch in Singapore.
Sang-hun, are you moving there too?
Yes.
It's happening so fast.
Apparently, this is his last day here.
Really? I'm sad, Sang-hun.
I know. I'll miss you.
Is Sang-hun moving there
because he can't get first place?
What's wrong with that? If he can be
successful, that's all that matters.
I'm jealous.
Then ask your parents
to send you to a school overseas.
Your family is rich.
I don't want to move away from home.
Girls, let's go for lunch.
-What?
-I'll beat you girls.
Hey, wait up!
-Go ahead.
-Let's go have lunch.
Let's go eat.
Let's eat.
Sang-hun.
Don't talk to me. I'm not in the mood.
I'm surprised.
I didn't think you'd ever give up.
Look who's talking.
You were forced to transfer here.
You are giving up.
You used to tease Hwi-yeong and
constantly go up against Hwi-yeong.
What happened to that spirit?
Shut your mouth.
You don't even know anything.
Even I'm still staying here,
although I was forced to transfer here.
I considered running away back then too
but holding out actually helped me
figure out a solution.
Had I run away back then,
I would've regretted it forever.
I feel great about my decision.
Go away.
Then how about a showdown
before you leave?
With the newbie
that was forced to transfer here.
We'll start on the count of three, okay?
No.
When that's gone.
Where is it headed?
Hey, where are you going?
Singapore... Darn it.
How many laps?
One? Two?
-Jo Sang-hun.
-What are you doing here?
-Did really you see it?
-See what?
Me stealing the watch.
-What?
-Did you see it?
Did it feel unfair back then?
What? Are they running again?
Hwi-yeong.
I think the school nurse is out.
Well, is there something I can do for you?
Hwi-yeong, wait.
Oh, my gosh.
What? Don't you trust me?
Don't worry. You might not believe it,
but I was a medic in the military.
All right.
Gosh, you startled me.
I haven't even touched you yet.
Here we go.
Gosh, that must sting.
There you go.
You're done.
Hwi-yeong.
Are you doing okay?
I mean, if something's bothering you,
you can always talk to me.
That might take a load off your mind.
Even though I didn't graduate
from a university in Seoul,
I have some experience
in counseling others.
What do you know?
You didn't graduate from
Seoul National University.
You didn't even go to a university
in Seoul.
What do you know?
Nothing's bothering me.
Thanks anyway.
All right.
Hwi-yeong. Are you doing okay?
Sorry. Did I startle you?
No.
Come to think of it,
the study leader has to be the strongest.
Carrying things all the time...
-I am strong. Give them to me.
-Just until there.
Have you decided on the movie?
We should buy the tickets soon.
Well... The thing is...
I've given it some thought...
Is that what happened?
Hey. Come.
Why are we hiding?
I'm not sure.
Anyway, let me know
which movie you want to watch.
I'll carry them to the classroom.
Well...
Are you going to give up
on your love because of Ro-mi?
I wouldn't call this love.
Let's call Ro-mi. We have to settle this.
No. Ro-mi is not in a good mood
these days.
Her family is in a bit of a situation.
Isn't that just another lie?
-She lies all the time.
-I agree.
She's like that.
We've been hanging out with her
because you begged us to.
She used to have no friends at all.
She's so stuck-up.
Stop it. I don't really want
to talk behind her back.
Anyway, it's probably best
not to tell her for the time being.
So please help me, okay?
I think we should do as Soo-bin says.
Fine, we'll help you.
On one condition.
Go to the movies with him.
Yes. It's not like you guys are
cheating on anyone.
Jun-u and Ro-mi weren't
together or anything.
We'll cover everything for you.
Gosh, you're only 18 once.
-What is this?
-She's right.
Soo-bin, go.
-Will you?
-Go.
Go to the movies at least.
There's nothing wrong with it.
-Of course not.
-There's nothing wrong with it.
-It's just a movie.
-Exactly.
Get one coke too.
-Popcorn too. A small one.
-Get just one coke.
I'm so jealous.
Are you jealous?
I'll go to the movies with O-je too.
You didn't have to do this.
Eat it at home.
You must be hungry after your shift.
-I should have packed fries too.
-Hey.
-Good night.
-See you.
All right.
Jun-u.
What's this?
-What?
-Are you and Soo-bin going out?
What?
"Soo-bin said this was a secret,
but I'll let you know.
Jun-u and Soo-bin are
our class's couple number two.
Exclamation mark."
You...
Well... It's...
not that serious yet.
Da-huin has a big mouth.
Are we really best friends?
How could you keep this big news from me?
-I was going to tell you, but...
-But?
Things got a little complicated.
Complicated?
Oh, that explains why Chan-yeol...
Because of that, my head was a total mess.
But all the puzzle pieces
have just fallen into place.
Jun-u, you're incredible.
You were dating a girl
without your best friend knowing?
-That's not it.
-Unbelievable.
-You completely blew my mind.
-Hey.
-Yes?
-It's not like that.
Yes, it is like that.
You got this completely wrong.
I didn't get anything wrong.
It says everything here.
Do you want to see it?
I just have to scroll down.
No. Let's just talk tomorrow.
-Go back in now.
-Tomorrow?
-Tomorrow it is.
-Just go.
Soo-bin and Jun-u are
watching a movie together tomorrow.
They're going out now.
Should I have bought some clothes?
What should I wear?
Soo-bin!
Yes! Coming!
-Come eat!
-Okay! Just a second!
Come out!
Are you coming?
Yes, I'm coming right now!
Gosh, what a waste.
What should I wear?
Let me see.
Why do all my clothes look the same?
What do you think looks good?
You don't know? Neither do I.
Not this.
Not this either.
I have to sleep. I have to.
Soo-bin, go to sleep now.
Good sleep makes your skin look better.
Better skin.
This is not good.
I have to sleep.
Oh, my gosh. My face is so swollen!
I came out an hour early.
How stupid of me.
Why did I come out so early?
I still have ten minutes.
Jun-u probably isn't here yet.
You're here.
Oh. I'm sorry for being late.
You're not late.
You're ten minutes early.
Shall we go?
I'll hold this.
Thanks.
This isn't cold at all.
There's no ice in here.
Well... It's been a while
since I bought it.
I guess they all melted.
You came early too.
-I'll go get a new one.
-No.
I don't like cold drinks.
This will do.
Let's go.
Okay.
Excuse me. Your tickets...
Oh, sorry.
This situation is always in dramas.
But this popcorn seems a bit too big.
Oh, cell phones.
What is it?
It's nothing.
What's wrong?
Was he really using me?
I can't let him take her away from me.
I can't let that happen.
I understand.
You must've been so desperate.
-Lee Yeon-u...
-Ms. Yoon Song-hui?
Still, this won't work, right?
If you did, I think this is
a very serious situation.
Do you want another tissue?
And don't tell Jun-u
that I know about this.
Because that would hurt my pride.
You can let me know what I did wrong.
I'll fix it.
It's finally time for the school trip!
Why don't those of us who want to
enjoy our school trip
prepare something fun?
Not those who think it's a waste of time.
You know, our school trip event...
Can't you join us?
If you grant me my wish.
You must have liked me a lot.
Soo-bin.
Subtitle translation by Wayne Ryu