Because you were out of line.
You started to raise doubts about me
instead of getting lost quietly.
How dare you do that...
to me.
You should eat something.
Hey, what are you doing?
-Jun-u.
-Hey, Jun-u.
Hey, stop him!
Stop them.
Hey, Jun-u, stop!
Jun-u, what's wrong? Jun-u!
Jun-u, stop!
He really said that to you earlier?
But why did you hit Hwi-yeong then?
You said Gi-tae was the one who paid them.
Why did you hit Hwi-yeong?
Because the one controlling Gi-tae
is Hwi-yeong.
Hwi-yeong?
Come on. Why would Hwi-yeong do that?
Hwi-yeong. Are you really okay?
Don't you have to go to the hospital?
I'm fine.
By the way,
why did Jun-u hit you all of a sudden?
Did something happen between you two?
No.
Jun-u is probably
mentally unstable right now.
I heard they've been best friends
since childhood.
I guess his emotions suddenly exploded.
I understand.
Do you remember the guys who came earlier
to pay their respects?
Did they say something to him?
What would they say to him?
Oh, my math teacher called me.
Just a second.
Why isn't he picking up?
The person you have called
is not available.
-You're getting a call.
-What?
7 MISSING CALLS
HWI-YEONG
-What?
-What happened?
It's my tutor.
It's nothing serious.
Emergency.
Tutoring apartment in 30 minutes.
So-ye, my tutor wants to start
early today.
I have to go now.
-So suddenly?
-I have a lesson.
Sorry. I'll get going.
Continue practicing.
I'll message you later.
Jun-u, hang in there, okay?
Let's talk again.
Okay.
All right. Go back in.
Jun-u.
See you at school.
It must be so hard for Jun-u.
Yes. He's probably staying here
until his friend's family arrives.
Thank you all, guys.
Hwi-yeong, are you okay?
Yes.
I hope Jun-u will
pull himself together soon.
I'm worried.
Right.
Let's go.
How strange. Why am I feeling this way?
My heart aches a little.
Jeong-hu,
what do I do now?
What...
am I supposed to do?
Gi-tae, did you give them money?
Are you crazy?
I had no choice. They said
they wouldn't do it without getting paid.
You told me to drive Jun-u away
by all means.
Jun-u's friend died.
If things go wrong,
we might take all the blame.
What are you talking about?
I mean... Why?
I don't know!
He had a car accident on his way to work
after quitting school.
What will you do if someone finds out
you paid those guys?
Hwi-yeong, you said you'd take
responsibility if there's any problem.
That depends on the problem. Did I--
Did I tell you to pay them?
What should I do?
What do I do?
-What do I do now?
-Why are you asking me?
So-ye.
What are you doing here?
So-ye!
Are you guys dating?
Does she know what we did?
So-ye.
Did you follow me?
Why?
So the rumor was true.
Lee Gi-tae is Ma Hwi-yeong's minion.
So-ye, that's not it.
How could you even do...
I'm disappointed in you, Gi-tae.
What's with So-ye?
She's not picking up her phone.
She ignored all my messages yesterday too.
Seriously, what's going on?
I'm back.
Did it go well?
Are you okay?
What about O-je?
Where's my O-je?
He's at the store.
How is Jun-u holding up?
Not very well.
They've been best friends since childhood.
Guys, just a second.
Soo-bin, you're taking
Mr. Son's class today, right?
Stay with Hwi-yeong.
The midterm's coming soon. Ask him
in detail how he's preparing.
Isn't it so great?
-You're in the same class as him.
-Yes.
Okay.
Did you find out?
Your level test score for Mr. Son's class.
You said you'd find out
whether you passed or not.
There you go again.
Ro-mi, do you really think
this is a good time for that?
-Do you want to know?
-Yes.
Pack up.
You're quitting? Why?
You won't let me know my level test score.
It doesn't really feel right.
Also, I prefer studying alone.
Still, this is too sudden.
I'm sorry.
I brought a friend who wants to see you.
Ro-mi.
Hello.
I'm Soo-bin's friend, Hwang Ro-mi.
I'm also close to Hwi-yeong.
I see. Hi.
Please let me take the level test.
What?
I'm trying to get you
into Hwi-yeong's math class.
They don't let just anyone
take a level test for that class.
-What are we doing right now?
-Just follow me.
Soo-bin wants to be in Mr. Son's class?
Yes. I talked to Mr. Son,
and he said we need your permission.
No. You did the right thing, Soo-bin.
Where are you going, Soo-bin?
Are you looking for Hwi-yeong?
-Where is Hwi-yeong?
-Where is he?
Hwi-yeong.
Soo-bin.
Why are you so startled?
I'm not. Let's go.
I...
quit the class.
Why?
It didn't feel right.
Please don't tell my mom
for the time being.
Soo-bin.
I'm sorry. You went through
so much trouble for me.
Please understand me.
By the way...
Never mind.
What is it? Say it.
When Jun-u was hitting you earlier,
why didn't you hit him back?
To me,
it seemed like you were letting him
hit you on purpose.
Who would do that on purpose?
I just couldn't dodge him.
By the way,
why did you...
What?
Never mind.
You must have been shocked today.
Go home and get some rest.
I'll talk to Mr. Son.
So come to the next class, okay?
See?
Hello.
From what I can tell,
you're not dating Yeong-bae.
Do you have a crush on him?
Who's Yeong-bae?
Park Yeong-bae.
You know, the kid who works here.
That's what everyone calls him here.
You mean Jun-u.
Kiddo, give him up while I'm being nice.
I've already called dibs on Yeong-bae.
Give who up?
It's not like that, lady.
What? Lady?
Hey! I'm not a lady. I was born in 1998!
Darn it. You have such
a handsome boyfriend. Don't be so greedy.
More soda, please.
Okay, just a minute.
Two extreme combos, please.
Oh, the extreme combo.
Dad, two extreme combos.
-Yes, sir!
-Okay.
Okay. Here's your soda.
Have a good night!
-Bye.
-Come again.
-I'll be waiting!
-Bye.
O-je.
Da-huin.
Are you really going to do this?
You keep ignoring my texts.
You won't call me or take my calls.
What kind of boyfriend does that?
It's been pretty hectic today.
-Sorry.
-O-je!
-Yes.
-The extreme combos.
-Here you go.
-Father.
It's nice to meet you.
Who...
I'm O-je's girlfriend, Kwon Da-huin.
It's nice to meet you.
Girlfriend?
O-je has a girlfriend?
Of course.
It's our third day already.
Should I serve this now?
Yes, over there.
O-je.
Enjoy.
You punk.
Why didn't you tell me
you had a girlfriend?
She's so pretty too.
She's not.
-She's not, what?
-She's not.
-Welcome.
Welcome.
That way, please.
Hi, Jun-u. Are you going home?
Who is it?
Your name is Geon-hyeok, right?
Why did you tell Jun-u
that a kid in my class paid you guys?
Why?
So that Jun-u wouldn't get the wrong idea.
Jeong-hu didn't die because of us.
Yes, he quit school and left...
because we bullied him, but...
he got into a car accident
while going home from work.
I already got into so much trouble.
That's why I'm in here.
If that gets tacked on as well, I'm dead.
Is it true that a student from my class
gave you money?
Yes, but it wasn't much.
Gi-tae, that bastard.
We asked him to give us money,
and he got scared and gave it to us.
I see.
Still, I'd like you to testify
to what you did do wrong.
Please do that.
You can say exactly what you saw, right?
Yes.
Okay.
Thank you, Geon-hyeok.
Thank you.
-Really?
-That's right.
Geon-hyeok promised me that he'd do it.
I informed the school too.
Let's all get together tomorrow,
hear the whole story
and figure it all out.
I think Gi-tae must have had
his reasons for doing that.
Don't be too upset, kid.
Okay.
Thank you.
You're thankful, right?
See? Things work out.
Life isn't completely unfair, okay?
Let's change things up.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Okay.
You said you'd take responsibility
if there's any problem.
That depends on the problem. Did I--
Did I tell you to pay them?
So-ye, please answer my calls. Please?
God, you scared me.
That's ridiculous.
Did they say
I paid them to get you expelled?
It wasn't you.
Hwi-yeong made you do it.
That's probably why he was
looking for you so desperately.
It's true that I paid them.
The truth is...
my little brother is a troublemaker.
He got into an argument with them
while playing a game together,
and they got into a scuffle.
I met them to take care of that.
Gi-tae.
You know, right?
That Hwi-yeong will weasel out of this,
and that you will take the fall
for the whole thing.
Just tell the truth tomorrow
-that Hwi-yeong made you do it.
-He had nothing to do with it.
I just...
My friend died because of you guys.
If you cover for Hwi-yeong,
do you think he'll have your back?
Why are you so loyal to him?
Isn't it so he'll help you
get into a good college?
Gi-tae.
Do the right thing.
Or you'll regret it later.
Jun-u.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Jun-u.
I'll get on my knees.
Can't you forgive me
just this once? Please?
Can't you just let it slide
just this once?
Jun-u, I'm really sorry.
Please be understanding
and let it slide just this once.
Your life is already ruined,
but mine is different.
I've been doing well until now.
I've worked really hard.
My mom and dad...
They have high expectations of me.
I'm the only one in my family
who can make it to college.
Please.
Gi-tae.
No life is "already ruined."
We're only 18.
Both you
and me.
And Jeong-hu.
I have faith that you have a conscience.
Don't worry.
I won't tell the others
that you and Gi-tae are going out.
I heard everything...
you and Gi-tae said.
What?
I won't tell the others either.
But...
make sure nothing happens to Gi-tae.
Like what?
If anything happens to him,
I won't...
just stand by.
Son, you're home.
Son.
What's wrong with your face?
Who did this to you?
Are you okay? Let's go to the hospital.
We need to get a medical certificate.
Let's go.
Mom.
-Dad's not home yet, right?
-No, he's running late.
You're lucky he's coming late.
What in the world is this?
Come on, let's go to the hospital.
Mom.
Help me.
LEE GI-TAE
Jun-u, are you home?
Are you okay?
Of course, he's not okay.
Mom.
I was so worried about you.
So I thought I should be with you today.
The house is a total mess.
You should've cleaned.
Goodness, look at your desk.
-Do you want some?
-No, it's okay.
Jun-u!
I bought two.
I peeled mine like this.
-This is delicious.
-It really is.
Jun-u.
I'll go buy some water.
But we have water.
What is wrong with him?
Jun-u will be here today, right?
He probably will.
He called O-je yesterday.
-He asked where Gi-tae lived.
-Da-huin.
Good morning.
Why did Jun-u ask where Gi-tae lived?
My god. The newbie got himself
into some serious trouble.
It's beyond our imagination.
How could he even think
of hitting Hwi-yeong?
I guess he doesn't care about
his school life at all.
He has some guts, that's for sure.
Pil-sang, where did you hear that?
I was called to the teacher's office
just now.
I happened to overhear
the vice-principal scolding Jun-u.
"How could you hit Hwi-yeong?
He went to the funeral hall
to comfort you.
-You punk..."
-Pil-sang.
-What?
-Be quiet.
-She's telling you to be quiet.
-Is it true?
Is that why Hwi-yeong didn't come
today? Is he hurt?
It's not that bad.
Did you know about it?
Gi-tae, they want you to come
to the counseling room.
What? Why is Gi-tae being summoned?
I got it.
Lee Gi-tae, Ma Hwi-yeong, Choe Jun-u.
There must be a big incident involving
these three that we don't know about.
What do you mean,
an incident we don't know about?
It's just because Gi-tae is
Hwi-yeong's best friend.
No, his best friend is Soo-bin.
Pil-sang, go take your seat.
Hwi-yeong,
is it really true Jun-u hit you?
-It doesn't look that bad.
-Hey. Pil-sang.
What?
I'm so curious about what happened.
Hwi-yeong, is it true?
You think Jun-u's a gangster?
Why would he hit me for no reason?
Let's quiet down and study.
Of course, Jun-u is a gangster.
Why can't we call a gangster
a gangster? This is so messed up.
Hwi-yeong's just trying to play it cool.
I know. He's not even good at fighting.
-Hwi-yeong.
-Oh, no.
-My gosh. Are you okay?
-Jun-u.
-Yes.
-Your mom called me this morning.
Do you know how surprised I was?
I'm okay, sir.
-Go on inside.
-Okay.
Mr. Oh, you're not the homeroom teacher
of Class Three now.
You shouldn't join us for today's meeting.
Wait. But I was the one
who reported to you about this incident,
and I even talked to the students
from Byeongmun High School.
As the assistant teacher.
Yes, good job.
But...
the homeroom teacher of Class Three
will be returning soon.
I believe you should clear out
his space before his return. Bye.
But still, sir...
Mr. Lee?
It's taking longer than I thought.
What is going on?
Why is it taking so long?
Geon-hyeok, can you repeat
what you said to Jun-u?
Detective. I heard Lee Gi-tae
gave Geon-hyeok and his friends money.
Can you ask him if it's true?
We heard Lee Gi-tae paid you
and your friends. Is that true?
Geon-hyeok?
I didn't receive any money.
Then is it true
that you tried to lure Jun-u
into a fight
and get him expelled from school?
No.
That's odd...
-I'm sorry.
-It's okay.
He is
a transfer student.
My mom took care of everything.
Thanks. Thanks, Hwi-yeong.
Did you really think I'd abandon you?
Earlier, I was just so upset.
You understand that, right?
Of course, I do.
You're the friend I trust the most.
See? Things work out.
Life isn't completely unfair, okay?
Let's change things up.
-I'll see you tomorrow.
-Okay.
Why does he sound so hopeless?
You stupid idiot.
You're worse than the kids.
Do you call yourself a teacher?
A grown-up?
You worthless...
Are you even a teacher?
Jun-u.
Your closest friend just died.
You must be so heartbroken and angry.
That day,
you must have wanted to relieve
your extreme stress at the moment
as a means of self-defense,
to protect yourself.
In such a situation,
it is hard to control yourself,
which can lead to an impulsive
display of violence and aggression.
It can happen to anyone.
Even I have been in that situation.
That's why I don't believe
your violent behavior defines you.
During adolescence...
It went well.
That's a relief.
You're lucky
that your dad didn't find out.
This should never happen again. Ever.
-Do you understand?
-Yes.
I'm sorry, Mom.
HOW DID HE GO
FROM A REGULAR EMPLOYEE TO A CEO?
Hwi-yeong.
-Mr. Oh.
-I heard how the meeting went.
Jun-u got the wrong idea
about you and Gi-tae.
Yes.
He's wrong, right?
Of course.
Right.
There's no way you would have lied.
Hwi-yeong.
Well... I want to apologize.
Now that I look back,
I think I was seeing the situation
only from Jun-u's perspective.
I must have felt sorry
for what Jun-u was going through.
But you're my student too.
I'm sorry I suspected you
even for a short while.
It's okay. Jun-u is disadvantaged here.
You just wanted to be
on the side of the disadvantaged.
It's understandable.
Thank you for everything.
"Disadvantaged."
Did you have lunch?
I hope I didn't apologize to you
for no reason.
I really do.
You must be so relieved now.
Isn't it so nice? Whether you're
a homeroom teacher or just an assistant,
taking charge of a class is such a hassle.
That's not what I mean.
-Mr. Oh.
-Sir, listen.
I mean, you can't say that now.
Don't you think?
Hey. No. You...
Mr. Oh!
Hold on. No. Just a second.
Mr. Oh. Let's...
Mr. Oh.
What was that?
As a means of self-defense,
Choe Jun-u acted violently out of anger?
Is that what the teachers said?
Well, it's what they're guessing,
at least.
I don't know.
They kept using big words like that.
How did Jun-u react?
Didn't he try to smash anything?
He looked blank.
As if he didn't care about anything.
Has he completely given up?
What is he going to do now?
He totally got on the wrong side
of the teachers.
O-je said Jun-u's a good kid, though.
Gosh, he must have completely given up.
Where are you going?
If you're here to ask me
if I'm okay, don't. I'm not.
I'm not here to ask you that.
Something happened
between you and Hwi-yeong, right?
That's why
you beat him up
at the funeral hall, right?
Were you upset that I beat up Hwi-yeong?
You're his girlfriend, after all.
How could you say that?
Even though I might not be able
to be of much help,
I wanted to help
in case you were treated unfairly.
Why would you help me?
Out of pity?
I was forced to transfer
and keep getting in trouble.
And I just lost my only friend.
Is that why?
It's not out of pity.
Cut it out.
I don't need
a sheltered kid like you pitying me.
I'm fine.
I've been holding back
my anger well all this time.
And why am I taking it out on her now?
To be honest,
I just wanted to see you.
I don't know why.
If I made you even angrier, I'm sorry.
Oh, my. I have some shocking news.
Oh Han-gyeol quit.
-What?
-Seriously?
-Why?
-Really?
Yes. I heard he quit.
So suddenly?
Pil-sang, will you sit down?
Hwi-yeong.
Did Mr. Oh really quit?
Yes. I don't know exactly what happened,
but something must have come up.
And our homeroom teacher got sick again
and went back to the hospital.
It'll be a while before we get
a new homeroom teacher.
The midterm's next week.
I knew something didn't feel right.
I'll post which chapters will be
on the exam on our online community.
I'll also upload summaries
of each subject, so you can use them.
-That'd be great.
-You're the best.
-You're amazing.
-Nice.
I love you.
I don't need it.
I hope you all will get
good grades this time.
The summaries are only to be shared
within our class.
Of course.
If we share them with friends outside
the class, it'll only hurt us.
-That's right.
-Ro-mi is always right.
Mr. Oh!
-What happened?
-What?
Mr. Oh.
-Please continue.
-I'm done. You can say goodbye.
Mr. Oh, what happened?
Are you really quitting?
That's not fair!
Can't you at least stay
until the homeroom teacher comes back?
-Stay until then!
-That's right!
-Please stay!
-Stay!
Guys, you're just making him feel bad.
Let's not say anything about it.
Thank you for everything, Mr. Oh.
Please give us some nice parting words.
Sure. Okay.
What I want to say is...
Jun-u. Are you leaving?
I don't need to tell you, do I?
You're not our teacher anymore.
Jun-u.
Hey, you.
Just hear me out, okay?
These aren't parting words!
I mean, I was just going to quit,
but I changed my mind.
You guys kind of grew on me too.
And...
it's really hard to get a job these days.
Plus, it's a very secure job.
That's his true self.
Seriously. I can't believe we fell for it.
And one more thing.
From this moment forth,
the official homeroom teacher
for Class Three of the second grade,
is me, Oh Han-gyeol.
It's nice to meet you!
Mr. Oh. Are you
our real homeroom teacher now?
Was I a fake before?
Applause!
Yes! Awesome!
CLASS THREE, MR. KIM
What?
Hello?
Mr. Oh. Mr. Oh Han-gyeol!
Stop. Stop for a minute.
Gosh. I said to stop. I got you.
You said I should take my hands off it.
So I'm taking my hands
-off everything.
-Hey. Hold on.
Please stay
until we get a temp to fill in.
Class Three's homeroom teacher
is going back to the hospital.
Help me out here.
Oh, right.
I'm sorry. I apologize.
I'm sorry too. I apologize.
Mr. Oh.
Be the assistant teacher
until we get a new homeroom teacher.
No. I will not be an assistant teacher.
Mr. Oh. Please.
Make me
their homeroom teacher.
Awesome!
My gosh. Keep it down.
Hwi-yeong. Gi-tae.
Yes?
I am now your homeroom teacher.
So I wanted to make things clear.
I'll keep my eye on you.
You understand, right?
Sure.
Okay. Looking forward to it.
SEOUL JUVENILE
CLASSIFICATION REVIEW CENTER
Jun-u.
Are you going to work?
It must be hard for you
especially with exams coming up.
Gi-tae.
Are you happy now?
Since your life wasn't ruined?
-What does he mean?
-You're so random.
What's his problem?
Let's go.
Jun-u.
We had a nice funeral for Jeong-hu.
That punk Jeong-hu
was grateful to you guys
for eating with him at school.
Whether to eat alone or with someone,
it's a big deal for kids like us.
Because he and I grew up
pretty much on our own.
Because we've lived floating around
here and there like a ball of dust.
I'm going back.
Geon-hyeok.
Take care of yourself.
Jun-u.
Did you have a nice talk?
Yes.
You're glad you met up, right?
You didn't believe me, did you?
When I called you the other day,
all excited.
How humiliating.
Why? That's your charm.
-You're naive.
-What?
Listen. I have a new goal after that day.
To become a teacher
that Choe Jun-u trusts completely.
I trust you.
Don't lie to me.
It's written all over your face.
"I don't trust Oh Han-gyeol at all."
Don't touch my hair.
You'll mess up my style.
Your style.
It's written here too
that you don't trust me.
You punk, ordering your teacher around.
Thank you for coming with me.
Jun-u.
Now, forget everything that's happened,
and let's start over together. Okay?
Let's cast aside depression,
self-blame, things like that.
Okay.
Your heart sank when I said
I was leaving earlier, right?
No.
You were tearing up.
I saw it. You were tearing up.
I was not.
You weren't? No?
I washed it. Thanks.
To be honest, I just wanted to see you.
-No!
-That's not it!
-I swear.
-I'm going to...
-No.
-Don't hit him!
Quiet!
-No.
-Just once.
Why would you help me?
Out of pity?
SOO-BIN
Yoo Soo-bin.
Sorry.
-Let me help with that.
-No, It's okay.
Give it to me.
Bye.
I'll win tomorrow.
I played some basketball.
Guys, this is a supplemental reading
material for Social Studies.
Pick up your notebooks yourselves,
and take one and pass it back.
You know the test is
just around the corner, right?
To prepare for the test
more efficiently, let's change seats.
Check your group chat message.
NEW SEATING ARRANGEMENT FOR CLASS 3
Come on, what is this?
You placed everyone with poor grades
in the back of the class.
That's not true.
I gathered study group members
close together, so it may seem that way.
That's the same thing.
Those of you who were
my classmates last year
know how efficient this is.
He's right. Our grades improved
a lot back then.
Let's change seats then.
Hwi-yeong, is this really necessary?
Our class voted early this semester
to follow my decisions
regarding seating arrangements.
I hope you cooperate.
Yes, sir.
Did everyone agree with changing seats?
Well, Soo-bin, me, Chan-yeol,
and everyone I know were against it,
but he still received
a majority of the votes.
If we arrange the seats like that,
we can help each other study,
so those with good grades
all agreed to it.
It's time for the end of day
announcements. Let's...
What happened to your seats?
Since the midterm is coming up soon.
We changed seats.
Without even discussing it with
your homeroom teacher? Which is me.
We always changed seats freely like this.
We did it for the last mock exam too.
Oh, I see.
I said we have a supplementary
English class today, right?
Let's begin in 20 minutes
in this classroom.
Sir, we can't attend
the supplementary class.
We have a study group session.
You won't attend the class
due to your study group?
Since it's not a regular class.
Oh, since it's not a regular class?
Then who doesn't want to
attend the supplementary class?
Are you guys in the group too?
No. We're going to study on our own.
Us too.
Hands down.
Sir, we'll stay
for the supplementary English class.
-Me too.
-I'll stay for it too.
Okay, then.
Jun-u...
I guess Jun-u really gave up
on studying, right?
Mr. Oh, I can't yield this to you.
It's a matter of our grades.
"Yield"?
Do you come to school
to yield things to me?
No, that's not what I meant.
Then does it mean you yielded
by accepting a pitiful person like me
as your homeroom teacher?
If I lashed back at you like this,
it would be like admitting
my ego has hit rock bottom.
Change your seats back to the way
they were.
And make sure your study group sessions
don't overlap with my classes.
Got it?
Lord, Buddha,
Grandma...
I should believe in a religion.
Mr. Oh.
Why don't you find some students
to keep an eye on him for you?
Thanks.
Here.
Jun-u.
I want to join this study group too.
Too bad.
You have to be at a certain level
to join this group.
Oh, if you need help with your studies,
I can help you later one-on-one.
You're lucky, Jun-u.
A certain level?
Do you think I'm not good enough?
Why do you think so?
I'm sorry if you were offended.
You can join us then.
Since it's your first time,
you can sit in the front.
I guess I can't.
I need to go to work.
Sorry to bother you.
See you, Jun-u.
But...
Why do you do this?
What?
Aren't you busy enough studying alone?
To remain at the top of our year?
-That's...
-Hwi-yeong is always like this.
He helps us and supports us.
He wants all of us to turn out well.
It's something like that.
Oh, really?
I see.
It must be tough being you.
As you can see, gerunds
and present participles
can be distinguished
by a verb plus "ing"...
-Hello.
-Yes.
I'm sorry. Can I speak to Soo-bin?
-Hello.
-Hello, ma'am.
-Soo-bin.
-Ma'am, what is this about?
Something urgent came up.
Please continue with your class.
I was in the middle of the class.
Did you
quit Mr. Son's class?
You've lost your mind.
Follow me.
Come here.
Yoo Soo-bin. Are you crazy?
Have you really lost your mind?
Don't you know how much
I kissed up to Hwi-yeong's mom?
Didn't you see me act
like a servant around her?
But you quit the academy
without even discussing it with me?
What for... Why?
How could you suddenly barge in
like that? It's embarrassing.
Embarrassing? Are you embarrassed?
Look who's talking. I'm the one
who's embarrassed because of you.
I'm so embarrassed that
I can't even attend my alumni reunion.
My friends' children all attend science,
private and foreign language high schools.
Or they're top of their year
at regular high schools, at least.
They have no trouble getting into SNU.
But what about you?
Do you have anything to be proud of?
So I'm struggling so hard
to get you into Seoul National University.
But what is the matter with you?
Did you get married to attend
an alumni reunion?
Did you give birth to me
just to brag to others?
Then why don't you just
get rid of me right now?
Go adopt a smart kid
that's good at studying.
Why are you tormenting me?
What, you brat? What did you just say?
Say that again.
Keep going. Say that again, you brat.
I won't make it to SNU.
Even if you bring a more
talented teacher than Mr. Son,
I can never make it. It's impossible.
I'll be glad if I can make it
to any university in Seoul.
Even I know this so well.
Why can't someone who's so smart
and graduated from SNU like you, see that?
Go. Go do what you want.
Go and live as you please now.
Get out of my house.
I don't need a daughter like you.
I don't need a daughter like you. Go!
Did you think I wouldn't go?
Thank you for letting me live as I please.
Hey, come back here.
Yoo Soo-bin. Come back here.
Hey, Yoo Soo-bin. Come back!
Hey!
So what is the role
of a present participle?
-Moon Chan-yeol?
-Yes?
You don't seem to know anything...
Soo-bin.
-Are you okay?
-Yes. I'm sorry.
Mr. Oh, I'm sorry,
but can I leave class early?
-Soo-bin.
-Well...
Okay. You can do that.
All right. See you tomorrow.
Soo-bin. I'll call you.
Just go.
I don't want to fight with you right now.
Go.
I'm going.
Are you okay?
Isn't that
what I usually say?
You're right.
But can't I say it?
I'm worried about you.
I saw your mom earlier.
I didn't mean to eavesdrop, but...
So, now you know.
My life hasn't been as easy as you think.
You're not the only one who has suffered.
I guess so.
Well...
-I'm sorry about yesterday...
-Can you just go?
What?
I want to be alone.
By the way...
Why do you never apologize?
-Just now, I tried to...
-Also,
I'm not Hwi-yeong's girlfriend.
And why do I want to help you?
Is it out of pity?
I know it isn't. That's why I...
It's because I like you. What are you...
going to do now?
Hey! Jun-u!
Are you really...
Soo-bin. Seriously...
I'm not going home today.
It's dangerous to walk alone at night.
Soo-bin is at Chan-yeol's place.
I just wanted to ask a few things
about the kids of Class Three.
That day, what exactly happened?
He's done that a few times before too.
I'll make sure Hwi-yeong
doesn't get the highest grades here.
So this is the issue you have.
Jealousy. Anxiety.
Do you think that'll humiliate me?
I'll make you feel sorry
for those you've looked down on.
-Soo-bin. Oh, no.
-Oh, my god.
I'll carry her.
Subtitle translation by Wayne Ryu