I'm sorry.
Why?
Jun-u,
I'll just go alone today.
It's really okay.
But I want to walk you home today.
It's my birthday, and...
I don't want to send you alone.
Okay.
Go on in.
Okay. Thanks for walking me home.
I was worried you might get lost.
I'm sorry about earlier.
For saying that
without thinking about your feelings.
Me too.
I know how you feel.
You were worried
I might be scolded by my mom.
And whether my mom finds out or not,
you just wanted to keep your promise.
Thank you for today.
It was the best birthday of my life.
Really?
See you.
Okay.
Jun-u, happy birthday.
Thank you.
You should go now.
You're home early, Mom.
Yes.
My meeting ended early today.
She wasn't waiting for me today.
I know.
I told her to quit.
I thought about it, and it felt like
I was too harsh on you.
And your grades improved this time.
Mom, actually,
today was Jun-u's birthday.
I know I shouldn't have broken
the promise I made with you,
but I wanted to celebrate his birthday,
so I went to Jun-u's home.
I begged her to let me go.
I didn't go alone.
I went with Chan-yeol, Da-huin,
and everyone else.
I'm sorry.
You knew you shouldn't have
broken your promise.
But why did you?
Because I like Jun-u.
From now on, I'll keep
all the promises I made with you.
I'll attend the academy and
private lessons you found for me.
And like you want...
No, I'll do better on my own.
Okay.
Fine.
You said you'd do better on your own.
You have a math level test today,
but forget it if you don't want to.
I'll take it.
Thank you for finding it for me.
What time is the test?
I should get ready right away.
Soo-bin.
Take this. I know it's uncomfortable
without it.
Song-hui, how have you been?
Gosh, I called you several times,
but you never called me back.
I was so disappointed.
Oh, I was busy.
I'm on my way to Seoul right now.
I made some side dishes for you,
and I can drop by on the way.
Shall I go to your company?
No, I don't need side dishes.
Yeon-u, I'm sorry but I'm a bit busy now,
so I have to go.
Oh, I see.
The thing is, today is Jun-u's birthday,
so that's why I'm coming to Seoul.
Okay, then. Call me later.
-Happy birthday to you
Here.
How did you guys know?
-Blow them out.
-Many happy returns.
-Happy birthday.
-Congratulations.
All right, then.
Come on in!
Yeon-u, can we meet?
Look at this right here.
Like this.
Hello.
Is Mr. Lee Jeong-min here?
That's me.
Mr. Oh sent me here.
-Are you Choe Jun-u?
-Yes.
It's nice to meet you.
-Didn't it take so long to get here?
-No, it was okay.
Come on in.
Have you ever properly
learned to draw before?
No.
I just attended a small art academy
when I was little.
You're really talented,
just like Han-gyeol said.
Did you always like to draw?
Yes.
Since I was little,
I've always found doodling
very comforting.
I think it makes me happy.
Nice, that's what I call talent.
But preparing a portfolio
for college admission is not easy.
Since you're starting late,
you'll have to work even harder.
-No problem.
-Then shall we begin today?
Sure.
Jun-u.
This part should be like this.
Yeon-u.
About Soo-bin and Jun-u...
You knew, didn't you?
Can I ask a big favor of you?
What is it?
Could you...
transfer Jun-u to a school
in the city where you live?
Sorry?
I don't think those two should be
left together in Seoul now.
I considered moving Soo-bin
to a different school,
but I can't do that because of my work.
Wouldn't it be better for Jun-u
to live with you?
Yeon-u, I know
how selfish I must sound right now.
I'm fully aware of it.
I'm really sorry. But when it comes
to things that concern my child,
I can't be more understanding.
I'm such a coward, aren't I?
I'm sorry.
But you see... Yeon-u, Soo-bin is...
I'm suggesting this because I think
she really likes Jun-u.
I think she likes him a lot.
Girls at that age can fall
for someone very hard, you know.
Even if you try to stop yourself,
you can't really control
your feelings at that age.
I know that Jun-u is a great guy
because he takes after you.
He's very kind. I know that.
But as you know,
they should focus on studying
more than anything at the moment.
I'm sure you also want him
to focus more on studying now.
Yeon-u,
let's split them up for the time being.
Okay?
We moms should put our feet down.
What else can we do?
Yeon-u, I'm really...
I'm really sorry.
I'm so sorry,
but I beg you.
Please?
I'm begging you. Please do it for me.
Did you meet with Jun-u separately
by any chance?
You didn't say anything
that might have hurt his feelings,
did you?
Song-hui.
You're not the only mom in the world.
I'm a mom too.
I'm not as competent as you are,
but I am a mother too.
I, too,
can do anything for my child.
Nothing scares me if it's for my son.
But you know what?
I respect Jun-u's feelings.
To me,
his emotions are more important
than anything else
in the world.
Song-hui, listen.
I do not want to disrespect...
or trample on his feelings.
Soo-bin's mom hasn't found out
that you two are dating, right?
No.
Mr. Lee.
-Mr. Lee.
-Yes.
Well...
I have to go to my part-time job.
All right, Jun-u.
But are you sure you can juggle this
with your part-time job?
Of course. I can do it.
I'll tidy up for you, so get going.
Thank you. Bye.
STUDENT RECORD
MA HWI-YEONG
REPORT CARD
-Hey, Jun-u!
-Mr. Oh.
I had my first class at the academy
you put me in touch with.
I see. How was it?
-Did you do well?
-Yes.
I'm glad to hear that.
Jun-u, that instructor is
very good at what he does.
So just follow his instructions
and do your best.
Don't worry about anything.
Okay, I'll do my best.
Oh, and I really wanted to thank you.
I'm hugely...
What? Go on.
I'm hugely indebted to you.
Oh, okay. My goodness.
Don't be silly.
-Are you going to work now?
-Yes.
All right. Work hard.
And try to get some studying done
whenever you have a chance.
Okay.
LETTER OF APOLOGY
CHOE JUN-U
So this is... It's a case of forced...
A forced transfer, sir.
Lower your voice.
You're...
I'm surprised.
You have a talent. You did
a great job of drawing this ladybug.
I'm sorry I'm late.
SELF-MADE CEO BRIBES HIS SON'S TEACHER
CHOE JUN-U
Happy birthday, Jun-u.
No one's birthday has ever felt
this important to me.
-Let me do it.
-Hurry up.
-Give it to me. No, wait!
-I'm done.
-Where? It looks fine.
-Gosh.
-Let's just wrap it like this.
-It's not ripped.
I always thought it was such a cliché
to thank someone
for being born into this world,
but you taught me
that one could truly mean it.
Jun-u, thank you for being born
into this world.
You're the most precious person to me.
You've finally found your path,
so I prepared this for you.
But the thing is,
I know nothing about art.
I'm not sure if this is right.
I hope you like the gift
even if I got it wrong.
To Choe Jun-u.
From Soo-bin.
It can never be wrong
if it's from you.
Jun-u.
Mom?
Thanks for the food.
-Is it good?
-Yes.
But you shouldn't eat
right before you go to bed.
I skipped dinner, so I was hungry anyway.
Today is a very special day.
It's your birthday,
and it was your first day
at the art academy.
Actually, Mr. Oh was a big help.
He found an academy for me
and put in a word for me
so I wouldn't be burdened.
I know. We owe him a lot.
How should we repay him?
I'll have to work harder.
Mom.
After all,
I met many good people at this school.
Mr. Oh...
and...
You also met Soo-bin?
Well...
You didn't say anything that might
have hurt his feelings, did you?
My mom still thinks that the time
she spent with her first love
years ago was the most
beautiful moment in her life.
Back when she was 18.
She still misses that moment.
You have something to tell me, don't you?
No, I don't.
Are you sure? I think you do.
Jun-u.
You've grown up to be
such a kind, thoughtful boy.
Thank you for being my son.
Eat up.
Okay.
I wonder if he liked my present.
I miss him.
It's pretty hard, right?
But preparing a portfolio
for college admission is not easy.
Since you're starting late,
you'll have to work even harder.
Jun-u.
Have you gotten over him yet?
Yes, I feel a lot better now.
I'm completely over him now.
What about you?
Me too.
I feel a lot better too.
Da-huin.
Hi, O-je.
-Hi.
Hi.
We're best friends now.
Shall we go in?
Sure.
Let's go, besties.
-Let's go.
-Gosh.
Are you feeling better now?
Stop it.
Thank you for your present.
I was very, very
touched.
Also, I went to the academy yesterday.
Really?
How was it?
It was nice.
The room was full of kids
drawing something.
It made my heart flutter.
The teacher is very competent too.
I think I'll learn a lot from him.
That's great.
That's really awesome.
But I guess you'll be more tired
from now on.
With the academy and your part-time job.
Can you pull them both off?
Isn't the academy a bit far away?
I have to. I can do it.
I'm Choe Jun-u.
I'm the best.
I went to a new academy yesterday too.
-Really?
-Yes.
I told my mom everything.
I told her that I went
to celebrate your birthday.
Was it okay?
Yes. I promised her I'd work harder.
Luckily, she seems to be
feeling a bit better.
I even went to take a level test
at an academy she found.
Good job.
You too.
-Good job.
Mr. Oh.
Jun-u.
Can we talk for a moment?
Sure.
Jun-u.
Listen carefully to what I say.
The Office of Education will inspect
our school soon
regarding Hwi-yeong.
They'll investigate the grade tampering
and the incidents you were involved in.
It'll probably dig up some bad memories,
and I feel bad about it.
But we still need to put things right
and prove your innocence.
That's the thing I felt most guilty about.
I see.
It's Hwi-yeong.
Will he be kicked out?
Leave it.
I said, leave it.
I'm just cleaning up the mess.
I'm not doing it for you.
-Thank you.
I have to run.
-I'm leaving.
-See you.
Let's go home.
I'm sorry I'm late. Sorry.
CHOE JUN-U
I'm sorry. I'm sorry I'm late.
PASSION SNACK RESTAURANT
-Isn't it really good?
-Yes.
I made it.
It seemed like you were skipping
your meals.
This is our signature dish, fried squid.
-Try it. It's good.
-It looks yummy.
Dip it in the tteokbokki sauce,
and take a big bite.
I'm so lucky to eat this,
thanks to school ending early.
You should eat more.
Eat some rice balls,
fries, and sundae too.
Eat everything, okay?
-I better finish up and go.
-Okay.
I'm sorry I'm late. I'm sorry.
Hey, you're early.
Mr. Oh.
Didn't you ask me to fill in
for you today?
Saying you'd be a bit late today.
You came early.
How about working somewhere
near your art academy?
The owner asked me to work here
until the end of this month.
Oh, I see.
Mr. Oh.
Thank you very much
for today.
And I'm sorry.
Come on. You're embarrassing me.
If there's anything else
you're having trouble with,
you can keep asking for help.
Okay.
Soo-bin,
I'm having a really tough day.
Still, coming here made me feel better.
You must be asleep already.
Good night.
I'm not sleeping yet.
How did you know?
I don't know.
I guess we just clicked again.
You must be exhausted.
No, I'm not. I'm full of energy.
Why did you come here then?
Well, just...
I was bored at home,
so I wanted to get some fresh air.
Since the weather is nice and all.
Hey, you're bleeding!
Were you upset?
Because you couldn't see me around?
Oh, I have something for you.
This is a book on writing cover letters.
This is a book that gives helpful tips
about writing cover letters.
This is a book that teaches you
the key points of English tests.
And this is the perfect workbook
for learning common knowledge.
And this
teaches you the secrets of
nailing interviews. There you go.
Why are you giving me these?
I'll be going then.
Mr. Oh. Why are you doing this?
To tell you the truth,
I was planning on waiting
until you open up your heart to me,
but I thought about it carefully,
and that seemed wrong.
I came to the conclusion
that I should help you while waiting.
I also started an internet forum
about English studies.
I'll send you some material every day,
so you can study them.
I'll even give you some homework
from time to time.
I'll provide feedback as well.
You know that I'm a teacher, right?
Teacher Oh.
I'll go now since you're working.
-Mr. Oh.
-Yes?
But this makes me
feel uncomfortable.
No, don't feel pressured.
Shouldn't I do this at least
as someone who likes you?
Don't you think?
Ji-min, whether you see me or not,
that's up to you to decide.
Okay.
Okay, goodbye.
I know what you were thinking.
"Even with his nose plugged
like that, he looks handsome."
No, I wasn't.
Well, if you're okay now,
you should take that out.
It's tough, isn't it?
No.
Don't say no.
This feels nice.
It's comfortable.
Why aren't you saying anything?
What is there to say?
What's important is being with you.
Am I doing a good job?
I'm proud of you.
I'm very proud of you, Choe Jun-u.
I know it's tough for you now,
but as time passes, don't you think
things will become better?
I guess so.
Things will become better, right?
Well, that's what grown-ups told me.
That things would become better.
I don't know either.
But when you're having a tough time,
just think of happy thoughts.
Like making it into the art school
that you want,
and doing something you dreamed of.
And being beside you.
I'm happy now too.
Me too.
Next, Hwi-yeong.
Next, Jun-u.
Yes, sir.
What? You're 36th?
Does that mean Sang-hun
got the highest mark?
Soo-bin.
Hwi-yeong. You're okay, right?
Check your grades, guys.
If you have any questions,
ask the teacher in charge.
-Okay?
-Okay.
Pil-sang, I can't believe
you made it into the top 200.
-Hey, stop it.
-Girls, isn't he so cool?
Seriously, cut it out.
My god, someone's going to the movies.
Ro-mi, I really came in 200th.
-What? Oh, my.
-Look at you, Pil-sang.
I thought it was 500 at first,
but it's 200.
Go away, Pil-sang.
What?
It's your fault. It's all your fault!
Pil-sang, I'm impressed
that you came in 200th.
Mr. Oh, Ro-mi and I will go
to the movies together.
-Seriously?
-Yes.
Ro-mi, you can do better next time.
After the summer break.
There's no next time.
Guys, look at the sky.
The sky is flawlessly blue,
and you guys are 18-year-olds
with a bright future.
You have so many opportunities
ahead of you. Keep it up.
-Congratulations, Pil-sang.
-Thank you.
-Ro-mi, let's--
-No.
-Gosh.
-Ro-mi. Wait, Ro-mi!
My, he's so cool.
Enough, okay?
He is so cool, though.
Did you do well, Da-huin?
Yes. I did so much better
this time, right?
So studying hard does pay off, you know?
I was so surprised.
Jun-u.
I did much better this time.
You did too, right?
Yes, a little.
Hey, your grades jumped so much.
This is amazing. Congratulations.
Oh, right.
We shouldn't have met up like that
last night.
I forgot about that for a moment.
It's okay. We should let ourselves
breathe a little when we can.
"When we can"?
When we're at school, at least.
What is it?
Mr. Oh suggested that I do this.
I took a quick look at it.
If I win an award in this contest,
I can do early application
under the special talent category.
You're right.
Hey, I'm so excited right now.
I think you'll do great.
I'm going to try really hard
since I'm getting a late start.
I want to find my path soon too.
I'm still so lost.
Everything will go well.
I know you'll find your path very soon.
Everything will be fine.
You'll be fine, Soo-bin.
What's this? A magic spell?
My gosh, Sang-hun.
You finally got the highest mark.
-I should learn from you...
-Stop flattering me.
-You finally got what you deserved.
-Seriously.
Don't you agree, Hwi-yeong?
Guys, let's go study.
Go back inside. Go on.
It turned out that it was my dad.
The person who e-mailed you
and reported the case.
I am sorry
that this happened.
I never intended this to happen.
Are you all right?
Just worry about yourself.
Right, I should. You never let me down.
This is the Ma Hwi-yeong I know.
I'm relieved now.
I have to say, you have a mind of steel.
I really should learn that from you.
I apologize for what my parents did
to you and your father.
But you and your family
have gotten enough out of this.
So can't we call it even now?
I'm impressed
by how shameless you still are.
Gosh, you and that ego of yours.
You're really something.
But you know what?
I'm bored now.
Studying is only fun
when I have you
competing fiercely against me as my rival.
Who am I going to compete with
from now on?
All right. Our government's
export-driven policy...
-What's going on?
-Be quiet.
Who are those people?
They look like some high-ranking officers.
Hey.
-Pil-sang.
-Yes?
I told you to be quiet.
Ro-mi and I are going to the movies.
Okay, sure. Stand straight, guys.
In a fairly short amount of time,
the focus shifted from light manufacturing
to heavy, chemical,
and high-tech manufacturing.
In this process,
industrial facilities were mainly
built in the metropolitan area
and the Yeongnam region.
Both had a lot of growth potential.
"It pours out,
collides against the rocks,
and fights fiercely."
In this passage...
Hello.
We're from the Office of Education.
Oh, welcome.
-Hello.
-May we get started?
Yes, sure.
Mr. Oh.
-Yes.
-We'll begin the investigation
on the allegation that Ma Hwi-yeong
had his grades tampered,
based on the statement made by
his former homeroom teacher,
Mr. Kim Byeong-cheol.
We'll also look into whether
any school violence took place
and how it was dealt with if it did.
In connection with the same student,
Ma Hwi-yeong.
We'll need to interview a few students
during our investigation.
The accused, Ma Hwi-yeong and Lee Gi-tae.
And lastly, another student
of yours, Choe Jun-u.
Sure.
I'll answer all questions truthfully,
to the best of my knowledge.
The thing is though,
Hwi-yeong,
as well as all other students,
are still very young.
Please keep that in mind
and try to be considerate of them.
Please.
Could it have something to do
with those people?
What's going on, So-ye?
Is there anything you know?
Did they summon Gi-tae too?
It's true that Hwi-yeong
asked me to do it,
but paying them was my idea.
They did ask for the money,
but I wanted to impress Hwi-yeong as well.
I told them everything. Now, I can
face you without feeling ashamed.
And I apologized to Jun-u as well.
That's great, Gi-tae.
You did the right thing.
They'll interview me as well
because I'm your homeroom teacher.
And I plan to tell them the truth
even if that will hurt your feelings.
I know. I'm prepared
to deal with the consequences.
You should tell them the truth.
I believe that this is the best thing
I can do for your sake.
Yes.
Jun-u, come to the counseling office.
In addition to the allegation
of grade tampering,
could we verify a few other things
regarding your classmate,
Ma Hwi-yeong, with you?
Sure.
Are these allegations against him
all true?
Jun-u?
Gosh.
I really didn't think
Hwi-yeong would ever do such things.
The fact that he rigged his grades
was shocking enough.
I can't believe
he did the other things too.
So-ye.
Why didn't you tell us?
I wish you had told me everything.
I had no idea what Jun-u
was going through.
I'm sorry. Back then,
I was scared things would get out of hand.
So-ye must have had her reasons.
Soo-bin!
Why didn't you tell me all this time
what you were going through?
Since I knew you'd be hurt.
How could I tell you?
Still...
How did you deal with it all alone?
Why didn't I find out earlier?
Why didn't I even try to find out?
Soo-bin.
You and Hwi-yeong have been friends
since you were little.
You must have hoped
Hwi-yeong wouldn't be such a person.
You don't have to feel sorry.
I understand you.
Don't blame yourself.
I'll take care of it
the way I want.
Jun-u.
How have you been enduring it all?
Somehow.
Thanks to you.
Jun-u.
It'll pass soon. This painful moment.
Let's...
endure it together.
Your punishment
for the grade tampering
will be decided soon.
I see.
Do you admit everything
regarding the incident
with Choe Jun-u as well?
Yes.
I'm sure Jun-u told you everything.
He put off answering the question.
Jun-u.
I'll give you a ride.
I realized...
something earlier.
I haven't forgiven Hwi-yeong yet.
Deep down, I still fiercely resent him.
You've been holding up well.
By the way, why did you
postpone an answer?
You could have let it all out right there.
Were you trying to hold back?
That's why I hate myself even more.
I don't know what I'm feeling right now.
I hated him so much,
and I still can't forgive him. But...
But for some reason,
I couldn't say anything.
I couldn't understand.
I felt so stupid.
Do you know why?
It's because you're a nice person.
You hesitate
because you're afraid to hurt someone
with your anger and resentment.
That's who you are.
Jun-u.
All you have to do is
do what you think is right.
Why did you do that?
I have nothing to say.
We've been best friends
since we were little.
I can't believe...
you did such a thing.
I've always been a bad person.
You know what?
What hurts me the most is
that even while saying
you're my best friend,
I had no idea until now.
That I just let you
turn into this person.
I'm sorry, Soo-bin.
I might have...
felt it
at some point,
although I wasn't sure.
I probably hoped...
you weren't such a person.
I might have been scared
to know the truth.
That's what I regret the most.
No.
You've been a great friend to me.
I have to go.
I'm home.
Hi. How was the academy?
Good.
-I want some water.
-Sure.
Soo-bin.
Are the things about Hwi-yeong true?
What about the thing with Jun-u?
Mom, do you see now?
Jun-u is not a bad kid.
He's a good one.
Mom.
As you said, my grades have improved,
and I've proven
that I can do well on my own.
So can you trust me now?
Soo-bin.
I trust you.
But it's a very important period
for you right now.
Also,
although you think
you can do everything well on your own,
at your age, nothing goes your way.
Even you don't know
what you're feeling at that age.
Just trust me for now.
No matter what.
Don't imagine anything
or make any assumptions.
Nothing bad will happen to me.
Jun-u also...
improved his grades a lot this time,
and he tried really hard.
He's found what he wants to do...
and we both tried so hard.
We'll continue to try hard too.
I just wanted to say that.
I'll go to my room then.
Soo-bin.
I came to pick you up today.
You know, you came to see me all the time.
Come on, it's okay.
Let's go.
You can tell us comfortably.
Okay.
I won't...
make any more statements.
Please just investigate things
based on Hwi-yeong's statements.
Jun-u.
Soo-bin, I...
You don't have to tell me.
Whatever decision you made,
you are right.
Good job.
DROPOUT APPLICATION FORM
Hwi-yeong.
You want to drop out of school?
I want to leave this school
as soon as possible.
But this...
For now,
why don't you take some time
and think about it, okay?
I'll drop out.
Hwi-yeong.
This isn't the right way, okay?
I'm sorry, Mr. Oh.
Jun-u.
You should've told them
everything about me.
Why did you do that?
I don't think I have to explain that
to you.
I'm going to drop out of school.
Hwi-yeong.
Drop out of school? Who said you can?
Why? Does that disappoint you?
Because you forgave me
but I'm just running away?
Who says I forgave you?
Do you think I didn't say anything
because I forgave you?
How could I forgive you
when you don't even regret what you did?
Then what should I do?
I'm giving up everything and leaving.
This is the best way I can think of.
I'm scared and afraid as well.
What do I have to do then?
What should I do?
Have you ever been genuinely sorry
for what you did to me?
From the bottom of your heart.
You've never been sorry.
The only thing that's important to you
is your pride.
Ma Hwi-yeong.
You haven't been forgiven.
And yet, you're just running away...
like a coward.
Choe Jun-u!
I'm sorry.
Subtitle translation by Wayne Ryu